Chapter 203 – Finally, Some Strategy

Even though there wasn’t a precise probability for a dead player to drop items, in the normal servers, the probability wasn’t high. For a weapon to drop when Huang Shaotian wanted one to indicated his incredibly good luck. It probably wasn’t any lower than an Orange weapon dropping from a BOSS.

The Blade Master saw Huang Shaotian’s word bubble, but who would believe that? To him, it seemed as if he was being mocked. When he revived, he told his guild buddies about this nightmare. As for getting the weapon back, by killing him? With such a low probability of a weapon dropping, no one had much hope.

The players, who were now chasing after Lord Grim, originally didn’t pay too much attention to Flowing Tree, but this guy was too excessive. Not only did he take the initiative to offend them and kill two players, but an Orange weapon had even been dropped. Although a portion of those players were happy about this news, they couldn’t ignore what this player had done.

“It dropped! It dropped! It dropped!” Huang Shaotian was shouting at Ye Xiu!

“What dropped?” Ye Xiu asked.

“The Level 25 Orange Strike Sword! Are you jealous of my luck!” Huang Shaotian was quite happy.

“Not bad. Keep it up.” Ye Xiu said.

“Your position?” Huang Shaotian asked for his coordinates.

“1645, 1866.” Ye Xiu reported his coordinates.

“How many have you killed?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“Two.”

“Me too! Let’s compete to see who wins!” Huang Shaotian messaged.

“You lose.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why!” Huang Shaotian refused to believe him.

“You don’t have enough potions.” Ye Xiu firmly replied.

Huang Shaotian was speechless. It wasn’t easy for him to become speechless…… It was true though. His Flowing Tree only had a bit of food and potions left that were given to him by Ye Xiu. If they were to compete in this type of PK game, he would definitely lose.

“We’ll kill until I have no more potions.” Huang Shaotian still wanted to continue. He sent the message as he rushed towards the coordinates that Ye Xiu had sent him.

Two top-tier Gods in the pro-scene.

Two players standing at the top in Glory.

At this very moment, they were hunting down a group of normal players.

Will numbers prevail? Or will the strong come out on top?

These questions described the current situation. The difference between pro-Gods and normal players was monumental, especially in PK. Compared to running dungeons, the difference was much greater.

From mechanics to experience to mental fortitude to usage of terrain……….

Congee Forest.

For Ye Xiu to have everyone meet up here, as well as bringing all the pursuers, Ye Xiu naturally had everything planned out. It could be said that Ye Xiu had confidence that they would be able to beat these unorganized players using the forest’s terrain. Huang Shaotian’s appearance only helped him save some time.

One, two, three…….

Players fell one after another. In the beginning, everyone thought that it was because they were being careless and that such a thing definitely wouldn’t happen to them.

However, only until a total of ten players died did their views finally change.

It was too unlikely for so many to be careless.

They searched around Congee Forest for another ten minutes. Lord Grim would appear and disappear at times, leading them around the forest. In addition, there was also that Level 27 Blade Master, Flowing Tree. He would also run out from time to time. With a chatterbox in their vicinity, Congee Forest was abnormally loud.

The pursuers finally realized that the situation wasn’t looking good.

The guild leader decided to take back his previous order of “Spread out and look around. Report anything you find.” Under that order, two of Samsara’s guild members had already died.

The other guilds also made similar decisions. Now, everyone gathered together and temporarily stopped chasing.

“I feel…… like they’re not trying to escape from us, but rather trying to kill us……..” Someone in the crowd finally broke the silence.

No one answered him. A bit of fear lingered in everyone’s hearts.

Of course they knew which of their allies had died. Every time one was ambushed, they all wanted to try and save them, but it was no use. By the time they rushed over, all that was left at those coordinates was a corpse. The other side also left tracks, but looking back, it was probably intentional.

Whether it was Lord Grim or Flowing Tree, they weren’t running around with the intent of escaping from them; they rather to mess up their formations and hunt down stragglers.

Formation? Was that even a thing? They didn’t even know themselves. All they were doing was chasing after whatever tracks the opposite side had left behind. Under this type of situation, was the other side able to understand their patterns?

“Everyone…….” Lonely Drink acted as the leader, “The current situation is a bit dangerous.”

Everyone was silent.

“We originally had 32 players, but now, we only have 22! We can’t keep continuing on like this. We need to change our strategy. Our disorganized actions gave our enemies a chance. I believe that we urgently need to move as an orderly group from now on.” Lonely Drink hadn’t lost his reason yet. He calmly analyzed the situation and their opponents’ strength. His tone was also humble and appropriate.

‘You’re right…….” Someone stood out to support him.

“Next, each of our guilds will form small teams. We’ll then move about in these small teams, how about it? I suggest that each team should have at least four players.” Lonely Drink said.

Lonely Drink had come to this decision after contacting others. Right now, they had members from five different guilds, with four or five players from each guild remaining.

“Each team will keep in contact with each other and be ready to report their positions at any time, sound good?” Lonely Drink said.

If they continued to chase in an unorganized fashion, what would happen? Their original 32 players hadn’t formed teams and because of that, they had suffered numerous casualties.

Under such pressure, each of the guilds put down their rivalries with each other and upheld a cooperative spirit. Following Lonely Drink’s proposal, they created a group. Each team entered the group where they could communicate in. A part of Lonely Drink’s clever strategy was that there wasn’t any one leader everyone had to follow. He only acted as a player with an idea, letting the other guilds accept it more easily.

After forming the groups, Lonely Drink continued: “Let’s all head in the same direction! If we can force them out of this forest, then that would be very good for us. The forest’s cover is the main reason they’re able to appear and vanish.”

The players split into five teams and fanned out. They headed towards the last known location of Lord Grim and Flowing Tree.

“They’ve switched their strategy.” Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree was hiding nearby and saw through their pursuers’ new strategy.

“More like they actually have a strategy now.” Ye Xiu corrected Huang Shaotian. His Lord Grim was obviously nearby as well.

“There’s at least four players per team. Each team isn’t too far from each other either. The region they control is very large……. If we keep on evading them like this, we’ll be forced out of the forest, but four players……. it looks like we’re going to need to team up to attack.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Even if we team up, we might not be able to beat them before support arrives.” Ye Xiu said.

“Or maybe you should come take a look at this team.” Huang Shaotian said.

“What do you mean?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Three Cloth, one Leather. They’re placed on the edge. Only one team can support them in time.” Huang Shaotian said.

Cloth armor had the weakest Physical defense. Leather was the second weakest.

“We probably won’t be able to completely wipe them out, but two or three shouldn’t be a problem.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Then what are we waiting for? Position?”

Huang Shaotian sent him the coordinates and Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim immediately headed there. The two characters had previously been doing their own thing, but now they were about to work together.

“I’m feeling a bit light-headed.” Huang Shaotian said after meeting up with Ye Xiu.

“To be able to make yourself go light-headed from speaking so much, you really are a genius.” Ye Xiu said.

“More like the Alliance prohibits players from using voice chat……. If I had to keep talking during the match, that wouldn’t be healthy!” Huang Shaotian cried.

“No one would be as talkative as you.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ve decided that I’m going to use word bubbles in a bit.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Don’t block my sight.” Ye Xiu said.

“They’re here!”

“Let’s go from the right!”

“Go…..”

Chapter 204 – Bullying Cloth

Summoner, Elementalist, Ghostblade, Assassin.

Three Cloth-armored classes and one Leather-armored class. Right now, they were positioned on the left-most side of the formation and were maintaining contact with the other four small teams using the group channel, while carefully looking around.

These four players were from Tyrannical Ambition. They didn’t have any high-positioned officers among them, but were all veterans from the Heavenly Domain. After coming to the new server together, their relationships had grown closer and they were already almost inseparable friends. This was why they had even participated in this type of activity together.

Speaking of them, they had a small relationship with Lord Grim. They had once fought together shoulder-to-shoulder for the Goblin Merchant First Kill, but right now, their guild was in a difficult situation because of Lord Grim. The guild leader had decided to take a hostile stance and they could only follow along with the decision.

However, they had personally witnessed Lord Grim’s skill before, so they didn’t dare act careless, especially after two of their guild buddies had been swiftly eliminated. One was killed by Lord Grim while the other by Flowing Tree, but in both cases, their reports were the same; they weren’t able to fight back.

They had witnessed Lord Grim’s skill level before, but for an unknown Level 27 Blade Master to have been so dominating… where did this holy saint come from? Why did Lord Grim always have experts cropping up here and there? Every one of the members in his party: Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, Cleansing Mist, Flowing Tree, and even the newest name, One Inch Ash…….. the records they set were already proof that they were strong.

But, to be able to completely dominate someone six levels higher, “strong” wasn’t enough to describe him.

And that brother, who had been killed by Flowing Tree, emphasized angrily about that Blade Master’s endlessly moving mouth and stressed the anguish Flowing Tree’s trash talk gave him.

The person on the scene is baffled, the onlookers see clear.

Hearing this description, the experienced Glory players all thought of one person.

Huang Shaotian. Of course, they thought of Huang Shaotian. The Blade Master in Glory, who was most famous for his non-stop talking, would definitely be him.

Even though they thought of him, there was no way they believed that it was actually him. A God like him would enter the game and play cat and mouse in the forest with them? No one would believe that.

“This person is definitely a fan of the Sword Saint.” The Ghostblade reckoned.

“Yeah!” The others agreed. The God obviously had a lot of fans. Fans would mimic their idols. It was a case in every game.

“I once knew a person like this. He would always shout randomly when PKing, making your head go dizzy.” The Assassin said.

“Ha ha. How does that count as anything? I’ve even seen players that talk to monsters.” The Elementalist laughed.

“But this guy really is strong. We should be cautious.” The Summoner said.

“Of course.” The other three replied. The players continued to carefully tread through the forest.

A word bubble suddenly popped out from the forest.

“Over there!” The Assassin yelled as he headed in that direction. The other three players looked as well, but didn’t see anything, so they didn’t dare act too careless. The Summoner waved his magic staff and prepared to summon a pet. The summoned pets only lasted for a certain amount of time and each summon required quite a bit of mana. Because of this, Summoners usually summoned at the beginning of battle or before the battle began.

“Bang!”

A gun sound and a flash of light.

A bullet flew out and the Summoner’s cast was interrupted.

“Triple Slash!”

“Upward Slash!”

“Watch my sword!”

“Sword Draw!”

“Lunge!”

……

They hadn’t even found their opponent yet, when a chain of word bubbles floated up.

While they were surprised, Flowing Tree rushed out using a Triple Slash with the word bubbles above his head. He slashed the Summoner and interrupted the Summoner’s casting again.

“He’s here!” They cried out in fear. The Summoner did his utmost to try and escape, while the other three players rushed forward together. Magic and swords exploded towards Flowing Tree.

At this moment, a blur went by the three player’s eyes and a figure appeared before them. The figure swung his arm and with a whoosh, a giant umbrella opened up in front of them, blocking their attacks.

The Elementalist’s burst wasn’t large enough, but the Assassin’s Shining Cut and the Ghostblade’s Ghost Slash attacks weren’t light so Lord Grim was pushed back.

“F*ck! You crashed into me.” Lord Grim was pushed back into Flowing Tree. Huang Shaotian immediately responded. The collision had affected his fighting.

“My shield’s weight is low.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? How light?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“So noisy. Concentrate.” Ye Xiu said.

Word bubbles continued to spout out.

In order to maintain relevant even without a pet, many Summoners spent a few skill points on Level 20 and under Mage skills, especially Battle Mage ones.

The Summoner was like this, but…….. at this moment, he felt that using his skill points like this was a bit of a waste.

The skills he learned were completely useless. No matter which one he used, the outcome was still the same.

His attacks and magic were all interrupted.

Seeing those word bubbles say the name of the skill, it was as if the system was telling him which attacks he was going to be hit by. All he could do was watch, unable to find a way out.

His three friends were in a deadlock with Lord Grim and had no way of helping him. From what he saw, if they didn’t get any help, his three friends might not even be able to last themselves.

Their two opponents suddenly teamed up. Weren’t they doing their own thing before?

He finally had time to think about this issue. Under the constant attacks, the Summoner quickly fell to Flowing Tree’s blade.

The reason Ye Xiu and Huang Shaotian chose to go after the Cloth-armored ones first was because they would die quicker.

Their first target, the Summoner, wasn’t chosen at random. A Summoner without a summon was just looking to be bullied, but once a few summons came out, he would be a difficult class to deal with and could survive for a very long time.

And in the end, the Summoner wasn’t able to show off his strength before he turned into a corpse.

“You should have been the one to kill him. Your level is higher and you do more damage, so it would have been quicker.” Huang Shaotian immediately went to help Ye Xiu after killing the Summoner. Having him stay quiet was obviously impossible.

“What’d you say?” Ye Xiu said while stabbing the Elementalist with a Dragon Tooth and that Elementalist never stood up again…….

“F*ck……” Huang Shaotian cursed. He was 4 levels higher with a Silver weapon too. His damage was much greater than his low-leveled Blade Master. In the time it took him to kill one, the other side was fighting three while killing one too.

“Stop that one!” It was now 2v2. Ye Xiu put the Assassin into his sights and gave the Ghostblade to Huang Shaotian.

“Watch my sword……”

Word bubbles began to roll out again. Not just his opponent, the Ghostblade, but even the Assassin were starting to feel irritated. After looking at the scene carefully, in reality, the Blade Master’s attacks weren’t as quick as the word bubbles. It was because he was using a Broadsword and his Attack Speed wasn’t enough. Even so, his skill name shouting never stopped. Could he be typing blindly?

The Assassin was never Ye Xiu’s opponent. He was even distracted by Huang Shaotian’s trash talk. His loss was inevitable and he was quickly defeated. That Ghostblade was the same. Under Huang Shaotian’s attacks, he was unable to hang on and backup hadn’t yet arrived. Their ambush had gone even more smoothly than they had anticipated. They originally thought that they would kill off two or three and then be forced to retreat, but right now, they had killed them all.

“Watch my sword. Watch my sword. Watch my sword.”

Huang Shaotian continued to shout using only normal attacks. Ye Xiu knew that this guy had no more mana and helped him kill off the Ghostblade. He also threw him some potions and food to use.

“Let’s run.” Huang Shaotian said, while Flowing Tree picked up the items.

“There’s still no one here. That’s strange.” Ye Xiu said.

Huang Shaotian thought for a bit and agreed: “After killing off two of them, the closest team should have arrived.”

“Did they go somewhere else?” Ye Xiu looked around.

“Maybe they ignored these four players and used the time to surround us?” Huang Shaotian said.

‘This position…….” Ye Xiu looked at the coordinates, “It’s a trap…….”

Chapter 205 – You’ve Been Surrounded

“One died!!”

“Another one!”

“So quick…….”

“What’s going on? Why haven’t the other teams arrived yet?”

In the group chat, the players saw system notifications that said two of their players had died. After the four Tyrannical Ambition players met with the enemies, they immediately reported it. The other players hastily headed over there to surround them, but midway, they received two notifications that two had already died. The players ran crazily, while grumbling in the chat.

“Stay in formation! This time, we definitely won’t let them escape. Blossom Valley, attack from the 8 o’clock direction. Excellent Dynasty, go from the 4 o’clock direction. Void Walk, 12 o’clock. We’ll surround them and then close in. Tyrannical Ambition, stand firm. We’ll be there soon.”

Lonely Drink’s messages popped up in the group chat. Each of the teams knew they had to cooperate, so they didn’t have too many objections towards Lonely Drink’s commands. Sure enough, the three guilds rushed out towards the directions Lonely Drink had suggested.

Lonely Drink’s Samsara was on Tyrannical Ambition’s right side and should have been the first to arrive at the scene, but their team stopped in the forest and had no intention of moving.

“Let them be killed. If we don’t give them more time to play around, then our encirclement won’t be completed in time.” Lonely Drink gave his guild’s brothers an explanation, while exposing a sly grin.

“Ha ha ha.” The players laughed as well.

If they went to rescue them at this moment, Ye Xiu and Huang Shaotian would immediately run away and continue to hide in the forest. The teams that were heading towards their position were at different distances from each other, so it wasn’t possible for them to complete the encirclement in such a short amount of time.

As a result, Lonely Drink held back his troops. With no one disturbing them, Lord Grim and Flowing Tree wiped out those four Tyrannical Ambition players. In the end, this sacrifice gave them time to complete the encirclement and completely blocked off the entire area.

Lonely Drink had intentionally suggested such a formation with the intent of using those four low-defense Tyrannical Ambition players as bait. Four players in each team? That amount of players wouldn’t be enough to defeat two great experts. Lonely Drink believed that the other side would definitely find this flaw.

Reality didn’t let him down. In Congee Forest’s southwest area, Tyrannical Ambition’s group was ambushed by two players. The other players were preparing to perform a pincer attack. This was all according to plan. The goal was to defeat them with superior numbers.

“Another one died!!!” After Tyrannical Ambition’s third player fell, players began panicking.

“What position are you guys at!!!” Lonely Drink seemed to be the most alarmed. Of course, he was worried. Except he wasn’t worried about whether Tyrannical Ambition’s players would live or die. He was only worried that the other teams wouldn’t arrive at their positions in time. If that happened, then their sacrifice would have been for nothing.

The three teams reported their positions, but Lonely Drink wasn’t sure how long the last Tyrannical Ambition member would last. Everything depended on luck.

“After getting into position, immediately head towards the targets!” Lonely Drink sent the message and finally had his Samsara’s five players move out.

While dashing over, Lonely Drink watched the final member of Tyrannical Ambition closely. Finally, after a system notification, the final member fell.

“F*ck!!”

“What’s going on, Samsara?”

“Samsara’s too slow!!!”

The other three teams were naturally complaining. They made an alliance with the agreement that they would save each other if something were to happen, but Tyrannical Ambition’s team was wiped out without any sign of Samsara’s players. This conflicted with their expectations. How could they know that Lonely Drink had done so intentionally?

“Calm down! The other side is extremely strong. Going out one by one is just asking for death! Are you all in position yet? Everyone, forward.” Lonely Drink wouldn’t waste his time explaining every detail. He believed that the other guilds wouldn’t be too distressed over Tyrannical Ambition’s small team. In the end, everyone was only worried whether those two would escape again. But this time, with their arrangement, 18v2, Lonely Drink was confident they would win.

“Charge!!” Some typed out it out in the group chat; some directly shouted it out. The four teams closed in.

“Force them out of the forest!” Lonely Drink yelled. There wasn’t enough time to completely surround their targets, but their current position was close to the edge of Congee Forest, which would force their two targets out of the forest. There would be no place to hide out of the forest and it’d be difficult for them to escape again.

Lonely Drink was extremely satisfied with their positions and felt that he had created a rare masterpiece.

“I see them!!”

“Where?”

“In their original position. They seem to be resting.”

“Don’t rush! Wait for us!” Lonely Drink sent the message and saw their targets. One was standing up with his lance, while the other was sitting on the ground, drinking potions, recovering mana.

“Are you all there? Are you all there?” Lonely Drink was anxious.

“Here.”

“Here.”

“…….”

“Hurry, hurry, hurry.” One team hadn’t arrived yet. Lonely Drink urged them.

“Here.”

“Up!!” Lonely Drink shouted. Bringing with him his anger towards Lord Grim, he bravely charged forward. At the same time, he also saw movements from several directions. Their players had already completely surrounded the area. This time, there was no escape!

“Lord Grim!!” Lonely Drink shouted and dashed in front of the two targets.

“Bang!” A huge noise erupted. The sound of an explosion came from the southwest direction. Lonely Drink looked towards there in surprise. All he saw was the smoke from the explosion.

“What’s going on?” Why did someone attack from over there? Which idiot used a skill?

“You’ve been surrounded. There’s no escape!” Ye Xiu said.

Lonely Drink was completely dumbfounded. Wasn’t that what he was going to say? Why did it just come out from Lord Grim’s mouth?

“What……” Lonely Drink was only able to say one word, when the Blade Master, Flowing Tree, suddenly jumped out. A string of word bubbles flew above his head and a sword leapt at him.

Lonely Drink had heard of this Blade Master’s strength. He had no intention of fighting him one on one and surrounded him with his four brothers. What did Lord Grim mean by that? Lonely Drink fought, while wanting to ask in the group chat, but there was no time to. In front of a God, he didn’t have the ability to fight while asking.

Players poured out from all around the forest. The more Lonely Drink watched, the more confident he became. Weren’t these all his players! Weren’t they the ones surrounding them?

With this confidence, Lonely Drink’s fighting became braver.

“Not bad. You’re the strongest one I’ve met so far today.” Huang Shaotian gave him a compliment.

“But it’s no use. I think it’d be best for you to give up. You seem to be the leader. If this continues on, then things will turn ugly. Are you willing to lose face in front of your bros?” Huang Shaotian’s word bubbles poured out as always. His attacks never stopped either as well as his mouth.

“Move to the side a bit!” Ye Xiu yelled.

“What do you want!”

“Your word bubbles are blocking my view!” Ye Xiu cursed.

“What do you know!”

“We’re here!” Another gun sound erupted from behind them. Cleansing Mist jumped out from the smoke with her heavy cannon. A female character with a heavy weapon burst out, brining a strong visual impact. Behind her was Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash, who was carefully treading forward. A purple aura emanated from him and a Ghost Slash was sent flying towards the player closest to him.

“We’re here? Who are these guys? Your friends? …… oops……” From a different direction, Steamed Bun Invasion came out with his hand clutching another player’s throat. Behind him was a Summoner, who tripped. A bunch of pets walked around randomly behind the Summoner. They were clearly not being well controlled.

“Bang!”

It sounded like a gunshot, but experienced players knew that it was the sound of a Battle Mage using Falling Flower Palm. Judging from how loud the sound was, three or more targets had been hit. Sure enough, three players flew out from the forest although they did complete a Quick Recover to land well. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist carried her Battle Lance with Chasers surrounding her. Without a word, she chased them out and headed towards the closest players. She had died quite a few times today…….

Chapter 206 – Tyrannical Class

Lonely Drink’s heart broke…….

Dealing with Lord Grim and Flowing Tree alone was hard enough for them, and the other guilds, who were supposed to come pincer them, were suddenly ambushed. Lord Grim’s team had unexpectedly arrived. Even though they still had the advantage in numbers, there was a big difference in the quality!

Lonely Drink didn’t know exactly how strong these players were , but they couldn’t be any weaker than the Level 27 Blade Master, Flowing Tree, right?

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist blowing away three players with just one Falling Flower Palm was a dominating entrance. Lonely Drink’s heart immediately trembled at the sight of it.

Tang Rou’s entrance, as well as her travel here, appeared heroic.

The other team members arrived through hiding and running, while she directly slaughtered her way out of Congee City.

While recovering from her Critically Ill state in the city, Tang Rou noticed that there were always spies nearby from the big guilds watching her.

But Tang Rou didn’t care. After buying several potions and putting them in her bag, she directly walked out of Congee City.

There were quite a few players from the big guilds outside of the city. Tang Rou wasn’t the only one they were waiting for; they were ready to kill anyone who had returned to the city.

Everyone knew that Soft Mist had died and returned to the city. Seeing that Soft Mist had dared to walk out of the safe city, they obviously thought that she was being stupid.

But Tang Rou, this sister, did just this.

Before going, she had sent Ye Xiu a message. Ye Xiu didn’t stop her. Even if she died, losing 10% of her experience wasn’t anything significant. He agreed to let Tang Rou go along with this because Soft Mist’s class was a Battle Mage.

Even though Ye Xiu was given the title of Glory’s Encyclopedia and was proficient in all classes, Battle Mage was still undoubtedly his most proficient class.

Various buffs from all sorts of Chasers.

The range advantage of a long weapon.

The strong knockbacks.

……

Ye Xiu couldn’t be any clearer on the strengths of a Battle Mage.

As a Battle Mage, the most suitable style for Tang Rou was to be direct. Battle Mages were supposed to be tyrannical like this.

In order to play a character, not only did you need mechanics and knowledge, but you also needed a type of temperament.

Tang Rou’s aggressiveness and willpower suited the Battle Mage class. If not, then before she chose a class, Ye Xiu would have had a more rational recommendation, similar to when he recommended Qiao Yifan to play as a Phantom Demon.

As a result, at this moment, Ye Xiu definitely wouldn’t stop Tang Rou from doing this type of action that others saw as suicidal. Even if she really did die, Ye Xiu believed that it was still worth a try. This would allow her to grasp the essence of the class, as well as train her temperament.

Tang Rou appearing here was undoubtedly proof that she had successfully accomplished her task. Ye Xiu was very happy with this.

He could imagine how dumbstruck the guards outside of the city were when this sister rushed out of the city.

Slaughtering her way through their encirclement was obviously very difficult, but the harder a task was, the more enthusiastic she was about it.

To her, the battle outside of the city was a performance that was beyond her skill level. With an intention of breaking through the encirclement, she had noticed every single detail. Even though she hadn’t completely killed off an opponent, she had already completely deduced the tyrannical style of a Battle Mage.

When she fiercely tore through the encirclement, the players, who had been surrounding her, only had one feeling in their heart: chaos.

Correct.

Even though none of them died, with some not even losing any health, they all had a feeling of “chaos” in their heart.

They hadn’t prepared to block just Soft Mist. They had been waiting to block all of Lord Grim’s team from moving out of Congee City, but in the end, a single Soft Mist, confidently rushed out. Their original meaning had been erased.

They weren’t even sure if they should chase or not. If they chased, who would stay behind and stop other characters from leaving the city?

This was a big issue they were pondering over. In their minds, they hadn’t even thought of the possibility of a character breaking through their encirclement. At best, the character would have to retreat back into the safety of the city. This was what they had thought before Soft Mist had opened up a path.

After hesitating and asking around for directions, they soon realized that there was no longer any point in doing so.

Not a single trace of Soft Mist could be seen.

Without a single leader guiding them, they could only think for themselves. The guards waiting outside of the city also had this problem.

In Congee Forest, Lonely Drink had led this operation. In the original plan, twenty two players working together should have been more than enough to easily suppress Lord Grim and Flowing Tree.

Unfortunately, Lord Grim’s other team members suddenly appeared out of nowhere and ruined his plan.

“Ha ha, you’re here! You’re all here! Oh? That’s a new face? A Summoner? F*ck me! Where’d you find such a pitiful Summoner? Everything he does is so bad! D*mn! Did he just bump into a tree? Did you guys see that? Does this guy even know how to play?” Huang Shaotian hacked at the enemies while chattering. He was fighting against five opponents with Lord Grim, yet he still had the ability to talk.

“Senior!” Steamed Bun Invasion smashed a Brick onto the back of someone’s head, while greeting Ye Xiu. When Ye Xiu turned around to look at him, that Summoner’s messy display made him feel nauseous. However, after seeing his ID, he felt extremely surprised.

Concealed Light? What a coincidence!

“Senior, this is a bro I met at the bottom of a well.” Steamed Bun Invasion introduced Concealed Light to Ye Xiu.

“Hi.” Ye Xiu greeted Concealed Light.

But Concealed Light seemed to not have heard him. Ye Xiu could tell that he was busy trying to stabilize himself. Seeing his summoned creatures moving and stopping at random times, Ye Xiu began to sweat. He made a brave judgement. This noob might not even know what the hotkeys were for different controls and frequently messed up as well, causing his character to spasm uncontrollably without any sign of a skill coming out.

“Woah! F*ck, a sneak attack!” Steamed Bun Invasion was talking to Ye Xiu when he was suddenly hit from behind by a bullet. He immediately leapt up and grabbed the person, while complaining to Concealed Light: “What are you doing? If you’re like this, how can I trust you with protecting my back?”

Concealed Light didn’t have the ability to bother with Steamed Bun Invasion. He was having a lot of difficulty controlling his summoned creatures so they wouldn’t crash into trees. Ye Xiu had been in the tenth server for this long, but he had only seen two players with such terrible mechanics. One was that noob girl, Immersed Jade, and the other was this Summoner, Concealed Light. Thinking back to those Idiot’s Guides, Ye Xiu was sure: this guy had definitely used videos as sources to write his guides. With a skill level like that and without an expert babysitting him, he was 100% a team killer. Every run would end up in a wipe, and to be able to write such a detailed guide, talking about so many things, could this guy even do what he wrote?

“Wow! It’s only been a short while since we’ve last seen each other, but Soft Mist got better again. One versus three, so strong! Aren’t we too shameful? It’s been so long and we haven’t even taken down these five! Work harder! What? I go and you run? F*ck me. How shameful! What a terrible friend!” Huang Shaotian, once again, began talking non-stop. Lord Grim had suddenly used an Aerial Fire to go to where Cleansing Mist was and Eagle Stamped the enemy behind her.

Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist turned halfway and sent Anti-Tank Missiles towards Lord Grim’s target. The two instantly changed targets without any discontinuity.

“Kill them all!” Ye Xiu shouted.

“D*mn, so fierce! You don’t want to let any of them to run away? That’s fine by me!” Huang Shaotian yelled as he moved, Falling Light Blade. He had used it extremely quickly! Normal players weren’t even able to see him jump up. To them, it just seemed like he had used it standing there.

The five players weren’t able to dodge in time and were hit by the shockwave. Some successfully Quick Recovered, while some failed to do so. Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree sent out a Sword Draw. The three players, who had successfully Quick Recovered, were actually in a bad spot. As soon as they finished rolling, they were hit by the sword slash and were sent flying into the center of battle.

“Three came. I’ve sent them over. There’s still two more. They’ll be there soon.” This guy was still talking.

Tang Rou and Qiao Yifan had heard Ye Xiu’s orders as well. They went to chase after their own targets. The eighteen players were originally in an encirclement, but after Su Mucheng and the other team members arrived, openings began to pop up everywhere. Some realized that the situation wasn’t looking good and began to retreat. Ye Xiu saw this, which was why he had reminded everyone.

After helping out Su Mucheng for a bit, he went to help out Steamed Bun Invasion.

“Hey! It’d be better if you don’t summon any more creatures!” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim arrived and gave Concealed Light some advice.

Chapter 207 – Your Guides

“Why?” Concealed Light’s character didn’t turn and continued to stare at the group of creatures in front of him.

Level 30 Summoners already had Thunder and Fire spirits. Two of each could be summoned and could last up to 30 seconds. Aside from these, at Level 5, they could also summon Goblins, which lasted 90 seconds. The maximum of 5 creatures were summoned and were spinning around in confusion, like headless house flies.

Looking at Concealed Light and his creatures’ movements, Ye Xiu knew that he was trying his hardest to control them. Except……. his mechanics were simply too slow and imprecise. He even made mistakes. Even with his ten years of Glory experience, he had no idea what he was trying to do.

Concealed Light wasn’t any ordinary noob. Seeing how he was able to write those Idiot Guides, Ye Xiu knew that he had a strong grasp of game knowledge and theory. As a result, his moves should have some sort of purpose behind them and they shouldn’t be like that of an actual noob who was just randomly pressing buttons, but watching those creatures running around randomly, Ye Xiu just couldn’t watch any further.

“My senior’s instructing you! Listen to him! It’ll be a gift of a lifetime.” Steamed Bun Invasion threw a Brick to grab Concealed Light’s attention.

Concealed Light finally looked at Lord Grim: “Lord Grim…….”

“I’ve read your Idiot’s Guides.” Ye Xiu said as he moved his Lord Grim forward. Concealed Light had an opponent. In the beginning, this opponent was a bit worried, but he quickly saw that the Summoner was absolutely terrible. He decided not to bother with him and was just about to leave. Ye Xiu didn’t place his hopes on Concealed Light utilizing his summoned creatures to block for him.

“Oh? What’d you think of them?” Ye Xiu finally caught Concealed Light’s attention, who quickly followed him.

But Lord Grim suddenly stood there without moving or speaking.

“Hello? Hello? What’d you think of them?” Concealed Light asked. He then heard a “Bang!” and looked. Lord Grim was using a Falling Flower Palm to blow the player over.

“Shadow Clone Technique!” Concealed Light called and felt depressed. He wasn’t able to distinguish real from fake and had been talking with the fake one.

The player, who had been blown away by Lord Grim, used a Quick Recover to roll up. Terrified, he saw Concealed Light and then rushed towards him.

Concealed Light panicked. He wanted to roll away, but he also wanted to run. In his mind, he came up with four or five different ways of escaping, but his hands were unable to use any. Right before he was going to be hit, he heard three gunshots. Lord Grim had fired Anti-Tank Missiles and launched the player away. He then rushed forward to follow up.

“They’re written pretty well. They’re very detailed without any mistakes, but they’re very impractical.” Ye Xiu answered Concealed Light’s question. While talking, he controlled the field and maneuvered around freely.

“Hmph…… impractical again.” Concealed Light clearly wasn’t happy. This was the most common comment on his guides. He originally thought that a great expert like Lord Grim would be different, but he turned out to be just like everyone else.

“Yeah! Normal people have no way of completely following such a complicated and detailed strategy all the way through.” Ye Xiu said.

“That just means their skill level isn’t good enough. If they’re good enough, then they’d be able to do it.” Concealed Light said.

“I could do it, but I still wouldn’t use your guides.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?” Concealed Light didn’t understand.

“Because people that have the ability to follow it can easily kill those BOSSes using all sorts of different methods. Why should they follow your guide and do things step by step?” Ye Xiu said.

Concealed Light stared blankly.

“These types of guides are meant for players who aren’t able to kill these BOSSes, so the simpler the better, but for your guides, they’re so complicated that only highly skilled players can follow them. Highly-skilled players don’t need these types of guides. You’re writing these guides for players who don’t need guides……. how is that not impractical?” Ye Xiu said.

“This……” There was nothing Concealed Light could say. The reasoning was very simple, but somehow he hadn’t been able to think of it. After creating his first Idiot Guide, he felt immeasurable satisfaction, but no one agreed with him. He didn’t give up and continued writing guide after guide, hoping that others would see how correct he was.

He finally understood. His guides were correct, but at the same time, they were completely useless in reality. It was just like Ye Xiu said; he was writing guides for people who didn’t need them.

Concealed Light stood there in a daze. He even forgot to continue controlling his creatures until he heard Lord Grim say: “Why’d you call your guides the Idiot Guides? That’s unfortunate. These guides aren’t idiotic at all, they just ask too much of the user.”

“It’s too bad they’re trash……” Concealed Light mumbled.

“You want to write valuable, high-leveled guides?” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Of course.”

“Then research dungeon records!” Ye Xiu said. “If you’re able to make the fastest dungeon record, then this is the place where high-leveled guides are needed.”

Concealed Light’s heart moved: “I’ve written one before, talking about your Boneyard record. Have you read it?”

“I did.” Ye Xiu said.

“How was it?” Concealed Light was a bit nervous. Even though he knew from Steamed Bun Invasion that his analysis of using Orange equipment might be wrong, he wanted to know how many things he got correct.

“It was pretty good, but you didn’t discover enough.” Ye Xiu said.

“What?”

“The 2nd BOSS Zombie Bailey can also be trapped.” Ye Xiu said.

“How?” Concealed Light was astonished.

“There’s a hole on the wall where the BOSS is. Did you know that?”

“No…….”

“Over there, if you send the BOSS into it, it’ll be trapped there.”

“Then how many Orange weapons did you have in your team?” Concealed Light immediately asked.

“One.” Ye Xiu said. At the time, Flowing Tree had the Level 25 Vampiric Lightsaber.

“Ah……” Concealed Light’s face burned red! His prediction that they all had Orange equipment was wrong and he believed that there was no reason for Lord Grim to lie to him.

“But there was a Silver Weapon.” Ye Xiu said.

“Silver….. Silver weapon?”

Concealed Light couldn’t help but notice the Thousand Chance Umbrella in Lord Grim’s hands. The weapon, which had been in the form of a lance, suddenly retracted and Lord Grim suddenly took out a sword from it and used a “Sword Draw”, attacking the blown away opponent.

“This one…..” Concealed Light called.

“Correct.”

“It can change forms, so there’s no cooldown in changing weapons.” Concealed Light said.

“Oh? A new player like you knows about unspecialized players?” Ye Xiu said.

“Uh…… When I researched your Boneyard strategy, I specially studied materials on unspecialized players.” Concealed Light said.

“Oh……” Ye Xiu said, “Correct, this weapon almost perfectly lets me overcome the restriction of being unable to easily use skills from different classes.”

Ye Xiu spoke as he had Lord Grim chase after another target. Concealed Light was no longer paying attention to his pets anymore and was now frantically trying to follow behind Lord Grim.

“Almost?” Concealed Light noticed this particular word.

“Yeah, you saw…… switching forms still requires a bit of time……” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, you can’t completely overcome this?” Concealed Light said.

“The only thing I can do is press the keys faster.” Ye Xiu said.

“This weapon is too amazing!” Concealed Light gasped in admiration.

“You’ve researched self-made equipment before?” Ye Xiu asked.

“A bit, but it was too complicated. You’d have to completely understand how the game is set up and know about equipment data at the very least. There also has to be large amounts of testing and it would require a lot of money. Normal players wouldn’t even be able to play with these requirements.” Concealed Light said.

“You’re correct.” Ye Xiu nodded his head and sighed. In order for the pro Clubs to be able to research about self-made equipment, it required a large guild in game to provide them materials and real money to support them. Only then were they able to create self-made equipment for those pro accounts. And the Thousand Chance Umbrella? It didn’t have that type of manpower to support its development. It completely depended on the individual doing business in the game. Developing this type of self-made equipment was indescribably difficult.

“Then your Silver weapon…..” Concealed Light was puzzled.

“It’s from a long time ago.”

“Because unspecialized players couldn’t level….. it became useless?”

“Yeah.”

“And now?”

“You can level in the Heavenly Domain at Level 50.” Ye Xiu said.

“Heavenly Domain at Level 50…….” Concealed Light sucked in a breath. Entering the Heavenly Domain had always been one of Glory’s most difficult challenges. It required players to finish it on their own. Other players couldn’t help them. With each increase in the level cap, the difficulty of entering increased as well. The current max level was 70, yet this guy wanted to complete the Heavenly Domain challenges at Level 50.

Chapter 208 – Summoner

“Don’t summon too many creatures! Practice controlling two for now!” Ye Xiu said to Concealed Light.

In Concealed Light’s eyes, his image of Ye Xiu had already changed drastically. He trusted what Ye Xiu said. He turned his head and saw that his summoned spirits had already faded away.

Controlling summoned creatures was quite difficult. It almost felt like the Summoner was playing a strategy game, but because of Glory’s first-person point of view, controlling these creatures like troops wasn’t as simple.

Luckily, Summoners possessed a few command skills for controlling their creatures. The Level 10 Follow made summoned creatures follow behind the Summoner. The Level 15 Mark cast a Mark, where the summoned creature would head towards. This Mark could also be thrown onto a player or a monster. The summoned creature would then attack the target with the Mark.

These two skills used very little mana. They greatly helped the Summoner control their creatures. The higher the skill level, the greater the range of the skill.

At Level 20, the Summoner could learn Lash, which would whip a summoned creature. The Lashed creature would then have its movement and attack speed increased. The higher the skill level, the greater the buff.

In addition, when a player changes classes to a Summoner at Level 20, the player would learn Strengthen Creature, which increased the attack and defense of their summoned creatures.

After changing classes, Summoners are able to learn Summon: Thunder Spirit and Summon: Fire Spirit at Level 25 and Level 30 respectively. The Spirits did similar amounts of damage, but the Thunder Spirit’s attacks have a chance to Stun, while the Fire Spirit’s attacks have a chance to Burn.

The other two Spirits, Ice and Dark, also had their own crowd control effects. Currently, Level 30 Summoners didn’t have access to these two types of summons though,

Concealed Light listened to Ye Xiu’s suggestion and concentrated on controlling only two creatures. He looked around left and right, but didn’t know who to coordinate together with. Lord Grim didn’t need his help and he didn’t know the others. In the end, Concealed Light went to Steamed Bun Invasion and controlled both a Goblin and a Thunder Spirit to attack Steamed Bun Invasion’s opponent.

He threw a Mark, wanting to hit Steamed Bun Invasion’s opponent, but who would have thought that while fighting, the two would suddenly switch positions? The Mark had landed on Steamed Bun Invasion’s back.

Steamed Bun Invasion had fought against numerous players in the Arena, so he knew the skills from every class and immediately recognized the Summoner’s Mark. He looked back and saw Concealed Light’s two summoned creatures rushing at him. He shouted furiously: “What’s wrong with you? Is it that hard to land a skill?!”

Just before, Steamed Bun Invasion had thrown a Brick at Concealed Light to have him listen to Ye Xiu speak. Now that he’d been hit by a Mark, he thought that it was the guy trying to pay him back for the Brick.

“Move aside! You move aside!!” Concealed Light shouted. Mark had a very low cooldown. He was just about to throw another one, but Steamed Bun Invasion blocked him.

“You two form a party.” Ye Xiu sent a party invite to both of them. Not only had these two players not formed a team, they were also attacking each other!

The two joined the party. Concealed Light’s Mark could no longer attract the summoned creatures’ attacks and instead made the creatures followed behind Steamed Bun Invasion. This was one way a Summoner could have his creatures move around.

“I’ll give you one to play with!” Steamed Bun Invasion shouted. He flashed behind his opponent and used a Knee Attack on what seemed to be that player’s butt. The player stumbled towards Concealed Light.

“F*ck!” Concealed Light yelled. Even Ye Xiu couldn’t predict what Steamed Bun Invasion would do sometimes so how was he going to be able to? The opponent pounced over. Concealed Light, once again, thought of several ways to escape, but before he could make a decision on which to choose, his opponent had already closed in. This player was a Striker. He used a “High Kick” and sent Concealed Light flying into the air.

“Stupid!” Steamed Bun Invasion cursed as he rushed over to help him.

“I’ll do it. Keep an eye on that one, Steamed Bun.” Ye Xiu called out. Steamed Bun Invasion had a Spellblade, on that side, who was trying to escape. Ye Xiu had already anticipated that something would happen on Concealed Light’s side. If not, then how could he have known to run towards them to help?

Steamed Bun Invasion turned around and looked. Sure enough, a Spellblade was trying to run. He immediately shouted and threw a Brick at that Spellblade.

Lord Grim flashed over with a Shadow Clone Technique and quickly beat the Striker onto the ground. Concealed Light fell. Quick Recover was clearly too difficult for him so his character crashed directly to the ground.

The other opponents had already been sent into the circle. Of the 18 guild players, 16 were in the circle. There were still two left on Steamed Bun Invasion’s side.

Lord Grim flipped the Striker over and used a Blow Away attack to send them over. Steamed Bun Invasion’s Brawler didn’t have that type of skill so he had to fight with the Spellblade for a bit. In the end, Steamed Bun Invasion was the better player and the Spellblade was sent into the circle. At this moment, the side with the greater number was trapped by the side with fewer people.

Having been beaten down to such an extent, how could these players not understand the difference in strength between the two sides? They all understood that they needed to retreat. Lonely Drink jumped out and led the way.

“6 o’clock direction. Everyone rush in that direction!!”

Lonely Drink was quite perceptive. He saw that the Brawler and Summoner’s side was the weakest link. However, he didn’t have the time to type while fighting and could only shout it out.

“How could I let you run away so easily? Six o’clock? If you say it out loud, how are you going to run? You should train your hand speed bro! If you had sent your group a message unknown to us, then we wouldn’t have had time to react! Uh oh! Maybe you’ve already done so? You say 6 o’clock on the surface, but maybe you’ve secretly messaged a different direction? Uh oh! Uh oh! Everyone, be careful!” Huang Shaotian chattered, mocking them, while warning everyone else.

The eighteen guild players heard Lonely Drink’s shout and sure enough, rushed towards the six o’clock direction.

“Uh oh! They’ve really come over here!!” Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly felt a lot of pressure: “What was your name? Whatever your name, hurry up and have your summoned creatures form a wall!”

Concealed Light summoned five creatures, but he wasn’t able to control so many so the five summoned creatures formed a crooked blob.

“What are you doing! Are you trying to let the sheep out?” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Throw the Mark onto me!” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim yelled. The panicked Concealed Light immediately stopped trying to arrange his summoned creatures and threw a Mark at Lord Grim.

Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella was raised up and a five-pointed star magic circle was formed on the ground. This was a summoning circle. And the only Level 20 and under Summon that could be learned was a Goblin.

The summoning light glowed and then receded. A green Goblin stood in front of Lord Grim. Concealed Light’s Mark flew and hit the Goblin’s head.

Concealed Light’s five summoned creatures immediately headed towards Lord Grim’s Goblin. He then saw Lord Grim use a “Follow” skill and his Goblin ran behind him. Concealed Light’s summoned creatures followed the Goblin. After a few steps, the six summoned creatures stood in an orderly line.

Concealed Light watched with wide eyes, but with his eyes, he wasn’t able to see how Lord Grim was able to do this.

Afterwards, Lord Grim also threw his own Mark. The Goblin led Concealed Light’s five summoned creatures and blocked the path of those eighteen guild players.

Of course, it wasn’t possible to block these eighteen players with just these few summoned creatures, but it did buy them some time. They began sending attacks at those eighteen players. They were no longer trying to restrict and control them, but rather they were beginning to kill them.

Tang Rou was the quickest and most ominous. She raised her Battle Lance and slashed horizontally. Like a viper, she Double Stabbed and Bled the opponent. Sky Strike into Falling Flower, the blown away players crashed into other players. A large wound suddenly appeared on all of the eighteen players.

“Wow! This sis, how strong! Amazing! Amazing! Ghostblade, cast a…….ah? Already cast? Wow, not bad! You have good perception! Very promising. Very promising.” Huang Shaotian chattered, while his sword continued to flash. Even with three players fighting him, he was still pushing them back step by step.

Qiao Yifan had noticed Flowing Tree a long time ago. Sharp and talkative. Plus, this Blade Master was unexpectedly only Level 27…….

“This this this……. is he Huang Shao……?” Qiao Yifan felt like as if he heard his heart jump. He was actually fighting shoulder-to-shoulder with two Gods?

Chapter 209 – Whoever Kills the Fewest is the Loser

“KILL KILL KILL KILL KILL KILL KILL!!”

During the battle, Huang Shaotian suddenly changed to the largest and boldest font to write “KILL” seven times.

Under the dense word bubbles, Flowing Tree’s attacks seemed to have become sharper.

Qiao Yifan became more and more convinced of his assumption. That Flowing Tree’s attacks never stopped and even while maintaining such a high tempo, he still had the ability to type words. With such a high hand speed, if this person wasn’t Huang Shaotian, who else could he be?

However, even with these sharp attacks, the first of the eighteen guild players to fall wasn’t killed under Flowing Tree’s sword. His level was too low and his skills didn’t do much damage. The damage reduction under the six Level Suppression couldn’t be ignored either. Of the eighteen players on the field, the first to fall was under Soft Mist’s Battle Lance.

This sister had died twice today and had been trapped in the city for a long time. Who knew how much pent up anger she had? The only thing people saw was her non-stop battling.

Ever since she arrived at the field, she hadn’t said a single word. The only thing she did was fight. If Huang Shaotian’s seven “KILLs were written by her, it couldn’t have fit her any better.

The white movement speed buff surrounding her feet, the Fire-attribute Strength buff surrounding her arms, and the light blue defense buff surrounding her body all displayed this Battle Master’s strong battle spirit.

She wasn’t attacking those on the edge, but instead, had directly rushed into the enemy’s ranks. But the opponents had no way of dealing with her, on of them had even gotten killed.

Not even Huang Shaotian had this type of courageous spirit. Huang Shaotian was pretty much fighting with players, who were in his eyes — noobs. He definitely held the initiative, but his opportunistic style couldn’t be changed. His style was to hide and then kill in one hit. He wasn’t the type to sweep away everything in his path and charge forward blindly. Every player had their own style; play style, habits, decision-making, these all reflected a player’s temperament.

Tang Rou’s actions made even Huang Shaotian a bit surprised or perhaps it was because he had only seen her fight in PvE before. Against systematic and monotonous NPCs, everyone had a certain set playing style. But in PvP, the situation was much more complicated and required much more from the player. A player’s style would appear more prominently here. Right now, Huang Shaotian was able to see Tang Rou’s style. Even though her skills weren’t perfect, her style could clearly be seen.

Lonely Drink and his brothers, however, still dared to slash once or twice towards Flowing Tree, but towards Tang Rou’s Soft Mist, their only feeling was to run away in fear.

“She’s talented!” Huang Shaotian finally witnessed Tang Rou’s strength. Before, in the dungeon, he hadn’t cared too much.

“Bang!” Soft Mist once again used a Falling Flower Palm to blast several players away. A sudden flash suddenly used this opportunity to dash in. With an arc of a sword, ice drifted down from the tip of the sword and a blue Ghost Boundary formed. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash had rushed in to throw down an Ice Boundary.

Lonely Drink and the others wanted to interrupt him, but they weren’t fast enough. One Inch Ash finished casting and rolled away, just barely dodging their attacks.

“Beautiful! In just an instant, you were able to clearly see where everyone was and determined their positions and possible attacks to choose a path that would let you complete your Ice Boundary without any interruptions. Amazing, really amazing! That wasn’t blind luck was it?” Huang Shaotian praised and even explained everything that had happened. When he finished, the numerous players were all frozen like ice cubes.

“Ah…… it wasn’t that good……” Qiao Yifan was flustered by the God’s praise. After saying “Ah…”, he wasn’t sure what to say. But at this moment, Huang Shaotian was already back to trash talk and equipped with his word bubbles, he continued to attack.

A Laser Rifle suddenly fired. The eighteen, no, already seventeen players were once again brutally ripped apart. On the other side, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim also used a Falling Flower Palm to create an opening. Steamed Bun Invasion dashed over and used Sand Toss, immediately Blinding two players.

The two, whose screens turned black, didn’t know what their situation was so they randomly attacked and fired off skills.

When their Blind wore off, one stared in a daze as he discovered that the world had already turned grey. His character had already fallen and next to him was his friend who had also been blinded. Lord Grim’s sword tip sliced across his friend’s neck. The liquid that spurted out seemed to be blood. It was just that in a dead person’s point of view, even the blood was grey.

It was only a Blind and the effect should have lasted at maximum six seconds, yet both of them had been killed in this time. They didn’t know what attacks their opponents had done. They could only look at the system log to check who had killed them: Lord Grim.

This person was originally their most terrifying opponent, but amidst the chaos, they had carelessly neglected him.

Lord Grim had been here all along!

Lord Grim is still the strongest!

But by the time they had realized this, the two had already fallen.

Lord Grim continued to battle. His tyrannical oppression wasn’t any weaker than Tang Rou’s when he used his Battle Lance. But when he changed weapons, his style immediately changed…….

The players were still trying to run away in fear, while that Flowing Tree continued to talk non-stop: “Ah! You’re not trying hard enough! You’re not fully utilizing an unspecialized player’s style. You’re always using the battle lance. Do you think you’re a Battle Mage?”

“Does it matter?” Ye Xiu laughed. Lord Grim’s lance stabbed forward and with a Circle Swing, another player died.

“You’re going to lose.” Ye Xiu said.

“What?”

“I’ve already killed 11.” Ye Xiu said.

“D*mn it! You were keeping track?” Huang Shaotian shouted. He had completely forgotten about the game. Now that he thought about it, he had only killed 9 players. In the beginning, they had the same. This difference between two players had appeared amongst this big mess.

“What are you competing for?” Tang Rou finally said something.

“Whoever kills the least loses.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha ha ha.” Steamed Bun Invasion laughed out loud, grabbing everyone’s attention. Afterwards, he calmly turned to Concealed Light and said in an official voice: “You lost.”

Concealed Light was still focused on controlling his creatures. His summoned creatures had been blocking the eighteen heroes. Those that were killed off were killed, those that ran out of time had run out of time. He had now, already, summoned a new wave.

This time, he succeeded.

Concealed Light was able to accurately throw a Mark onto one of the players that had been turned into ice cubes by One Inch Ash’s Ice Boundary. One Goblin, two Thunder Spirits, and two Fire Spirits rushed forward and surrounded the ice cube.

The Fire Spirit’s fire attack immediately broke the Freeze effect, but with five creatures surrounding him, running away wouldn’t be easy. Even though Concealed Light’s mechanics were poor, summoned creatures automatically attacked.

The pitiful player was bombarded on all sides and was actually killed off this way.

“Ah! Ah! I killed one!” A wave of excitement washed over Concealed Light. He saw the message that he had killed some player on his log. The happiness on his face made it seem as if he had gone on TV.

“D*mn!” Steamed Bun Invasion said angrily. Concealed Light had unexpectedly killed off someone. If things kept continuing like this, wouldn’t that put the two of them at the same level?

“How many have you killed?” Steamed Bun Invasion immediately asked Qiao Yifan.

“Two.” Qiao Yifan said.

4, 3, 2, 2……. At this moment, everyone began reporting their numbers. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had killed 4. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had killed 3. Su Mucheng and Huang Shaotian had both killed 2.

“F*ck!” Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t want to lose the game. But right now, only three remained of those original eighteen heroes. Lonely Drink was helpless. Even worse, no one planned on showing them any mercy. They all wanted them for points.

Who knew how many weapons and skills landed on their bodies. Blood and light flew everywhere and the three were instantly turned into corpses. Among these three players was Lonely Drink. With his guild leader status and strength, he was undoubtedly the strongest of the eighteen heroes, but even so, his fate hadn’t changed.

The moment his health bar emptied out, his world turned grey. The last sounds he heard came from two different people: “Ha ha ha ha, I KSed one.”

F*ck! Are we monsters?

Lonely Drink fell gloomy, but couldn’t tell who had been laughing. The penalties for dying wasn’t too bad. A bit of money and 10% of their EXP.

But, wiped out…… this word struck Lonely Drink hard. Under his lead, their group of 32 pursuers had been wiped out?

Chapter 210 – A Beautiful Misunderstanding

Congee Forest. 32 corpses lay in this quiet forest.

Of course, most of the corpses were no long there. Almost everyone had already chosen to revive and return to the city. Only Lonely Drink, the last one to fall, was still there.

A huge crowd of guild players had pursued them here. But sadly, their 32 member army was completely wiped out. Currently, no one knew where Lord Grim and his group’s position was. Lonely Drink didn’t hurry and revive because the battle wasn’t over yet. He wanted to see where they would head towards next.

Lonely Drink floated around like a ghost, looking over his corpse and over the nearby seven players in the forest.

“Ha ha ha, I killed one. You lose!” Steamed Bun Invasion laughed madly, talking to Concealed Light while admiring his system log.

“Huh?” Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly asked a question. His gaze fell onto a corpse —- Lonely Drink, the player he had just killed.

“Why hasn’t this guy revived yet? Is he not completely dead?” Steamed Bun Invasion began being a noob again. His character stepped on Lonely Drink’s corpse and even kicked him twice.

Lonely Drink couldn’t hear what Steamed Bun Invasion was saying, but seeing him kick his corpse made him want to cough up blood.

“Too excessive!!” Lonely Drink angrily took note of Steamed Bun Invasion’s name.

Just at this moment, Lonely Drink suddenly saw Lord Grim lift his head.

When a character moved his camera up, the movement would like as if he was lifting his head in other players’ eyes.

Lonely Drink knew that the system gave him a camera, but there no ghost actually existed. But when Lord Grim lifted his head and stared directly at him, Lonely Drink felt as if he was looking at him face to face in person.

“He knows I’m here……” Lonely Drink thought. Soon after, Lord Grim and the others ran towards a direction and quickly left his view.

The ghost camera after death was centered on the corpse. The player had no way of adjusting it. In the beginning, he had planned on determining where they were heading to next, but after seeing Lord Grim lift his head, he wasn’t sure what to do.

If Lord Grim knew he was there and knew his intent, is this direction he’s heading towards a trick?

Lonely Drink kept his death camera for a while, but Lord Grim’s group never showed up again.

Lord Grim’s group had already left.

“Follow me.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was at the front.

‘Where are we going?” Su Mucheng asked.

“The other side definitely has more people coming to find us. The moment you guys showed up, pursuers from every direction began heading towards Congee Forest.” Ye Xiu said.

“The route we’re taking lets us avoid encountering these people.” Concealed Light added.

“What are we hiding for? Let’s attack them head on.” Tang Rou said.

“Against those numbers, we had the advantage.” Ye Xiu laughed, “However, there’s no end to them, even if we kill them again and again, in the end, they’ll have won.”

“Why? What’s their goal?” Tang Rou asked.

“To stop us from training and slow down our leveling speed. Right now, it seems like experts from the big guilds are chasing us, but I’m sure that each guild also has two or three elite teams that are still continuing to power level. And us? All of our time will be wasted on dealing with these guys. To these big guilds, they don’t care if these players die. They have the manpower and plenty of accounts. But we don’t have that luxury.” Ye Xiu was quite detailed. He knew a new player like Tang Rou wouldn’t understand these types of guild politics.

“Then what do we do now?” Tang Rou asked.

“Dungeons, still dungeons. They’re scared of us taking down dungeon records……” Ye Xiu said.

“Hey hey hey. Dungeons again? Didn’t you say we’d spar! Everyone in your team is quite good! This Ghostblade lil’ bro that I’ve never seen before seems pretty strong too. Go go go. Let’s spar.” Huang Shaotian shouted.

Qiao Yifan felt extremely excited, hearing a God praise him. It looks like playing as a Phantom Demon was correct. His previous class didn’t fit him, so it limited his ability.

Qiao Yifan’s morale was boosted. But he was thinking a bit too much.

The only reason Huang Shaotian praised him was because they were in a game and he was regarding him as a normal player. Such a display by a normal player was more than enough for praise. If Huang Shaotian knew that he was a pro-player, then his criteria would be much higher. Ye Xiu’s and Su Mucheng’s display had been amazing, but Huang Shaotian didn’t praise them.

“Thank you senior for you praise.” Qiao Yifan’s tone carried a sense of joy. It was a misunderstanding. But even so, this beautiful misunderstanding boosted his confidence by quite a lot.

“Senior? What Senior? Who are you calling a Senior? Who are you?” Huang Shaotian was surprised.

“My name is…… Qiao Yifan……” Qiao Yifan was frightened and replied hesitantly.

“Qiao Yifan? You are…..” Huang Shaotian was a secretive person. The word “Senior” was enough for him to figure out Qiao Yifan’s identity. Normally, no one would be so polite in-game. Even if he was, Huang Shaotian had only just met with him. And seeing his skill, he couldn’t be a new player, so how could he have been certain that he was his “Senior” and not his “Junior”?

This guy’s from the pro-scene. And he’s even guessed who I am! But who is he? Which team? Calling me a senior? A newcomer? Huang Shaotian had already deduced several things.

“Ah…..” Qiao Yifan heard from Huang Shaotian’s tone that something wasn’t right, but he didn’t know what to say.

“Who are you calling a Senior? Me? How could I be your Senior? Do people still say that? Are we in some Wuxia film?” Huang Shaotian laughed insincerely, while sending messages to Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng: “F*ck me f*ck me f*ck me. What do I do? My identity’s been exposed! Who is this guy? If it comes out that I’ve run into the game to kill normal players, how can I show my face again? Hurry up and protect me! Hurry up and protect me!”

“Cough!” Su Mucheng coughed, “Yifan, who do you think he is?”

“Huang…… Huang……” Qiao Yifan didn’t know what to call him. If he directly said “Huang Shaotian”, he couldn’t show his respect towards him; “Huang Shao”? Only people close to him could call him that; “Senior Huang Shaotian”? That should’ve been the correct way to say it, but called him “Senior” seemed to have offended him?

“Huang Shaotian?” Su Mucheng helped him finish.

“Su Mucheng, you f*cker!!!” Huang Shaotian privately messaged her. He then immediately explained: “Lil’ bro, you’ve got quite an imagination. How could I be Huang Shaotian?”

“You’re not?” Qiao Yifan was dumbstruck.

“Yeah, he’s not.” Su Mucheng unexpectedly said, “How could he be Huang Shaotian? Huang Shaotian is a very noisy guy. He constantly buzzes around like a house fly. If he was next to you, then you’d go crazy in a less than a second. This fellow Flowing Tree has a bit of a Huang Shaotian style, but his noisiness isn’t even one ten-thousandth of Huang Shaotian’s! Right, Flowing Tree?”

“Ha ha….. ha ha…..” Huang Shaotian laughed dryly, while madly sending Su Mucheng messages: “You f*cker You f*cker You f*cker You f*cker…….” He then received an emoticon of a smiley face with sunglasses on from Su Mucheng. Flowing Tree’s cheeks streamed with tears as he sent a message to Ye Xiu: “Can you take care of it, old man?”

Ye Xiu wasn’t able to say anything yet, when Qiao Yifan said: “Oh, so it’s like that. My mistake.”

He wasn’t an idiot. Seeing the look on Su Mucheng as well as Flowing Tree’s weird reaction, he was completely sure that this person really was Huang Shaotian. However, the God clearly didn’t want others to know who he was.

Huang Shaotian didn’t treat him like an idiot either. He knew that with this, Qiao Yifan knew who he was. But even so, the other side acted as if he didn’t know, which meant that his identity was safe.

Huang Shaotian heaved a sigh of relief. In the end, all he heard was Steamed Bun Invasion mutter: “Huang Shaotian? What’s that? Sounds kinda familiar.”

Chapter 211 – The Waves Behind Drive the Waves Ahead

“You don’t even know who Huang Shaotian is??” Concealed Light was flabbergasted. In his eyes, Steamed Bun Invasion was quite strong. He hadn’t expected him to ask such an ignorant question.

“What’s that?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“Sword Saint! Do you understand?” Concealed Light said.

“Nope.” Steamed Bun Invasion replied.

“The strongest of the Blade Masters.” Concealed Light said.

“Oh? That sounds interesting. My spirit’s fired up. You’re the Sword Saint?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked Huang Shaotian.

“Not me. Huang Shaotian is.” Huang Shaotian replied dully. This nooby Steamed Bun Invasion was much easier to lie to.

“That’s too bad. I would have fought with you if you were.” Steamed Bun Invasion said high and mightily.

“Yeah yeah……” Huang Shaotian said, resisting the urge to kick his ass.

“Who’s the strongest Brawler?” Steamed Bun Invasion was already past Huang Shaotian and now asked Concealed Light.

“Uh, most people say that Team Hundred Blossom’s Tang Hao is the best, but his Brawler character Delilo isn’t the strongest. The strongest is probably Team Wind Howl Lin Jingyan’s Three Hits.” Concealed Light said.

“Oh…… really……” Steamed Bun Invasion listened while scratching his head. This time, there were two players and two characters. One was the strongest player while the other was the strongest character, making him a bit confused.

“You know quite a lot, Concealed Light!” Ye Xiu said. Concealed Light was a new player just like Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion, but he knew a lot about Glory. This was at least a show of his passion and interest in the game.

“That’s what I read online. Is it right?” Concealed Light said.

“Pretty much. But Lin Jingyan is probably going to retire soon.” Ye Xiu suddenly said with lament. This type of feeling was something he was currently going through.

“Yeah…… after this season ends, he’ll probably be able to play for at most another year.” Huang Shaotian added after hearing Ye Xiu’s lament.

“Wind Howl will probably find a way to snatch Tang Hao!” Ye Xiu said.

“Right now, pretty much everyone knows that Lin Jingyan is going to retire soon. Wind Howl will probably get ripped off. From a business standpoint, Hundred Blossoms is doing a lot better, so it’s very likely that Hundred Blossoms will buy Three Hits.” Huang Shaotian said.

Apart from buying and transferring players, accounts could also be traded. How many equips the character has is negotiated by the two parties involved. Usually, the character brings all of its equipment. A character without any equipment might have a few more skill points and some fame, but that’s all.

“That’s true.” Ye Xiu said.

“See how smart your Excellent Era is? Without any word, they brought in Sun Xiang and then made you retire…… if they made you retire first and then had Sun Xiang come over to fill in the spot, then he’d be at a completely different price.” Huang Shaotian said.

‘Yeah.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha, in any case, another strong opponent is about to be born. Lin Jingyan is already no longer a top-tier Brawler like he was before. Tang Hao and Three Hits…….. a new God!” Huang Shaotian swiftly returned to the topic.

eSports was cruel like this. As soon as your skill started declining, you could be replaced at any time. Formerly famous names eventually disappear one after another and a new generation with new faces appear. Sun Xiang, Tang Hao…… these risings stars of the new generation were slowly climbing up onto the stage as the main characters.

When I came back, how many familiar people will be left? Ye Xiu thought.

How sad! Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree moved a bit closer to Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. He lowered his voice and said: “I see it.”

“See what?” Ye Xiu asked.

“When you return to the Alliance, you’ll pull together your own team!” Huang Shaotian said, “Su Mucheng of course will obviously come over when her contract ends. That sis there and even that Steamed Bun have huge potential. I know why you’ve come to the new server to play. The new server is full of opportunities and talents. Besides the new server, where else would you find so much fresh blood? In the old servers, all of the big guilds would have already found the talents.”

“Ha ha, it’s all a coincidence. That sis is a co-worker at the Internet Cafe I work at. As for Steamed Bun, I just randomly bumped into him. It really wasn’t intentional.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then that Qiao Yifan? You’ve even scooped someone out from the pro-scene! Which team is he from? I’ve never heard of him.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Tiny Herb.”

“Tiny Herb? D*mn, a member of the Champion team, yet I haven’t even heard of him. This kid’s been buried into oblivion! No wonder you were able to dig him up.”

“Dig him up? You’re exaggerating too much. I’m currently retired and working at an Internet Cafe. What digging? The kid needed some help, that’s all.” Ye Xiu plainly said.

“For now, maybe. But when you return, how could anyone know about these circumstances? With so many outstanding new players beside you, don’t tell me you don’t have any plans for them.” Huang Shaotian said.

Ye Xiu fell silent. As he had said, meeting Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion were fairly coincidental.

But in the new server, just like what Huang Shaotian said, meeting these types of players with potential, some were incidental, some were inevitable.

Meeting Tang Rou was purely coincidental. Meeting with Steamed Bun Invasion was somewhat inevitable and somewhat coincidental. As for discovering Concealed Light, there was a bit more initiative on his end.

As a new player, Concealed Light’s mechanics were far from Tang Rou’s and Steamed Bun Invasion’s. However, he had a strong grasp of the theory and possessed a certain amount of tactical intuition. If his mechanics improved, he would also become a good player.

Even though Concealed Light and Steamed Bun Invasion had coincidentally met, even without these two meeting, Ye Xiu would have actively looked for him. Because of these Idiot’s Guides, he had already seen this person’s potential.

Towards new players, Ye Xiu never felt begrudged teaching but the people he taught had to want to be taught and had to want to learn.

Of the people beside Ye Xiu, Tang Rou had great enthusiasm. Not only did she want to learn, she also wanted to exceed him.

Steamed Bun Invasion was already following his own path. Ye Xiu was really only giving him basic reminders. Afterwards, he would form his own playing style.

Qiao Yifan didn’t need to be talked about since he was the one who asked Ye Xiu to teach him.

Concealed Light was able to create such detailed guides without any practical experience. However, he had written them for people who didn’t need it and his talent was being wasted in the wrong place. In reality, the reason Ye Xiu was looking for him was to tell him this.

Gathering these people together and forming a team…….

Huang Shaotian wasn’t wrong. Ye Xiu had thought of this before, but all he had done was thought about it. Ye Xiu understood clearly that making it into reality wouldn’t be easy.

Forming a team and going pro wasn’t simple. It was a type of life. Ye Xiu could determine his own life, but he had no way of determining other people’s lives.

Become a pro-player? Perhaps this was something many Glory players wanted to become. But what about them?

The main reason Tang Rou entered the game was to compete with Ye Xiu. Her interest in Glory was still developing. She had even rejected an invitation from a Champion team like Team Tiny Herb. What could Ye Xiu do to persuade her?

Steamed Bun Invasion, on the other hand, was simpler. Ye Xiu didn’t doubt that he’d nod his head and accept immediately. But because of this, he would have to set the road for Steamed Bun Invasion and take full responsibility over Steamed Bun’s life.

Qiao Yifan was a member of a Champion team. For Team Tiny Herb to add Qiao Yifan to the team meant that they felt he had potential. Qiao Yifan might only be overlooked because of Gao Yingjie’s talent. As long as he practiced, his skill level would definitely rise. There was no way he’d be abandoned.

As for Concealed Light, his research spirit would definitely be beneficial if he joined a team. Researching a map, researching the opponent’s tactics, creating tactics for his own team….. at the pro-level, strategy and tactics were definitely a big factor in whether a team won or lost. Winning or losing wasn’t as simple as which team had the better equipment and mechanics. But Ye Xiu had only just met him and wasn’t familiar with him yet. So wanting Concealed Light to do as he wished was unrealistic.

Huang Shaotian’s chatter made Ye Xiu seriously ponder over this issue.

Bringing a new team to the Alliance, that really would be as if the waves behind drove the waves ahead!

Chapter 212 – Doing Their Own Thing

“Why’d you stop talking? Why’d you stop talking?” In places with Huang Shaotian, there was no such thing as silence.

“Later!” Ye Xiu could only respond. He still needed some more time to think about it. He had only mulled over it for a bit before Huang Shaotian interrupted him.

“Forming a team and what not sounds a bit like a fantasy in your current situation, but you can still prepare for it. Dig out a couple more new players and you’ll definitely be able to put one together. If you just take that Steamed Bun, from the looks of it, he seems very easy to persuade. If you tell him there’ll be steamed buns to eat, he’ll definitely come and follow you. Up the mountain and into the frying pan……” Huang Shaotian said.

“There’s someone up ahead.” Ye Xiu suddenly said to everyone loudly, interrupting Huang Shaotian’s chatter. The two were at the very head of team with their voices lowered, so the people behind them couldn’t hear what they were talking about.

“It’s just a person. There’s no need to make such a fuss about them.” Huang Shaotian said.

“There shouldn’t be anyone here.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim looked around. There was nowhere to hide. Even though they were far away enough that they couldn’t see each other’s IDs clearly, if the player ahead was from the big guilds, they’d be seen as very suspicious.

“Not true! People come here from time to time.” Concealed Light said.

“Oh?” Ye Xiu was surprised.

“In Congee City’s chain quest “The Coming of Weiss”, the seventh part requires you to look for an abandoned windmill at the edge of Line Canyon. It then requires you to go to Congee Forest to compare the wood grains. If someone came here to finish this part of the quest, then it’s possible that he’s heading towards Congee Forest from the abandoned windmill.” Concealed Light said.

Ye Xiu was astonished. His nickname as the Glory Encyclopedia didn’t cover quests.

The Coming of Weiss. Ye Xiu might have done this quest ten years ago, but right now, he really had no memory of it. This quest definitely didn’t reward any skill points or good equipment, which would be why he had forgotten about it after all these years.

“What’s that?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked everyone. Presently there were four pro-players, two of which were God-level players, but none of them had even the slightest clue about this quest.

This Concealed Light truly did have incredible knowledge of the game. He even remembered a random quest like this and explained it to everyone.

But who cared! Only Steamed Bun Invasion replied with “Yeah yeah yeah” to make it so that Concealed Light wouldn’t lose interest in explaining the quest to everyone.

With Concealed Light’s reminder, they didn’t avoid the passerby. There was nowhere to run anyways.

“This person might reveal our whereabouts. If the pursuers meet him, they’ll definitely ask him if he’s seen us.” Huang Shaotian showed his careful side.

“By the time they ask for our whereabouts, we’d have already left.” Ye Xiu said.

“But by knowing where we are now, they can figure out where we’re heading towards!” Huang Shaotian said.

“Our destinations will be revealed sooner or later.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?”

“We’ll be going on TV.” Ye Xiu said.

“You remind me of something……. You guys are going to Line Canyon, so why am I following you guys?” Huang Shaotian jumped up.

“No idea.”

“F*ck f*ck f*ck f*ck! I’ll be going online tomorrow night! When the time comes, I’ll be seeing you at the Arena. I’ll be using my Troubling Rain to teach your unspecialized a lesson.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Maybe if there’s time.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck! You have time to run dungeons, but you don’t have time to fight me?”

“I’m sure you can see that I’m very busy right now……” Ye Xiu said.

“Then when you have time contact me, PK! We have to PK!” Huang Shaotian said.

“Okay.”

“You guys can play! I’ll be getting off.” Huang Shaotian waved goodbye to everyone and then logged off.

The team continued forward just a few steps, then there was a sudden flash and Flowing Tree ran back to them.

“What are you doing?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I almost forgot. This Broadsword I have is someone else’s. I said I’d return it, so send me back to the city.” Huang Shaotian said.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything more and sent out a bunch of attacks, killing Flowing Tree. Before he died, Huang Shaotian said a “Bye” and then flew back to the city to revive.

“Concealed Light! We’re going to go set a record at Line Canyon in a bit. What are you going to do?” Concealed Light’s skill level clearly wasn’t good enough for setting records. Ye Xiu trusted that Concealed Light understood that his skills were too poor. Fixing it wasn’t something Ye Xiu could do with just a few words.

“Oh oh……. setting records! Then I’ll go research how to get the fastest record for this dungeon!” Concealed Light said.

“Good luck. This time, your guide will definitely have many players reading it.” Ye Xiu said.

“Thanks, I’ll be going then.” Concealed Light logged off.

“Line Canyon, let’s go.” The five remaining players continued towards Line Canyon. Line Canyon still wasn’t the main leveling area yet, so there weren’t many players here.

Ye Xiu led the four other players to the dungeon entrance, avoiding the sparsely scattered players. The dungeon entrance was a bit more crowded. There were players, all looking for parties to join. These random teams clearly weren’t from the big guilds. The players were all in a crowd with word bubbles flying around, making it even harder for them to be discovered.

And like this, the five players entered the dungeon. As for the big guilds, their pursuers were heading towards Congee Forest from different directions. Some were from Desolate Land and Hades Village, some were defeated by Tang Rou at Congee City some were elites from random areas, and some were unable to be categorized. There were also the 32 avengers, who had revived. Right now, they were all gathered together and surrounding the entire forest.

32 players wiped out?

The big guilds already knew about this. If a random passerby heard this, he’d be scared to death. Even by knowing why it had happened, the big guilds weren’t any happier.

The battle strength of Lord Grim’s team was clearly much greater than they had anticipated.

The Battle Mage Soft Mist charged her way through the encirclement around Congee City.

The Blade Master Flowing Tree wasn’t at a disadvantage when fighting Level 33 players as a Level 27. He could even 1v3 or 1v4.

These two were the focal points. The 32 player troop described in great detail how strong and difficult Flowing Tree was. The guards outside of the city also continuously stressed how terrifying Soft Mist was. The two sides seemed to have turned into Flowing Tree and Soft Mist fans, even disputing which one was stronger.

“Flowing Tree is only Level 27! Level 27!”

“How many players were standing guard outside of Congee City? I could give you a Level 40 character and you still wouldn’t dare go!”

These two troops came out of Congee City together and as a result, they argued the entire journey.

Outside of Congee Forest, players amassed from seven different guilds. There were three guild leaders present: Cold Night, Lonely Drink, and Chen Yehui.

The other four guild leaders were currently dungeoning and power leveling. Ye Xiu’s guess wasn’t wrong in the slightest. The big guilds left their most elite teams to continue power-leveling. The guild leaders were more than happy to play their part as a member of their guild’s most elite team.

As for these three?

Cold Night was a Knight. As a Tank class, he wasn’t a part of the five-player dungeon record team for now, so he didn’t need to worry about power leveling.

Lonely Drink had been shamed the most as he was one of the 32 players who was wiped out. His corpse had even been kicked by Steamed Bun Invasion. At this moment, he brought with him newfound hatred and intent on being involved in this operation.

As for Chen Yehui, he was the original organizer. His purpose was much more complicated than what he had told everyone else.

Impeding on Lord Grim’s team’s leveling and furthering the level advantage to maintain their power as holders of dungeon records was what Chen Yehui had said to the other guilds. The other guilds had gathered together for very reason.

But Chen Yehui held yet another hidden intention. He hadn’t said it to anyone and also couldn’t say it to anyone.

While the big guilds were slowing down Lord Grim, weren’t they also slowing down their own development? As for his Excellent Dynasty, they had invested much more and had much more manpower than any other guild in the tenth server. And even so, they had sent in the least amount of troops.

Chapter 213 – A Match In Which the Outcome Is Already Known

Of course, Chen Yehui had his own personal reasons for going against Ye Xiu, which was much stronger than those for Lonely Drink. Lonely Drink only felt that he had been played by Ye Xiu, while Chen Yehui felt that Ye Qiu had completely changed his life.

But at this moment, he displayed reason and not impulse.

This was something Liu Hao had made him understand.

He was the one who persuade Liu Hao to work together and kick out Ye Qiu as a major task. He had considered Liu Hao a chess piece.

They had completed the task beautifully, making Chen Yehui very happy.

During this time, he had established a relationship with Liu Hao and had even received help from the pros on their pioneering in the new server. Liu Hao seemed to continue to acting as a good chess piece for him.

Up until they met Ye Qiu again.

This time, suppressing Ye Qiu could only be considered a side task. However, the two both felt that this task was more enamoring than the previous main task and the two had set out to complete it without any hesitation.

His chess piece excitedly stepped up to do the task, so Chen Yehui followed.

However, the chess piece was defeated miserably. Chen Yehui didn’t take the matter too seriously. It was just a chess piece after all!

Afterwards, he also tried to step up to the task, but failed as well. But he had discovered a new path and as a result, immediately looked for his chess piece only to find that his chess piece had already walked away and left him, while he himself, didn’t have the space to leave.

Chen Yehui finally realized that the task of kicking out Ye Qiu was more beneficial to his chess piece than him.

The real chess piece seemed to have actually been Chen Yehui.

Liu Hao turned around and went to do his own tasks, while he left the side task of suppressing Ye Qiu to Chen Yehui. If the task was completed by Chen Yehui, Liu Hao would be happy as well.

And Chen Yehui had no way of avoiding this task either because this had already become a part of his main task which was to pioneer in the new server but Ye Qiu was a huge obstacle.

Chen Yehui had no choice in this matter. The only thing he could be thankful for was that he had finally woken up and did not continue misplacing his priorities.

If this was a part of his main task now, then he might as well use him!

This top-tier God of Glory didn’t make him disappointed.

The few beating the numerous, 32 player wipe-out, made Lonely Drink angry. As a result, the big guilds would definitely unleash an even greater force right?

The tenth server had truly become much more complicated because of Ye Qiu’s existence. Chen Yehui pondered over this as he discussed with Cold Night and Lonely Drink on what to do with Lord Grim.

However, the three guild leaders only commanded their own troops. There were still the players from the four other guilds who didn’t care about them and were randomly searching for any signs of Lord Grim.

“F*ck, are they idiots? Do they really think they would just wait there for us to kill them?” Lonely Drink did not look highly upon these players.

“Seeing how no one saw them on their way here, we can deduce a few directions they might have headed towards.” Cold Night said.

“They won’t hide around pointlessly to waste time. They definitely have a final destination.” Chen Yehui said.

“Congee City, Desolate Land, or Boneyard. If they were heading there, they would have been exposed long ago. The only other options are Line Canyon or the higher-leveled Fire Forest.” Cold Night said.

“They could also be doing quests in the small villages scattered around Congee City.” Chen Yehui said.

“We can send people to take a look.” Lonely Drink said. The three discussed, while maneuvering their troops.

“If it’s Line Canyon……. oh……” Cold Night suddenly stopped midway.

“What?” The other two asked.

“I just received a message. We have their location.” Cold Night said anxiously.

“A message from where?”

“A player heading towards Congee Forest to do a quest met them on his way. From the direction they were heading towards, they’re definitely going to Line Canyon.” Cold Night said.

“Line Canyon, they’re not planning on running the dungeon are they?” Lonely Drink felt depressed. If Lord Grim’s group continued to dungeon, it would make it seem like their big guild’s actions were pointless. Nothing else could make them feel worse.

“These guys aren’t planning on setting a dungeon record right……?” Cold Night wanted to cough up blood. He really was scared that Lord Grim and them would set a record that they had no way of beating.

“Too arrogant!” Lonely Drink cursed. He was sad that they weren’t able to find Lord Grim and the others but became angry when they found their whereabouts. In any case, everything made him unhappy.

“There are a lot of dungeon entrances in Line Canyon. It won’t be easy stopping them….” Chen Yehui said.

“As they go in and out, we’ll definitely be able to find them. First, we can figure out their positions and then gather up people to stand guard.” Cold Night said.

“What are waiting for? Let’s head to Line Canyon.” Lonely Drink led the way and the Samsara players followed; heading towards Line Canyon.

Inside Line Canyon, Ye Xiu pushed forward like an autumn gale. However, they made a mistake in the beginning, rendering their run useless. As a result, the team just casually performed.

When they entered the dungeon, Tang Rou fought fiercely. She was clearly still in the PK mindset from before. However, after the first BOSS, Tang Rou gradually began to lose spirit and no longer had her energy from before. The same happened to Steamed Bun Invasion. The two players’ conditions went from hot to cold and eventually turned into a casual attitude.

“Hey hey, you two.” Ye Xiu called, “Have some spirit! Steamed Bun, sing a song for us.”

“NO!” Su Mucheng and Tang Rou cried out simultaneously. Quite a few customers in the Internet Cafe looked their way.

Tang Rou had been provoked and her spirit rose a bit. But after a short while, her spirit dwindled again.

“What’s wrong? You feeling bored?” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah…..” Tang Rou said.

“It’s normal.” Ye Xiu laughed. Tang Rou’s entire gaming life had been seen by him. Dungeon records were pretty boring to new player’s eyes. Tang Rou only liked the feeling of competition. But to her, how could this type of competition compare to directly fighting against other players?

Tang Rou had experienced a bit of PK in the Arena, but today was very different.

In the Arena, players were easily defeated by her and there wasn’t much sense of satisfaction.

Fighting against Team Tiny Herb was too hard for her though. She tried her best, but she had no chance of victory. No one would feel happy about that.

Today though, breaking through the encirclement was difficult and challenging and also was only able to be done by going 120%. This was a very satisfying victory. This was her first time truly feeling the joy of playing games. That type of satisfaction and happiness was something she had never experienced ever since she had played Glory.

Her moment of excitement had carried on for so long, but was now beginning to fade away. Compared to that, these dungeons felt dull and boring.

The main feature of PvP was the sense of battle at every moment. You had to concentrate, observe, and quickly make a decision; formulating or carrying out a tactic.

As for PvE, you had to concentrate in order to not make a mistake. For example, Concealed Light’s Idiot’s Guides were true reflections of the dullness of PvE. And worse, the best dungeon records could only be set by performing perfectly.

Once you grasped the strategy, everything else afterwards became boring. Monsters? BOSS? Dungeons? It’s a match where you already know the outcome: hit the monsters, clear the dungeon.

Once you know the outcome of a match, the process of getting to there will never be suspenseful.

Ye Xiu wasn’t going to try and make Tang Rou find interest in PvE, but only used it as a way to practice. And even though Tang Rou was improving through this type of practice, she wasn’t able to tell.

Chapter 214 – Limited Practice

“Dungeons are relatively boring.” Ye Xiu said to Tang Rou, “But if you want to improve, you can’t avoid doing these monotonous practices.”

He didn’t tell any emotional stories or give examples of any outstanding people to persuade her. Ye Xiu only said this.

“I understand.” Tang Rou replied. This reply was within Ye Xiu’s expectations. He knew that he didn’t need to explain any more.

Tang Rou’s hand speed couldn’t have been reached naturally. It was definitely a result of long-term practice. This was why Ye Xiu believed that she had done this type of practice before. Results wouldn’t come from just practicing once or twice. The important part was persistence.

“Although killing monsters and running dungeons are robotic, if you treat it seriously, it’ll be a lot of help towards your consistency and concentration. Right now, you have absolute hand speed, but you’re not completely using it when you’re microing. For practice, you can try targeting a specific place when attacking. For example, every time you have to hit the head. By limiting your conditions, you can train your microing and your control. We call this type of training Limited Practice.”

After explaining the theory, Ye Xiu moved one step further and told the specific practice method.

Limited Practice was something pro-players were very familiar with. This was a basic practice method. The theory is that the individual sets his or her own conditions and slowly increases the difficulty.

Pro Clubs would even create their own specialized sets for their players to practice. And this type of simple and direct practice was the most detested and boring practice pro-players had to do.

It was the same as football and basketball. Practice with the ball was always more fun than practice without the ball. Glory players didn’t like to dully use their mouse and keyboard to perform the same action again and again either.

But no one could argue that this type of dull practice was very effective.

As for Tang Rou, Ye Xiu didn’t doubt her perseverance and willpower, but he still wanted to see just how great her determination was. After all, he still had no idea how much this girl really liked Glory. Her perseverance wasn’t fake, but how much effort did she want to put into the game?

“Every hit should be on the head?” Tang Rou was ready to accept Ye Xiu’s suggestion.

“Hitting the head is just my example. You can do whatever you’d like.” Ye Xiu said.

“These are all insects. I really can’t tell where their heads are, so I’ll hit their first segments!” Tang Rou said. Most of the monsters in Line Canyon were crawlers such as sandworms and scorpions. They all had a segmented body, so Tang Rou set those as her targets.

“Sure.” Ye Xiu replied. He also called for Steamed Bun Invasion at the same time: “Steamed Bun, would you like to try a challenge?”

“Oh? Challenge? You think a man like me would refuse a challenge?” Steamed Bun Invasion rushed forward.

“Good. We start now. When you attack, you can only attack these insect’s first segments, got it?” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? First segment?” Steamed Bun Invasion looked at the insects and began to study what their “first segments” were.

“Under these conditions, let’s see which one of you kills the most efficiently. We three won’t be helping you.” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim retreated to where Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan were. Even though Qiao Yifan was there to ask Ye Xiu for help, he did these types of fundamental practices every day at the Club. What he needed help with was more advanced topics.

Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan knew that Ye Xiu was intentionally training these two new players. As a result, after clearing the monsters they had already pulled, they didn’t go and pull any more new monsters. At this moment, there were only sandworms and scorpions on the field.

“Two for each of us.” Tang Rou said to Steamed Bun Invasion.

Steamed Bun Invasion laughed: “Ladies first.”

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist moved forward and pulled a sandworm and a scorpion. Sure enough, her attacks only hit the two insect’s first segments.

At this moment, Steamed Bun Invasion showed up on stage like a star and smashed a Brick onto a sandworm’s first segment. He then used Sand Toss and threw it at a scorpion. After throwing it, he froze and then called: “Senior, does Sand Toss count?”

“As long as it hits.” Ye Xiu laughed. Sand Toss would spread out when it was thrown. It wasn’t really possible to only hit the first segment.

“Then I didn’t break the rules!” Steamed Bun Invasion shouted.

“Yup! Keep going!” Ye Xiu said.

The two players pulled their insects to the side, so they wouldn’t disturb each other. While the three sat there watching, Ye Xiu suddenly said: “Who do you think will win?”

“Uh…… Steamed Bun!” Su Mucheng said.

Qiao Yifan seemed to be thinking deeply and carefully said: “I also think Steamed Bun will.”

“It seems pretty obvious!” Ye Xiu said.

If it was just based on hand speed, Tang Rou was better than Steamed Bun Invasion. But determining how fast her effective hand speed was something that even Ye Xiu couldn’t do. It was simply because Tang Rou’s hand speed was too unstable.

Most of the time, Tang Rou’s hand speed could reach 200 or even 250. But once she runs into a complicated situation, her hand speed will drop to 150 or even lower. It all depended on the situation.

Steamed Bun Invasion was different. He was more familiar with games so his fundamentals were better. His hand speed was much more stable and was usually at 180-200. Even for complicated situations, it wouldn’t leave that range by much.

By limiting the target, the player had to be more detailed with his or her playing.

Because of this, Tang Rou’s hand speed would drop significantly. In reality, this limited practice was specially for Tang Rou. Ye Xiu wanted her to know her weaknesses. As for Steamed Bun Invasion, just the “first segment” probably wasn’t hard enough for him. If he was going to give Steamed Bun Invasion limited practice, then Ye Xiu would give him more complicated conditions.

As for Tang Rou, it was better for her to experiment herself.

Soon after, the results confirmed their guesses.

The conditions reduced their killing efficiency, but Steamed Bun Invasion’s flowed much better, so he was the first to kill off the two insects. As for Tang Rou, she seemed to be having more trouble. After a while, her two insects finally died.

“How do you feel?” Ye Xiu asked them.

“Easy!” Steamed Bun Invasion unexpectedly stole the initiative. Tang Rou was silent. Compared to Steamed Bun Invasion, she was too embarrassed to say anything.

“You made a lot of mistakes.” Ye Xiu said to Tang Rou.

“I know, six times…..” Tang Rou counted.

“You hit other places six times, but you also missed three times. So that makes nine total.” Ye Xiu helped Tang Rou count.

“Let me try again.” Tang Rou said.

“Come at me!” Steamed Bun Invasion challenged.

“There’s no hurry. You can do this type of practice any time. First let’s finish the dungeon. After that, you guys can continue setting the conditions.” Ye Xiu reminded.

After all, dungeons occupied everyone’s time. Even though Tang Rou felt that it was urgent, she couldn’t hold up everyone’s time. As a result, they continued to dungeon. Tang Rou adopted Ye Xiu’s suggestion and only hit the “first segment” even when they fought BOSSes.

“You can try and slow down at first and make sure you don’t make any mistakes. Afterwards, you can slowly increase the speed. Don’t rush.” After finishing the dungeon, Ye Xiu helped Tang Rou conclude.

The five players exited the dungeon. Right as they were about to enter again, Ye Xiu suddenly saw a familiar ID out on the corner of his eye.

Chapter 215 – Tooth for Tooth

Endless Night.

As soon as Ye Xiu exited the dungeon, he saw this Tyrannical Ambition Cleric. He was also at the dungeon entrance with four others. When Ye Xiu saw them, Endless Night and his group turned around as well and looked at him.

Ye Xiu acted without taking time to think and used a Shadow Clone Technique to dash in front of them.

“Hi Little Cleric!” Ye Xiu smiled and sent a Sky Strike at them.

Endless Night hadn’t anticipated that he would act so quickly and was just barely able to dodge the Sky Strike., but, Lord Grim moved one step faster and launched him into the sky with a Kick. The Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into its Gun form and a Gatling Gun, aimed at Endless Night, bombarded him with a barrage of bullets.

There were a lot of players outside of the dungeon, so many of the skills would inevitably hit others. Ye Xiu simply used a BBQ Delivery Gun to directly send Endless Night out of the crowd.

“F*ck!” By the time Endless Night cursed, he was already in midair.

“What’s wrong?” Su Mucheng had only just noticed, but seeing that Ye Xiu had acted, she immediately lifted up her handcannon. Right when it seemed as if Endless Night was going to land and use a Quick Recover, he was suddenly hit by Anti-Tank Missiles. Endless Night was launched flying, like a firecracker into the mountain wall of Line Canyon.

Hitting walls in Glory didn’t allow users to Quick Recover, but there was a common skill called “Wall Jump”, which allowed the character to step on a wall or tree when jumping to perform a double jump.

Endless Night was just about to use a Quick Recover to roll, when suddenly, he had to use a “Wall Jump”. He wasn’t able to perform it fast enough and his head tore through the dirt.

Tang Rou, Qiao Yifan, and Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t react any slower. By the time Endless Night was able to dig him out of the wall, the three had already arrived and were ready to surround and attack him.

The surrounding players were a bit stupefied. Everything had happened so suddenly. They just saw a guy fly out from the crowd and crash into a wall.

Endless Night’s four companions were obviously all from Tyrannical Ambition. While the others were chasing after Lord Grim and the others, they were still continuing to power level in the dungeon in order to maintain their high levels and competitiveness in the dungeon records. They were the elite of the elites of the big guilds, but by coincidence, they ended up bumping into Lord Grim’s group and then watched helplessly as Lord Grim sent Endless Night flying.

And these four players made an incorrect decision. Without thinking, they decided to rush forward to rescue Endless Night……

5v5…… the result was obvious. There’s no need to describe it.

“Who are these guys?” Tang Rou asked as she stabbed at her opponent’s head. This sis was unexpectedly still practicing by only hitting the head.

“They’re from Tyrannical Ambition. They were one of the guilds that was chasing us.” Ye Xiu said. Even though the pursuers didn’t have their guild names, Ye Xiu had fought with Tyrannical Ambition quite a few times. He had joined the guild for a bit, so he had some memory of quite a few of the player names.

Since things were like this already, there was no need to be polite to Tyrannical Ambition.

Ye Xiu understood the significance of this dungeon team. By killing this team, it was similar to fighting tooth for tooth. The guilds wanted to hinder his team from leveling and now, Tyrannical Ambition’s elite team was the first to lose experience.

When those four players rushed up to rescue Endless Night, they immediately recognized their mistake. Unfortunately, it was already too late.

In this confrontation, Endless Night and the others struggled. They could be considered first-string experts, but compared to Lord Grim and his group’s clutch, none of them were able to escape.

Endless Night laid on the ground. A thread of chilliness arose in his shameless heart.

This Lord Grim’s attack was so decisive and he even smiled and greeted me? Was he not feeling any pressure at all?

While he revived back in town, Endless Night reported to Cold Night what had happened.

When Cold Night received the message, he felt extremely gloomy.

Unlucky! How unlucky! Why was his Tyrannical Ambition so unlucky?

Good things never came. Bad things always came one after the other. All the other guilds’ elite teams were continuing to level. Why did they have to bump into Lord Grim? What type of luck was that?

Cold Night immediately contacted the other members that were leveling. Among these was his boss, Jiang You, and the elite team that he had personally brought over from the Heavenly Domain.

With this information, Cold Night at least knew where Lord Grim and the others were now. However, he didn’t believe that Lord Grim would be so stupid as to wait to be surrounded. Lord Grim would definitely switch to a different dungeon entrance.

And after that, he didn’t report the information to the other guilds. The other guilds had to be unlucky too and get wiped out by Lord Grim’s group a few times……

The seven big guilds that had gathered were now outside Line Canyon.

“Following the original plan, first we’ll send people to wait outside dungeon entrances to verify where they are.” Chen Yehui said.

“Right now, they should already be doing their second run. Hurry. When we find out where they are, we’ll get into position and catch them before they start their third run.” Lonely Drink said.

The three guild leaders had found the other guilds and discussed the plan with them. In the end, they split their numbers evenly and a hundred players headed to different dungeon entrances.

“We’ve guarded the entrances. If we keep waiting, they’ll have to show up eventually, right?” Someone said.

“What if they stay in the leveling area and don’t come out?” Another one said.

Inside Line Canyon.

The dungeon entrance where Endless Night’s group was wiped out was completely silent. Not even a word bubble asking for a party invite could be seen.

PK was very common in game. But they had been shaken heavily by the five murderers. These random players outside of the dungeon felt weak and along. None of them dared to offend the five.

They didn’t know what Lord Grim’s intent was. When his team passed by them, they all felt a tremble in their hearts.

“More?” Someone in that team still seemed to want to continue.

“Crash!” In an instant, they dispersed.

“None for now! Let’s go!” Ye Xiu said.

“Huh? Where?” Steamed Bun Invasion saw that Lord Grim wasn’t heading towards the dungeon.

“If we stay here, won’t we be stopped later?” Ye Xiu said.

Steamed Bun Invasion scratched his head to think. Ye Xiu had no idea if he understood. In any case, he said “Oh” and then followed him. Under Lord Grim’s lead, they went through an empty area and found another dungeon entrance.

“Is there anyone to kill?’ Tang Rou asked. This sis’s eyes were probably sparkling with greed. She definitely hoped that the players outside of the dungeon entrance were all enemies. Killing them all would be a great challenge.

“There will be soon.” Ye Xiu laughed. Lord Grim unexpectedly went past the dungeon entrance.

“We’re not going in?” The four were puzzled.

“It’s now time that they exited the dungeon.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 216 – Even If We’re Killed, We Won’t Tell Anyone

“Time they exited the dungeon?”

“Yeah, if they entered the dungeon at 12, it’s about time they finished their three runs and are prepared to leave.”

“We’ll be sending them off.” Ye Xiu laughed.

Now, Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan understood what Ye Xiu was trying to say.

As for Steamed Bun Invasion, even though he had gaming experience, he was relatively innocent and didn’t get it, so he continued to ask: “Send who?”

“The people who weren’t polite to us.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then why should we send them?” Steamed Bun Invasion still didn’t get it. Even Tang Rou understood by now. Ye Xiu had once analyzed this type of situation: the opponent’s left their elite teams to continue leveling. At this moment, they were finished with their three dungeons so wasn’t it obvious what they were going to do?

“But….. how do you know which ones to attack?” Su Mucheng asked.

“I asked.” Ye Xiu said.

“Asked?”

“I have a lot of guild leaders on my friends list.” Ye Xiu said.

Their pursuers hadn’t lit up their guild tags, which meant they wanted to cover it up. However, this kind of thinking was too naive. Many guilds wanted to pull in Ye Xiu, so his friends list was full of guild leaders from all sorts of guilds. As a result, all he had to do was send all of them messages telling them which names he had encountered during battle and asked which guilds they were in.

Ye Xiu understood the competition between each of the guilds. Even if they were in an alliance temporarily, they might be using it to pressure each other. For example, in Congee Forest, when those four players had baited Ye Xiu and Huang Shaotian, Ye Xiu suspected that someone had set them up without them being aware.

With this sort of relationship, the guilds that were asked might not intend to sell out other guilds, but they didn’t know if they would be betrayed or not. As a result, if they sold out others, they, at least, wouldn’t lose out alone.

And just like Ye Xiu had predicted, many guilds actively replied. However, the replies differed. It could be seen that some of the guilds were covering up for their own players.

After filtering out the bad answers, he found that there were six or seven guilds. Ye Xiu wasn’t sure if it was everyone, but he had acquired a few targets already.

“Line Canyon (TL: Entire map which includes leveling area + dungeon) only has two entrances, but my guess is that their main force is already guarding those. Our only choice is to look for another opportunity.” Lord Grim’s footsteps stopped.

“This place is?” Su Mucheng asked everyone.

“If you leave from this Line Canyon dungeon entrance (TL: Dungeon has several entrances into it), there’s a high probability that they’ll pass through here.” Ye Xiu said.

“You know so much!” The others gasped in amazement.

“Yeah, I just looked it up.” Ye Xiu said.

“……”

“Look, a team.” Tang Rou suddenly said. Hearing that they were going to PK, this sister’s spirit immediately flared.

“Misty Castle…… no.” Ye Xiu said.

The five players were currently crouching behind a sand dune and were stealthily observing the players heading towards this intersection.

“Another team! Samsara?” After Misty Castle’s team left, another team followed, which Tang Rou immediately noticed.

“Go!” Ye Xiu ordered and the five players leapt out from the sand dune. Samsara’s players were hurrying forward and not paying attention.

“It’s only five players, do we really need to ambush them?” Tang Rou realized that these five were walking along the road cluelessly.

“You can shout at them to get their attention if you’d like.” Ye Xiu said.

Tang Rou decided not to do it since shouting wasn’t her style.

Ye Xiu was the first to move out. Lord Grim used a Shadow Clone Technique to flash behind them. His Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into a Scythe, a Priest weapon type, and a blue light glowed on the ground. The five players realized that something wasn’t right, but by the time they looked back, the blue light had already risen and the five players were launched into the sky.

Cleansing Mist immediately lifted her handcannon and sent artillery shells and a Gatling Gun, sending the five players tumbling through the sky. One Inch Ash moved up, waved his Demon Slaying Blade, and then cast an Ice Boundary. When the five players landed, two of them were Frozen into ice cubes, making it so that they were unable to Quick Recover.

Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion shot forward, one on the left and the other on the right. Tang Rou took her battle lance and stabbed at their heads. In comparison, Steamed Bun Invasion shamelessly bullied the ice cubes.

Soft Mist’s Scarlet Moon Lance twirled like a dragon. It wasn’t difficult to see that her hand speed wasn’t ordinary. In addition, Lord Grim assisted her from the side. The players were unable to resist and by the time the two ice cubes melted, one of them had already fallen.

The two who had melted out of their ice cubes weren’t any better off. One of them was directly Strangled by Steamed Bun Invasion and then beat up. The other ice cube tried to escape, but after taking two or three steps, a Scarlet Moon Lance stabbed at his head, and like a mop, he was thrown towards his two allies.

The battle occurred extremely quickly.

When the Misty Castle players heard the commotion behind them, they turned their heads and saw that the scene wasn’t a PK, but a massacre. The Samsara players were bullied so miserably that even normal monsters looked better than them. Seeing this, their hearts tightened.

“Lord Grim…..” One of the players quietly said.

“Where’d they come out from……” Another player was puzzled.

“Let’s hurry up and leave.” The third bro reminded them to not watch. The place was currently dangerous and it was best to hurry and leave.

The players continued to madly run, while looking back from time to time. Samsara’s players quickly turned into corpses. Seeing that Lord Grim didn’t seem to be chasing them, they let out a sigh of relief.

“He’s not our enemy!” One of the players said. Seeing Lord Grim attacking other guilds and not mind them, the five wanted to watch the commotion.

“What???”

When Lonely Drink received the message, the five players had already died and returned to the city. During the battle, they weren’t able to send out a message for help. They were only able to report it after they died.

“F*ck!” Lonely Drink couldn’t resist cursing out loud. The characters he was leading, even himself, could be sacrificed. Their purpose was to wear down one another, delaying their leveling. But the five players who had just died were different. These were players who were supposed to be power leveling and taking a hold of the records. However, they had been wiped out by Lord Grim, making Lonely Drink’s heart ache.

“What’s wrong?” His cursing brought the attention of others.

“F*ck……. I burnt myself with my cigarette.” Lonely Drink lied.

Lonely Drink’s heart was just like Cold Night’s. He had hoped that Lord Grim would make it even by attacking the other guilds. Their guild couldn’t be the only one to suffer! Which was why even if they had been killed, they wouldn’t tell it to anyone.

In Line Canyon, Ye Xiu and the others had already encountered another team.

“Blossom Valley, go!” Ye Xiu said. This time, they didn’t ambush them and instead directly clashed with them.

“That team there is from Void Walk! They’re also targets.” Another team followed after Blossom Valley’s. Ye Xiu looked and saw that they were also one of the pursuing guilds.

“Two teams! This is going to be fun.” Tang Rou excitedly said. She immediately rushed forward as if her toys were going to run away.

“Pay attention to controlling the field. Don’t let any of them escape!” Ye Xiu warned.

“Relax, senior. Leave that to me.” Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly went forward and began with a Sand Toss.

“Steamed Bun Invasion!!” Steamed Bun Invasion yelled out his name and invaded the enemy forces.

“Steamed Bun, you’re so lively.” Ye Xiu praised.

“Ha ha ha ha…..” Steamed Bun Invasion’s laugh echoed throughout the canyon.

Chapter 217 – Void and Hundred Blossoms

Void Walk was the guild backed by Club Void. The name of the guild was a bit different than the others. It sounded like a name given to a bad guy. In reality, this name represented Club Void’s mission: to surpass oneself. However, no one really bought this explanation.

No one in Void really cared. Their guild continued to use this mocked guild name and as for their team, they continued to uphold their unique style.

Many teams had one Ghostblade character and player, but Team Void was the only one that used a Ghostblade as the core of their team.

The Team Void leader, Li Xuan, and his character, Sobbing Ghost, were considered the Alliance’s first Phantom Demon. He was Qiao Yifan’s current learning model.

Team Void and their unique playstyle was a strong contender in the Alliance in recent years. In the past seven years, they had entered the playoffs five times. Their current ranking this season was fifth place, a very hopeful position.

As for Blossom Valley, they were the guild that was backed by Team Hundred Blossoms. Team Hundred Blossoms was also a strong contender in the Alliance, though currently they were in a transition phase.

When last season ended, the team captain, Zhang Jiale, suddenly announced his retirement. This sudden decision messed up Team Hundred Blossom’s original plans and forced them to adjust.

Zhang Jiale was also a God-level character. His Spitfire, Dazzling Hundred Blossom, was a splendid player. In his six years as a pro, he had entered the playoffs six times, played in the finals three times, and claimed the title MVP. However, he hasn’t won a single Championship yet. Zhang Jiale’s name was known far and wide, but he was definitely one of Glory’s most tragic players.

Last season, Team Hundred Blossoms lost in the finals. Zhang Jiale fell into a discouraged state, causing him to suddenly announce his retirement. Team Hundred Blossoms was unable to persuade him and had no choice but to respect their player’s decision.

As a result, during that summer rest period, Team Hundred Blossom was forced to find someone to replace him. However, in the end, they were unable to find anyone suitable to succeed “Dazzling Hundred Blossoms”. In the current season, the team’s strongest account unexpectedly fell into a new player’s hands. The new player’s performance was quite good, but he clearly wasn’t good enough yet to become the team’s core. This was something Team Hundred Blossom couldn’t do anything about.

However, there was something this season that made them pleasantly surprised. A young player on their team, Tang Hao, rose abruptly during his second year as a pro and his performance was already being considered God-level. The only thing restricting him was his average Brawler account, as well as Team Hundred Blossom’s messy playing.

The similarity between the name Team Hundred Blossoms and their core character Dazzling Hundred Blossom wasn’t just a coincidence. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was a very old God-level account and could be considered the root of Team Hundred Blossom’s founding. The Spitfire had always been their core class. This was something they hadn’t changed over the years. This year, the core changed because of Zhang Jiale’s suddenly retirement and Tang Hao’s abrupt rise, however, the team still wasn’t used to it.

Impacted from this, Team Hundred Blossoms was currently ranked tenth and the situation wasn’t looking good for them. This season might be the first time they were unable to enter the playoffs.

However, Tang Hao’s progress gave them hope. Their current team was beginning to get their things together and it was still possible to come back in the second half of the season. Even if they didn’t make it into playoffs, they would have already successfully re-established their foundation.

In short, even though Team Hundred Blossom wasn’t doing too well right now, they were preparing for a complete renewal. They didn’t plan on falling and as a result, their guild Blossom Valley was still pushing forward.

Presently, the elite teams of Blossom Valley and Void Walk came across Ye Xiu’s team. Even though it wasn’t an ambush, it was still unexpected to have Ye Xiu and the others take the initiative and rush forward.

Steamed Bun Invasion gleefully invaded Blossom Valley’s troops, but as soon as he entered, he was hit. One of the players looked up to dodge the Sand Toss’s Blind and then quickly snapped back. He then kicked and used a “Punisher” on Steamed Bun Invasion. Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t careful and was stomped into the ground.

This Blossom Valley dungeon team was being led personally by the tenth server guild leader. The Spitfire, who had stepped on Steamed Bun Invasion, was their guild leader, Backlight Bomb, and was a Heavenly Domain expert, similar to Blue River’s status. He had the ability to fight Steamed Bun Invasion. Steamed Bun Invasion had originally planned on going up and fighting 1v5, but he had underestimated them too much.

After using “Punisher”, Backlight Bomb tossed a Grenade, while shouting “Scatter!” Blossom Valley’s players immediately scattered. He then raised his automatic pistol with his right hand and used his left hand to reload.

This wasn’t a normal reload, like when Gunners ran out of ammo, but rather, it was a Spitfire skill.

The speciality of Spitfires was that they used different types of bullets. A Spitfire reloading meant that they were switching to a special kind of bullet.

The grenade that was thrown exploded. Steamed Bun Invasion, who had been forced onto the ground by the Punisher, had no way of dodging. He had been hit as soon as he rushed forward, but he didn’t run. Steamed Bun Invasion got up and continued to close in on Backlight Bomb.

“Eat my fist!” Steamed Bun Invasion shouted. He was like a comic character, who shouted the skill before attacking, but compared to Huang Shaotian, who had been doing it for a purpose, Steamed Bun Invasion just did it because he found it fun. He hadn’t thought about distracting or scaring his opponents.

This shout didn’t scare Backlight Bomb though. Backlight Bomb rolled to the side and fired. Strangely enough, even though bullets came out, there was no smoke from the gun. The bullets that flew out glowed a pale blue and their speed wasn’t as fast as a normal bullet. Experienced players could see that he had used an “Freezing Bullet”.

Ice Bullet was a Spitfire Level 30 skill. When an Ice Bullet hit the opponent, there was chance that the opponent would enter a Frozen state.

These types of special bullets could be fired up to 15 times and when the player changed classes at Level 20, they would learn the skill “Ammunition Expansion” which allowed them to hold up to 20 of these.

While rolling, Backlight Bomb was able to maintain his steady aim. His skill level clearly wasn’t ordinary.

However, Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t so easy to deal with either. Ice Bullets moved slower than normal bullets. Steamed Bun Invasion’s body moved and shook left and right in order to dodge the Ice Bullets. Backlight Bomb continued to adjust his aim, but every time he fired, Steamed Bun Invasion would move left or right and dodge it. Gradually, Steamed Bun Invasion closed in on Backlight Bomb.

However, Steamed Bun Invasion had, not just one, but five opponents.

Steamed Bun Invasion closed in on Backlight Bomb, but behind him, a Berserker leapt forward and used a Collapsing Mountain on Steamed Bun Invasion.

Ice Bullets in front and a Collapsing Mountain behind, Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t look as if he would be able to escape. A white light flashed and Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella stabbed forward. The White-Wolf Fanged lance tip stabbed through the Berserker’s Body. Lord Grim’s arm swung and stopped the Berserker mid-leap with a Circle Swing. Collapsing Mountain was cancelled and Circle Swing smashed him towards the ground.

Ye Xiu moved his mouse and Lord Grim turned around and sent a sudden strike at the Cleric behind him. The Cleric had wanted to heal the Berserker, when suddenly, a Sky Strike launched him into the air. Lord Grim’s left palm shot forward and a Falling Flower Palm blasted him away.

The Cleric flew back and a curse from their side was heard.

The team from Void Walk was fighting against Tang Rou and was currently surrounding the struggling Battle Mage. A Blade Master had snuck up behind Soft Mist, but how could he have known someone would come flying over and block him.

Tang Rou heard this and immediately understood what had happened.

“Careful.” Ye Xiu warned and then continued to attack his targets.

Su Mucheng’s Launcher attacked from afar. Both teams were in her firing range, so she would fire whenever there was a chance. Qiao Yifan observed the situation for a bit and then headed to assist Soft Mist.

Chapter 218 – Crowd Lover

Sword Boundary!

The Sword Ghost flowed outward from One Inch Ash’s sword, creating a circular boundary. Tang Rou was inside the range, so her strength and intelligence were increased.

Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist stepped in as well.

Qiao Yifan had calculated the range of the Sword Boundary to envelop both players. Then he stepped forward two times and raised his sword to prepare to cast an Ice Boundary. This Ice Boundary was meant for the enemies, so it wasn’t placed in the same spot as the Sword Boundary. One Inch Ash moved accordingly and began to chant.

“Interrupt him!” Void Walk’s team leader hastily shouted and a Striker pounced over. “Bang! Bang! Bang!” Three shots rang out and the Striker was forced back. Cleansing Mist had fired to protect One Inch Ash.

The time gained from this was enough to cast the Ice Boundary.

“Back!” Void Walk’s team leader shouted again.

Against a Ghostblade’s formation, the best way to deal with them was to retreat outside the boundary range. This way, it didn’t matter what boundary you cast or how terrifying it was, it would only be a backdrop.

But retreating wouldn’t be so simple. As soon as his voice fell, Soft Mist’s Scarlet Moon Lance stabbed forward. Once Qiao Yifan finished casting the Ice Boundary, he immediately sent a Ghost Slash towards two players, who had rolled to the side.

Ghost Slash was a skill with a considerably long attack range. An arc of purple shot out and passed through both players like a skewer through meat.

The other two players were able to successfully retreat. But when they looked back, they saw that the other three were trapped inside the Ice Boundary. Being the only ones that had escaped, they didn’t know what to do. Should they rescue their allies or not?

One of them felt like it wasn’t right to run away, so he moved just outside of the Ice Boundary’s range and began sending out long-ranged attacks to save his teammates. But, Void Walk’s players weren’t sure what to do and were all doing their own thing. Everywhere they looked, there seemed to be Chasers and sword lights flying towards them. There was also that Launcher, who was always sending them gifts when they didn’t need them.

The person at the edge of the Ice Boundary was closed in on by One Inch Ash, who used a Moonlight Slash to launch him into the sky. Then One Inch Ash leapt into the air and turned around to use a Falling Light Blade. While sending the person into the Ice Boundary, he also knocked down another player with the shockwave.

Tang Rou, Qiao Yifan, and Su Mucheng controlled the four players, while focusing one of them and quickly killed him off.

“Retreat!” Void Walk’s team leader finally shouted again.

He had been trying hard to direct everyone during this battle and had made a total of three commands: “Interrupt”, “Back”, and “Retreat”. From these three words, anyone could clearly see their preparation from going to battle to their downfall to fleeing for their lives.

Unfortunately, only the player that stood far outside the boundary had the opportunity to follow it. As soon as the team leader shouted the command, he was hit tumbling by Soft Mist and then hit again by a Chaser, exploding him to death. Even though the other two hadn’t died yet, they were currently airborne.

The player that was far away had awkwardly stood there in hesitation. Only until he heard “Retreat!” did he begin to run. Soft Mist immediately chased after him with a movement speed buff. Su Mucheng also fired a few shots to block him but sadly, he was caught by Soft Mist.

‘He almost got away.” Tang Rou said as she used a Falling Flower Palm to blast him backwards. As for the rest, 2v3ing wouldn’t be a problem for them, so Su Mucheng stopped helping them and went to focus on the Blossom Valley battle.

Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun had been making fair progress. They had killed off two players and only Backlight Bomb was a bit of a problem.

Ye Xiu reckoned that he was a fan of the recently retired, Hundred Blossom’s team captain Zhang Jiale. Unfortunately, he was drawing a tiger like a dog. Even with the same class, he didn’t have the dazzle that Zhang Jiale had and was fighting wretchedly. In fact, he was quite similar to Steamed Bun Invasion.

He had clearly been engrossed in his fight with Steamed Bun Invasion and when he recovered and looked back, he saw that two of his team members had already been killed. The Cleric was now running madly from Cleansing Mist’s attacks.

This short distraction was taken advantage of by Steamed Bun Invasion. He punched, kicked, and bricked Backlight Bomb, who was unable to resist. After all, Backlight Bomb was a long-range class and wasn’t good at close combat.

。

It would only be a matter of time before the remaining players were killed. Ye Xiu wasn’t wrong when he said this was the most frequented road in Line Canyon. Another five players from a guild appeared and these guild experts cleared at similar speeds, but because they entered at different entrances and at different times, their exit from Line Canyon was different.

Tyrannical Ambition!

Ye Xiu immediately noticed their guild tag. He even recognized one of the players in the team.

Crowd Lover. The appearance of this ID was quite appropriate.

This Elementalist had helped them in setting the dungeon record for Frost Forest. Even though his hand speed might be a bit slower than Tang Rou’s and Steamed Bun Invasion’s, he was much more experienced and had an impressive understanding of strategy. He wasn’t someone Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion could compare themselves to.

Hand speed wasn’t a conclusive factor. This person was without a doubt the most skilled player amongst all the normal players he had met in the tenth server.

Ye Xiu believed that this type of, hard to come by, expert wasn’t a nobody in Tyrannical Ambition. He was definitely an experienced veteran from Heavenly Domain who had come to substitute for the dungeon records.

However, was this Crowd Lover the same as that time’s Crowd Lover?

Jiang You was also startled when he saw Lord Grim and the others. Their guild alliance had already arrived at Line Canyon and these few still dared to run amok?

He knew that Endless Night and the others had been killed. Cold Night had also warned him to be careful because of that.

When Jiang You exited the dungeon, he was already on guard, but after finding out that Lord Grim wasn’t there waiting for them, he put aside the matter. How could he have known that they would encounter Lord Grim’s group here? It even looked like they were currently in the middle of wiping out Blossom Valley’s and Void Walk’s teams.

“Forward!” Jiang You said without hesitation. Of the teams that had come, they were the first to initiate an attack on Lord Grim and the others.

Jiang You saw the situation clearly.

He had only seen Lord Grim and his team run a simple dungeon once, so his insight on them was limited and he wasn’t able to see exactly how deep each player’s strength was.

But at this moment, it could be seen that Lord Grim’s team clearly had the advantage against the two other teams. PK was the best indicator of how strong someone was. A judgement based solely on sight could only go so far.

Jiang You was no longer bringing with him experts from the tenth server, but instead brought the strongest elites from Tyrannical Ambition’s headquarters. In a 5v5, he still didn’t have too much confidence. As a result, he didn’t want to waste any time and would immediately rescue the remaining Blossom Valley and Void Walk players. Together they would be able to suppress Lord Grim’s team.

Flame Explosion!

Jiang You used this low-leveled skill. Raging Flames and Blizzard had high damage and high range, but they would also entangle the players from the two guilds. They weren’t partied together, so they would take damage too. Jiang You was scared that his attack would kill them off.

His Flame Explosion flew directly towards Lord Grim. Ye Xiu dodged to the side and stabbed with his lance. He forced his opponent to step to the side and unfortunately, this opponent was hit by Crowd Lover’s Flame Explosion.

‘F*ck, this b*tch is too evil.” Jiang You cursed, while immediately sending Cold Night a message: “Lord Grim, coordinates: 2875, 3400.”

Chapter 219 – PvP Is Even Scarier

Cold Night received Jiang You’s message.

They were just so unlucky. Their Tyrannical Ambition already had a team wiped out and another team encountered them. He had originally planned on waiting for the other guilds to suffer, but he was the one to suffer again. Cold Night really wanted to shout “Why always me!!!” to voice his current feelings.

But he had received the coordinates and there was no time to waste. The important part was to hurry and save them and possibly kill off Lord Grim too. Of course, this wasn’t something he was going to do alone. He needed the strength of everyone. Cold Night was just about to speak, when someone else shouted: “Coordinates 2873, 3398!”

The person yelled, while typing out the coordinates for everyone to see. Cold Night looked and saw that it was a player from Blossom Valley. The coordinate was similar to the one Jiang You had sent.

Cold Night was slightly startled. Clearly, Blossom Valley’s players had also encountered Lord Grim.

“Yes! Lord Grim’s here. Let’s hurry up and go!” Another one shouted. Seeing that he no longer needed to personally act, Cold Night didn’t say anything and informed his Tyrannical Ambition players to immediately go.

Currently, three teams were fighting Lord Grim’s group and there was still time for them to be rescued. It was different from Endless Night’s and Samsara’s teams where the battle was sudden. The fight was over in an instant, so Cold Night and Lonely Drink didn’t receive any messages until it was all over.

Seeing how all the guilds were beginning to move, Lonely Drink guessed what had happened. Even so, he still acted slowly and asked: “What happened?”

This guy wanted to sit down with everyone and talk for half an hour. Before, he had also wanted to kill Lord Grim, but after having his elite team wiped out, Lord Grim was placed last in his mind. He wanted the other elite teams to be killed off and then kill Lord Grim.

“Lord Grim’s appeared.” Cold Night simply said. He had already guessed what Lonely Drink was thinking and doing, which was why he didn’t say anything more. After saying it, he began to organize the movement.

Lord Grim’s appeared.

This was enough reason to act. The others began to move and there was no point in Lonely Drink stalling, so all he could do was order his Samsara to move out as well. The guild alliance had been split up to guard the city and check the dungeon entrances, so there were only a hundred elites gathered together. Even so, this was more than enough to defeat Lord Grim and the other four players.

However, these so-called “elites” were only relative. In the new server with new players all over, they were elites. However, if they were in the old servers, they would only be considered as veterans. The true elites were those who were currently running dungeons. Unfortunately, two teams had already been wiped out and the remaining were also in danger.

Jiang You could be considered as a top-tier player among the normal player population. After having his magic borrowed by Lord Grim, he didn’t lose his cool. He rolled and sent out a Frost Ball and then fired another Flame Explosion, this time, towards One Inch Ash.

At this moment, Jiang You’s Crowd Lover was attacking different players and his heavy magic was fired gently like a true mage.

“Careful, Steamed Bun.” Ye Xiu hastily yelled. The Frost Ball was headed towards Steamed Bun Invasion. Jiang You planned on making a sneak attack.

With him acting out, things couldn’t have been more clear.

This Crowd Lover was definitely the same expert as the one who had dungeoned with them in the past. Ye Xiu understood why this type of expert would silently run to the tenth server. Tyrannical Ambition urgently needed to take back their pride in this dungeon.

Su Mucheng immediately placed Crowd Lover as her target. Cleansing Mist fired a Gatling Gun, spraying bullets towards Tyrannical Ambition’s players, However, this was a game, so players wouldn’t die from one bullet. With Su Mucheng shaking her gun, the scattered bullets had their damage split.

Using Gatling Gun this way wasn’t for damage, but rather for temporarily stopping the opponent’s offense. Against a new player, they would probably be running away in fear right now, but Jiang You and the experienced veterans knew what was happening. The few bullets that would hit them wouldn’t do much damage. The annoying part was the brief stun and interrupt after these bullets hit.

These five players moved about impressively; they were running, jumping and rolling to break through the rain of bullets.

The Sharpshooter amongst the five players dodged and also raised his gun to fire back. Cleansing Mist was still in mid-animation and had no way of dodging. This Sharpshooter wasn’t bad and used this opportunity to fire at Cleansing Mist.

Su Mucheng was helpless. She could only cancel her skill to avoid the bullets. She then sent Anti-Tank Missiles to counter and in the blink of an eye, the two began firing at each other.

This team was different!

Seeing how strong this team was, the longer this went on the worse the situation would become. Ye Xiu immediately made a decision. He used a Sky Strike to launch an opponent into the air and used a Falling Flower Palm to send him towards Crowd Lover’s team. He then used “Fling” to throw another opponent over, this time, disrupting the enemy team’s formation.

After throwing the two Blossom Valley players like bullets, Lord Grim immediately used a Shadow Clone Technique and appeared between all five experts.

The five players were originally in formation, but were disrupted by the two meat bullets. Ye Xiu used this opportunity to instantly move to the opening.

“You’ve got guts!!” A Striker shouted and rushed forward to Front Kick him.

Front Kick was a Striker skill and had a slight knock-back effect. Ye Xiu wasn’t worried. He moved his mouse and returned with a Dragon Tooth.

The Striker felt that his Front Kick would connect, but a white light suddenly flashed and Lord Grim’s battle lance appeared in front of him.

The lance was long and the leg was short. At this moment, there was no way his Kick would hit first, so he immediately cancelled the skill. He didn’t expect the Dragon Tooth to be so quick though and was stabbed mid-jump. His heart suddenly dropped. The battle lance arced towards him and a Sky Strike launched him into the air.

He had incredible mechanics and his lance speed was also quick!

The Striker had suffered an attack, but instantly understood what went wrong. Ye Xiu’s hand speed, as well as the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s Attack Speed of 5, were both uncommonly quick, causing him to lose.

Circle Swing captured the Striker mid-air. Lord Grim flung hard and he became another meat bullet. The surrounding players dispersed to dodge. Lord Grim retracted his battle lance and fired three Anti-Tank Missiles, attacking the three front players.

This Gun Shake maneuver was unimaginably difficult. At such a short range, he was able to scatter the artillery shells at such large angles apart from one another. Of the three artillery shells, two were unable to dodge, hitting and exploding at contact.

Lord Grim then turned around and tossed a grenade into the air.

“F*ck!” The Blade Master behind him had jumped and planned on using a Falling Light Blade to make a sneak attack. But this Lord Grim unexpectedly seemed to have eyes at the back of his head and threw a grenade at him mid-air. After the explosion, the Blade Master fell like a broken-winged angel and fell face first into the ground.

How unfortunate. He had planned on using a Front Roll to Quick Recover, but he made a mistake. He messed up his Front Roll and crashed into the earth.

Tyrannical Ambition’s five, top-tier, experts were being 1v5ed by Lord Grim, who had instantly hit four of them. Jiang You was dumbstruck. Lord Grim’s PvP was even scarier than his PvE! During this moment, he was thankful that he had sent a message to Cold Night before-hand.

Chapter 220 – Screen Cannon

Jiang You was the only one on his team who hadn’t been hit by Lord Grim yet. Right when it looked like he was going to be hit, he immediately cast magic and Raging Flames roared up in an attempt to attack and defend at the same time.

But the attack missed. Did Lord Grim not rush forward? He then heard a whistling sound growing louder and louder. By the time Jiang You reacted, Crowd Lover was already in a huge cloud of smoke. The Launcher on the side had suddenly fired at him.

Quick Recover!

Jiang You obviously didn’t want to be hit onto the ground by the explosion, so he rolled forward. When he got up, he heard someone say in his ears “Long time no see.” A battle lance arced up and his Crowd Lover was thrown into the sky.

“Clang!” A cold light flashed.

Jiang You had only just been launched, when Lord Grim suddenly slashed an incredibly quick Sword Draw. It was so quick that it seemed as if the combo had been done by two players instead of one.

Just as the Blade Master on the side climbed up, Crowd Lover flew right in front of him. No one knew if he had gone stupid from falling, but the Blade Master wasn’t able to dodge in time and the two crashed into each other.

Terrible!

Jiang You and the others were all fairly big names in the game. With their main accounts, they were on the same level as Changing Spring and Blue Bridge Spring Snow in the Heavenly Domain.

No one dared to say they were undefeatable in PvP, but for Jiang You and his team’s skill level, it really was the first time they had been beaten up so badly.

When Jiang You and the Blade Master climbed back up, their other two teammates, the Sharpshooter and Striker, were now on the ground. As for their Cleric, he was standing there foolishly, unsure of what to do.

“Steady!” Jiang You saw that everyone had been beaten senseless. Usually, they weren’t this bad. The others weren’t ordinary players after all. With Jiang You’s status, he was often in contact with pro-players. It wasn’t that he had never played with Tyrannical Ambition’s pro-players before; it was just that he had never been beaten this badly.

Ultimately, it was an issue with their attitudes. Lord Grim’s strength was far greater than they had imagined and as soon as they began fighting, he disrupted their formation. They had lost their tempo and were having trouble finding it again.

“Just stall for time!” During this moment, Jiang You immediately lowered everyone’s requirements.

Shortly after, he heard the Cleric shout “Careful!” Jiang You didn’t ask anything and rolled to the side as he saw a bright laser brush past him. He was one of the faster ones while the other teammate, who had been in the laser’s path, was directly hit flying.

Evil!!

From this, Jiang You saw Lord Grim’s treachery.

He rushed up to fight them in order to force them out of their position. Their cameras were all on Lord Grim of course. As a result, the Launcher was able to fire behind them over and over again.

Jiang You had just been hit by a missile and if the Cleric hadn’t warned him, he would have been hit again.

Jiang You moved his camera. Cleansing Mist’s cannon was no longer directed at them, but instead was directed towards Steamed Bun Invasion’s side. Jiang You discovered that it appeared as if Lord Grim’s group had split up and found their own targets to battle with, but with this Launcher at their center assisting them, they formed a single body.

This type of strategy…… Jiang You suddenly felt that it seemed a bit familiar. At this moment, he heard a teammate yell another “Careful!” Jiang You hastily rolled to the side to dodge the attack behind him, but this time, he crashed into his teammates and coughed blood. Why did things turn out this way as soon as he looked away?

Could it be a dead angle strategy?

Jiang You finally thought of the strategy’s name.

Dead angle strategy. It utilized the opponent’s dead angles to move and attack.

This type of strategy was effective, but was not fun to watch, especially when it was from a bird’s-eye view. You would only see the people being attacked while running and dodging stupidly against obvious attacks.

At this moment, Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist seemed to be using this type of strategy. Whenever his back was faced towards Cleansing Mist, she would attack and whenever he faced towards Cleansing Mist, Lord Grim would attack.

Against this dead angle strategy, you either had to move in a way such that both sides could be seen or use terrain to protect your dead angle.

“Everyone…….” As soon as he shouted this out, he discovered that his teammates were charging towards Lord Grim. Their backs were towards him, which meant that their backs were also facing the Launcher.

“Careful!!” Jiang You shouted. And just as expected, the Launcher used this opportunity to shoot out three Anti-Tank Missiles and one of them was even headed towards him.

Jiang You had already dodged when he shouted out. He had dodged the bullet, but the four players in front were standing in a line, which made it difficult for them to dodge left or right so the artillery shell Jiang You dodged exploded on them.

“I’m right, it’s a dead angle strategy!” Jiang You confirmed. It wasn’t a coincidence but rather, it was a strategy that was being employed. Lord Grim had intentionally set up this scenario.

Apart from the dead angle strategy, Jiang You also remembered the Launcher’s strategy of using firepower to protect her teammates. This type of coordination was called a Screen strategy. It was a support type strategy that long-range classes used. Because Launchers had the highest range in the game, their ability and range to support was the best, so this strategy gradually began being called “Screen Cannon”.

After recognizing these two points, Jiang You at least knew that Lord Grim’s team weren’t just random players. Only those who truly understood Glory would be able to utilize these types of strategy at the correct time.

Being able to see through Ye Xiu’s and Su Mucheng’s coordination could be seen as an indication that Jiang You also understood Glory well. Many ordinary players knew a lot about theory, let alone Jiang You who has played Glory for so many years as well being Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader. At this point, the game has already become a career for him.

Dead angle strategy as well as Screen Cannon. In order to break through, they had to head towards the Launcher.

Jiang You instantly cleared his thoughts. He wouldn’t entangle himself with Lord Grim and help his teammates. Instead, he turned his head and charged towards Cleansing Mist.

Flame Explosion!

Frost Ball!

Jiang You quickly moved and Crowd Lover chained two spells. Flame Explosion headed directly towards her, while Frost Ball predicted where she would move to. Sure enough, Cleansing Mist had to deal with it. After dodging the Flame Explosion, she lifted her cannon and accurately fired at the Frost Ball.

How precise……..

Jiang You was shocked, however, he had already planned what he would do next. His Raging Flames was almost finished casting and it would explode and certainly hit her.

“Bang! Bang! Bang!”

Three explosions rang through Jiang You’s ears. He saw Crowd Lover’s casting get interrupted while black smoke permeated the air around him and he was forced stumbling.

“What happened?” Jiang You stared blankly.

He raised his camera and saw Cleansing Mist’s cannon fire a Cannonball.

Bang!

The Cannonball hit Crowd Lover’s body and he was sent flying away. As the viewpoints kept changing, the sky seemed to spin. It was almost as if he was watching a cartoon as he saw Lord Grim fling a player such that they would crash into his teammates.

Jiang You understood what had happened. The Anti-Tank Missiles didn’t come from Cleansing Mist; They came from Lord Grim. That guy was an unspecialized, so he could use Launcher’s skills as well.

This “Screen Cannon” strategy had two supports as the center.

Crowd Lover fell to the ground. Just as he was about to roll away, everything in front of him turned black. His character once again drilled into the ground.

“Woah! I just killed one and another came! Our synergy is so amazing!!” Jiang You wasn’t able to see anything. All he could hear was someone yelling into his ears.

“F*ck! That Sand Toss was too shameless!” Jiang You figured out what happened.

Chapter 221 – Forceful Control

Of course Steamed Bun Invasion would be the one to Sand Toss Jiang You’s Crowd Lover.

Ever since Blossom Valley’s two unfortunate players were sent flying into Tyrannical Ambition’s group by Lord Grim, they had become human meat bullets. Their remaining member, their guild leader Backlight Bomb, didn’t have any helpers and was unable to beat Steamed Bun Invasion in close combat.

Once Backlight Bomb fell, Crowd Lover was sent over, making Steamed Bun Invasion very happy.

In reality, in terms of skill level, Jiang You was better than Steamed Bun Invasion. But before he was able to adjust his camera after being sent flying, he was Blinded by a Sand Toss.

Elementalists were even worse than Spitfires in close combat. Jiang You was experienced though and immediately cast an Electric Ring. This skill came out extremely quickly and created a lightning ring around his body.

Jiang You wanted to use this skill to make Steamed Bun Invasion hesitate. But a Brawler was a Brawler. Steamed Bun didn’t care about a bit of damage and continue to fight like usual. As soon as Jiang You made the control to make his character stand up, he was punched and then clawed by Steamed Bun Invasion. When Crowd Lover’s blind wore off, he saw the Brawler locking onto his throat and his health rapidly dropping.

At this moment, concentrated fire came. Su Mucheng’s Anti-Tank Missiles and Laser Rifle shot over. Lord Grim also sent over a few presents.

It’s over…….

Jiang You understood very clearly. His Elementalist had low-defense Cloth Armor and low health. There was no way he could last long in this situation.

What about his teammates? Jiang You’s camera swiveled over. He would rather get Blinded again than watch anymore!

Circle Swing, Back Throw, Wave Wheel Slasher, BBQ…… no class at Level 30 had so many Grab techniques, even Grapplers. All of Lord Grim’s skills were these short-cooldown low-leveled skills. After using them all, the cooldowns would be back up and he could continuously confuse his opponent.

Jiang You watched as his teammates were grabbed by Lord Grim one after the other and were all thrown until they had no idea what they were doing anymore.

“F*ck……” Crowd Lover’s health finally dropped to zero. When he fell, he saw Lord Grim throw another person over, his team’s Cleric. Steamed Bun Invasion jumped over and punched the Cleric. At least, there was no more talking from him, Jiang You could no longer hear anymore.

“Where are you guys!!” Jiang You revived back to the city and swiftly sent Cold Night a message. In all of his years at gaming, he had been stepped on like this in the new server of all places. How could he accept this?

“Almost there! How are you guys holding up?” Cold Night replied.

“Dead!” Jiang You angrily replied.

“Ah…..” Cold Night didn’t know what to say. The guild leader was already very mad.

“How have you guys arranged it? That place is an intersection. Don’t let them escape.”

“Yeah, the dungeon entrance has our people from our side. If they catch up, then we should be able to surround them from every direction.” Cold Night said.

“Should???” Jiang You dug out the word.

“We didn’t have time to research the map……” Cold Night said.

“Then hurry up.” Jiang You was extremely annoyed. He wanted to know his teammate’s situations, but they definitely didn’t have the time to reply.

Tyrannical Ambition’s four experts were still hanging on. However, Void Walk’s three players were already unable to hold out and turned into corpses one after the other. Tang Rou and Qiao Yifan had killed them off.

Ye Xiu was currently 2v5ing with Su Mucheng. The five players looked as if they were being extremely badly, but in reality, their life wasn’t dropping very fast. In order to control the field, Ye Xiu had to give up on a lot of opportunities to inflict heavy damage on an opponent. Many skills weren’t able to be used.

He had the ability to kill off one or two of the players, but if he did that, then the others might escape. Ye Xiu didn’t want players to interrupt in the other two battles. As a result, he had forcefully controlled his opponents.

At this moment, Tang Rou and Qiao Yifan finally arrived and joined in on Ye Xiu’s battle. With support, Ye Xiu immediately erupted and turned to combo an opponent next to him.

“Hurry!” Ye Xiu shouted.

Qiao Yifan’s Sword Boundary was released and Tang Rou began fighting within it. Su Mucheng’s entire offensive was concentrated here. Steamed Bun Invasion was only dealing with a Cleric, so he didn’t need any help.

Blossom Valley’s players fell first. Only Tyrannical Ambition’s experts remained.

Among the normal player base, they were definitely top-tier experts. Unfortunately, they were trying to fight with a top-tier God among the pro-scene. Lord Grim was even able to bully Tiny Herb’s pro-players. Such a one-sided battle already hurt their confidence.

“More players are coming!” Tang Rou suddenly called as she continued to dish out damage.

Ye Xiu’s heart couldn’t help but drop. There was no way they could continue fighting like this. Ignoring all else, they didn’t have enough mana! If Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion hadn’t learned about how to conserve mana during battle, then they probably would have run out already.

Besides being unable to continue battling, Ye Xiu was also worried about reinforcement arriving. The reason he didn’t let a single person go before was because he thought that there was enough time to kill off everyone.

But if another dungeon team came…..

Ye Xiu looked, but discovered that the players coming might not be a hindrance.

“Hey, you just finished dungeoning?” Ye Xiu greeted this team. The team’s players slowed down.

“Cough…… you’re killing?” The other side slowly said. Blue River was speaking. This team was from Blue Brook Guild. Ye Xiu had met with the others, Bound Boat, Thundering Light, Returning Cloud, etc. long ago. The people behind the computers were all staring forward with grotesque faces.

“Yup!” Ye Xiu replied while sending an opponent flying.

Blue River and the others watched as the player flew up and then fell. They were completely silent. They had no intent on joining the battle and also didn’t seem to want to leave either.

“Blue Bridge, you coward! A few dungeon records and you’re scared?” Someone suddenly cursed.

Only Heavenly Domain players who knew him would call Blue River, Blue Bridge. Could he be an expert from Tyrannical Ambition’s headquarters? Blue River was startled. He took another look at them……. Even though he wasn’t able to tell who it was from his voice, he already figured out who they were by looking at their classes. Blue River suddenly felt quite good.

“Sigh, today’s my birthday, so I’ll be going off early. I’ll be on my way then, have fun, everyone!” Blue River said. He didn’t look on any further and led his team away.

“Do you know any shame, Blue Bridge……” Tyrannical Ambition was still talking to him.

Chapter 222 – Searching for Tracks

Even though Tyrannical Ambition’s top experts hadn’t participated in the pursuit for Lord Grim, they understood their situation in the tenth server. Blue Brook Guild should be feeling more pressed to suppress Lord Grim than they were.

But after Blue Brook Guild was stepped on in Desolate Land, they seemed to have stayed outside of matters.

Were they scared? Or had they reached an agreement with Lord Grim? Or did they have some other scheme up their sleeves? No one knew.

Their current movement would have benefited every guild in the tenth server that was competing for dungeon records. Even though Blue Brook Guild was currently in the worst state, who would look down on Blue Brook Guild’s strength? As soon as Lord Grim was suppressed, Blue Brook Guild would jump back as one of the strongest contenders for the dungeon records, especially since they wouldn’t have sacrificed anyone to suppress Lord Grim…….

How could the other guilds just let Blue Brook Guild take advantage of their hard-earned win like that?

Originally, competing for dungeon records was up to the player and facing against other opponents was also up to the player.

But because of one another’s interests, such simple rules no longer belonged. As a result, everyone created a hidden set of rules that everyone had to uphold.

Those who hadn’t participated in the elimination of Lord Grim would not have the qualifications to fight for the dungeon records. This was what the seven guilds who had participated were thinking.

In their eyes, Blue Brook Guild wasn’t upholding the rules.

Seeing how Blue River wasn’t going to help them, they could clearly see his attitude towards this subject.

This was why Tyrannical Ambition’s expert was extremely spiteful and was loudly looking down upon them. However, this wouldn’t change Blue River’s decision; it wouldn’t change their current plight.

Three players quickly became two players.

Two players quickly became one player.

When the last player fell, Steamed Bun Invasion also finished up with his Cleric. Currently, they could hear footsteps closing in from a distance.

“They’re here. Run.” Ye Xiu said.

But only after running a bit, he suddenly stopped. After waiting for the others to catch up, he suddenly headed towards the left fork: “This way. Stick close to the side.”

“This is?”

“To avoid the dead player’s eyes?” Qiao Yifan noticed that that Blade Master’s corpse was still there. However, he didn’t know how large his ghost camera was.

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim led the way, while the others followed closely behind in a line.

“Pay attention to any players you see.” Ye Xiu said again.

“Hm?”

“In order to find where we were, besides blocking the entrances to Line Canyon, they also sent players over to keep watch at the various dungeon entrances. Right now, they know where we are, so players from the dungeon will be heading over there.” Ye Xiu said.

“How come they still know where we are!” Su Mucheng exclaimed.

“It’s just a possibility!” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you mean?”

“Turn this way!” Ye Xiu changed directions again.

“Don’t tell me you want to find a route where we’ll avoid everyone?” Su Mucheng said.

“It’s not that complicated.” Ye Xiu smiled, “We just have to take a long detour to stay as far away as possible from them. Here, this way.” Ye Xiu continued to lead the way.

Less than a minute after Ye Xiu’s group left, at the place where a great battle recently took place, the troops from the seven guilds finally arrived.

On the way, they bumped into Blue Brook Guild’s group. Blue River was still as calm as ever and he, along with Bound Boat and the others, were looked down on as they passed by each other.

Four of the seven guilds began to burn with anger after seeing the tragedy. Some of the vestiges of battle hadn’t yet disappeared yet.

Blood, smoke, sword scars……

In just a few short minutes, the elite teams of each of the four guilds had been wiped out. Tyrannical Ambition lost the most. Two of their teams had been wiped out, including their team that the guild leader’s personally led.

“Just how strong is Lord Grim?” Cold Night thought as he looked at the rage messages sent by Jiang You.

With the situation being like this, the news about the elite teams from each of their four guilds had already been spread. The other three guilds expressed their sympathies, but they knew that they were laughing at them on the inside.

Only Chen Yehui wasn’t surprised by the outcome. He was the only one understood just how strong their opponents were.

He had once used numbers to try and bully the few, and the result? How could these elite experts compare to their Excellent Dynasty’s players?

Though unfortunately, Herb Garden and Royal Heritage hadn’t been touched in all of this.

Chen Yehui thought as he looked at the players from these two guilds. He felt that their half-heartedness was a little suspicious, especially Herb Garden. They were one of the Three Great Guilds, but among all of them, Herb Garden had sent the fewest number of players and their movements were also the slowest. Chen Yehui suspected that Herb Garden had other plans just like them.

“Lord Grim went this way.” After the Blade Master revived, he sent a message to Cold Night, telling him the direction they went towards.

“Directions from another corpse?” Lonely Drink had experience scouting out as a corpse.

“Yeah.”

“Then it might not be accurate.” Lonely Drink said. At that time in Congee Forest, Lonely Drink’s directions had been wrong.

“So we should exclude this direction?”

“That…..” Lonely Drink wasn’t confident.

Right now, three forks were in front of them. The information the corpse had provided was ignored.

Split the troops three ways? They didn’t dare…… Even though the terrain here was completely different from Congee Forest’s, the 32 players wipe out was still fresh in their minds.

“Players that come here from the dungeons will have seen them.” Someone said.

“There’s no way they can stop them. It’d be too late by the time we get there.”

“What if they used this opening to slip out of Line Canyon?”

Everyone immediately froze.

“Maybe it’d be best to get back to the Line Canyon entrances?”

“Looks like that’s our only option.” The guilds discussed and in the end, that was their final decision.

Their discussion didn’t go on for very long this time. After admiring the vestiges of battle for a short moment, they quickly returned to guard duty.

The players from the dungeon entrances that had rushed over reported back.

No, no, no…….. no one had found them.

“F*ck! They really ran off?” Someone cursed.

“Maybe or maybe they’ve temporarily hidden themselves?” Another guessed.

Both possibilities made them want to go crazy, but they had no way of verifying. All one hundred players coughed blood and then went to guard the entrances. The players who had been guarding the dungeon entrances were given another order: to scout around the leveling area and search for traces of Lord Grim’s group without exposing their identity.

Chapter 223 – Wild BOSS Discovered

2 AM, Line Canyon.

The pitiful players of the seven guilds weren’t sleeping, leveling, dungeoning, or questing, but were forced to blindly search the leveling areas instead.

The players at the dungeon entrances weren’t having it any better either. They were extremely lonely. Even worse, were the hundred players outside of Congee City. They had already been waiting for so long…….

They searched the leveling areas and possible quest locations, but found nothing.

And just like this, half an hour passed in the blink of an eye.

News of Lord Grim’s group suddenly popped up in front of everyone.

System Announcement: Congratulations to players Lord Grim, Cleansing Mist, Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, and One Inch Ash for breaking the Line Canyon record, time: 29:51:44.

“F*CK!!” This sound echoed from all around Line Canyon. The seven guilds had searched madly around the entire world, while their targets went to set a dungeon record.

The Line Canyon dungeon record had already been broken by Lord Grim twice. In the past, whenever Lord Grim’s team broke the record, they always did by more than 1 minute. Afterwards, no one could even hope to compete, but these two records that were set by them had only improved the record by a bit. It wasn’t as ridiculous.

However, now that they thought about it, right now, Lord Grim’s team consisted of four Level 31s and one Level 30. When they hit Level 33, what record would they be able to achieve?

As for how they had somehow escaped from under their watchful gaze, there was already no point in figuring it out.

“Dungeon!! Guard the dungeon entrances.” Everyone immediately received new orders. They could only curse as they rushed towards the dungeon entrances.

“BOSS! Wild BOSS!” More news arrived. Of course, the messenger didn’t send it to everyone; it was only sent to his guild leader.

“There’s no one else here. It’s only me. This place is really empty!” The player who discovered the wild BOSS was somewhat incoherent.

They hadn’t found Lord Grim, but they had found a wild BOSS. Cold Night was very moved.

It’s been such a terrible night! Who could have suffered more than my Tyrannical Ambition? Maybe the system is feeling sorry and is taking care of us?

The cold night stayed silent. In the currently sparse Line Canyon, they might be able to take down the wild BOSS without anyone knowing.

But the other guilds were still guarding the Line Canyon entrances. If he suddenly maneuvered a large amount of troops, he might arouse their suspicion. As a result, Cold Night reported this news to Jiang You.

Jiang You hadn’t logged out yet and was still in the tenth server. He was currently together with the four other experts that had come from the Heavenly Domain. Their wipe-out half an hour ago was still looping through their minds. It truly wasn’t a happy memory.

They had specially come over to compete with Lord Grim for the dungeon records, but they had been defeated by their opponents in direct combat. They weren’t even been able to last long enough for backup to arrive. In just a few minutes, they had bit the dust……..

If news of this got out, how could they have the face to consider themselves top-tier experts? They’d probably become a laughing stock. Poplar Beach was an example of this.

If Poplar Beach were to ever have the chance to turn back time, he definitely wouldn’t try to challenge Lord Grim. Even if he decided that they would battle, he would go in with an alternative account.

Unfortunately, that wasn’t what happened. Poplar Beach dueled Lord Grim and lost extremely miserably. Who knew how many players had already gone to laugh at him?

Ever since then, Poplar Beach never appeared online again.

Thinking of Poplar Beach, Jiang You and the others could only feel that they were considered lucky. They were, at least, wearing armor and weren’t the center of everyone’s attention.

Lord Grim was very strong, but Jiang You and the others wanted to redeem themselves. During the past half an hour, they had been discussing the strategy and tactics Lord Grim’s team had employed, Lord Grim’s difficult to deal with unspecialized, as well as how they would beat them next time.

“What about Lord Grim?” Jiang You was more concerned with Lord Grim.

Cold Night was startled. Lord Grim had just gone on TV, did Jiang You not see it? What had they been doing the past thirty minutes?

“They were dungeoning. They just broke the record.” Cold Night could only say the truth.

“Record?” Jiang You immediately checked the record leaderboards. He looked at it and then let out a sigh of relief: “It doesn’t look like it’s anything impressive.”

“Yeah, they probably weren’t going all out.” Cold Night said.

“By the time we wait for them to go all out, it’ll be too late. Have you found their location yet?” Jiang You asked.

“No……”

“What do you mean no?” Jiang You was not in a good mood.

“We didn’t know how they got into the dungeon. This time, we’ll guard the dungeon entrances better.” Cold Night could only try and explain.

“They can still dungeon one more time. If we guard the Line Canyon entrances, we’ll definitely catch them.” Jiang You said.

“Okay…. then what about the wild BOSS?”

“Let’s go!”

“Do we need more players?”

“No need. More players will attract too much attention.” Jiang You replied. He suppressed the urge to prove that they really were experts.

“Okay…..” Cold Night said.

After setting the dungeon record, Ye Xiu immediately led the group away.

“We can’t continue dungeoning.” Ye Xiu said. Previously, they had gone around the guild players in order to enter the dungeon, but there was no way they could ensure that they wouldn’t be found this time.

They wound around the map until they reached a very remote place. They looked around and there wasn’t a single person there, which meant that they hadn’t been discovered.

“If I knew of this earlier then we could have ran it one more time…… Well, whatever. Let’s just kill some monsters and level here!” Ye Xiu said.

“Then I’ll be going off.” Su Mucheng said.

“Me too.” Qiao Yifan said. The pro-players couldn’t stay up all night.

“Go ahead!”

The two players said bye. Only Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, and Steamed Bun Invasion could stay up and play until daylight.

“Pay attention to any suspicious movements. The other side might be looking for us.” Ye Xiu warned them.

Even though the monsters here weren’t as strong as the monsters in the dungeons, they could still be used as practice. Ye Xiu gave them a limited practice set to see who would advance through it. The three players had previously cleared monsters like this in this desolate area in Line Canyon.

Ye Xiu was looking around at the surroundings. His camera turned and found something: “Oh? Isn’t that the legendary wild BOSS?”

Chapter 224 – False Report

Line Canyon’s wild BOSS, Cliff Ronin Alpine, was the strongest monster in this map. Currently, he was clothed in a black gown and was pacing back and forth with a katana on his shoulder.

“BOSS!” To Steamed Bun Invasion, the word BOSS was very attracting.

“Retreat, retreat.” Ye Xiu said.

The two didn’t understand why he said so, but listened anyways.

“There’s someone following him from behind.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim hid behind a rock.

“What type of person?” Tang Rou asked.

“Someone watching the BOSS. I’m guessing there’s going to be some people coming to kill him soon.” Ye Xiu replied to Tang Rou, while analyzing the map. Steamed Bun Invasion, on the other hand, was rolling around, a front roll and then a back roll and so on.

“Steamed Bun, what are you doing?”

“Investigating.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Investigating what?” Ye Xiu asked.

“That sword’s really long.”

“……Good, in a bit, you guys will need to be careful. This BOSS’s weapon has the range of a Broadsword and the attack speed of a Tachi.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? We’re going to kill it?’ Tang Rou said.

“Of course.”

“But there’s already people there.” Tang Rou said.

“Stealing a wild BOSS! I like it.” Steamed Bun Invasion licked his lips.

“That’s not polite, no?” Tang Rou felt embarrassed to do so.

“They’re from Tyrannical Ambition.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, then what are we waiting for?” Tang Rou immediately changed her mind.

“If we go right now, we won’t be able to finish the BOSS before Tyrannical Ambition’s players arrive.” Ye Xiu said.

“So?”

“Like Steamed Bun said. We’re going to steal it.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha ha ha ha…..”

“Quiet down, Steamed Bun.” Ye Xiu hastily reminded him.

Steamed Bun Invasion fell silent. Tang Rou had her Soft Mist stick her head out to look around: “But there’s only three of us.”

“For an event like a wild BOSS, Tyrannical Ambition definitely won’t want to alert the other guilds, so their movements must be small. They probably won’t have too many players come either.” Ye Xiu said.

“What if there are a lot?”

“Then all we can do is announce it on the world channel to make many more people come.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha ha, Senior, you’re too evil.” Steamed Bun Invasion laughed.

“It’s called strategy.” Ye Xiu corrected him.

The three hid behind a rock like this, peeking out from time to time. The Tyrannical Ambition’s player was carefully following the Cliff Ronin Alpine from a certain distance, afraid that he would enter the Ronin’s aggro range.

The Cliff Ronin deserved his name. As soon as he spawned, he would slowly wander around Line Canyon.

“We don’t know how long this guy’s been watching the BOSS, but he still hasn’t encountered anyone else. We’ve really struck gold this time.” Ye Xiu said.

“He has.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“If he had, then it’d have been stolen long ago.”

“Senior, we’re also people…..” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

Ye Xiu was speechless and just stopped talking.

“Are we just going to hide until they come?” Tang Rou asked.

“Hiding here is fine. But if the BOSS goes too far, it’ll be troublesome! Please get here faster!” Ye Xiu said. It wasn’t even time to kill the BOSS and they were already growing worried.

“It seems like the more he walks, the farther he gets.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Is there a possibility that the BOSS could suddenly turn around?” Tang Rou asked.

“That…..I’ve never really researched that.” Ye Xiu said. In reality, he was looking at a Cliff Ronin Alpine guide right now.

“Why can’t we go to that side? What type of terrain do we need?” Tang Rou asked.

“One that’s close enough. Since we’ll be moving out later, we have to be able to pull the BOSS’s aggro when we move out as well as wipe out their players. If not, then if even one player on their team survives and is still considered in battle, then even if we kill the BOSS, the BOSS will still be theirs. Understand?” Ye Xiu explained.

“Uh…… so you’re saying that as soon as we expose ourselves we have to quickly close in. Compared to killing the BOSS, wiping out the other players is more important?” Tang Rou said.

“Correct. See where the BOSS is going? There’s nowhere for us to hide over there. If the battle goes over there, then it doesn’t matter how perfect our timing is because by the time we rush over there, they’ll have discovered us. Under that type of situation, it’ll be very difficult to steal the BOSS.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what do we do?” Tang Rou was also growing worried now, “It really is going farther and farther away.”

“Worst case scenario, we can try our previous strategy.” Ye Xiu said.

“What strategy?”

“First we wait for Tyrannical Ambition’s players.” Ye Xiu said, “So slow.”

“They’re here! They’re here!” Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly said.

“Get your head back down here, Steamed Bun. How many?”

“Five.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Only five?” Ye Xiu hadn’t expected this. It was a wild BOSS. He thought that there would be at least ten.

“There’s five. I’m not wrong.”

“Got it.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Your strategy?” Tang Rou asked. The BOSS was too far away for their “quickly rush in” strategy.

“Pay attention to the world chat.” Ye Xiu said and then immediately typed out a message.

Lord Grim: Line Canyon: 2441, 3212, wild BOSS discovered. Hurry!!!

Even though most messages in the world chat would instantly vanish, Lord Grim’s name was too eye-catching. This was a name that many players cursed.

“Wild BOSS!” Line Canyon exploded with noise. Many players were already itching to head over.

“How?” Cold Night immediately asked the person watching over the BOSS.

“The BOSS isn’t over there……..” The person hastily replied.

“Wait!” Chen Yehui suddenly shouted, but besides the people surrounding him, no one else could hear his voice amidst the loud racket, but the people around him were enough because these were the people who commanded the troops.

“Was he really that lucky to find the BOSS, or is he trying to lure us away?” Chen Yehui said.

Cold Night loathed Chen Yehui and his Excellent Dynasty, but right now, Cold Night found Chen Yehui’s comradeship incomparably cute. His words were too on point.

Right now, Cold Night didn’t want everyone to begin looking for the BOSS from this false report. It would ruin their chance at secretly killing the BOSS.

Chen Yehui might be able to persuade the players here, but what about others? The ones who were scattered throughout the leveling area or those dungeoning. Even though it was late at night, Lord Grim would still attract the interest of quite a few players, no?

He had deliberately given false info to escape amidst the confusion! Cold Night hated Lord Grim to the core. That guy had this trick up his sleeve and he just had to use it when they found the BOSS. Go to f*cking hell.

Chapter 225 – A Separating Wall

“How’s it going over there?” Cold Night asked the person watching the BOSS.

“Guild leader’s here. The BOSS has also been pulled, but Lord Grim is too dirty. We have to bring the BOSS further in and try to hide it.”

“Sigh!” Cold Night could only sigh. Luckily, the players guarding the Line Canyon entrances had been stopped by Chen Yehui.

“Looking at the time, if Lord Grim’s group went to dungeon, they should be done soon, so the players who are guarding the dungeon entrances cannot leave. Open your eyes widely.” Chen Yehui said to everyone. He then sent a message in secret: “Coordinates 2441, 3212, go check it for me.”

Chen Yehui wasn’t lacking in manpower. He had invested a lot in the tenth server. He had already moved a large number of players trying to suppress Lord Grim and a considerable amount of elites were leveling and dungeoning as well.

Chen Yehui was hiding his strength, so there were many who weren’t participating. However, these players, who were hidden in the darkness, were without a doubt Excellent Dynasty’s most loyal and skilled players.

Right now, he was telling the six other guilds’ players that it was “a plot by Lord Grim”, while holding back a, “it’d be better to believe it, than not to” and sent players to the coordinates to check.

However, in his eyes, only the hundred players at Line Canyon had been held. As for the other six guild’s possibly hidden players, he had no way of stopping them.

In Line Canyon, Tang Rou asked Ye Xiu: “That’s your strategy?”

“Yeah, to scare them.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?”

“Those coordinate aren’t accurate, but right now, a lot of players in Line Canyon are going to head over there and they might pass by here. They’ll definitely bring the BOSS to a place where they won’t be found.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh really……” Tang Rou replied, while listening to the sounds of battle.

“It seems like they’re coming over.” Tang Rou whispered.

“Yeah.”

“We….. won’t we be found if we stay here?” Tang Rou looked at the surrounding terrain.

“They won’t be coming here unless they plan on bumping into players heading to the fake coordinates from the dungeons.” Ye Xiu said.

The three no longer dared to say anymore. The Cliff Ronin quickly whistled by and Tyrannical Ambition’s six players surrounded it. The person in front pulled the Cliff Ronin back, while the people at the rear used Blow Away and Knock Backs to push the BOSS forward.

Here was a small slope. From afar, it looked like a cliff; splitting this area’s Line Canyon in two. As of right now, the three were hiding on the left side of the cliff, while Tyrannical Ambition’s players were heading towards the right side of the cliff. It was the place where they had first seen the BOSS.

“Look, if it keeps heading that way, it’ll be convenient for us and we’ll have a good cover.” Ye Xiu’s plan succeeded. He had completely predicted what the other side would do.

Tyrannical Ambition’s six players consisted of Jiang You’s group and the player who had discovered the BOSS. After Lord Grim announced the fake coordinates on the world chat, Jiang You cursed while hastily guiding the BOSS to a different area. Right now, the players at Line Canyon were increasing. The further they were from the fake coordinates, the better. They had to escape the onrush of players coming there as well. Jiang You looked at the map and chose the only safe spot, which just happened to be the spot Ye Xiu wanted.

They were worthy of being great experts of the Heavenly Domain. After picking the “correct” path, they quickly pulled the BOSS over.

“They’ve gone further. Let’s go.” Ye Xiu called. Tang Rou, and Steamed Bun Invasion followed behind Lord Grim as they drilled out from behind the cliff. The cliff wasn’t too high or steep, so the three climbed up.

When they climbed up onto the wall, Tang Rou looked at the IDs of the players fighting the BOSS.

“It’s that team from before!” Soft Mist peeked out and then quickly pulled back.

“Oh, that team. Their skill level’s pretty high.” Ye Xiu said.

“Senior.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Hm?”

“If we jump down from here, will we die?” Steamed Bun Invasion looked down, studying the cliff’s height. The ground grew more and more distant as they climbed up the slope. They were no longer at the height they were at before.

“We won’t die. We’ll probably be half-dead!” Ye Xiu said.

“How high till we fall to our deaths?”

“I’ll tell you when it happens.” Ye Xiu replied.

“How steep does it have to be for us to stand steadily on top of it?” Tang Rou asked another question. Compared to Steamed Bun Invasion, it was a question of better quality.

“Oh, there’s no standard for that. It depends on the terrain. A slope will affect a character’s move speed. One of the guides I gathered for you earlier talks about this.” Ye Xiu said.

“Really? I haven’t seen any!”

The three continued chatting as they glanced down from time to time.

“If we continue going up, won’t we eventually exit Line Canyon?” Tang Rou asked.

“We’re almost at the end. This is just one small mountain in Line Canyon.” Ye Xiu said.

After climbing up for a bit, Ye Xiu called for the other two to halt: “Okay, let’s go down. Look, Steamed Bun. At this height, if we directly jump down, we’ll die.”

“Oh I see.” Steamed Bun Invasion looked at how high up they were. Then he discovered that there were players on the left side of the cliff as well, but they weren’t looking up.

“Oh, there are players coming from the dungeon. They’re going to those coordinates.” Ye Xiu said.

The three hid on the cliff, between two sides. On the left were players looking for the BOSS, and on the right were players attacking the BOSS.

Quite a few players had already reached the fake coordinates, but after seeing no sign of the BOSS, they began telling everyone in the world chat. However, the players heading over wouldn’t believe them and continued to rush there.

2441, 3212.

The place at those coordinates was already becoming more and more lively. The ones who hadn’t arrived yet were rushing over there. After arriving, they would begin searching around. Those without parties would ask to party up and those who were already in a party were asking for players to join their party…….

On Ye Xiu’s side, they had already found an opportunity to climb down the small slope and a small pit to hide in.

“When are we going to move out?” Tang Rou was tired of waiting.

“It’s still too early.” Ye Xiu said, “With only six players, it’ll take at least half an hour. We’ll just sit here for now. Everyone can go and watch some TV or take a look at a guide, whatever you want.”

“I’m going to get some water.” Tang Rou said.

“Then…… what should I do?” Steamed Bun Invasion was currently in deep thought. The other two had already stopped moving.

Chapter 226 – Wait Until the Arrow is at the End of its Flight

Not long after, Tang Rou carried her cup over and passed by Ye Xiu, who had his two legs crossed and a cigarette in his mouth, a very relaxed look.

When she returned to her seat, she put on her headphones and heard Ye Xiu discussing with Steamed Bun Invasion how awesome it’d be to fight with someone outside of Line Canyon and then push the opponent to his death.

“Yeah, I’ve done it before. It’s probably been ten years since then…….”

“Ten years ago? Senior, you’re not exaggerating are you?” Steamed Bun Invasion interrupted.

“It’s true. It’s definitely been ten years. It’s a story that took place in the first server.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh oh, please tell it…….” Steamed Bun Invasion wouldn’t interrupt him. Tang Rou didn’t interject either and listened to Ye Xiu tell of a battle at Line Canyon that happened ten years ago.

At that time, Glory hadn’t been open for very long, so a large amount of players had just recently entered a new world. Everyone was fighting over BOSSes, fighting over equipment, fighting over materials…… Ye Xiu and his friend had joined in on the mess as well.

“It’s a game, right? So the sword flies here and the sword flies there. The sword flies wherever, it’s a battle.” Ye Xiu said casually.

“We were only two, but our opponents were an entire guild, who were chasing us because we stole the drops from a BOSS. Even though we were good enough to wipe them out, there was no way our mana would last. So at that time, we fought while running, but those guys refused to give up and we eventually ran to here. At this point, a bright idea suddenly popped up in our heads and we began to use all sorts of ways to push those guys off the cliff. A Falling Flower Palm would blow away three, who would instantly die from the fall. It was so cheap. However, some classes wouldn’t die from the fall. For example, Gunners use Aerial Fire to avoid falling to their deaths, but it didn’t matter because even if they didn’t die, they wouldn’t be able to jump back up. Their only choice was to circle around…….” Ye Xiu explained.

“Then were you two able to push all of them off?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked excitedly, “How many did you push off?”

“I hadn’t counted, but we were able to push off nearly everyone in the guild! The remaining ones saw that they weren’t able to run, so they jumped off by themselves.”

“No way……” Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t believe him.

‘Yeah….. actually, since the game hadn’t been open for long, there weren’t that many players in a guild.” Ye Xiu said.

“How many?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“20?” Ye Xiu recalled.

“Tch…..” Steamed Bun Invasion disdained. The story had sounded so incredible, but it had just been a small battle against 20 players.

“Ha ha.” Ye Xiu could only laugh. He couldn’t forget their main mission, so he peeked out. Tyrannical Ambition’s players were really careful. They were worried they would be discovered, so they continued to bring the BOSS farther into the depths of the dead-end.

“We just have to close in slowly.” Ye Xiu said.

Under Ye Xiu’s lead, they would switch hiding places from time to time, never exposing themselves. On the world chat, quite a few players were now questioning what Lord Grim had said. Ye Xiu didn’t care. However, the players guarding Line Canyon’s entrances all thought that Lord Grim would take the chance to escape. They had been waiting for about an hour, but there was still no sign of him.

“Lord Grim’s evil schemes have been seen through. He doesn’t dare come.” Everyone confidently concluded as if they had won a battle.

On Lord Grim’s side, it was finally time.

“Okay, it’s about time now.” Ye Xiu said to the team. The three were hiding behind a small dirt mound. Lord Grim was peeking his head out more and more.

The battle was already extremely intense. The Cliff Ronin Alpine was now at Red Blood and released a mighty aura. Tyrannical Ambition responded in the same way. Seeing their character’s’ movements, Ye Xiu was able to see that Crowd Lover was the leader.

“Their teamwork is very good. They really do have enough strength to take down the BOSS.” Ye Xiu commented.

“When are we going to go?” Tang Rou asked again and again.

“Don’t be impatient. We’ll wait until the arrow is at the end of its flight, then we’ll take them down in one move. Remember, first kill the players, then the BOSS. We’ll set the targets now. I’ll give them numbers. That Elementalist Crowd Lover is #1, Blade Master #2, Sharpshooter #3, Striker #4, Cleric #5, Berserker #6, don’t forget.” Ye Xiu messaged.

“Got it!”

“Okay, wait for my orders.” Ye Xiu continued to spectate the battle.

Raging Flames!

Outside of the mound, Jiang You’s Crowd Lover waved his hands and cast a spell. A column of fire burst from the ground enveloped the Cliff Ronin Alpine, but the Cliff Ronin was currently in an Enraged state, so Raging Flames wouldn’t launch him into the air.

The Cliff Ronin slashed in a large 270-degree arc, but it was just a Sword Draw and nothing more. In his hands, such a normal skill became something incredible.

Jiang You and the others had expected it. Three of the players were behind the BOSS, inside the 90 degrees where the circular arc wouldn’t reach. Crowd Lover and the Sharpshooter were both outside of the range. Up front, the Blade Master stood directly in front and used a precise Guard to block the Sword Draw.

Guard only blocked a portion of the damage. Even when Guarded against, the BOSS’s skill still did a large chunk of damage. However, the Cleric was already ready and healed him. The Blade Master hit back with his own Sword Draw, slashing out a streak of blood across the Cliff Ronin’s body. The Cliff Ronin roared angrily. He stabbed his sword into the ground: the Berserker skill “Earth Shattering Slash” activated.

This move caused dozens of shattered rocks in the surroundings shoot up. A player’s Earth Shattering Slash wouldn’t have such an effect. It was clearly a buffed skill due to the BOSS’s Enraged state.

“Look at this skill.” Ye Xiu immediately called for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion’s attention.

“This skill is extremely difficult to interrupt. The scattered rocks are also random, so they’re difficult to defend against. But…… right before the rocks shoot up, the ground will stick up for a short instant. If you pay careful attention to it, you’ll be able to see it. If you react fast enough, you can even dodge them. Look, that Striker over there dodged them well.”

The skill took a heavy toll on Tyrannical Ambition’s team. They also knew how to dodge them, but they weren’t able to guarantee that they could perform such difficult actions precisely when needed. Among the six players, four were in range and three were hit by the rocks. Only that Striker had been able to avoid the rocks.

Tyrannical Ambition’s players didn’t panic though. The two long-range classes continued to attack, while the Cleric hurriedly healed the Blade Master. The Striker immediately used a “Dashing Jab” to close in and followed up with a Grappler’s Back Throw to interrupt the Cliff Ronin’s attack to give everyone some time to recover. From this bout, it could be seen that the Berserker, the player who had discovered the BOSS, wasn’t at the same level as the other five players. His playing wasn’t with the team.

The Blade Master leapt up into the air to avoid the BOSS’s shockwave from getting up and then followed with a Falling Light Blade. The Cliff Ronin Alpine was hit, but knock-back wouldn’t affect an Enraged BOSS. The Cliff Ronin countered with a slash, which the Blade Master Guarded and returned with a Sword Draw again.

Jiang You grew excited. They had been fighting for so long and the BOSS was finally about to be taken down. A Wild BOSS. The strongest of the BOSSes. The drops were also of the greatest value. Even these experts from the Heavenly Domain were excited.

“Almost there! Again!” Jiang You shouted. The others could also see that victory was almost theirs. Their morale was at a peak and once again went for another round of attacks. When the Cliff Ronin Alpine countered, the Blade Master was ready to Guard again.

But just at that moment, three shadows suddenly jumped out from behind a small dirt mound.

“Soft Mist #2, Steamed Bun #5!!”

Chapter 227 – The Greatest DPS

“LORD GRIM!!”

This shout held feelings of anger and uneasiness……

Lord Grim actually appeared now of all times…….

Seeing their IDs, Jiang You instantly understood what they were trying to do, though he didn’t know the details.

#2, #5? What is he talking about?

Jiang You set his eyes on Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion and took full precautions, but Lord Grim was the first to act. His Thousand Chance Umbrella flipped to show the tip, exposing a black muzzle. “Bang bang bang.”t Three Anti-Tank Missiles shot out, but these three missiles didn’t hit anyone and instead exploded on Cliff Ronin Alpine, immediately making him a part of the battle.

Right after the explosion, Steamed Bun Invasion threw a Brick, which flew like an immortal from the skies, towards the Cleric’s head.

The Dizzy didn’t take effect, but he was able to interrupt the Cleric’s casting. This was an action Ye Xiu had predicted the Cleric would do, which was why he told Steamed Bun Invasion to attack him.

The Cleric had seen the three unwanted guests appear, but his hands still instinctively tried to Heal the Guarding Blade Master. In the strategy they had been using for the past hour, whenever the Blade Master Guarded, he would immediately recover his health. From how the process played out, it appeared as if Steamed Bun Invasion had thrown the Brick first and then the Cleric tried to Heal in order to interrupt it.

Tang Rou’s Battle Mage didn’t have any long-range skills or any Chasers on her. Her target was Blade Master #2, who was some distance away from her, but Tang Rou wasn’t inflexible. She brushed past the Cliff Ronin and used a Falling Flower Palm on the BOSS.

In its Red Blood state, the Cliff Ronin was extremely resistant. The Falling Flower Palm’s Blow Away effect was also reduced and only made the Cliff Ronin stagger a bit. Tang Rou’s goal of having the BOSS fly into her target hadn’t been achieved yet, but at least she was able to produce a Fire Chaser. Tang Rou didn’t hesitate and immediately fired her Chaser. The Fire Chaser exploded on the Cliff Ronin and Soft Mist’s arms began to glow red. The Fire Chaser had buffed her Strength.

Tang Rou hadn’t forgotten about her target and continued to rush towards the Blade Master.

Seeing Soft Mist pounce over, the Blade Master appeared extremely cold. With the blade in the sheath, he quickly drew his sword. This attack headed towards both targets in order to block Soft Mist’s charge as well as to add damage to the BOSS.

“Swoosh!” The Blade Master suddenly saw a giant umbrella shield open up, blocking the sword light.

The player with the shield was knocked back, but at this moment, the umbrella retracted and a sword light flashed, sending a Sword Draw back at him.

This slash was the same as the Blade Master’s; one attack with two targets. The Sword Draw headed towards the Blade Master as well as the Striker, who was not far from the Blade Master.

With the Blade Master and Striker’s positions, the Sword Draw shouldn’t have been long enough to reach both, but Ye Xiu had utilized the knockback effect to use Sword Draw while moving backwards, causing the angle to change, allowing the sword aura to reach the Striker.

Tyrannical Ambition’s experts hadn’t anticipated this type of precise movement. The Striker was hit by the sword aura and he slid back.

The Blade Master immediately raised his Guard and blocked the attack. Just as he felt pleased, a scarlet flash swept past his eyes and his character flew into the sky. Soft Mist had used this opportunity to execute a Sky Strike.

Lord Grim followed up and jumped back. His Thousand Chance Umbrella swung down turning into the Gun form. Gatling Gun was employed and the bullets flew like rain. The brief Stun from each hit made it so the opponent wasn’t able to close in.

While the bullets rained, Steamed Bun Invasion dashed towards his target #5. This Cleric had once been bullied by Steamed Bun Invasion already. Seeing him run over, he immediately turned around and ran.

Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t give up. No one else mattered, only the Cleric. This was the task Ye Xiu had assigned him.

Tang Rou chased after the mid-air Blade Master and began a barrage of attacks. The Blade Master had no way of escaping as his health dropped rapidly. The Cleric was supposed to heal him, but all he saw was the Cleric running from Steamed Bun Invasion like a dog.

The Blade Master didn’t dare to be careless and immediately drank a potion. In this instant, his health shot up. This was an extremely precious potion that recovered his health in an instant. This type of potion was Purple-lettered. Jiang You and his party had brought the best quality potions with them to hunt this wild BOSS.

Normal potions healed over 10 seconds with a 1 minute cooldown. As for the instant heal potion, the cooldown increased to 2.5 minutes, but both potions shared the same amount healed. After consuming the instant health potion, he wouldn’t be able to drink another potion for 2.5 minutes.

Relying on the potion, the Blade Master survived. After rolling onto the ground, he raised his hands and used an “Upward Slash”.

“Don’t dodge it!” Ye Xiu shouted as the Blade Master used “Upward Slash”. Tang Rou had planned on jumping back to dodge it, but was startled by Ye Xiu’s shout. By the time she recovered, there wasn’t enough time to dodge. The Blade Master’s sword hit and Soft Mist was launched into the air.

“Were you talking to me?” Tang Rou was still confused. Being caught in mid-air wasn’t a good situation.

The Blade Master chased after her to follow up, but a sudden sword aura brushed past him. The Blade Master wasn’t able to Guard or dodge in time and was hit by the sword aura, causing him to fly back. As for Soft Mist, because she had been launched into the air, she was able to dodge the sword aura.

A shadow brushed past Soft Mist in mid-air. An extremely quick sword penetrated through and stabbed the Blade Master. That shadow never stopped moving and continued to slaughter his way through. The, still-alive, Blade Master was nailed against the mountain.

Berserker skill: Colliding Stab.

With an abnormally large range, the Cliff Ronin Alpine had used this skill. After eating two consecutive BOSS skills, the Blade Master’s health instantly dropped, his death was near.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim mercilessly added damage. Anti-Tank Missiles fired towards the nailed Blade Master while grinning towards Tang Rou: “I was talking to you! There’s no need to work so hard. The person with the greatest DPS is over there!”

Three Anti-Tank Missiles exploded, cleaning out the Blade Master’s little remaining health and his corpse smoothly slid down the cliff wall.

Soft Mist dropped down from the sky and stood up with a Quick Recover, startled by the already-dead Blade Master.

The Cleric was still running from Steamed Bun Invasion.

Jiang You and the others had been suppressed by Lord Grim and had only just gotten up, but in that short instant, their Blade Master unexpectedly died.

The Blade Master’s ghost stayed with his cheeks streaming with tears. Lord Grim had actually borrowed the BOSS to kill him. How much more shameless can you be?

The answer was already known.

After the Blade Master was nailed to the wall, the Cliff Ronin turned around and headed towards the Tyrannical Ambition’s players……

Chapter 228 – Forming a Party with the BOSS

Seeing the Cliff Ronin Alpine turn around and charge towards them, Jiang You’s party immediately froze. What stealing the BOSS? This was clearly using the BOSS as a helper.

Lord Grim’s group was absolutely last on the BOSS’s aggro list. As long as they didn’t run into the Cliff Ronin’s blade and dodge some of the BOSS’s AoE attacks, they wouldn’t be in too much danger. On the other hand, Jiang You’s group was Cliff Ronin’s main targets.

The Red Blood status Cliff Ronin was extremely terrifying. Under normal circumstances, he would be able to clean up three players with ease. However, Lord Grim’s strength wasn’t normal. Jiang You didn’t doubt that they were going to first clean them up and then kill the low-health BOSS.

KS? Run around? Retreat?

Numerous thoughts circled through Jiang You’s head. He didn’t have time to think too carefully. The Ronin’s sword aura was flying towards them.

The Cliff Ronin Alpine was swinging his sword with both hands from the ground up. This was the Spellblade skill Earthquake Sword. In the BOSS’s hands, the shockwave and attack was increased significantly. A crack in the ground would climb up from whichever direction the sword pointed to and as if an earthquake were happening, chunks of earth flew towards Crowd Lover.

After the Blade Master died, Crowd Lover was next on the Cliff Ronin’s target list. He was only wearing Cloth Armor. It was highly possible that he could die from even a single hit.

Jiang You hastily acted. Crowd Lover ran and rolled. Just as he was about to exit the sword aura’s range, a silhouette suddenly fell in front of him. Blocked, the two were hit by the earthen storm. Jiang You didn’t know if that player was dead or alive. All he knew was that his health almost dropped to zero.

He didn’t yet have time to drink his potion when Lord Grim appeared in front of him. Not waiting for him to get up, Lord Grim fired several times and sent Crowd Lover back to the city.

“F*CK!!” Jiang You slammed the table. His foot kicked a nearby chair.

As the manager of the guild for the club, Jiang You had his own specialized studio for him. Beside him were several other guild members. In the quiet of the night, these Tyrannical Ambition workers looked in alarm at their boss.

Jiang You glared at the screen. He had tried to drink a potion, but Lord Grim was quicker and he was killed off. His attempt to drink a potion became “click accept to revive” and he was already back in the city.

He stood there angrily for two seconds and then sprinted over to another person in the room.

During his extreme fit of rage, only one person didn’t look up from his computer to see what was going on. This was Jiang You’s teammate —- the Striker, who had been fighting beside him in Line Canyon. As for the other teammates, they weren’t in the same city.

Sweat could be seen on the Striker’s forehead. His heart was racing even faster. At this moment, he was under attack from Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and Cliff Ronin Alpine, a very difficult situation.

Jiang You glanced at the party list on the side of the screen. Of the originally six members, there were only three left. The player, who had crashed into his Crowd Lover, was that Berserker who had found the BOSS. From the looks of it, his name was already faded, which meant that he had died.

Left roll, right step, leap up, sprint to flee……

The Striker’s two hands furiously tapped the keyboard and mouse. The concentrated raps showed his current complex playing.

But no matter how he tried to dodge, his health continued to slowly be chipped away. He hadn’t been able to escape.

Lord Grim’s figure suddenly appeared in front of him. He had used a Shadow Clone Technique to block his path and then used a Falling Flower Palm. The Striker had no choice but to leap back, when he heard the sound of a sword being unsheathed. The Cliff Ronin’s fiery sword aura finally found its mark on the Striker’s body.

Cursing, the Striker watched as his corpse fell to the ground. He also slammed the table and jumped up from his chair, swearing continuously: “F*ck! Coordinating with the BOSS? What’s wrong with him???”

Everyone else in the room buried their heads. They were too scared to look or even ask. They knew what these two Heavenly Domain experts had come to the tenth server for, but……. it looked like the new server proved to be an extremely difficult task as even the top experts of their guild were crumbling.

They were Tyrannical Ambition. The fierce finger-pointing, and scolding style of Tyranny’s team captain Han Wenqing was often imitated by managers in the guild, except they didn’t learn it correctly. Han Wenqing only scolded them when the other side made a mistake, but these people only seemed to have learned the angry part. If they were in a bad mood or unhappy, they would find some reason to vent their anger. The people in the room didn’t want to be the ones to be vented out on.

Jiang You and the Striker looked at each other. They couldn’t scold each other, no? In the end, their gazes fell onto the screen. At this moment, the Striker’s ghost camera watched as Lord Grim’s group and the Cliff Ronin Alpine pounced towards the remaining two survivors.

“Shameless! How could anyone be so shameless!”

“Right, too shameless!”

Jiang You and the Striker pointed at the screen and furiously cursed, but the battle quickly reached outside of the ghost’s view and they were no longer able to see anything.

The Cliff Ronin dealt matchless damage like this along with the help of Lord Grim’s matchless shamelessness. At this point, what was the point in watching any longer? Even if they asked the entire guild to come over, it’d be too late!

Thinking of this, Jiang You immediately dashed back to his computer. The chat box on his screen flashed and flashed. He clicked on it and saw that it was Cold Night. Clearly, he had already found out a little bit about the situation from the dead Blade Master and was now asking Jiang You for what to do next.

“The BOSS will probably be stolen away by Lord Grim. Hurry up and gather people to stop that bastard. There’s only three of them and the BOSS doesn’t have much health left, but it’ll still take them some time.” Jiang You hastily replied.

“Got it.” Cold Night didn’t say too much. He immediately told everyone that they had found Lord Grim’s position. The troops promptly moved out.

At this moment, Jiang You received another message. It was from the Sharpshooter in his team. Clearly, no miracle had occurred.

“F*CK! These b*stards are too evil!!”

“So shameless!” The Cleric had also died.

“They were definitely watching us from the very beginning!”

“That b*tch probably announced those fake coordinates on purpose!”

The teammates continued to talk, cursing Lord Grim’s name numerous times.

“How much health did the BOSS have in the end?” Jiang You asked the other two.

“I wasn’t paying attention. The only thing I was paying attention to was how much health I had left…..” The two replied bitterly.

Chapter 229 – In the Blink of an Eye

Jiang You’s team was once again obliterated. They had no way of knowing what the situation was ahead of them and could only wait for Cold Night’s report.

Cold Night had already sent everyone Lord Grim’s whereabouts. He also leaked the truth: Lord Grim and the BOSS were together.

Hearing this, everyone went into an uproar. Excellent Dynasty’s guild leader Chen Yehui was met with at least 50 shouts filled with anger. Chen Yehui was also very gloomy. He had sent players to check who had verified that there wasn’t any BOSS, which meant that he had been played as a fool by Lord Grim just like everyone else was.

The hundreds of player sitting at Line Canyon for hours and hours began storming their way over. After Chen Yehui heard Cold Night’s report of Lord Grim’s whereabouts, he checked the map.

That f*cker! Ye Qiu was too shameless! The coordinates he had given and the actual coordinates were several hundred coordinates off. Why? Did he intentionally lure everyone away in order to fight the BOSS himself? Chen Yehui pondered as their troops hurried over.

The guilds all kept their distance away from each other. The BOSS “Lord Grim” didn’t need to be stolen, but the wild BOSS Cliff Ronin was different. Glory, equipment, materials, no one wanted to share these things with other guilds. Thinking about the rain of blood that poured with every wild BOSS, the guilds prepared themselves.

Cold Night was relatively calm. He understood the situation and reckoned that they probably wouldn’t be able to reach the Cliff Ronin Alpine in time. Lord Grim was too smart. He might have already calculated the time needed for his team to kill the BOSS and the time needed for Cold Night and the others to arrive.

Thinking of this, Cold Night looked for the other guilds in order to ask for the players guarding the leveling area and dungeons to scatter and head towards that area. They didn’t need to block Lord Grim, they just needed to find his whereabouts.

After saying this, everyone else was suspicious: “Aren’t your people supposed to be over there?”

Cold Night calmly replied: “We had just found them and they’re all dead now, which was why I warned everyone not to let Lord Grim escape. Lord Grim probably expected this to happen so he already knows where we are.”

“Unless he’s willing to abandon the BOSS, there’s no way he’d be able to run too quickly with the BOSS attacking him.” One player said.

“We should still take precautions. Let’s take a look at the map.” Another said.

As a result, the leaders studied the map as they ran. They figured out how to divide everyone and what routes to go along.

On Ye Xiu’s side, after killing off Tyrannical Ambition’s players, they turned towards the BOSS as their target. The Cliff Ronin Alpine hissed and roared. He unleashed an Earth Shattering Slash, spraying stones and gravel everywhere.

Ye Xiu was the quickest to dodge the attack. Seeing the Cliff Ronin begin his attack animation, he immediately used a Shadow Clone Technique. His fake body was left behind, while his real body moved outside of the attack’s range.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t have such a method of escaping. After hearing Ye Xiu’s “Careful!”, they stared forward at their screens.

“It’s here!” Tang Rou saw a slight movement on her screen, but her reaction was a bit too slow and a rock crashed into her. The sudden drop in health made Tang Rou feel pained for her Soft Mist.

On Steamed Bun Invasion’s side, his extreme luck exploded. Not a single rock headed towards where he was standing.

“Ha ha ha. I bet you didn’t know that luck is a type of skill too.” Steamed Bun Invasion said gleefully to Tang Rou.

“I have to say that what you just said is very logical, Steamed Bun.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim rushed forward and was also the BOSS’s target.

The Cliff Ronin only had so many skills. Before their ambush, Ye Xiu had explained this to the others. When they saw the BOSS wave his sword, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion went behind the Cliff Ronin to his dead angle.

After the two went behind the BOSS, Ye Xiu continued to rush forward. At this moment, Lord Grim leaped up at the perfect time and looked like he stepped on the Ronin’s katana.

“Hey, are you two watching a play?” Ye Xiu saw that Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion were both looking up in awe at him and weren’t using the time to attack.

The two heard and went back to reality.

Soft Mist used a Sky Strike and Steamed Bun Invasion attacked with a Brick.

Under the Enraged state, the Cliff Ronin was as steady as a rock. The Sky Strike wouldn’t launch him into the air and the Brick wouldn’t cause him to go dizzy. Lord Grim leapt over the BOSS and used the Striker “Eagle Stamp”,stepping on the BOSS’s head three times.

Ye Xiu had to hurry up and attack. At this moment, the difference in aggro levels between the three of them wasn’t large. If Lord Grim did a bit less damage, it was very likely that the two would pull the aggro away.

The Cliff Ronin obviously wouldn’t just stand there and let them attack him. He immediately swung his sword and this time, used the Berserker skill, Backwards Slash.

This attack had a large range; from in front of him to the top of his head to behind him. Not only was he attacking Lord Grim, but he was also attacking Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion who were behind him.

After seeing the katana swish towards him, Lord Grim suddenly pointed with his sword and used a “Falling Light Blade” in order to fall faster. The sword crashed down, swiping past the BOSS, who didn’t budge in the slightest. However, this attack allowed Lord Grim to dodge the attack. Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion had already jumped away before the slash hit.

Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella switched to the Tonfa form and used the Grappler Fling.

The Cliff Ronin Alpine couldn’t block this type of grab and was flung onto the ground.

Even though it was a priority grab, the Cliff Ronin Alpine still had a strong body and was only flung half the usual distance and height. It was called a fling, but in reality, it looked more like he tripped.

“Receive!” Ye Xiu shouted.

Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion concentrated and rushed forward together. Steamed Bun Invasion used a Strangle and accurately hit the Cliff Ronin’s throat. The effect was extremely brief, but Ye Xiu and Tang Rou was able to use this opportunity. The two of them looked as if they were doing the same movement. Their right hands held their lances behind them and their left hands flew out.

“Bang!”

The two noises together sounded like one. Just before the Cliff Ronin landed on the ground, they both used a Falling Flower Palm to forcefully blow him away. Soft Mist quickly followed with a Fire Chaser. Lord Grim’s battle lance retracted and the tip of his Thousand Chance Umbrella turned into a black muzzle. Anti-Tank Missiles followed closely after the Fire Chaser and exploded on the BOSS. As for Steamed Bun Invasion, he used a Sand Toss after letting go of Strangle.

The Cliff Ronin fell to the ground. They leapt back to avoid the shockwaves as he got up. Lord Grim drew his sword and a purple-like mist seeped out from his sword, quickly forming a Sword Soul.

Inside the Sword Boundary, their Strength was increased. After the Cliff Ronin rose, his eyes flashed and charged at Lord Grim with his sword raised.

This “Colliding Stab” was both fierce and quick. In the blink of an eye, he had reached Lord Grim.

In an instant, the Cliff Ronin seemed to have passed through Lord Grim.

The Cliff Ronin still had his katana facing forward, but his sword hadn’t hit anything. A streak of blood flew out from behind his neck. Steamed Bun Invasion and Tang Rou tried to think back on what happened in that instant, but weren’t able to remember any details. All they knew was that in that instant, Lord Grim had sidestepped and the Cliff Ronin had brushed past him. The blood that flew out made Steamed Bun Invasion think of a certain skill.

“Cut Throat?” Steamed Bun Invasion yelled absent-mindedly.

This skill could only be used behind the target’s back. Previously, when the Cliff Ronin and Lord Grim clashed, it was so brief that they hadn’t understood what exactly had happened. In that short instant, Ye Xiu was able to turn around and use a Cut Throat. Even though they had been with him every day, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion couldn’t help but be shocked.

“Dumbstruck again?” Lord Grim had already drawn his sword and used a Collapsing Mountain to follow up.

The Cliff Ronin’s “Colliding Stab” hadn’t hit, so he stopped, while still inside the Sword Boundary. The Cliff Ronin was only able to turn around halfway when he was hit by the Collapsing Mountain. Steamed Bun Invasion came in from the left and smacked him with a Brick, while Tang Rou came in from the right and stabbed twice with a “Double Stab”.

“AH!!!”

The Cliff Ronin let out one final cry, before the light in his eyes faded.

Chapter 230 – A Bit Early Today

System Announcement: Players Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and Steamed Bun Invasion have defeated Cliff Ronin Alpine.

Even though it wasn’t a first kill, a wild BOSS kill was still very big news. Among the clamors of surprise in the world chat, some players congratulated them.

Far away in Congee City, Jiang You saw the system announcement and these messages on the world chat. He really had the urge to cough up blood…..

Of course, the players who had been searching for the BOSS the past hour were very unhappy with Lord Grim. At that moment, Lord Grim’s reputation became quite unpleasant. After this system announcement, the number of players who questioned this also became much smaller.

Jiang You knew the facts, but he couldn’t tell them. The BOSS had been forcefully snatched away and their hour of hard work had been stolen.

“We have to kill Lord Grim!” Jiang You slammed his keyboard and messaged Cold Night.

Cold Night hadn’t personally experienced being killed and even though he was disappointed, his feelings were far from Jiang You’s level of resentment.

With the news of the BOSS, there was no longer any chance for them to stealing the BOSS, so the seven guilds quickly gathered together.

“What about Cleansing Mist and that One Inch Ash?”

“Dead?”

“Offline……”

“……”

But as long as Lord Grim was still there, they wouldn’t give up. The guilds were now maneuvering all of their troops towards that location. They had to close in on Lord Grim’s whereabouts.

They were closing in from every direction and had blockaded every single route. This time, unless Lord Grim could fly out of Line Canyon, then……

“F*CK!” Cold Night suddenly cursed.

“What?” Everyone else immediately asked.

“Lord Grim’s logged out.” Cold Night was gloomy. He had opened his friends list and saw that Lord Grim’s name had turned gray. He quickly used a search and sure enough, Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion had all logged out as well.

“F*CK!!”

The players from the seven guilds had worked bitterly the entire night and their result? All they did was run around the world looking for Lord Grim’s tracks.

And Lord Grim’s group?

They had wiped out a 32-player team.

They had run a dungeon twice.

They had killed elite teams.

They had killed a wild BOSS.

Everyone was scratching the walls and Tyrannical Ambition’s players were beating their heads against the wall, while coughing up blood. The 32-player team wipe out had their players. Two of their elite teams had died. And there was even information that others didn’t know: The Cliff Ronin Alpine had been stolen from them and their elite team had even died again. It could be said that Tyrannical Ambition’s elite teams had suffered a loss three times.

But now, the other side wasn’t even online. What were they supposed to say?

Someone suggested that they guard the place where Lord Grim had logged off 24/7, but who knew where Lord Grim’s group had logged off at?

They had blocked off all the roads and surrounded Lord Grim’s previous whereabout, but they still didn’t know when exactly they had gone offline. Lord Grim could have gone somewhere else to log off when the guilds were still getting in position to surround him. And the area they were surrounding was huge. They didn’t have enough manpower to stand guard 24/7.

The crowd of players from the seven big guilds stood there stupidly like rocks……

Back at Happy Internet Cafe.

Tang Rou left her computer and saw Ye Xiu smoking at the front desk. He looked like he was in quite a good mood.

Of course, Ye Xiu would be in a good mood. After killing the Cliff Ronin, an Amber Crystal had dropped, which was something he needed. Every year, only a few were found and for them, after only one try, it had actually dropped.

Just this was enough to make Ye Xiu satisfied. Apart from this, Cliff Ronin Alpine had also dropped a Purple weapon, two Blue equipments, and two Breath of the Cliffs.

The Purple weapon was a Level 30 Twin-Tailed Swords, which was often used by Assassins. No one in Ye Xiu’s group could use it, so the only thing they could do was sell it for gold.

As for the two Breath of the Cliffs, these were used as uncommon materials for creating accessories. Their drop rate was much higher than Amber Crystals, but they only dropped from wild BOSSes, so there was only a limited amount of them too.

“Are the materials that dropped useful?” Tang Rou asked.

“Yeah, the Amber Crystal is extremely useful! We can hold on to the Breaths of the Cliff for now. If we don’t use them, we can always sell them for money or equipment.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.”

“We got off pretty early today! It isn’t even six yet, so you can go to sleep early.” Ye Xiu got up and stretched.

“Then I’ll…… you still have to stay till seven.” Tang Rou patted the front desk.

“Yeah….. I almost forgot.” Ye Xiu sat back down.

“I’ll be off then.”

“Okay.”

Tang Rou said goodbye and then went to the second floor. When she got to the door, she saw a light coming from the room.

“Guo Guo, you got up so early today.” Tang Rou pushed open the door to enter, but when she looked inside, she saw the TV on. A TV channel was playing making the room turn dark and light on and off. When she looked again, she saw that Chen Guo was sleeping on the sofa again.

Tang Rou chuckled bitterly and patted Chen Guo: “Guo Guo, get up and go to your bed to sleep!”

“Huh? Is it morning already?” Chen Guo heard Tang Rou’s voice. She looked around and aside from the TV, everything else was dark. Chen Guo looked at the time drowsily: “Why’s it not even six yet?”

“Uh……” She had stopped playing abnormally early today. It would take a lot of time to explain, so Tang Rou didn’t know what to say right now.

“You got off early today? Did you eat?’ Chen Guo asked.

“Not yet.”

“Go eat some food and then go to sleep. I’ll go see what’s in the fridge.” Chen Guo got up from the sofa.

“No need. You should hurry up and go back to your room to sleep!” Tang Rou said.

“I’m hungry…..” Chen Guo said and went to the fridge anyways.

She took out some food: milk, bread, and jam. Tang Rou also went to help.

After making two jam sandwiches, they split it. Chen Guo ate, while asking: “How was your day?”

“Oh, it was fun!” Tang Rou ate, while explaining to Chen Guo.

Chen Guo listened quietly, laughing and gasping in surprise.

“Hurry up and level. I’ll be waiting for you guys in the Heavenly Domain. I’ll be going off to bed now.” Chen Guo said after eating and listening and then went to bed.

Tang Rou was startled. She knew that Chen Guo had always wanted to play with her. Now that she was playing, it seemed like Chen Guo was growing ever more distant from her. In the past, Chen Guo had frequently pulled her along to watch the pro matches and talked about stories in Glory, but she had also spent more time watching TV or doing something else with her every night.

In recent days, however, the time they were spending together was becoming less and less. And how many nights was Chen Guo freezing on the sofa alone?

Whenever Chen Guo was obsessed with the game, she never forgot to take care of me. But what about myself……

Chapter 231 – Looking for Help

Tang Rou went back to rest. Ye Xiu, on the other hand, didn’t have much to do. It was almost six and pretty much no one needed assistance. Half of them had their heads lying on the table.

Ye Xiu got up and wandered around for a bit. He then returned to the front desk to look at some videos and guides for Line Canyon.

In the blink of an eye, it was time to change shifts. He handed over his seat, ate breakfast, and then went to rest like usual.

But for the seven big guilds in the tenth server, that hour was unbearable. After a long dispute, in the end, they all agreed on a plan: guard the Line Canyon entrances.

Correct, they were going to stick with guarding the Line Canyon entrances. But this time, they weren’t going to have a hundred players stand there like before, just a few. The seven big guilds arranged the shifts. They would switch every hour. As long as they reported when Lord Grim’s group came out, then it’d be good enough.

This was already their only plan. Besides this, they felt that they couldn’t go on any longer. It was a small measure. Regardless of how it went, it made them feel a little bit better.

When the sun rose, they dispersed and logged off to rest. But for some people, even though they hadn’t slept tonight, they weren’t able to sleep during day. For example, Jiang You.

How could he fall asleep!

The night had passed terribly. Although the outside was icy and cold, Jiang You could only feel a burning anger in his heart.

Lord Grim!

Jiang You hated him to the core. Though as an expert, he wasn’t short-sighted. Even though Lord Grim had used a few dirty tricks and even though he was an unspecialized with that weird weapon……. if they switched positions and he had that character and that weapon, would he have been able to suppress everyone in such a dominating way? The answer was no.

How troublesome!

Jiang You turned and turned in his bed. He drowsily fell asleep. In his dreams, he saw the BOSS being stolen away in front of his eyes. He roared and went to find the KSer to vent his anger at. But then, one by one, the troops he brought with him disappeared from his sight. Then, a shadow suddenly flew forward. He wasn’t able to see clearly and felt a shiver down his spine. On the top of the shadow was the ID: Lord Grim.

“F*CK!!” Jiang You howled and woke up from his nightmare. The sun had already risen. The sunlight that shone through the window stung his eyes. At this moment, he was unexpectedly feeling lucky: Phew. It was just a dream. The stolen BOSS was all just a dream.

He checked the time. It was almost 12 o’clock. He had only slept four hours. A very bad night of sleep.

Yesterday night’s events and his dream continued to turn in his mind. Jiang You finally couldn’t take it anymore. He got up and put on his clothes. After quickly cleaning up, he rushed out of his room.

Club Tyranny, dining hall.

As an official employee of the Club, the game was his job and this was one of his benefits as an employee. However, he rarely used it for lunch.

Right now, quite a few of the Club members were using this time to eat. Everyone obviously recognized Jiang You and knew his habits. Jiang You appearing now made everyone surprised. Even the team captain Han Wenqing greeted him with a face full of surprise.

Jiang You greeted everyone. He ran to randomly pick a few dishes and sat opposite to someone in the dining hall.

The other person had two dishes, one meat, one vegetable, along with a small bowl of soup. His left hand held a bowl of rice, while his right hand held the chopsticks that were currently moving towards his mouth. Whenever his chopsticks moved down, the amount he picked up was practically the same every time.

This was Tyranny’s vice-captain Zhang Xinjie, a strict and serious person. From his clothing to his eating to his gameplay, they all reflected this.

Seeing Jiang You sit opposite to him, Zhang Xinjie looked at him and nodded his head.

“Vice-captain, I have something I want to talk to you about.” Jiang You said. He was going to ask Zhang Xinjie for advice on what to do about Lord Grim. He had planned on doing it awhile ago, but had held it off. After tossing and turning during the night, Jiang You finally decided that he couldn’t bear it any longer and needed someone to help him.

“Let’s talk after lunch.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Alright.” Jiang You replied and began eating faster.

Many people liked to pull along a friend to talk with while they ate, but everyone in Tyranny knew that their vice-captain never talked to anyone while eating, which was why no one was accompanying him right now. Jiang You usually liked to chat with others, but this time, he actually chose to sit with Zhang Xinjie, making everyone feel a little perplexed.

But no one really took it to heart. They continued on doing their own thing and after eating, they left the dining hall to rest, including the team captain Han Wenqing.

Jiang You had taken a glance at Han Wenqing a few times and seeing how the team captain wasn’t planning on doing anything, he relaxed. The in-game guild and the pro-team were interconnected. When one wins, both wins. When one suffers, both suffer. Yesterday night, their guild had lost a lot of face. If Han Wenqing heard about it, Jiang You felt that he’d definitely be yelled at.

Most of the people had already left the dining hall, but Zhang Xinjie continued to eat at his own pace. His pace was very regular. Jiang You was able to see the order which he ate. At that pace, the rice and dishes would be finished at the same time.

Jiang You, on the other hand, finished his meal at lightning speed and sure enough, Zhang Xinjie picked his dishes clean. Jiang You thought he was done eating and was just about to speak, when he saw Zhang Xinjie pick up his ⅘ full bowl of soup and quietly drink it one spoonful at a time.

Finally, when he finished the soup, he wiped his mouth with a napkin. Jiang You wasn’t sure if he was done, so he kept silent. After Zhang Xinjie put down his napkin, he looked over: “What are you here for?”

“For some in-game matters.” Jiang You hastily replied.

“Oh?”

Jiang You explained the situation to him. There had been quite some development in the past few days. Blue Brook Guild’s troubles and their troubles were all explained to him.

In reality, Jiang You didn’t fully understand the situation. The strongest three big guilds were all in trouble. Apart from Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition, Herb Garden’s reserves had almost been wiped clean by Lord Grim. The team backing them had been beaten by Lord Grim numerous times too. If Jiang You knew of this, he would have asked for help from even Han Wenqing long ago.

Unspecialized?

A weapon that can change forms?

A single person suppressed all of you guys?

Zhang Xinjie silently listened as Jiang You finished his report. He was mostly interested in these areas.

Apart from this, Zhang Xinjie didn’t care about the BOSS story that Jiang You was most distressed about. He had only asked for a bit more details about the strategies and tactics Lord Grim’s team had used in the first team wipe out. But Jiang You hadn’t really paid attention to many of these things, so he wasn’t able to answer them.

“Vice-captain Zhang really does care more about the strategy and tactics……’ Jiang You thought.

In the Glory pro-scene, there were four players who were titled Master Tacticians. No, there were only three now. Zhang Xinjie was one of them. The other two were the Blue Rain team captain Yu Wenzhou and the Thunderclap team captain Xiao Shiqin. Team Thunderclap wasn’t considered a very strong team, but by relying on their team captain Xiao Shiqing’s tactics and strategy, they would sometimes be able to come up with surprising upsets, which made it so that the high-ranked teams never looked down on them. The last one, who couldn’t be considered one anymore, was the retired Ye Qiu.

“This Lord Grim you talk about isn’t so simple. You have accounts I can use right? Let me go and take a look.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Uh, I do, I do.” Jiang You hastily said.

“I’m going to ask for time off this afternoon. I’ll then go over to where you are.” Zhang Xinjie said.

Chapter 232 – A Precise Position

After leaving the dining hall, Jiang You returned to his workplace at the Club and immediately contacted Cold Night, asking if he could hurry and find a Level 33 Cleric account for him.

All of the reserve account cards for the tenth server were with Cold Night, but Cold Night didn’t live in the same city as Tyranny’s Club, so it wasn’t as easy getting the cards from him as was for Plantago Seeds to retrieve the cards for Tiny Herb. It hadn’t been easy for Jiang You and that Striker to get their account cards for the tenth server.

“A Cleric? Is Endless Night’s fine?” Endless Night was in the same city as Tyranny’s Club, but Cold Night had only asked this randomly. Their most skilled Cleric in the guild already had an account. The other Clerics were also near the same level as Endless Night, so it didn’t make sense to give out his account card to worser players.

“Okay, tell him to come over this afternoon!” He didn’t think that Jiang You would actually agree.

Cold Night was surprised, so he asked curiously: “Who is it for?”

“Vice Captain Zhang.” Jiang You didn’t keep any secrets.

“Ah…..” There was some surprise in his voice, “Vice-captain Zhang is going to personally come out?”

“Yeah, I went over to talk to him and he said he’d take a look. Tell Endless Night to bring his account card over!”

“Okay okay.”

Cold Night hung up the phone and immediately contacted Endless Night. Endless Night had no objections and on the contrary, was extremely excited. He was a core part of Tyrannical Ambition and played a Cleric as well. How could he not admire Zhang Xinjie? It was an honor to let him use his account!

At 2 o’clock sharp in the afternoon, Zhang Xinjie arrived at the guild studio. Jiang You was already waiting there eagerly, but was still surprised when he saw Zhang Xinjie walk in through the door. Zhang Xinjie had said he would come take a look, but in actuality, he had brought his own keyboard and mouse.

Nearly all pro-players had their own keyboard and mouse. They had their own custom settings and a different keyboard would affect them slightly. In the pro-scene, such a difference couldn’t be ignored.

But Zhang Xinjie was only coming to take a look in the game. Zhang Xinjie bringing his own keyboard and mouse was a reflection of his strict and serious attitude. Endless Night excitedly handed his account card over to his idol, while Jiang You removed the original keyboard and mouse from the computer.

After connecting his own equipment, Zhang Xinjie sat down. Jiang You and the Striker sat beside him; one on the left and the other on the right. The three quickly logged into the game. Endless Night no longer had his account, so he couldn’t play, but he was still able to watch and admire Zhang Xinjie play. The other workers in the studio weren’t going to miss the opportunity either and all ran to watch. Jiang You was initially worried that Zhang Xinjie would be unhappy with this, but seeing that he didn’t seem to care, he didn’t say anything.

When Jiang You logged into the game, he checked his friends list. Jiang You said sorrowfully: “Aw, it looks like Lord Grim isn’t online.” He and Lord Grim had become friends at Frost Forest.

“Oh, you said he last logged off at Line Canyon?” Zhang Xinjie asked.

“Yeah!”

“We’ll go wait at a Line Canyon entrance.” Zhang Xinjie said as he maneuvered the character, Endless Night, towards Line Canyon.

“There’s no need for that. We already have people guarding there. If Lord Grim comes out, they’ll tell us.” Jiang You hastily said.

“There’s no hurry.” Zhang Xinjie still had his character continue running to Line Canyon. After arriving there, his character just stood there, quietly waiting.

“Lord Grim still hasn’t come online…….” Jiang You reminded him. It was still too early to wait.

But just as he reminded him, a prompt suddenly showed up for Jiang You’s Crowd Lover. He immediately checked it and sure enough, it was Lord Grim.

“He’s on.”

“Okay.” Zhang Xinjie replied and then put on his headphones.

Jiang You and the Striker didn’t dare be negligent and also hurried to put on their headphones.

Jiang You wasn’t the only person to receive the prompt that Lord Grim had come online. The other guilds had also received it. Cold Night was already talking to Chen Yehui, Lonely Drink, and the other guild leaders. Of course, he wasn’t going to mention Zhang Xinjie since they were, after all, only a temporary alliance.

They actually waited for a long time. In the blink of an eye, an hour had passed. The original players who were guarding the Line Canyon entrance had already changed shifts, but Zhang Xinjie’s Endless Night was still standing there, waiting. The person behind Endless Night was also waiting in the same way. He sat up straight without moving or talking.

Jiang You felt uneasy in his chair, but he didn’t know what to say. Tell a joke? Seeing Zhang Xinjie’s expressionless face, Jiang You gave up on that idea. He already had Cold Night ordering people search around in Line Canyon. There was still no sign of Lord Grim, even after an hour. He clearly hadn’t planned on just happily leaving the canyon.

Another long wait and another hour passed.

The guards had once again switched shifts, but there was still no sign from Cold Night. Zhang Xinjie was the same. The people who had originally been watching had already left. Even Endless Night had gone on another computer to play some online games. All Jiang You and that Striker could do was sit there. If Zhang Xinjie hadn’t relaxed yet, how could they dare to?

Lord Grim, you f*cker! Jiang You could only curse at Lord Grim.

“He’s here.” Zhang Xinjie suddenly said. He had been standing with his camera zoomed out to the max. He had been standing on the right in the middle of the entrance and was the first to find Lord Grim. He was currently running along the slope.

Jiang You immediately called for everyone’s attention. He and the Striker had been sitting beside Zhang Xinjie and hadn’t been distracted. But the other three, the Sharpshooter, the Cleric, and the Blade master, were probably tabbed out and passing time.

After receiving Jiang You’s message, the three began to move. They also knew that Endless Night was being controlled by Zhang Xinjie. It was obviously who the leader of their team was right now.

Zhang Xinjie had begun moving!

His two hands danced across the keyboard. His rapid tapping immediately drew the attention of Endless Night, who was playing something else. He threw down his game and ran over to watch.

Zhang Xinjie had just typed some messages out for the team. Five orders. Five classes. Five coordinates. Five positions. He was arranging the team’s formation.

The positions could be construed as sub-coordinates.

One coordinate was to move sideways ten steps. Ten steps indicated ten steps of a character’s walking, which was the same for every class. Each step’s distance could be seen as a certain position. For example, if someone were given (2,5), they would move to a certain position within an area.

Zhang Xinjie was meticulously arranging the positions of everyone.

Jiang You and the others didn’t dare act careless and all went to their respective positions. And that guard from some other guild was still standing there stupidly without moving.

Jiang You and the others ignored them. With Zhang Xinjie leading them, they were confident that they could take down Lord Grim. They didn’t think that they would need help.

After Ye Xiu got up in the afternoon, he hadn’t seen Chen Guo nor Tang Rou. When he asked people in the Internet Cafe, they said that they gone out to take a walk. When he came online, he went around and killed some monsters and currently planned on going back to the city.

He had to go back. With all of the intense fighting from yesterday, the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s Durability was almost gone. Faced with this issue, for such a precious Silver weapon, even Ye Xiu couldn’t stay calm.

Ye Xiu knew that after being noticed by the seven guilds, he would be chased relentlessly. As a result, he chose routes where no one was there. Just as he was about to leave the canyon, he saw a character standing on the left of the middle of the entrance.

“A very precise position…….” Ye Xiu had Lord Grim move to a position that was good for observation as well. It was just a simple position, but among experts, they each had their own judgements.

Chapter 233 – Sacred Fire

Line Canyon Entrance. One of them was inside the canyon, the other was outside. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and Zhang Xinjie’s Endless Night saw each other at the same exact time.

Ye Xiu recognized this ID, but his stance gave him an unusual feeling.

In any case, he had already been found, so he sent Endless Night a message: “Who’s there?”

The real Endless Night behind Zhang Xinjie saw Lord Grim’s message and immediately felt that Lord Grim really was very arrogant.

“You won’t be leaving.” Zhang Xinjie quickly replied. It was so quick that it looked like a blur to Endless Night. When he finished reading it, he saw that Lord Grim had already replied back: “Oh? Is there an ambush out there?”

Another flash and Zhang Xinjie sent another one: “Yeah.”

“How many?”

“Six.”

Jiang You and the others were all ready to battle. How were they supposed to know that the two were actually chatting with each other. Only Endless Night, who was standing behind Zhang Xinjie, watched in disbelief.

They chat so fast! Endless Night gasped in amazement. From Zhang Xinjie’s screen, he saw Lord Grim calmly running up the slope, while looking left and right from time to time around the canyon.

“Your positioning isn’t bad!” Zhang Xinjie received another message from Lord Grim.

“Ha ha. If you’re done looking, you’d better be careful!” Zhang Xinjie replied.

“Coming.” Lord Grim replied. He suddenly sped up and his character sprinted up the slope, making the spectating Endless Night’s heart jump. Seeing that Lord Grim was coming, Jiang You and the Striker nervously glanced at Zhang Xinjie.

Zhang Xinjie was as calm as ever and focused on the screen in front of him.

Close. He’s getting closer and closer…….

Jiang You’s hands were trembling. He wanted to start attacking, but with Zhang Xinjie there, he was too afraid to start anything and could only wait for Zhang Xinjie’s instructions. However, Zhang Xinjie still hadn’t said anything.

We’re still not going to attack? From our current positions, I should be the first to attack, no? Or maybe my thought process is too simple and Vice-captain Zhang thinks that I shouldn’t require instructions and is waiting for me to make a move?

Countless thoughts revolved around in Jiang You’s head. He once again glanced at Zhang Xinjie and saw his lips suddenly move.

“Mage!” A voice resounded through his headphones.

“Hm?” Jiang You stared blankly for awhile before he understood that Zhang Xinjie was giving him a command. He immediately turned his head back and began to act. There’s no need to think so much.

His play making was still good though. Flame Explosion and Frost Ball rolled down the mountain along with a Raging Flames that was ready to be unleashed at any moment.

Jiang You controlled his spells well. Flame Explosion and Frost Ball didn’t shoot forward in a straight line. The two spells flew one after the other at different angles. But when Lord Grim met with the Flame Explosion, he suddenly changed directions and then switched back, avoiding both spells without losing much speed.

“F*ck!” Endless Night cried out. There were many ways of dodging Jiang You’s two spells, but Lord Grim had used the quickest and most dangerous method. It had to be known that the Line Canyon exit was a slope, which affected a character’s move speed. Successfully using a “Z Shake” in this type of terrain wasn’t easy.

The results from his difficult maneuver were astonishing. Lord Grim had barely slowed down from these two spells and instantly lessened quite a bit of distance between them. Jiang You hadn’t expected this, so his Raging Flames was thrown in the wrong direction and landed behind Lord Grim.

“Gunner!” Zhang Xinjie’s voice resonated. The Sharpshooter immediately lifted his gun and shot a round at Lord Grim.

Lord Grim rolled and the bullet landed besides him, creating several sparks. He then rolled another three times to a spot below the cliff and escaped from the Sharpshooter’s line of sight. The Sharpshooter stepped forward and jumped off the cliff. He turned his body midair and was about to shoot again, when suddenly he heard a warning: “Careful.”

“Swoosh swoosh swoosh……..” By the time the Sharpshooter noticed these three sounds, it was already too late. Three Shurikens hit his body making his character lose balance as he flew out.

Ninja skill, Ninja Tool: Shuriken.

After knocking away the Sharpshooter, Lord Grim immediately leaped towards that direction. As soon as his head was exposed, the Striker appeared and welcomed him with a Dashing Jab.

Zhang Xinjie gave directions with both shouts and through messages. The Striker had received the message long ago to follow the Sharpshooter and to guard this direction.

The sudden punch hit its target and sent Lord Grim back into the Canyon.

“Yes!” The Striker roared, cleansing him of yesterday’s sorrows. His character rushed forward and jumped to follow up with an Eagle Stamp.

“Yes, my ass!” His Eagle Stamp hadn’t connected, when Lord Grim poofed and disappeared, turning into a cloud of smoke.

How could the Striker not know that this was the Ninja skill: Shadow Clone Technique? But in order to use this technique, you had to set up where the real body and fake body would be. Determining the direction and the distance as well as using it was quite complicated. How could he have done it in such a short amount of time?

The Striker hastily turned to look behind him. He saw Lord Grim’s real body standing on the cliff where he had been guarding. His hands were raised and pointed towards him. A chaotic black energy ball floated beside him which then rotated and formed a few black arrows that shot at him.

Warlock skill: Curse Arrow.

The Striker had nowhere to run. He had almost been shot by a barrage of Curse Arrows.

Warlocks, Assassins, Thieves, and Ninjas were all Night Walkers. Curse Arrow was a type of skill that could be charged to increase its power. The longer it was charged, the more arrows there would be. Lord Grim hadn’t had time to charge, so he only shot a few arrows over and then went on his way.

But as soon as he turned his body, a sword light sliced towards him. Lord Grim immediately jumped, just barely dodging the Blade Master’s Sword Draw.

At this moment, a storm of white flames rained down. Lord Grim had leapt up and had nowhere to dodge.

Everyone stared in awe and watched as the white flames continued to coil around Lord Grim’s body after he fell. Only then did they know that this time, they had successfully hit Lord Grim. The one who had done this attack was Zhang Xinjie using the Level 30 Cleric skill, Sacred Fire. Clerics weren’t a class that only healed.

Sacred Fire was a DoT skill, which lasted 5 seconds. The damage decreased with every second and after being cast, it didn’t matter whether it hit the target or not since it would continue to burn in the place it landed for 5 seconds. In those 5 seconds, if the target bumped into it, the skill’s full effects would take place. But the damage wasn’t the scariest part about Sacred Fire.

The scariest part about Sacred Fire was its 3 seconds Silence. Characters that were hit by Sacred Fire wouldn’t be able to use any skills for 3 seconds.

Priests and Night Walkers couldn’t compare to Mages, Fighters, or even Swordsman and Gunners in their ability to kill, but they had many CC skills.

Being unable to use skills was an extremely bad situation for Ye Xiu. Even worse, after Zhang Xinjie used Sacred Fire, the other Cleric also moved up to use it as well. Under Zhang Xinjie’s lead, Clerics weren’t the backline, but the main force in controlling the field.

The Cross in the Cleric’s hands glowed white. Ye Xiu knew the skill was coming, but didn’t randomly jump around. He didn’t know where the Sacred Fire would be cast and if he was Silenced again, he’d be in a hopeless situation.

Ye Xiu decided to jump off the cliff. He immediately adjusted his camera and looked around him. When he looked down, he saw Crowd Lover’s staff pointing up……

A column of flame erupted and Lord Grim was instantly rooted in his position. Another Sacred Fire rained down once again.

Chapter 234 – Two Traps

Lord Grim was launched into the air by Raging Flames and the Cleric’s Sacred Fire hit its target as well. Lord Grim’s movements had been seen through by them.

Ye Xiu could only quietly watch as his Lord Grim was once again burned by Sacred Fire and Silenced for another 3 seconds.

The damage overlapped, but the CC did as well, so having the skills overlap was a waste.

However, Tyrannical Ambition’s two Clerics linked their Sacred Fires almost perfectly, maintaining the Silence on Lord Grim for 5-6 seconds. The Striker, who had been shot down, had already caught back up and the Sharpshooter had gotten up as well. They clearly wanted to kill Lord Grim right here.

Jiang You and the others shouted in happiness and pounced over. But Zhang Xinjie was a bit disappointed; he hadn’t seen what he had wanted to see.

“Why didn’t he use Aerial Fire?”

This was something that puzzled Zhang Xinjie. If Lord Grim were any other class, there wouldn’t have been any possible way of him escaping, but Gunners could use Aerial Gun to move in the air and stall for time. Aerial Gun was only a normal attack, so it wouldn’t be Silenced. There was no difference in this aspect between unspecialized and Gunners.

But Lord Grim hadn’t done so. After Raging Flames took effect, he directly dropped down.

Jiang You already had his Crowd Lover cast another spell. The Blade Master was ready to provide backup at any moment. The Striker rushed forward with his fists and the Sharpshooter slid on the ground. They didn’t want Lord Grim landing onto the ground.

“Pa!” A sound was heard among their yells, seemingly unimportant. But the Sharpshooter’s Slide Kick was stopped because of this sound. He kept his sliding position on the ground but on his screen, he could see his right leg was clamped onto the ground by steel spikes.

Thief skill: Spike Trap!

The Sharpshooter was startled.

Where’d the trap come from? Did Lord Grim set it? No way! Ever since Lord Grim appeared in front of them, not a single movement of his had been missed. This place…… Lord Grim had only rolled over here for a bit. Could he have actually set such a trap while he was rolling?

Since the trap had been set earlier, it wouldn’t just disappear after being Silenced. As soon as someone touched it, it would trigger.

The Sharpshooter hadn’t yet figured out what had happened when he heard a rippling sound. A light smoke came up from the ground and spread out. The Striker had been caught inside the fog of poison and his face quickly turned green.

Another Thief skill: Poison Gas Trap.

Earlier, when Lord Grim rolled to dodge the bullet, he hadn’t set only one trap, but instead had set two. The Sharpshooter had a hard time believing it, but the reality was in front of his eyes. It couldn’t have been placed by some random person.

When the Sharpshooter saw the position of the two traps, he instantly figured out the reason. This was an escape route that Lord Grim had kept in case he needed it. If he ran into trouble when he jumped up, he still had somewhere to go. He had set up these traps to protect himself.

And his escape route had worked. If those two traps weren’t there, then the Striker and Sharpshooter would have plastered Lord Grim onto the wall forever.

And now? Even though the Sharpshooter hadn’t taken much damage, he had been stalled.

The Poison Gas Trap, on the other hand, mainly did damage and didn’t have any movement restriction effects. However, the instant the target was poisoned, it would create a very brief Stun, interrupting the Striker’s Dashing Jab. With this, Lord Grim was able to land and roll away. Roll was a common skill and didn’t count as a skill from a class, so it wasn’t Silenced by Sacred Fire.

Crowd Lover’s Blizzard had arrived though. His Blizzard stormed down, but Lord Grim was able to roll away.

All of this happened in a mere three seconds.

In the first second, two of the players fell for the traps. Lord Grim’s Quick Recover was successful.

In the second second, Lord Grim rolled past the Sharpshooter. The trap didn’t restrict attacks, so the Sharpshooter tried to shoot him, but how could he compare to Ye Xiu? Lord Grim’s left hand took out a sword and slashed, hitting the Sharpshooter.

The Striker rushed out from the Poison Gas but the green-color on his face hadn’t gone away. The poison was still lowering his health.

And in the third second, Ye Xiu didn’t even need to look at his status bar to know that the Sacred Fire’s Silence was gone. With the status effect gone, how could he be afraid of facing the Striker? The two characters clashed; the Striker punched forward, but Lord Grim suddenly ducked and then countered.

The sword light curved into a beautiful arc. The Assassin skill: Shining Cut. The Striker’s fist hit nothing but air, while his body was left open. Shining Cut sliced across his waist, leaving a trail of fresh blood. Two sword lights crossed and intersected at his neck, cutting across like a giant pair of scissors.

The two swords returned and the blood flowed outwards from the Striker’s neck.

The spray of blood looked terrifying, but this was a game, so the injury didn’t mean that the Striker was dead.

This sudden change was completely outside of everyone’s expectations. By the time the Blade master jumped down to give chase, Lord Grim had already run far away.

Crowd Lover was the closest to Lord Grim now. Jiang You hoped for Zhang Xinjie’s instructions, but he didn’t say anything. He couldn’t just watch as Lord Grim ran past him, so Jiang You pounced after him to try and block him. However, Elementalists weren’t good at blocking. Crowd Lover put his staff behind him and prepared to use a Falling Flower Palm.

Jiang You wasn’t very good in this area. In front of him was the forefather of the Battle Mage as well. Jiang You was pretty much displaying his measly skill in front of a God. But if Ye Xiu was hit by this Falling Flower Palm, then retirement was the right choice.

Lord Grim gently turned and Jiang You’s Falling Flower Palm flew by him. Lord Grim jumped up and the Twin Tailed Swords in his hands picked Crowd Lover into the air using Assassin skill: Leaping Blade.

Lord Grim landed first and then sent Crowd Lover flying away. At this moment, the Sharpshooter finally freed himself from the trap. But the Striker’s Poison hadn’t ended yet and green spots covered his body. The Blade Master was also still far away from him.

And Endless Night? Ye Xiu turned his camera and saw Endless Night behind him, still standing there, not moving.

Ye Xiu chuckled and sent a message to him: “Almost. A bit more and you would have gotten me. Try again next time.”

After sending him the message, Lord Grim turned his head and left. He didn’t plan on continuing to fight with this team. The team had some sort of expert helping them, who had forced him into a dangerous situation. If he hadn’t judged incorrectly, then the person controlling Endless Night was probably Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie.

Luckily, the others weren’t pro-players. Their ability to carry out his instructions weren’t good enough. If not for this, it would be hard to say whether he’d have been able to escape from these six with just the Twin Tailed Swords in his hands.

Chapter 235 – Bet

Lord Grim disappeared shortly after.

Seeing that Zhang Xinjie’s Endless Night wasn’t moving, Jiang You and the others didn’t go and chase. All they could do was helplessly move their characters over to Endless Night’s side.

Even though none of them had died this time, the outcome was completely different than what they had expected. When Lord Grim was hit by Sacred Fire, they all thought that the situation was already set. They were all exclaiming how different it was to have a true expert help them. But in the end, two traps had turned over the double Sacred Fire situation and Lord Grim had escaped. From this point of view, the winner was still Lord Grim.

Jiang You and the others couldn’t help but feel dejected when they heard Zhang Xinjie say: “The weapon in his hands didn’t seem to have changed forms.”

A voice from outside of the game came: “He wasn’t holding his original weapon. That’s the Nightwalker class Level 30 Purple weapon, Twin Tailed Swords.”

The one who spoke was Endless Night. He played in the new server, so Endless Night was very knowledgeable about equipment at this level. It didn’t matter what class the weapon was from, he could recognize it.

“Purple weapon?” The others repeated it back.

From when Lord Grim first appeared to his escape, the entire battle hadn’t even taken a minute. They hadn’t yet had time to reflect on the details of the battle. Endless Night, who hadn’t been playing, had seen everything clearly. He had been standing behind Zhang Xinjie and Zhang Xinjie hadn’t done much in the battle besides giving commands. The only time he really did anything else was when he used Sacred Fire. His character’s camera constantly shifted to observe each player’s situation. Having a general outlook of the field was an important skill for Clerics to have. Endless Night hadn’t even watched for a minute, but already felt like he had gained a lot.

“Oh, that guy fought all throughout the night yesterday and hadn’t had the chance to return back to the city. My guess is that his weapon is running out of Durability.” Jiang You thought for a bit and then said. His guess was quite on point.

“So it’s like that.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“How unlucky. If it wasn’t for those two traps…….” The Striker gloomily said. In this battle, he had been the most unfortunate. The blood from the Cut Throat made his character look miserable and the Poison from the trap had only just wore off.

“If the Gunner had been a bit faster, then he wouldn’t have had the chance to put down those two traps.” Zhang Xinjie quickly said.

“Uh……” The Sharpshooter didn’t know what to say.

“The Cleric’s Sacred Fire was half a second early. The Mage initiated just a bit too slowly.” Zhang Xinjie continued.

Jiang You and the Cleric were silent.

“The Striker likes to punch while moving fast…… but he needs to work on his accuracy.”

“Oh…..” The Striker replied.

Of the team of five, four of them had been called out by Zhang Xinjie. They couldn’t help but shudder when they thought of what would have happened to them if they had partied with the team captain Han Wenqing. If all of these mistakes had led to Lord Grim escaping, they’d probably have been bombarded by the team captain’s shouts already.

“Then what should we do next?” Jiang You and the others felt like they didn’t have the ability to stop Lord Grim, so they didn’t have any suggestions to make. Right now, with Zhang Xinjie, they took the chance to ask for his advice. There was clearly no way Zhang Xinjie could continue to accompany them and waste his time on Lord Grim. He had only said he would “take a look”, so he was probably done looking around by now. What would the vice-captain suggest? Jiang You looked forward to his answer.

“The main conflict is the competition for the dungeon records. If we keep fighting like this, then all we’re doing is wasting each other’s time and effort. There’s nothing good that will come from it.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Yeah!” Jiang You hastily replied.

“That’s why I made a deal with him. Tonight, we’ll go to the Arena and do a 5v5 team competition. If we win, they won’t touch the records set by Tyrannical Ambition.

“Ah! Really?’ Jiang You exclaimed happily.

‘But he has conditions on his side too. I’ll send you it. See if you can accept it.” Zhang Xinjie said and sent Lord Grim’s message to Jiang You. The final decision had to be done by Jiang You, since Jiang You was the person in charge of the guild.

Jiang You looked at the stakes. Eight Scarlet Scorpion Tails, eight Scarlet Stingers, a Scarlet Illusion Blade, forty Sandworm Silk. So familiar! Wasn’t this list very similar to the one that Lord Grim had given when Cold Night went to negotiate with Lord Grim over Line Canyon? But, it was a bit different compared to last time.

Amber Crystal! Lord Grim hadn’t included an Amber Crystal this time, which was originally the most valuable item. Which means……. Could the Cliff Ronin Alpine have dropped an Amber Crystal? Now that he has it, he doesn’t need it? F*ck!

But if the other side has it already, then the stakes were a lot lower. Jiang You thought as he said: “Yeah, I can accept these conditions……..”

“Hold on. I haven’t sent everything yet.” Zhang Xinjie sent another message. Jiang You looked at it and fell even more depressed. The stakes hadn’t lowered one bit. With the new message, there was another list of uncommon materials, which equalled in value to an Amber Crystal.

Jiang You cursed at Lord Grim and then closed the message.

“So he said that if we win, then they won’t touch any of our Tyrannical Ambition records ever again?” Jiang You asked Zhang Xinjie.

“Yes. That was the agreement.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Then I can accept these conditions.” Jiang You said, “I’m just afraid he won’t uphold the agreement!”

“It’s not like we’ll lose much if we win the team competition, no?”

“That’s true.” Jiang You nodded his head and pondered silently. Endless Night, who was behind them, stood out and said: “You can trust Lord Grim. There hasn’t been any crazy records recently.”

“Really?’ Jiang You saw Lord Grim as evil and deceitful. Hiding for a half and an hour to steal their BOSS, sneakily setting up two traps, just looking at these two events, Jiang You wasn’t able to see Lord Grim as anyone trustworthy.

“We can tell the whole world of the bet. That way, if he goes back on his word, everyone will know and no one will ever trust him again.” Someone suggested.

“Hm…….” Jiang You hesitated and looked at Zhang Xinjie. He really wanted to know how confident Zhang Xinjie was in the team competition, but asking him would mean that he would be questioning Zhang Xinjie’s skill. Should I ask or not……

Telling the whole world of the bet was a double-edged sword! Didn’t the Poplar Beach massacre just happen? He lost so badly that he was too afraid of playing again. If they lost this fight, then the players participating wouldn’t be the only ones losing face, but the entire guild. It’d be even worse than Poplar Beach.

“Vice-captain Zhang, what do you think of our chances of winning?’ Jiang You decided to ask him.

“If we’re going by individual strength, Lord Grim’s skill level is certainly above yours, which is why I asked for a team competition. Team competitions require strategy, coordination, and a team synergy. You said that Lord Grim’s team have only just recently been formed, while you guys have been playing for a long time together. In terms of synergy, isn’t it obvious who has the advantage? Their individual ability might be their advantage, but we are a better team.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“We don’t completely lose in individual strength! We still have you, vice-captain!” The Striker said.

Everyone chuckled, but Zhang Xinjie shook his head: “In a team competition, controlling each individual’s tempo and coordination is more important. You must be calm. Blindly showing off your strength will only seem out of place. Coming apart from the team’s tempo will only lead to you being the team’s weakness.”

The Striker’s flattery hadn’t gone well. Jiang You didn’t pay attention to all this. Even after saying so much, Zhang Xinjie only told them of their advantages. He didn’t say what their chances were exactly. Jiang You wanted a direct answer. Zhang Xinjie continued to speak though: “In any case, as long as it is a competition, there is no way of knowing the odds completely. I can only say that in theory, we have a higher winning chance. If not, then I wouldn’t have directly asked to bet with Lord Grim.”

“Alright! Then I’ll agree to the bet. We can talk about the other details later!” Jiang You decided. Now it was just a matter of whether he should announce the bet to the world. That, he’d have to consider some more!

Chapter 236 – Assumptive Guides

Ye Xiu received Endless Night’s agreement to the conditions and smiled. He then replied: “I’ll see you tonight then.”

“Tonight? What time?’ Endless Night asked.

“That’s hard to say. The people on my side are a bit complicated. I need to contact them first and even then, it’s hard to set a time. You’ll all be on at night, right? We’ll go when everyone’s here!” Ye Xiu casually answered back.

“You can’t contact them right now?”

“They’re not online.” Ye Xiu said.

“Nine o’clock. There’s still 4 hours and 37 minutes until then. Will you have your players gathered by then?”

“Uh, probably……” Ye Xiu really wasn’t sure. Tang Rou and Chen Guo had left together and he didn’t know when they would come back. Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan usually weren’t on by then. Steamed Bun Invasion was usually on, but if he didn’t come on, Ye Xiu had no way of contacting him.

“Then tonight at nine.” The other side replied.

“Alright, be there or be square.”

“Don’t be late. I won’t wait for you.” The other side concluded.

He really is Zhang Xinjie, Ye Xiu laughed and didn’t reply back. Right at this moment, his Lord Grim was hurrying on. He figured that he was still everyone’s target. Even though he had already made a bet with Tyrannical Ambition, Ye Xiu couldn’t guarantee that they’d stop chasing him.

He only wanted to fix his Thousand Chance Umbrella. The NPCs that could do this were in many of the small villages as well, so he didn’t need to return to Congee City.

In the end, Ye Xiu chose to go to Buzzer Village, which was near Frost Forest. This type of small village wasn’t considered a safe area and also didn’t have any leveling monsters either; there were only a couple of NPCs, one of which could fix equipment. This place was already considered a low-leveled area. Since there weren’t any valuable quests to do around here, he didn’t think many guild players would be here.

Everything was as Ye Xiu had expected. After finding the NPC, his Thousand Chance Umbrella was fixed. At Level 25, fixing equipment didn’t require any materials; it only required money. This small amount of money wasn’t anything to Ye Xiu. The surplus of materials that he had gotten from Tiny Herb could be sold at any time for money.

Just as he was about to leave, he heard a system notification from his friends list. Ye Xiu checked and saw that it was Concealed Light.

“God, you’re on!” Concealed Light said hi to Ye Xiu.

“Yeah, I’m on! Have you gone online in the day time? How was it? Did you meet any trouble?” Ye Xiu asked. Concealed Light had been drawn into the conflict for no reason. If the guilds decided to watch over him as well, then that would really be unlucky.

“I went on for a bit in the afternoon. Nothing in particular happened!” Concealed Light said.

“Okay, that’s good. How’s your research on your guides going along?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Uh, this one is a lot more complicated than fighting a BOSS!! I’m about ⅕ of the way done. Do you want to take a look, God?”

“Sure!”

“How do I send it to you?”

“Add me on QQ!” Ye Xiu said and then sent him his ID. He then logged onto his QQ and received a friend invite not long after. He checked the invite and saw that the other side was using his in-game ID, Concealed Light. He looked at his own QQ nickname and saw that he was using his in-game ID.

The profile picture for his QQ was a red maple leaf.

One Autumn Leaf was his QQ’s nickname.

Seeing this, Ye Xiu sighed. He lit up his cigarette, opened the settings, changed his profile picture to the default one, and then changed his name to Lord Grim.

One Autumn Leaf was already of the past, even though it actually hadn’t been that long yet.

Ye Xiu silently accepted Concealed Light’s friend request and Concealed Light immediately sent him a file: Line Canyon Idiot’s Guide.

“Idiot’s Guide still! Even though you’re listing out the details step by step, it can’t be called idiotic in any way.”

“It’s just a name. I can change it any time. Hurry and check it out, God.” Concealed Light clearly didn’t care about the name.

“Okay, I’ll take a look. You do your business, I’ll look for you in a bit.”

“Thank you!” Concealed Light said.

Ye Xiu had run Line Canyon many times already and already had an idea on how to set the dungeon record. Early in the morning, when Tang Rou had gone to sleep early, he had spent his time studying dungeon guides and records, so he had a general idea of the strategy.

Now what type of strategy could this purely theoretical Concealed Light have come up with? Ye Xiu opened up the file and took a look. Like before, the introduction was on the class set-up, which turned out to be a party of an unspecialized, a Launcher, a Battle Mage, a Brawler, and a Ghostblade. It was clearly based off of Ye Xiu’s team. Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. He had only looked at the first line and was already looking for Concealed Light: “Why’d you put in an unspecialized. My character isn’t typical.”

“Ha ha…… I just wanted to try it out.” Concealed Light said.

Ye Xiu reckoned that Concealed Light wanted them to do an experiment, to prove the possibility of his guides. But the problem was that using Lord Grim as a template limited the guides only to them.

An unspecialized with the Thousand Chance Umbrella and an unspecialized without one were two completely different things. Concealed Light didn’t understand this self-made Silver weapon, so he wouldn’t be able to write an unspecialized guide that suited Lord Grim. Guides like his that analyzed the damage from every single hit and required there to not be a single mistake couldn’t lack this aspect.

Ye Xiu decided to keep on looking though. Sure enough, it was just as he expected. The content regarding unspecialized wasn’t correct.

“This probably won’t do……” Ye Xiu said the truth to Concealed Light. Concealed Light wasn’t stupid, so with just these few words, Concealed Light realized what the problem was.

“Unspecialized won’t do I guess. I need to change it to a different class.” Concealed Light replied to Ye Xiu.

“Clearing a dungeon and killing a BOSS the fastest are very similar in that they both have an optimal class set-up.” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah, I saw a few guides talking about this. In the beginning, I planned on doing that, but I felt like your unspecialized was more powerful.”

“The advantages of an unspecialized are extremely obvious in the early stages of the game, but the problem is, there aren’t any more unspecialized. If your guides only talk about using an unspecialized, then it’ll be the same as your previous BOSS guides. They’ll be guides that no one can use.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Okay, I understand.” Concealed Light said.

“You still have to dungeon when you have the chance in order to increase your experience.” Ye Xiu said. Concealed Light’s theoretical knowledge of the game was quite impressive. He was also very smart, but there was a difference between theory and reality.

Concealed Light went back to researching for his guides. Ye Xiu checked his QQ friends list and saw that Su Mucheng was online.

“Are you free at nine tonight?” Ye Xiu sent a message.

Su Mucheng looked at the message and stared blankly. The ID number was very familiar, but the profile picture and name had changed.

“I’m free. To do what?”

“Come to the game. A PvP team competition.”

“Oh, with who?”

“Zhang Xinjie.”

“Him? Why’d he run over to the new server?” Su Mucheng was surprised.

“Yesterday, after you and Yifan went off, we wandered around and encountered a wild BOSS, which Tyrannical Ambition had also found. We waited and then KSed it. They probably went mad with anger. Then today, I encountered Tyrannical Ambition’s team and as I guessed correctly, the Cleric on that team should have been Zhang Xinjie substituting in.” Ye Xiu said.

“So then you agreed on a team PK tonight?” Su Mucheng asked.

“Yeah, he asked me. My guess is that he doesn’t know who I am.”

“Really? Then he miscalculated this time. Everything points to disaster for him.” Su Mucheng said.

“I also thought that, so I agreed.” Ye Xiu replied.

“What’s this?” After sending his message, he received an image from Su Mucheng.

“Your new profile pic.” Su Mucheng said.

Ye Xiu opened the image and took a look.

“F*ck, what is this? “笑”? It looks like a “哭”. Why hasn’t your handwriting improved after so many years?” Ye Xiu replied, but he had already changed his profile pic to this new clumsy “笑” picture. (TL: 笑 means to smile or laugh. 哭 means to cry)

Chapter 237 – The Members Aren’t Together

After chatting with Su Mucheng, it was time to eat so the two went on their way to eat dinner. Chen Guo and Tang Rou still hadn’t come back. After eating, Ye Xiu didn’t hurry and log into the game. He instead went onto the Glory forums.

The forum had lots of sections such as a section for dungeons, a section for every class, a section for the Pro Alliance and so on. Each category had their own subject, but if you wanted to find random information, you would have to browse around.

From the first server to the tenth server in addition to the Heavenly Domain, they were all extremely active. Famous players, resentment, and fun stories, they all went into here. Among these, the most popular was the Heavenly Domain and the second most popular was the tenth server.

The main topic of the tenth server was undoubtedly Lord Grim. From the Beginner’s Village all the way to the different records, as soon as someone opened up the page, they would see Lord Grim’s famous name all over the place.

In the tenth server, the dungeon records had become Lord Grim’s. Even the godly Three Great Guilds had to look for Lord Grim for help if they wanted a dungeon record.

The forum users had already figured out what was going on. They were all talking about how the big guilds would develop in this situation.

Right now, the guilds were all talking about their power behind-the-scenes. They would brag about how amazing their pro-team was or brag about how amazing their guild was in the Heavenly Domain or even brag about how amazing their guild was in the other servers. But for the tenth server, all they could do was cry.

In the tenth server, they appeared pretty amazing, but Lord Grim was more so. Some users commented this way.

In the forums, there was no shortage of users who would justify the big guild’s actions, but in front of the undeniable evidence from the dungeon record leaderboards, there was nothing they could say. In comparison, Excellent Dynasty was different. In Frost Forest, even though it was the lowest level dungeon, they at least had beaten Lord Grim. Just from this, Excellent Dynasty was able to brag and press down on the Three Great Guild’s influence.

Seeing these posts, Ye Xiu could only let out a little laugh. If this was ten years ago, he would have been extremely delighted about all this. But now, these weren’t his goals. He had created the current situation in the tenth server. Some of them were intentional, some weren’t, but none of them were surprising. How could they get what they wanted? That was what Ye Xiu was thinking about and what the guilds were thinking about as well.

After checking the tenth server section, Ye Xiu took a look around at the skills section, the equipment section, the dungeon section, etc. The forums gathered a large amount of posts and were an accumulation of many players’ knowledge. It could be said that it was Glory’s largest intelligence network. If you were good at searching, there were many things you could find.

In the blink of an eye, it was eight. Tang Rou and Chen Guo still hadn’t returned yet.

Ye Xiu asked the other employees for Tang Rou’s phone number. He was going to call her and ask her what was going on.

“Hello? Who is this?” Tang Rou was pretty loud and her surroundings were noisy. She was clearly in a crowded place.

“It’s me! Tonight at nine. PK! Are you coming?’ Ye Xiu asked.

‘Ah…. PK!” Tang Rou’s tone seemed very excited, but after a bit of silence, she regretfully said: “I won’t be back by then. Guo Guo and I are about to go watch a movie!”

“Oh, then have fun.” Ye Xiu hung up.

Tang Rou couldn’t come…… that was something unexpected. Tang Rou had played together with him most of the days. How could he have known that she wouldn’t come play today of all days.

After putting down the phone, Ye Xiu logged into the game. When he went online, Steamed Bun Invasion was there, so he hastily asked him: “Steamed Bun, today at night, PK.”

“Oh? Who’s so impatient to die?? Steamed Bun Invasion had massacred players all throughout yesterday. He was extremely arrogant right now.

“The guys who we KSed the BOSS from.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, looks like they just don’t give up. Perfect. I’ll teach them another lesson.”

“Where are you right now?”

“Line Canyon.”

“Are there any problems?” Ye Xiu asked. Tyrannical Ambition would temporarily halt their movements, but the other six guilds were still there! The players were currently looking for them and as soon as Steamed Bun Invasion appeared, it was very possible that they were watching him.

“There is!” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“What is it?”

“I can’t go out.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

‘You’ve been blocked?”

“No….. I’ve never been here, so I’m a bit lost……” Steamed Bun Invasion replied.

“…… Search for a Line Canyon map and take a look at it. Remember to take detours and make sure no one is following you.” Ye Xiu began to sweat. The place Tyrannical Ambition had brought the wild BOSS to actually was a very remote place in Line Canyon.

“Senior, you’re so smart! There really is a person following me.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Really? And what?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I’m about to go fight.”

“…….” Ye Xiu was speechless. It felt like Steamed Bun had found people right after he had reminded him. He couldn’t have gotten the wrong people, right?

Steamed Bun Invasion hadn’t made a mistake though. In the beginning, the pursuer had carefully followed Steamed Bun, but he soon realized that Steamed Bun wasn’t paying attention at all. He had been found twice, but the guy just ignored him and kept on walking. As a result, he became more and more careless. Right now, he was wondering what Steamed Bun Invasion was doing since Steamed Bun Invasion was just walking around. He hadn’t killed any monsters and he had already gone in a circle three times.

“Is he lost?” The pursuer guessed. Steamed Bun Invasion turned his head again and then suddenly dashed towards him.

The pursuer panicked. He looked left and right. There were only monsters around him. Is this guy planning on fighting some monsters? Just as he was thinking this, Steamed Bun Invasion flung his arm and a Brick went flying towards his head.

The player hastily jumped to dodge it. He sent an “I’ve been found” to the guild and immediately began fighting with Steamed Bun Invasion.

Steamed Bun Invasion’s opponent wasn’t a normal player. After a few bouts, the player was killed.

“Ha ha, I killed him. This guy. I was always wondering why he was following me.” Steamed Bun Invasion reported to Lord Grim.

“Phew, how long had he been following you?” Ye Xiu hastily asked.

“Maybe ten minutes?”

“Steamed Bun….. you’ve been exposed. A lot of players are probably coming to surround you very soon!” Ye Xiu said.

“Really? Then I guess I’m going to have to fight.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Be careful of your weapon’s Durability.” Ye Xiu reminded Steamed Bun Invasion.

“Weapon…… Huh? Where’d my claw go?”

“F*ck! Did it break? When the Durability goes to 0, your weapon will break! Check your system log.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Uh oh. That’s not good.” Steamed Bun Invasion obviously understood the importance of a weapon. He checked his system log and sure enough, his claw broke when he was killing that player.

Ye Xiu didn’t know what to say.

“A fight without a weapon. That’ll be difficult!” Steamed Bun Invasion was still discussing the matters with him.

“Do you think there’s hope?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Nope. Unless you save me.”

“By the time I get there, you’ll be dead and back in the city.”

“Since things are like this already, there’s no point in you coming here. I’ll just go directly to the city and we’ll meet up there.” Steamed Bun Invasion really was straightforward and easy-going. He went up empty-handed and pulled a large mob of monsters. The guild players quickly converged. They saw Steamed Bun Invasion in the middle of the mob yelling at them: “Have a good day!” and then died.

“F*CK!” Everyone cursed. What was this Steamed Bun doing? He had been walking around in circles, making it difficult for them to figure out what he was doing and after a lot of effort, they finally surrounded him only to watch as he killed himself.

The monsters left after killing Steamed Bun Invasion. His corpse was already gone.

Chapter 238 – Randomly Chosen

“Senior, I’m in Congee City.” Steamed Bun Invasion revived in the city and sent Ye Xiu a message.

“You’re terrible.” Ye Xiu replied.

“But I don’t have a weapon and I don’t have money…..” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“You…… really are terrible. I’ll be there in a second!” Ye Xiu said.

“OK!”

Ye Xiu didn’t immediately return to Congee City, but went towards Line Canyon instead. His team all logged out at Line Canyon. Even though he didn’t think the other team members would be as innocent as Steamed Bun, they would probably encounter some difficulties too.

At 8:30, Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist came online.

“Hm? Why isn’t everyone here?” Su Mucheng asked.

“Can’t do anything about it.” Ye Xiu replied helplessly. Tang Rou definitely wouldn’t be coming and Qiao Yifan hadn’t come on yet.

“Can we still do it?” Su Mucheng asked.

“We’ll see. Come out of Line Canyon first. Be careful.” Ye Xiu said.

Su Mucheng knew what to expect. Even though there were players watching her, Su Mucheng easily shrugged them off.

Ye Xiu went over to receive her. As he approached Line Canyon, he noticed a few players standing outside of the entrance. They didn’t seem to be going in or heading out. Ye Xiu made a calculation. He then rushed forward and cleared them away.

Each of them sent a message to their respective guilds: Lord Grim is in Line Canyon.

After 20 seconds, the soldiers who had found him were killed.

“Oh! You came to receive me?” At Line Canyon, Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist had already reached the entrance. When she climbed up, she saw Lord Grim.

“Of course.” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim stood there. Beside him were even a few corpses, the guards who had been waiting there. Even though they died, they didn’t immediately revive and stayed to keep watch instead. They really were responsible and diligent.

“Way to ruin the scene!” Su Mucheng wasn’t happy with the corpses.

“Let’s go!” Ye Xiu said and the two left.

The guilds dispatched their troops and began to pursue them. The participants were the ones from yesterday, but they didn’t have the same fighting spirit like before.

The players that had participated in battle though were still able to turn their anger into motivation. But the majority of the players had just run around randomly, waiting, or doing something dull and boring. After knowing that they were going to continue today, everyone had prepared their movies, comics, novels, and snacks to better waste their time.

Ye Xiu led Su Mucheng around the map to escape from the guild’s search web. Afterwards, they headed to Bulls Town.

As the first town players would go to after Beginner Village, even though it was small, it had everything. It was possible to go into the Arena through here as well.

When they arrived at Bulls Town, it was already almost nine. Ye Xiu first sent Steamed Bun Invasion some money to buy a weapon. He then searched his friends list, Seven Fields, Sleeping Moon, and Drifting Water were on. But if they were to join, they would also join the conflict between Ye Xiu and the guilds. Ye Xiu didn’t want this.

At 9 o’clock sharp, Endless Night came online and his character was also already in front of the Arena entrance. Crowd Lover and the others were already waiting there. They didn’t dare have Zhang Xinjie wait for them.

They didn’t dare, but Ye Xiu did.

“Start?”

“Not enough players.”

“4 hours and 37 minutes wasn’t enough time?” Zhang Xinjie was very unhappy.

“No choice. How about another time. Is 12 okay?”

“No.” 12 was Zhang Xinjie’s sleeping time.

“Then what do you say.” Ye Xiu replied.

“When will you be able to gather your players?’ Zhang Xinjie asked.

“12…..”

“Tomorrow then. I hope you won’t miss it again.” Zhang Xinjie concluded. He didn’t want to waste time.

“Ah, wait! I have someone.” Ye Xiu hastily called. He had just received a prompt. He hadn’t checked yet and the message was already there: “PKPKPKPKPK.”

“The noisy guy’s here again!” Su Mucheng disdained.

Lord Grim quickly entered the Arena. He opened a room and after finishing, he sent the room number to Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree.

“Wait for me to switch accounts!” Huang Shaotian immediately said.

“Come here for now!” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“First help us play a round.”

“F*ck f*ck f*ck!! I came to PK with you. Do you think I’m a summoned creature!” Huang Shaotian cursed.

“It’ll be quick.” Ye Xiu said.

“No weapon!” Huang Shaotian called.

“Look for Steamed Bun Invasion. He’s currently buying a weapon. Let him buy you one.” Ye Xiu replied. Huang Shaotian went to contact Steamed Bun Invasion.

In the Arena, the other team immediately entered after receiving the room number. Jiang You’s team hadn’t changed classes, except the Cleric had become Endless Night.

On Ye Xiu’s side, his Lord Grim and Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist were already there. The three empty spaces hadn’t been filled.

“Where are your players?” Endless Night messaged. Suddenly, the third spot was taken and a character locked in: Steamed Bun Invasion. Quickly after, the fourth: Flowing Tree.

“Flowing Tree?” Jiang You was surprised.

“Who’s this?” Zhang Xinjie asked.

“We didn’t meet him yesterday, but he killed quite a few players in Congee Forest. He’s only Level 27.” Jiang You introduced him.

“Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up!” Flowing Tree immediately began hurrying them.

“He also talks a lot.” Jiang You added.

“The Blade Master’s words are already flowing.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Then who is this?” A fifth players locked in. The Striker was puzzled when he looked at it. This fifth player was a Level 31 Assassin called Zero Kills. He hadn’t heard of such a player.

“Zero Kills?” Jiang You was also puzzled. He quickly sent Cold Night a message. Cold Night didn’t know either.

。

“Ready ready ready ready ready ready ready ready ready ready!” Flowing Tree typed again.

“If you don’t want to be exposed, then talk a bit less.” Ye Xiu said to Flowing Tree.

“Hm?”

‘That Endless Night over there is Zhang Xinjie.”

“You serious?” Huang Shaotian was surprised.

At this moment, everyone clicked ready and the team competition began. They quickly entered the battlefield and the map Lava Cemetery was randomly chosen.

“You serious?” After entering the map, Huang Shaotian asked again.

“No. You keep on chatting!” Ye Xiu said.

Usually, Huang Shaotian would begin typing crazily into the public chat as soon as he entered, but this time he resisted. As for that Zero Kills, he impatiently rushed up to battle.

“Hey, this bro’s so impatient. Who is he?’ Huang Shaotian asked.

“No idea.” Ye Xiu said.

“No idea?” Huang Shaotian didn’t understand.

“We didn’t have enough players, so a random person joined.” Ye Xiu said.

Everyone went crazy. Ye Xiu didn’t put a password in his room, so anyone could join. Previously, the three spots had been flashing like crazy because whenever a person joined, Ye Xiu would kick him. He did that to keep Steamed Bun Invasion and Huang Shaotian’s spot. After they joined, he didn’t care. As a result, the next random person who joined was this Assassin, Zero Kills.

As for Tyrannical Ambition, they were the ones at stake. If they won, they didn’t get anything, but if they lost, they would lose a lot of precious materials. Who else would accept these conditions?

“Even though that Flowing Tree is low-leveled, the reports say he isn’t weak. As for that Assassin, I have no idea. But in order to participate in this match, his strength shouldn’t be looked down on.” Jiang You analyzed.

“Look, that Assassin’s coming.” The Striker called. The Assassin, Zero Kills, had left the team and rushed forward.

“What type of strategy is this?’ Zhang Xinjie wondered, when Zero Kills suddenly stopped and turned back.

“He’s going back now?’ Tyrannical Ambition’s players were utterly confused.

Chapter 239 – First Target

Tyrannical Ambition watched as Zero Kills rushed forward and then suddenly retreated. Just as they were standing there stunned, an even more surprising event occurred. The Assassin, who was running back to Lord Grim’s group, suddenly disappeared in front of their eyes.

“What happened?” The Striker asked in astonishment. He even thought his computer had broken or something.

“He’s out!” Jiang You called. Zero Kills suddenly rose up from the ground, but quickly fell back down soon after, disappearing yet again. The distance was too far, so they couldn’t see clearly. However, it seemed like a flame had appeared on Zero Kill’s body…….

“No way, right???” Besides Zhang Xinjie, everyone yelled in surprise.

Following their yells, Zero Kills once again rose from the ground, except this time, he didn’t fall down. Instead, his body glowed white. He was currently being healed by a Cleric skill.

“Could he have accidentally fallen into the lava?” The Striker started.

“And he wasn’t even been able to jump out the first time?” The Blade Master also found it hard to believe.

Lava Cemetery was similar to Boneyard; coffins, gravestones, dried-up trees were the main backdrops. The difference was that Lava Cemetery had countless rivers engraved into the map. Some of these rivers were deep, while some of them were shallow and some were wide, while others were narrow. Also, instead of water, lava flowed through them. If a player jumped into one of them, they would immediately take Burn damage. Even after they jumped out, they would still take damage for five extra seconds.

“To have actually dropped into the lava, is this guy stupid?” The Sharpshooter said. They hadn’t considered such a low-leveled mistake.

“Maybe it was just a mistake.” The Striker couldn’t believe it.

“Even so, twice?” The Blade Master replied.

“Anything’s possible.” The Striker didn’t want to look down on this Assassin since he felt it was necessary to have this type of attitude.

“Okay, enough. Just don’t be careless!” Jiang You said.

At this moment, Zhang Xinjie finally spoke. He directly commanded them: “X Formation. Striker and Sharpshooter left, Blade Master and Elementalist right. Ten steps.”

X Formation was similar to the five dots tile in Mahjong. The Striker and Blade master would be in the front on the left and right while the Sharpshooter and Elementalist would be in the back. The four quickly took formation ten steps long, while Zhang Xinjie stood in the middle.

“Forward!” Zhang Xinjie ordered. The five players maintained formation and rushed forward. Zhang Xinjie stayed in the middle and observed the other side’s movements closely.

On the other side, Ye Xiu had first yelled for Zero Kills to stop. He then watched as the guy dropped into the lava and even had to try twice to jump out of it. The burn effect continued to lower Zero Kill’s health, so Ye Xiu had to immediately heal him.

This guy didn’t seem very good! Ye Xiu sighed. It would have been good if they had randomly gotten an expert, but his luck today clearly wasn’t good.

“Bro, you’re so impatient!” Huang Shaotian’s Flowing Tree went up and laughed at him.

The Assassin was also scared. After seeing his health recover, he let out a sigh: “Didn’t one of you say to hurry up and finish this quickly?”

“Remember his voice. Don’t listen to anything he says.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck!” Huang Shaotian wasn’t happy.

“Who said that?” Zero Kills was still asking.

“The one next to you.” Ye Xiu said.

Zero Kills looked at Flowing Tree and then said, “Level 27? Stupid noob. If you don’t know what you’re talking about, then don’t say it, okay?”

“F*ck me. This f*cking noob actually dares call me a noob?”

“Okay, calm down! Everyone get ready. The enemies are coming.” Ye Xiu said. The two immediately quieted down and focused. The other side had begun to move. They had dispersed and were now heading towards them.

“X Formation, huh. What do we do?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“Charge straight down the middle!” Ye Xiu said.

“Good. Simple and direct.” Huang Shaotian praised.

“How could it be simple.” Ye Xiu laughed, “Follow me!”

Steamed Bun Invasion immediately jumped forward and followed behind Lord Grim.

“Be careful. Don’t fall into the lava.” Ye Xiu reminded again. The team’s skill levels weren’t matched, so he had to warn them of every little thing.

The two sides both headed towards the middle of the map. Who knew how many channels they had jumped over? Just from this, the difference between each player’s mechanics could be seen. The other players easily jumped over them, while Zero Kills, on the other hand, had to jump extremely carefully. He was clearly finding it difficult and if things went on like this, he’d drop out from their group early, where as Tyrannical Ambition went forward neatly and smoothly.

“Slow down. Slow down.” Ye Xiu could only call out. The team slowed down to match with Zero Kill’s speed.

So slow…… Jiang You and the others clearly saw that they were going faster than the other side. It seemed as if the other side weren’t as good as they were on this map. Their morale was immediately boosted and they jumped over the rivers of lava joyfully.

“Pay attention to the Launcher!” Zhang Xinjie warned when they got into the Launcher’s range. Cleansing Mist hadn’t yet acted, but Tyrannical Ambition were already on guard.

Lord Grim’s team was all over the place, but as they approached, they began converging closer to the center. Zhang Xinjie immediately saw through it and shouted: “Front two back three!”

Jiang You and the other experts understood this command. The Blade Master and Striker slowed down and moved towards each other. The Sharpshooter and Elementalist caught up and stood beside Endless Night.

“They changed formations.” Huang Shaotian called.

“I can see.” Ye Xiu said, “Launcher, get ready.”

Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist lifted her gun as the two sides grew closer and closer. Now, there was only one final river of lava left between them. No one said anything. Aside from the sounds of the flowing lava, only footsteps could be heard.

Ye Xiu and Zhang Xinjie watched each other’s movements. Lord Grim’s party were now in the Sharpshooter and the Elementalist’s range.

Neither side attacked yet since they were both waiting for the most optimal time. Whoever seized the opportunity first would take the advantage.

“Fire!”

“Dodge!”

Both sides shouted. One side quietly sent their party the message, while the other side shouted it. The two orders were less than a second apart.

Cleansing Mist’s cannon immediately fired three Anti-Tank Missiles.

Tyrannical Ambition’s players had already prepared themselves. When the cannon fired, Zhang Xinjie immediately shouted the command and the team separated.

The Anti-Tank Missiles went through the enemy team’s formation and none of them took damage. Lord Grim, Flowing Tree, Steamed Bun Invasion, and Zero Kills quickly rushed forward and about to jump over the river of lava. During this moment, Cleansing Mist fired a Laser Rifle, attacking the two players on the right side. Tyrannical Ambition’s team had temporarily been split in two so Ye Xiu’s team took the opportunity to quickly attack Zhang Xinjie’s Cleric.

Zhang Xinjie chuckled at this.

This Lord Grim’s skill level wasn’t bad and he had seized the most optimal timing to attack. However, it wasn’t that he wasn’t able to grasp that timing. It was that he had intentionally given the opportunity to Lord Grim. The timing he had needed was now.

“Forward!”

Another message flashed in the team’s party chat. The Blade Master was already prepared for this. He used a Sword Draw and sliced his sword through the air towards the river of lava Lord Grim was currently jumping over.

Also at this moment, the Elementalist cast a Raging Flames. The Striker followed behind the Blade Master and used an Eagle Stamp towards Lord Grim.

Their two three formation wasn’t a normal spread. The Striker and Blade Master had dodged to the left, protecting the Cleric and the Sharpshooter and the Elementalist had dodged to the right. This type of formation allowed them to counter attack effectively.

Ye Xiu’s first target was Zhang Xinjie’s Endless Night.

Zhang Xinjie’s first target was Lord Grim too.

Chapter 240 – All-Star Tactic

In mid-air, Ye Xiu saw the sword aura along with fire rising up from the Raging Flames. Lord Grim suddenly turned and flung open his Thousand Chance Umbrella.

Aerial Fire!

Just as he was about to be hit, he used an Aerial Fire to move in the air. His original targets switched from the left wing to the right wing.

The left wing had the Striker and Blade Master, protecting the Cleric Endless Night.

The right wing had Jiang You’s Crowd Lover and the Sharpshooter.

Jiang You’s Raging Flames had almost connected with Lord Grim, while the Sharpshooter was in a standoff with Cleansing Mist, when Lord Grim suddenly turned and headed towards them. They knew of Lord Grim’s strength and immediately panicked a bit, retreating.

On the left wing, the Striker had stepped down with an Eagle Stamp, but the target had suddenly flown away. All he could do was watch as his character landed on the opposite bank. Unfortunately, who was standing on the opposite bank? Flowing Tree! Huang Shaotian was one of the best players in the pro-scene at seizing opportunities.

The Level 27 Blade Master short hopped and raised his sword. A sword aura flitted by, brushing by the Striker’s body. The Striker hadn’t been slashed flying away, but his pathing had been changed. When he landed, he stepped onto the edge of the bank. The Striker wanted to use a Wall Jump, but how could Huang Shaotian let of this opportunity go?

A sword light fell and smacked the Striker’s head.

The Striker didn’t have any moves left and fell into the river of lava. The lava enveloped his body and his health immediately began burning away. The Striker grumbled about his hardships and hastily tried to run back to land.

Seeing that the Striker had jumped into the river, Zhang Xinjie had to save him. He raised his cross and began chanting. As for the Blade Master, his only long-range skill, Sword Draw, was on cooldown, so he could only stand and watch from the side.

Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t stay idle. He jumped over and wanted to throw a Brick at Endless Night, when Flowing Tree moved in front to block him: “No use, he’s too far.”

“It should be enough, no?” Steamed Bun Invasion had some sense.

“Just a bit off. He’s intentionally baiting you.” Huang Shaotian said.

“How evil!” Steamed Bun Invasion immediately believed him. As a result, he threw the Brick towards the Striker instead.

The Striker hastily dodged it. Steamed Bun Invasion shouted angrily: “How dare you dodge!” and sent a Sand Toss at him.

The Striker was bewildered. Why shouldn’t he dodge? Dodging around left and right, the Striker was finally able to return to the bank. He immediately jumped, but then noticed a dazzling shot out of the corner of his eye. Cleansing Mist had sent him a shot.

“F*ck!” The Striker was hit tumbling by the shot and fell back into the river of lava.

“Jump!” Zhang Xinjie’s voice suddenly resounded.

The Striker heard the command and without even checking the situation, jumped up. Endless Night’s Sacred Fire showered down and began burning on the banks of the river.

The timing was perfect. Huang Shaotian had no choice but to retreat to escape from the white flames. And at this moment, the Blade Master’s Sword Draw was off cooldown. He timed it well with the Sacred Fire and used it to try and push the enemies back another step.

There’s a small hole, but there shouldn’t be enough time….. Just as Zhang Xinjie was thinking this, he saw a sword light flash by, a Sword Draw.

The formation he had used should have been able to completely rescue the Striker, in theory. But it required three players to coordinate. If a single player was just slightly too slow, then it wouldn’t be guaranteed. But who could take advantage of such a small opening?

Zhang Xinjie had originally thought like this, but now he knew his thinking was wrong.

Flowing Tree’s Sword Draw had been thrown out slightly late, but his target was also slightly closer. Between his and the Blade Master’s Sword Draw, which one would reach first?

If the Blade Master was faster, then his Sword Draw would be interrupted. He had to use it while dodging the Sacred Fire though. Would he be faster?

In reality, he had succeeded.

His Sword Light connected and the Striker was once again hit back into the river of lava.

The Blade Master’s Sword Draw had arrived just a step too late. After hitting the Striker, Flowing Tree quickly put his sword back and Guarded against the Blade Master’s attack.

“This person!” Zhang Xinjie’s face changed. Just from seeing this small detail, he could see that this was god-level microing. This Flowing Tree… who was he?

Even though the Blade Master’s Sword Draw hadn’t connected and the Striker wasn’t rescued, the Blade Master still continued forward with the plans Zhang Xinjie had made earlier. The Blade Master leaped up, his sword flashed, and a Falling Light Blade with him flew directly towards the opposite bank. The Sacred Fire there was an absolute protection. And at this moment, he suddenly heard Zhang Xinjie yell: “Not yet!”

“Ah?” The Blade Master had already flown over to the opposite bank. The Falling Light Blade crashed down and he saw Flowing Tree jump back to dodge the shockwave from his attack. Closely following, Flowing Tree’s feet also suddenly shot out a shockwave.

“A…. Falling Light Blade as well? To use it like that……” The Blade Master was astonished, but couldn’t change the reality of his character being knocked down by the shockwave. He immediately tried to use a Quick Recover, but seeing where he would land, he immediately began crying. Once he fell into the river, what was the point in Quick Recovering?

The Blade Master helplessly watched as he partnered with the Striker. The two burned in the river as they tried their best to move left and right to escape, but their shameless opponents were standing by the bank. As soon as they saw them jump, they would immediately swat them down. And just like this, these two players would be burned to death in the river.

The two glowed red and also white. Endless Night had been healing them non-stop. But they couldn’t last forever.

Zhang Xinjie was already seeing that things weren’t looking good. He was currently too busy to handle the Sharpshooter and the Elementalist. And those two’s situation looked even worse.

Crowd Lover was now in the lava as well, joining the crowd. That Sharpshooter was grabbed by Lord Grim and then directly thrown over.

At this moment, four of Tyrannical Ambition’s five-man team were struggling in the river, unable to get out.

Tactics? Zhang Xinjie had been watching the opponent’s pathing, movements, and intents the entire time.

But, now that he thought about it, was the other side even using tactics? It didn’t look like it. From the start, the other side had just rushed up and then……. things were like this now.

Lord Grim and Flowing Tree were clearly far more skilled than Jiang You’s group. That Launcher couldn’t be looked down on either. Her control and coordination were extremely outstanding and repeatedly shot the struggling team back down into the river.

As for that Zero Kills, what had he done? Nothing. Absolutely nothing. Steamed Bun Invasion had even thrown a few Bricks and some Sand Tosses, but that Zero Kills had done absolutely nothing. Oh, you guys are going that way, okay, I’ll go that way too. He was just cheering them on.

If this had to be called a tactic, then it would be called a Star Tactic. It didn’t matter what strategy or tactic you used, those two ridiculous guys were enough to crush you…….

A sudden, terrifying thought popped up in Zhang Xinjie’s head. The thought made a lot of sense, but he didn’t want to believe it.

Chapter 241 – The Joke’s Gone Too Far

Zhang Xinjie understood exactly how skilled Jiang You and the others were. As the most skilled players of Tyrannical Ambition, they might not be good enough to be pros, but they weren’t so bad that they could be bullied by just anyone.

But right now, the four were struggling in the river of lava. They were pretty much being toyed with by their opponents. They were trying their hardest too. Who knew how many times they’d already tried jumping up. The four tried gathering together, separating, diversion tactics, hiding and then popping out, etc. They tried everything, but nothing worked. Their opponents’ defenses were impenetrable. Their opponents wanted to wait for them to burn themselves to death in this river of lava.

Their health slowly burned away. And as for Zhang Xinjie, after leading them through several failed attempts, all he could do was run around. Seeing this, the four players understood that even Zhang Xinjie was at wit’s end.

Seeing that Zhang Xinjie was still healing them, even though the four players were already exhausted,all they could do was continue trying to escape.

“Run! Run far far away!!” Jiang You shouted.

One on each side, the Sharpshooter and Blade Master ran along the banks as far as they could. This was already their final gamble. By splitting far apart, they would leave the Cleric’s healing range and then there would be no way of coordinating with each other whatsoever. Without the healing from the Cleric, they would eventually be burned to death.

However besides this, what other method was left?

Zhang Xinjie bitterly laughed. He originally wanted to say something, but he stopped himself.

Jiang You’s method truly was stupid. Their opponents had experts and were superior to them in 1v1 scenarios. What Jiang You was doing was playing to their opponent’s strengths and their weaknesses. But since the situation was already like this and Jiang You and the others were still trying hard, it wouldn’t be a good idea to stop them.

And thus, Zhang Xinjie didn’t say anything. He continued to heal the members that were in range. Facing the unspecialized Lord Grim, who could be both close-range and long-range, he was finally able to witness the ever-changing Thousand Chance Umbrella. The two players were gradually getting farther and farther away and their opponents also had two players follow them, Cleansing Mist and Flowing Tree.

Everything was as Zhang Xinjie expected. This type of tactic hadn’t brought anything good to the table. The Blade Master and Sharpshooter were still being suppressed by Cleansing Mist and Flowing Tree just like before.

Zhang Xinjie sighed. He already knew the battle was already over. Cleansing Mist’s bullets fired and the Sharpshooter died, the Blade Master closely following after.

Crowd Lover and the Striker were under Endless Night’s healing, but they wouldn’t be able to stay alive forever.

“We’ve lost.” Zhang Xinjie typed the message into the public chat.

“Ha ha, I agree.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Who are you?” Zhang Xinjie asked.

“Just as who you think I am, an expert.” Ye Xiu said.

Zhang Xinjie was silent.

Ye Qiu, Huang Shaotian, Su Mucheng. These three names had flashed by in his head long ago, but he was a cautious person. If he wasn’t 100% certain, he wouldn’t be able to easily come to a conclusion.

If they really were these three, then Zhang Xinjie had to admit that he had played the joke too far this time. Trying to beat those three with just Jiang You and the others was impossible.

He had originally believed that the coordination and synergy between Jiang You and his team were their advantages.

But, in the Glory pro-scene, in the seven completed seasons, Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng had won Best Partners four times. The three times that they hadn’t won the award was because Su Mucheng had yet to entered the pro-scene.

Facing the two players with the greatest synergy in the entire pro-scene, how could Jiang You and his team’s synergy be an advantage? Hilarious.

If it really was like this, then Zhang Xinjie would feel very embarrassed, but he wouldn’t be able to take back his assumption.

He had intuitively felt that they were Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng, but he had no definitive proof. As for that Flowing Tree, his playing completely exposed his god-level skill. But once he got on stage, he quieted down. Before, the reports said that he was very talkative, so why was he quiet now?

Were they different people?

Talking a lot wasn’t his habit, but something he did on and off?

Or maybe he really was Huang Shaotian, but he intentionally hid his specialty?

Maybe he doesn’t want to be exposed? He’s afraid of being seen through? By me? Speaking of this, do they know who I am?

When Zhang Xinjie thought, he didn’t ignore any possibility. He thought, while quietly watching Lord Grim and the others. Crowd lover and the Striker had already jumped out but they were still burning. The two were silent; their current moods were obvious.

“If there’s nothing you guys want to talk about, then let’s leave?” Ye Xiu said.

Is that Ye Qiu’s voice? Zhang Xinjie tried hard to recall. Voice chat wasn’t allowed in pro-matches, so he wasn’t very familiar with Ye Qiu’s voice.

“Lord Grim……” Jiang You grinded his teeth. He really wanted to say some bad words.

“Are we going to meet up again at Line Canyon?” Ye Xiu laughed.

Jiang You really wanted to jump over the river and teach Lord Grim a lesson but he didn’t move because he clearly knew that he would lose if he talked.

“You just wait!” Jiang You threatened.

“Ha ha, I’ll wait. You can come bet with me anytime you’d like. I welcome you to try again.” Ye Xiu said.

“Let’s leave!” Zhang Xinjie left and the system announced that Lord Grim’s side was the winner.

“Ha ha ha ha, Zhang Xinjie is nothing! I can’t help but say that he was too naive. To think he’d be able to block me! Did you see my beautiful swordplay?”’ Huang Shaotian couldn’t help but begin chattering once he saw that the other side had left.

“Yeah, not bad. “ Ye Xiu said.

“Not bad? F*ck, let me tell you. At that time, the number of players who could do what I did can’t be more than ten.” Huang Shaotian said.

“I should be one of those ten, no?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Of course.”

“Then I don’t understand why you’re trying to brag.”

“Let’s see who’ll win! I’ll go and switch accounts!” Huang Shaotian called.

“Your beautiful swordplay definitely aroused Zhang Xinjie’s suspicions. But with his personality, he won’t come to a conclusion without solid evidence. If you log out of Flowing Tree and go onto Troubling Rain, are you trying to provide him proof?” Ye Xiu asked.

Huang Shaotian stared blankly.

The Assassin Zero Kills also stared blankly. Seeing the large list of items they had won from the info list made him thoroughly stunned. He hadn’t noticed that this had been a match with bets.

“Let’s all leave too!” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah…… that……” Zero Kills muttered. He wanted to ask what all those items were about and whether it was split between members.

“Thanks, brother! I’ll gift you this!” Ye Xiu prompted a trade with Zero Kills.

Zero Kills accepted and looked. The other side had unexpectedly put up a Level 30 Purple Twin-Tailed Swords.

Zero Kills happily accepted it. He hadn’t done anything in the match and won a Purple weapon. Was such good luck even possible? Zero Kills hadn’t yet fully thought it through yet, when the others left.

Chapter 242 – My Mistake

Tyrannical Ambition’s work studio was extremely quiet. Even though there were only three players participating inside, the others had all been watching.

As the guild leader, Jiang You felt somewhat lost after losing. The battle from the start to finish had simply gone too far from what he had expected. With Zhang Xinjie’s help, he thought that the conflict between Tyrannical Ambition and Lord Grim in the tenth server would finally end.

In the end, not only did the conflict not end, but the conflict escalated. After exiting the field, Jiang You had to resist smashing the table. After all, Zhang Xinjie had participated in this fight. Becoming furious wouldn’t look good for Zhang Xinjie.

Being thrown into the river of lava and burning to death was a type of noob-stomping strategy. We had a higher chance of winning?? Jiang You silently cursed a few words. He hadn’t seen any of the advantages that Zhang Xinjie had talked about for them. If Zhang Xinjie wasn’t Zhang Xinjie, he would have started shouting angrily long ago.

“My mistake.” Someone suddenly said in the studio. Everyone’s gazes shifted to the speaker, Zhang Xinjie.

“I vastly underestimated the other side’s strength. Whether it was Lord Grim, Flowing Tree, or Cleansing Mist, all of their individual skills are very high.” Zhang Xinjie said, “In that match, just the three of them were enough; the other two weren’t important.”

“How high exactly?” Jiang You couldn’t help but ask.

“Maybe we should try to further understand their skill.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Further understand?”

“Bet with them again.”

“Again?” Jiang You jumped up in fright.

“He said that we could bet with him anytime, no?” Zhang Xinjie said.

“He did say that, but we……”

“I’ll bring people over.” Zhang Xinjie said.

Everyone in the work studio was shocked. Zhang Xinjie was going to bring the pro-players from the team over? Was Lord Grim really so strong that the pro-team needed to come out?

Jiang You immediately lit up with excitement.

This time, they would most certainly win! He immediately thought. If Lord Grim and the others were so strong that even Tyranny wasn’t able to bring them down, then what were they doing in the tenth server? They could just enter directly as a pro-team and slaughter their way to become Champions.

“When?” Jiang You excitedly asked.

“In two days.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Okay!” Jiang You immediately replied and went to contact Lord Grim.

“He agreed.” He quickly received a reply.

“Good, I’ll be going off then.” Zhang Xinjie nodded his head and then left.

The match had ended quickly. It hadn’t even been 10 when Zhang Xinjie returned to the team and saw that the lights were still on in the practice room.

Zhang Xinjie walked over and saw Han Wenqing sitting in front of a computer, conducting a conventional practice with his Desert Dust.

Han Wenqing had his headphones on and was completely focused. The only sounds that could be heard in the practice room were the sounds of his keyboard tapping and mouse clicking. Zhang Xinjie quietly walked over behind him, but Han Wenqing didn’t notice.

Their practice was only ⅔ of the way done.

Desert Dust was Swift Running on the platform. He Z-Shook to avoid incoming arrows and then jumped over a deep trench and then rolled, dodged, and punched four floating balls. There was no longer a road in front of the platform; there were only a floating, moving rocks of different sizes.

Desert Dust didn’t hesitate and directly jumped and landed on top of a floating rock.

Without stopping, he continued jumping.

Onto the second, third, fourth…… Desert Dust continued to rush forward, quickly jumping forward, enough to make others gasp in amazement.

But Zhang Xinjie knew that things weren’t going that well. Desert Dust’s jumping rhythm had already gone awry. The problem might not have been from the jumping, but from the previous ⅔ of the practice. The slight mistimings from then might have finally taken its form here.

“Not enough time…..” Zhang Xinjie silently said to himself.

Desert Dust landed on another rock, but this time, he had to stop jumping because there were no more rocks for him to jump onto. He had to stand on the rock and wait for a bit.

But Han Wenqing continued to move forward following his style: aggressive and fearless. However, the rock he was jumping towards was off and his character brushed right past it.

Han Wenqing angrily tapped his keyboard. He should have already known the outcome.

Desert Dust fell and the screen turned black. The practice hadn’t been completed yet, but a progress bar and time record appeared as well as the reflection of Zhang Xinjie, who was behind him.

Han Wenqing turned his head, but Zhang Xinjie didn’t say anything. This wasn’t his first time seeing this.

Han Wenqing, the King of Fighting, Desert Dust. He had lost three times, but never gave up. Finally, in the fourth season of Glory, he defeated the previously undefeated Ye Qiu and Team Excellent Era. He had personally buried the reign of Excellent Era and became a legendary top-tier God. However, from the start of his career till now, his reaction speed and hand speed had already declined greatly.

The previous drill had all kinds of obstructions that required the user to attack, move, dodge, roll, jump, etc. to overcome. It was a drill that tested everything.

It wasn’t that Han Wenqing wasn’t able to complete the drill, but rather it was just that he was no longer able to reach his previous record.

Han Wenqing was still fighting against aging. He knew he wasn’t able to jump onto that rock anymore, but he still went ahead and did it. Because of this, Zhang Xinjie couldn’t say anything to comfort him. Even more so, Han Wenqing didn’t need any comforting words.

Han Wenqing didn’t need to do any explaining to Zhang Xinjie because he only turned around.

“How’d it go?” Han Wenqing asked. He knew what Zhang Xinjie had gone to do in the afternoon.

“We lost.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Lost?’ Han Wenqing’s mood slid down. He might not be in the best condition of his career, but his stern eyes remained the same.

“The opponents’ strength far exceeded my expectations.”

“How strong?”

“Pro-level.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“What a joke. Pro-level players going to that server to play?”

“I went too.”

“Let me see the recording.” Han Wenqing said.

Zhang Xinjie contacted Jiang You and had him send the recording. The recording began to play. There was nothing to look at on Tyrannical Ambition’s side, so Han Wenqing put the camera directly onto their opponents and then saw Zero Kills fall into the river of lava.

“What is this? How’d you guys lose to this type of opponent?” Han Wenqing was clearly angry.

“That person can be ignored.” Zhang Xinjie said.

Han Wenqing continued to watch.

The fight in the middle of the river of lava unfolded. The movements and tactics of the two sides were all common knowledge for the experienced Han Wenqing.

He watched up until Lord Grim used Aerial Fire in midair to dodge the combined assault Zhang Xinjie had put in order.

“Unspecialized? His speed is quite good.” Han Wenqing said. Zhang Xinjie knew that Han Wenqing was talking about Lord Grim’s reaction speed and hand speed.

Han Wenqing rarely praised anyone so his “quite good” remark was a very high appraisal.

And then Flowing Tree’s sword slash. Han Wenqing even paused the video there and replayed it three times.

Zhang Xinjie didn’t say anything. The most astonishing part of the battle occurred right here.

“This type of movement…..” Even Han Wenqing had no words.

However, this was just a video recording. Even though this person was able to do this, how many times could he do it successfully? Was it real skill, or was it luck? The answer couldn’t be found just from this. This movement truly was God-level, but to immediately view this player as a God-level player would be too careless. Zhang Xinjie understood this and Han Wenqing obviously did too, which was why he watched it three times before continuing.

And then the four players were repeatedly thrown into the river of lava.

The more Han Wenqing watched, the angrier he became. He closed the video. There was nothing else to see. The outcome was obvious. Forcing the four players to stay in the river of lava, there was nothing amazing that was needed to do that.

“Flowing Tree didn’t say anything during the fight, but before it, he was very talkative.”

“What are you trying to say?’ Han Wenqing said.

Zhang Xinjie didn’t definitively conclude anything. He just added: “Lord Grim’s weapon is completely suitable to unspecialized characters. It’s a weapon that allows the class to be viable. Cleansing Mist might not have done anything eye-catching, but you can see her extremely high-level knowledge of tactics and her ability to coordinate with the team, especially with Lord Grim.

“Even with all this, you guys lost a bit too badly, no?”

“It was my mistake.” Zhang Xinjie replied.

Chapter 243 – Rescuing Steamed Bun

Han Wenqing opened up the recording he had just closed. This time, the camera was focused on Lord Grim. He fast forwarded several places and only stopped to carefully look when Lord Grim switched weapon forms.

The camera could be moved freely and zoomed in. The different forms of Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella were obvious at a glance.

“Unprecedented.” Han Wenqing said. He had seen all kinds of weird equipment and play styles, but he had never even heard of a weapon like the Thousand Chance Umbrella.

“This type of weapon shouldn’t have appeared in the new server. Jiang You discussed this with me. He had suspected that someone from a Club was testing this Silver weapon, but after seeing Lord Grim’s attitude in-game, it doesn’t appear to be so.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Then what do you think?’ Han Wenqing asked.

“I think we need to take another step in order to gather more information.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“You’ve already come to a conclusion right?” Han Wenqing said.

Zhang Xinjie didn’t say anything.

“This weapon was clearly made for an unspecialized to use. However, possessing this type of weapon only resolves half of the problems that an unspecialized has. Besides having a strong character, the person controlling it must be skilled as well.” Han Wenqing said, “At present, who do you think is the most suitable for playing an unspecialized?”

“Uh……”

“Without a doubt, Yu Wenzhou. He’s good overall and even though his hand speed isn’t that good, he should be more than good enough to support his team with this class.” Han Wenqing said.

“Ah?” Zhang Xinjie was somewhat startled, but after thinking about it some more, he felt like it made sense. Flowing Tree was truly too similar to Huang Shaotian so it wouldn’t be surprising if he was with Yu Wenzhou. Testing the Silver weapon could be one of Club Blue Rain’s goals, but…..”

“But from the guild leader’s reports, Lord Grim is on every day for a very long time, and it doesn’t seem like anyone is substituting in for him. Whether it was Yu Wenzhou or anyone in the Alliance, no one had that kind of time on their hands. In reality…….there’s one other person…….” Zhang Xinjie was unable to resist giving his uncertain conclusion.

“Are you saying.. Ye Qiu?” Han Wenqing suddenly laughed coldly when he said this name, “He’s already been kicked out of the Alliance. Why would he appear again?”

Ye Qiu’s retirement made many fans surprised and sad, but Han Wenqing felt disdainful instead.

“Coward.” This was the comment that Han Wenqing gave when news of Ye Qiu’s retirement came. Zhang Xinjie felt that, underneath the disdain, Han Wenqing was probably also hiding a bit of unwillingness and loneliness. Even though right now there were a few competitors who wouldn’t lose to Ye Qiu right now, Ye Qiu was special. The number of times the two had fought was also a record in the Glory Alliance.

“What plan did you come up with?” Han Wenqing continued to stay on task.

“I set up another appointment for a match. I was thinking about bringing a few team members to come over.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Oh? What accounts do you have on hand?” Han Wenqing asked.

“There’s a Striker.”

“I can go and take a look.” Han Wenqing said. His gaze continued to stay on Lord Grim in the recording. Even though the most brilliant play had been enacted by Flowing Tree, Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie’s main focus was still on Lord Grim’s unspecialized.

In game.

They had unexpectedly lost the match, so Cold Night had to prepare the materials. The materials they had bitterly gathered up were taken away by Lord Grim. He felt even worse than Jiang You did.

However, he was quickly told that Zhang Xinjie was preparing to bring the pro team over, which brought his confidence back up. However, he still had to gather the materials for the new bets. Cold Night sent players over to the market, while telling those running dungeons to gather up the materials. As a result, he didn’t have time to waste on searching and pursuing Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng were residing in a small town. Steamed Bun Invasion, on the other hand, was in Congee City and was being watched by who knows how many people. As soon as Steamed Bun Invasion left the city, there were many people there who were waiting to welcome him.

“Come out a bit more. A bit more!” Some were silently thinking in their heads. Right now, Steamed Bun Invasion was too close to the safe area. He just had to take a few steps and he’d be safe.

In the end, Steamed Bun Invasion only walked a bit forward and marched left and right two steps. He laughed out loud: “Ha ha ha ha, you noobs. Did you really think I’d fall for your trap?” After saying this, he walked back into the city.

Everyone there spat blood in fury, but what could they do? If there were too few people, they wouldn’t be able to stop him; too many people and it’d be like now. Even a blind person could tell something wasn’t right.

“Senior, what do I do? I can’t go out.” Steamed Bun Invasion appeared arrogant, but he had secretly gone and asked Ye Xiu for help. He had only been able to notice something was off because of Ye Xiu’s warnings.

“We’re coming to get you. When things become messy, squeeze your way out of there.” Ye Xiu directed.

“Gotcha!” Steamed Bun Invasion set up a vendor booth inside of the city. He ran dungeons every day and Blue equipment often dropped. The way their parties worked was that if no one needed the item, then whoever wanted it could have it. Because of this, Steamed Bun Invasion picked up quite a few items. Right now, he was selling them under the name “The Greatest Items in the Universe.”

The players outside could only grind their teeth and wait. This guy was just standing there loftily, mocking them. He was even chatting happily with the nearby players.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng left the small town and arrived outside of the city. Without saying a word, they began their rescue operation.

Ye Xiu’s unspecialized and Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist jumped out into the open and each fired Anti-Tank Missiles towards the players who were waiting outside of the city.

“Lord Grim!!” Everyone immediately began counter-attacking amidst the smoke, but the two didn’t move closer and stayed on the outside, firing from afar.

PKing outside of the city walls was a very common occurrence. Many battles could take place at once. In the Arena, winning or losing would only account for points and statistics. Apart from this, there weren’t any rewards or losses, which was why revenge matches usually weren’t decided within the Arena, but rather outside of the city walls. Whoever died could come out and fight once again.

At this moment, there were two players dueling, but compared to Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng’s battle, their match was nothing. Over there were two players sneak attacking a group of a hundred. Even more so, it was done by the famous Lord Grim, which immediately caught their attention. The two decided to stop fighting and first, watch the commotion before continuing.

This type of commotion was the opportunity Ye Xiu was giving to Steamed Bun Invasion.

Many players in the city had gotten the news and came to watch. Steamed Bun Invasion received Ye Xiu’s message and followed the plan. He had even incited the two vendors next to him and ran out of the city together with them.

The players, who were watching Steamed Bun Invasion, saw him and two others suddenly mix into the crowd. After that, which one was Steamed Bun Invasion? They didn’t know. They just didn’t know!

The players who were watching pursued, looking madly into it. In Glory, there wasn’t a mark that you could put on a player’s ID and players couldn’t do a bird’s-eye view. In this type of crowd, there were way too many players and the IDs were all in a jumbled mess. There was no way to tell who was who. At this moment, they were all cursing at Glory’s setup.

Steamed Bun Invasion hid in the crowd and moved towards the outside while looking around, but the crowd also made it difficult for Steamed Bun Invasion to figure out where he was going.

Finally, Steamed Bun Invasion saw the guild players fighting with Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist in the distance. The two were fighting back to back, shooting around. The guild players were rushing from every direction to surround them and were currently contracting.

“Senior, you’ve been surrounded!” Steamed Bun Invasion was about to come help.

“Oh? You got out? Okay, head towards an empty place. We’ll be following closely behind.” Ye Xiu replied.

Chapter 244 – Destroying Their Confidence

The guild members thought that they had Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist under control as their encirclement was going smoothly, but at this moment, Ye Xiu received Steamed Bun Invasion’s report of his successful exit out of the city.

“Let’s go.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Su Mucheng replied. Her Cleansing Mist flipped her hands and used an Aerial Fire, flying backwards along the flat ground. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim used a Shadow Clone Technique. His real body was in front, waiting for her to arrive.

The guild members attacked from two sides and were currently forming a pocket. Sword auras flashed, bullets flew, and magic danced in the air in an attempt to block them.

“Ha ha, if you hadn’t gone and grouped up, then it’d have been better.” Ye Xiu said. The incoming missiles flew past the two of them. The occasional hits didn’t affect their movements too much.

As a result…….. the missiles flew from the left side to the right side and from the right side to the left side.

“Bang!!” Su Mucheng dubbed the sounds for them.

In the end…… the scene that they had been waiting for never arrived. The guild members were unorganized, spreading out like scattered sand last night and all of them learned about the importance of being a group now. Even though they wouldn’t obey each other’s orders, they were at least working together. After partying up, allies wouldn’t take damage, so even if magic and explosions enveloped both sides, none of them would take damage.

“Lame……” Su Mucheng mumbled. She turned her cannon and fired towards the players who attempted to block her.

Because they were trying to block two of them, the three players who had come forward to face them, ducked to avoid the attack. However, Lord Grim rushed forward and blasted them away with a Falling Flower Palm.

The players on the left and right had been planning on doing a pincer attack, but one of them was grabbed and flung back with a Back Throw. The grabbed player was thrown down onto the ground, and by the time they returned to their positions, Lord Grim was already gone.

There was a flash and Cleansing Mist chased after him with an Aerial Fire. Their Aerial Fires connected, and the two flew back some distance.

To chase or not to chase? The guild members immediately began thinking.

Should they silently return back to the city in shame, or should they clench their teeth and chase them non-stop?

The orders quickly came.

The final decision was to dispatch a few players to watch where they were going. Thus, a few players jumped out from the main army and chased after Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist.

They wouldn’t chase too closely. They weren’t planning on fighting because they knew that fighting them would only result in their deaths.

Find out where they were. That was the order their guilds had given them.

They often knew where they were, but what was the point? The two showed up on their own. They came and then left, but their orders were still to pinpoint their locations.

The players there didn’t know how to describe their current feelings. Doing something over and over again was scary. Doing something that they didn’t know if there would be any gain was even scarier. The guild members wished that it would end soon, but in reality, their wishes didn’t come true.

The players, who went to “understand their whereabouts”, followed Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist to a small village outside of Congee City. Here, they saw the two meet up with Steamed Bun Invasion. They immediately reported the news and the guilds would revise their strategy according to the news, but before they were able to come up with a plan, Lord Grim’s group took the initiative.

In the small village, the players were killed by an evil trick while searching for Lord Grim. Ye Xiu’s group had hidden themselves and then ambushed them when they got into their range.

Lord Grim’s whereabouts were once again unknown.

Reports of their whereabouts had been sent many times, but there was no progress among the guilds. This truly did make them unhappy and exhausted.

Reports from Line Canyon said that Lord Grim’s group had appeared. The guards at the entrances had been killed.

‘They’re going to Line Canyon now? It’s not 12 yet. Are they going to train there for a bit first? Or are they preparing to receive the two members who aren’t on yet?” someone said.

As a result, they began a great search in Line Canyon.

Another message came; a player in Fire Forest had been killed.

The guild players were about to go crazy……

Currently, their elites were Level 33, so of course they would begin looking out for the wild BOSS Fire Witch Cashew. Besides running the dungeons, a portion of the elites would come here to level and also look to see if the wild BOSS had spawned.

They really had found a BOSS. Unfortunately, it wasn’t the Fire Witch BOSS, but the Lord Grim BOSS.

The Lord Grim BOSS was very mighty. He could frontal assault, sneak attack, and flank. His aggro range was also extremely large and could wander around anywhere. He would automatically find players and then start attacking them.

Finding wild BOSSes were activities guilds did on their own. They wouldn’t work together and wouldn’t share the rewards. Only when their own guild members split up and looked, would they have the greatest probability of finding a BOSS!

After the various small groups in Fire Forest received the news, they immediately contacted each other and began to party up.

This made it easier for Lord Grim.

After only a short while, new reports came in. It was no longer two or three players dying; an entire party had been killed.

At that time, the team had been heading towards a place in the forest to converge. Unfortunately, they coincidentally bumped into Lord Grim and were immediately sent to converge at the city.

Fire Forest had already turned into a terror forest filled with death and misery. In this type of place, fleeing is the best option.

The elites began to evacuate from the forest. They were the future of their guilds and were delicate flowers that their guilds had worked hard to cultivate. They couldn’t let themselves be ravaged by Lord Grim. The big guilds dispatched their troops in preparation for storming Fire Forest.

In all of their gaming experiences, they had never encountered an opponent like Lord Grim.

As guilds, they would often say “If we see you, you’re dead.” to threaten others.

But for their current opponents, they were the ones dying.

Headaches. Besides headaches, there were only more headaches.

From yesterday until now, they had killed Soft Mist twice and Steamed Bun Invasion once, which comforted them a little, but compared to the sacrifices of their elites, their achievements were unable to close their injuries.

If these casualties hadn’t happened, then they wouldn’t have been so bitter. They might even be happy: “Look, even though we haven’t killed Lord Grim, our running around has controlled their movements and their leveling speed has slowed. Our goal has been achieved.”

This was true to a certain extent. The leveling speed of Ye Xiu’s group couldn’t compare to their previous speed. Their movements were being limited. What usually took them ten minutes, now took them twenty or maybe even more time.

This was why Ye Xiu chose to actively hunt them down. They couldn’t kill everyone, but they could hurt these guilds’ confidence and determination.

Because, in reality, all the guilds were still each other’s enemies. Those who hadn’t provoked him wouldn’t be touched. Ye Xiu would only attack the ones who were causing trouble. These elites would be dropping in levels, while the other guilds were still leveling up because they hadn’t participated in this movement.

These guilds’ casualties made them feel very unhappy about those other guilds who weren’t participating. Because of this, these guilds would begin to worry about their own development. Could they continue chasing after them like this with confidence?

Chapter 245 – A Hidden Agenda

The several guilds held hesitation and doubt in their hearts, they still continued with their actions. Over a hundred players had already stormed into Fire Forest.

Maps in Glory were huge. A hundred players sounded like a lot, but such an amount wouldn’t nearly be enough to cover the entire leveling area.

They didn’t dare to underestimate Lord Grim’s group. When the more than one hundred players rushed in, they formed parties of three to five, keeping close to each other. If they met Lord Grim, they could easily group together. Only after forming this type of arrangement did they feel safe enough to begin looking around Fire Forest for movements.

None of them were new to the game! All of the players that had been leveling in Fire Forest originally were undoubtedly the tenth server’s top players. These type of characters were practically raised by the guilds.

Seeing that these other players were focused on leveling, the pursuers bitterly looked at them in envy. At the same time, they were very unhappy that these guild members were just sitting there and enjoying the fruits of their hard work.

“Where’s Lord Grim?” The pursuers hadn’t found Lord Grim’s whereabouts and were grumbling left and right at their teammates.

“We haven’t found him, but at least that means that he’s trying to hide from us and doesn’t feel safe leveling. Our goal has been reached in the end, no?” Chen Yehui said to pacify everyone’s worried feelings. He himself wasn’t worried at all. This was the type of situation that he wanted to see. He even had thoughts of singing a song to honor the scene in front of him.

The big guilds all suffered some damage and Ye Qiu’s progress had been slowed. These two wins were too perfect for him.

“There isn’t even a place for him to level safely. What is he trying to accomplish by staying online? He might as well just log out.” someone said. If Lord Grim went offline, they wouldn’t have to work as hard and could happily level up. But this guy refused to leave, forcing them to keep on searching and asking for his whereabouts.

“Let’s not waste our time. We should fight monsters while looking!” someone suggested. As a result, the over one hundred soldiers hunted down Goblins together in Fire Forest. However, with so many players, each player only got a handful of experience.

And as for Ye Xiu’s group? They were still in Fire Forest. Fire Forest’s terrain was perfect for hiding and Ye Xiu had been thinking of using the terrain to hunt down these over one hundred players, but after seeing their formation, he knew that hunting them down was too unrealistic.

They were still a group of veterans. Now that they understood his skill level, they wouldn’t leave an opening for him to use.

“Should we leave?” Su Mucheng asked.

“There’s no hurry.” Ye Xiu said, while attacking nearby monsters. With only three players in their party, the amount of experience gained from killing monsters was normal, so their efficiency was much higher than that of the hundred-player army.

The three fought while moving. They were neither too far, nor too close to the army; they were maintaining a distance that wouldn’t expose them, but also let them observe their advances from time to time. After seeing the enemies out of the corner of his eyes, figuring out how much time it would take for the enemies to notice them wasn’t difficult for Ye Xiu. This was also the reason why he was so good at escaping from pursuers.

And, just like this, they toured around Fire Forest. The army however forced them to take a detour at times.

“Do you have some sort of plan in mind?” Su Mucheng asked Ye Xiu.

“I want to see if the Fire Witch is here.”

“It shouldn’t be up yet, no?”

“Yeah, but it should be soon.” Ye Xiu said.

Wild BOSS kills could be looked up on the leaderboards. Currently, the Fire Witch had last been killed by them a few days ago. The current elites of the big guilds entered the Level 33 range and were already coming to the Fire Forest to level. A second kill hadn’t been recorded yet, which meant that the Fire Witch Cashew hadn’t respawned since her last death.

BOSSes spawned three times every week. It was possible that one wouldn’t spawn for four or five days, but it was relatively rare. However, as long as the BOSS hadn’t been killed three times in a week, it would definitely respawn. This meant that today, on the last day of the week, even if it was on the last second, it had to spawn for its second or third time. Of course, if it hadn’t been killed before, then another one wouldn’t just spawn.

At this moment, it was already nighttime on Sunday. Since the Fire Witch Cashew hadn’t spawned for so many days, it would have to spawn sometime soon.

The three continued to level while looking around. Besides this, Ye Xiu paid close attention to those other players who were leveling as well.

Their efforts hadn’t been wasted. Ye Xiu finally noticed something.

“Over here!” Ye Xiu suddenly turned.

“What is it?”

“Follow those two players.” Ye Xiu said.

Su Mucheng and Steamed Bun Invasion moved forward and looked. They saw the “two players” Ye Xiu was talking about and saw that the two players had the same guild tag. They weren’t leveling in the same spot, but they were both heading in the same direction.

“The BOSS spawned!” Su Mucheng realized. These guilds probably discovered the Fire Witch and were currently sending players over there.

“Most likely.” Ye Xiu said. The three stopped attacking monsters and followed closely behind those two players.

Finally, when they had reached the depths of Fire Forest, Ye Xiu’s group saw a great blaze up ahead. A total of six players were surrounding the Fire Witch Cashew. They were players from the guild Parade. Among them were those two players that they had been following.

Parade was also one of the Clubs in the Glory Alliance. They were an extremely mediocre team and had a guild that they backed, just like every other Club there. Even though they couldn’t compare to the Three Great Guilds, they were still much better than the non-backed casual guilds. After all, every team had a loyal fanbase. When these fans chose a guild, many of them chose the Club that they supported. Normal guilds didn’t have this type of advantage.

Steamed Bun Invasion looked and felt somewhat familiar with this type of situation. He immediately began chattering: “I know. When they’re about to kill the BOSS, we jump out, kill them, and then the BOSS will be ours. Ha ha ha ha.”

“Ha ha, you learn so quickly!” Ye Xiu said.

“Of course.” Steamed Bun Invasion gleefully commented.

“But we won’t be doing that this time.”

“What?”

“This time, we’ll be true spectators.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?”

“You two go and hide well. I’m going to take a look around.” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim left them. Not long after, they heard shouts from within the woods: “It’s Lord Grim, he’s over here!!”

The forest began to liven up as more and more sounds of footsteps crushing leaves and branches could be heard. Lord Grim’s figure quickly appeared in front of Su Mucheng and Steamed Bun Invasion’s line of sight.

“Hurry! Hide!” Ye Xiu ordered.

The team, who was fighting the BOSS, had already increased to eight players now. However, they had noticed the situation. The sounds of footsteps meant that there were a lot of players heading towards them.

The eight players immediately began panicking. They had only just started attacking the BOSS! How’d they get found so easily? It was already too late to drive the BOSS away. Not long after, players began popping up.

When these players arrived, they looked on in astonishment.

“The Fire Witch!!!”

Countless cries, that were filled with astonishment, were shouted out. It had been too unexpected. Everyone’s attention turned to here. Where’d Lord Grim go? No one cared.

Troops continued to arrive. They had originally planned on surrounding Lord Grim, but now they switched their targets to the Fire Witch Cashew as well as those eight Parade guild members, who were attacking her.

Chapter 246 – Seems Like We Don’t Need To

The expressions of Parade’s players immediately changed. Where did all these hungry wolves come from? Why were there so many of them?

The eight players continued to fight the Fire Witch, but also split some of their attention to observe the incoming players. None of them wore their guild tags. However, aside from large guilds, who else could gather so many players at one spot? They were able to quickly figure out the answer from this: they were those guild members who were chasing Lord Grim.

The other side had an advantage in numbers and all of their guilds were more powerful than their Parade. The eight players immediately felt a wave of depression wash over them. It hadn’t been easy being the first group to find the BOSS, but they had been discovered too quickly.

“They’re from Parade!” The one hundred players, that had gathered together, began talking with one another. When Parade’s name was mentioned, most of them carried a hint of disdain. Whether it was in the Alliance or in the game, Parade wasn’t considered a strong opponent to them.

“Ha ha, this BOSS……” Some were talking with the players next to them, when suddenly, they realized that something wasn’t quite right. There was a change in the one hundred players there. They quickly began moving into formation and split into seven groups.

Seven groups. Seven guilds.

Currently, these seven guilds were no longer an Alliance, but were now opponents. No one gave the orders to do so, but everyone instantly made the decision to leave the party that they were in. Each of the guilds made their own respective parties and kept their distance from the other guilds. They began calculating their opponents’ strength as well.

Every time they fought over a wild BOSS, the damage dealt by other players was far greater than the damage the BOSS would deal. This was an indisputable reality.

In the old server, wild BOSSes were only killed by max-level characters. A Level 36 Fire Witch Cashew versus Level 70 players wouldn’t even be considered a fight. However, even then, there would always be large amounts of casualties. The killers were all players from other guilds.

In the Heavenly Domain, those extremely difficult wild BOSSes were originally created as a challenge for players. In addition to this, there would also be the fights between guilds. In these types of battles, many of the players would even die several times. Even though only max-level players would enter the Heavenly Domain, there were still leveling areas, monsters to gain experience from, and quests for experience too. These places were never empty, either. This was because there were more intense battles in the Heavenly Domain, so there were more deaths and more experience losses.

After quickly measuring one another’s strength, they found that the two guilds that were relatively weaker were unexpectedly Tyrannical Ambition and Herb Garden of the Three Great Guilds! These two guilds had the fewest number of players!

Everyone was turning their heads non-stop, sizing up one another. The chats in each of the guilds were bustling with noise.

Should they move out or not?

Right now they understood one another’s strengths well, but every guild would send out a message to their members asking for help. Help would arrive at different times and the tides could change depending on how much help came.

Chen Yehui was thinking a bit differently though. He had a weird feeling. Even though he also wanted to steal the BOSS, he didn’t want to have a fight with these guilds right now.

Someone was already thinking of moving out, but Excellent Dynasty’s Chen Yehui suddenly said first: “Everyone, for us to so coincidentally meet a wild BOSS, it means that the BOSS will definitely be killed, but if the battle is too fierce, then continuing our future alliance will be a bit difficult, no? What I’m saying is that this time, would it be possible for us to do things more peacefully? We’ll only attack the BOSS and, as according to the system, whichever side does the most damage, will get the BOSS.”

This wasn’t the first time such an event had occurred in the history of the game. In the past, there were successes, but there were also failures. However, the proposal that Chen Yehui put out this time was sincere. Under their special alliance, he truly didn’t want the seven guilds to fight with one another.

The other guilds hadn’t yet responded, when Parade’s eight players took the initiative.

They weren’t stupid. They knew that the Fire Witch wouldn’t fall under their hands, so why bother fighting her? The obvious choice was to run. They no longer cared if the BOSS lived or died.

The eight players decided quickly and their movements were swift. They turned around and directly fled. If they continued running like this, they would quickly leave the battle, but the BOSS would still chase after them initially. How could these one hundred players let the BOSS just leave?

The one hundred players immediately surrounded her. The battle began and all sorts of attacks flew towards the Fire Witch.

But the BOSS only had so much space around her and not every hit would successfully connect. As a result, the first thing that had to be done when stealing a BOSS was to first fight for a good position.

Who didn’t know of this? The melee classes rushed towards the Fire Witch. The long-range classes found advantageous DPS positions and the support classes tried their hardest to stick with their allies to provide support.

In this instant, the Fire Witch was fully surrounded. Even though no one had clearly accepted Chen Yehui’s suggestion, from the looks of it, it seemed like everyone had tacitly agreed to it. When they were fighting for positioning, none of them fought with each other.

However, in the end, they had rushed too much. Their positionings were all over the place and it was still a bit of a mess.

“Whichever guild’s Elementalist, can you please stop using Blizzard?” Some of the melee classes were shouting. Clearly, if an Elementalist used Blizzard, other players would be caught up in it as well.

“Who fired that Anti-Tank Missile?” Someone else cursed. AoE spells couldn’t be controlled, but a Gunner’s firing could be.

There were countless mistakes and countless shouts. The majority of the players were grouped around the Fire Witch. However, no matter how hard Chen Yehui tried to organize them, his voice couldn’t be heard amidst the commotion.

The Fire Witch’s two arms suddenly opened and a fiery light glowed around her.

“Meteor Shower, hurry and interrupt her!!” someone hastily shouted.

“Let me in!” When the Fire Witch was in her Super Armor state, only Grabs could interrupt her. But the Grapplers were currently stuck on the outside of the circle.

A Battle Mage quickly stabbed forward, piercing the Fire Witch’s waist. The light was still there, but the Fire Witch was thrown up with a Circle Swing.

The Meteor Shower was interrupted, but no one was content.

“NO!!” Countless players cursed. When the Battle Mage threw the Fire Witch, the Battle Mage threw the BOSS into the crowd of players.

Even worse, he had brought the Fire Witch into a different position. The players, who had originally been surrounding the Fire Witch, were suddenly on the sidelines.

One of the players, who was flung to the sidelines, used a Sword Draw in rage and slashed at the Battle Mage’s back.

“D*MN IT!” The Battle Mage stumbled and then returned with a Dragon Tooth, which connected with a different player.

“YOU NOOB!” The person who was stabbed was a Striker, who attacked back with a Collapsing Fist, sending the Battle Mage flying. While flying, the Battle Mage unfortunately crashed into a line of players.

Curses resounded throughout the forest. The battlefield was already uncontrollable. Chen Yehui wanted to completely start over, but he had also been one of the players who was hit and was on the ground eating mud!

All sorts of skills whistled around. Players who hadn’t been able to hit the BOSS were all attacking now. Aside from their own guild members, everyone was an enemy.

“STOP! EVERYONE, STOP! STAY CALM!!!” Chen Yehui shouted. As soon as he stood up, someone dropped down from the sky and smooshed him back down to the ground.

“I’M TELLING YOU ALL TO STOP!!” Chen Yehui’s mood was terrible. He was lying on the ground telling the leaders from the other guilds.

“That one. Excellent Dynasty’s guild leader. Kill him first!” Chen Yehui heard from somewhere and immediately felt hopeless.

Lord Grim, who had been watching from the sides, had a grenade ready in his hands long ago.

“Looks like I won’t need to.” Ye Xiu said, while having his Lord Grim cancel the Grenade.

“No wonder we went to Fire Forest.” Su Mucheng mumbled to herself.

Chapter 247 – Keyboard and Mouse

The chaos ensued.

The seven big guilds, that had originally been chasing after Lord Grim, were only focused on the Fire Witch Cashew now.

The players that were near the BOSS were ferociously attacking the BOSS, while the players behind them were ferociously fighting for a good spot. None of them had guild tags on them, so no one knew which guild the players closest to them were. As a result, no one bothered to check and just attacked whoever!

Stealing BOSSes was a frequent occurrence, but it was rare for it to be as chaotic as it currently was.

It had come so suddenly, but no one had expected things to turn out this way. It wasn’t as if these guilds didn’t want to stabilize the situation, but rather it was just that the situation had already gone out of control. If you didn’t attack others, someone else would attack you. Not a single person dared to back down and stop attacking.

Strategy? Leading? None of these could be used. The players were only relying on their instincts.

People who wanted to lead, like Chen Yehui, had already been killed or knocked out on the ground, unable to get up. Currently, whoever talked the most or whoever instigated things the most would become everyone’s primary target. In order to catch the bandits, one has to first catch the bandits’ ringleaders. The players there still held this sort of common sense.

No one could predict the outcome of this battle. Even Ye Xiu couldn’t. In such a chaotic battle, even if a God were thrown in there, he’d still be put to the test.

However, as players continuously fell, the number of players decreased, making the battle more and more clear. Those who were still alive probably weren’t extremely skilled. Most of them were either lucky or kept a low profile. The enthusiastic ones, who went all out, died quite explosively.

With fewer of these people in the fight, the field calmed down a bit. With a calmer scene, the distribution of the field could be seen more clearly. The members from the seven guilds had separated from each other.

At the same time, the BOSS Fire Witch Cashew’s movements could be seen more clearly as well.

Cashew waved her magic staff and a giant Fireball smashed towards a player.

This Fireball could be considered a disaster. Although, this was not in the sense of how much damage it did, it pointed to which group the Fire Witch was aggroed onto.

Whichever group had the highest aggro would become the BOSS’s first target, and how could this group not be the other guilds’ targets?

A disaster was imminent.

One of the groups was instantly eliminated. Ye Xiu’s group, which was on the sidelines watching, couldn’t even tell which guild’s troops had died.

The fight that ensued was no longer as chaotic and returned to the guilds’ usual tempo. They were no longer going all out attacking the BOSS, but rather, they were whittling her health down slowly. After many years of doing this, the guilds had become careful and patient.

In this type of situation, the number of players would gradually increase instead of decrease. The backup from the big guilds would continue to arrive and the guild leaders would try to outwit each other.

“We should go.” Ye Xiu whispered.

“What?” Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t sure what he meant.

“Let them kill!” Ye Xiu said. He had not planned on taking the BOSS for himself because after the complete chaos in the beginning, the guilds would try to reduce their casualties and the battle would eventually stabilize itself.

“

“We’re not going to kill?” The innocent Steamed Bun Invasion had wanted to massacre all of them, which would then leave them with the BOSS.

“They have too many people. We can’t kill.” Ye Xiu said.

Steamed Bun Invasion looked around and saw that there really were a lot of people. Right now, they were all circling around the BOSS. The scene in his mind, where everyone else was lying on the ground dead, didn’t seem too realistic.

“It’d be better to use this time to do our own business.” Ye Xiu said.

As a result, the three left Fire Forest. They didn’t know how the battle would develop, but the result would eventually be announced.

Sure enough, the three had temporarily been forgotten. When they arrived at Line Canyon, there weren’t even any guards watching over the entrances.

It was already 11. Ye Xiu temporarily logged out of the game to start his shift. At this moment, Chen Guo and Tang Rou finally returned with a bunch of shopping bags.

“Come here and help us!” Chen Guo called for Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu hastily went over to help them. He looked at the items stacked up in Chen Guo’s arms and his eyes brightened: “Woah, Blue Classic.”

“Oh? You know what’s what!” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu smiled. Blue Classic was a type of professional gaming keyboard. It was the keyboard Ye Xiu had commonly used in the past. The keyboard and mouse that Chen Guo provided in the Internet Cafe weren’t bad, but when compared to the Blue Classic, they couldn’t be compared.

“Seeing that you already know what’s good, I’ll give you one!” Chen Guo indicated Ye Xiu to take one of the keyboards between her arms.

“So nice?” Ye Xiu saw that the two had brought a total of three keyboards back.

“There was a discount if you bought three, so it was convenient to get one for you too.” Chen Guo said.

“So it was like that.” Ye Xiu took the keyboard.

“There’s a mouse too.” Chen Guo took out a box from her bag and handed it to Ye Xiu.

“Woah, this……”

“What is it?”

“I’m not too used to this one.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you mean you’re not too used to it?”

“It’s too heavy. Using it is too tiring.” The mouse Chen Guo had bought for him was called “Heavy Metal”. It was big enough, heavy enough, and very sensitive. It was a type of mouse that many players liked.

“How lazy can you be?” Chen Guo said.

“Thank you, though.” Ye Xiu still took the mouse.

“Then what mouse are you used to using?” Chen Guo asked.

“Seventh Edition Light Wind.” Ye Xiu said.

“That one? Isn’t that one meant for girls?” Chen Guo also knew of the model. It was just like she had said; that mouse was small and delicate, lightweight and portable. It really was something that girls preferred.

“As long as it suits you, there’s no difference between genders.”

And at this moment, Chen Guo took out another mouse. It just so happened to be a Seventh Edition Light Wind.

‘Wow! What a coincidence! Let me switch with you.” Ye Xiu took the “Heavy Metal” mouse and handed it over.

“Get lost. Who’s going to switch with you?!”

“This one suits you more.” Ye Xiu recommended the “Heavy Metal” mouse to Chen Guo. “For players like you, whose mechanics aren’t that good, this type of heavy mouse will help you increase your accuracy.”

“You just keep on making things up.” Chen Guo didn’t believe him.

“If you don’t believe me, you can just try it yourself.” Ye Xiu tried putting the “Heavy Metal” into Chen Guo’s hands again.

“Can I just plug the keyboard into the computer on the front desk?” Ye Xiu waved the “Blue Classic” keyboard in his hands.

“Go ahead!” Chen Guo approved.

“Then what about you?” Ye Xiu switched the keyboards and turned around to ask Chen Guo.

“Uh…… that’s a good question.” Chen Guo said. Even though there were a lot of computers in the Internet Cafe, they didn’t have any computer specifically for them. Switching their mouse and keyboards every time was too troublesome.

“Think about it!” Ye Xiu had finished plugging in his “Blue Classic”. He touched the surface and instantly felt a wave of familiarity. He had used this model for a good five years.

“I’ll think about it later. First, let’s find a spot to try it out on.” Chen Guo was impatient and found a computer to sit at.

Tang Rou had a lot more to be praised about. She knew to first put away the bags they had just brought in. She wasn’t like Chen Guo, who just threw her bags onto the Cafe’s counter. When the two girls went shopping, of course they hadn’t only bought keyboards and mice, but also they had bought several bags of clothes and make-up. She had to make two trips before she managed to completely put everything into the second-floor room.

Ye Xiu had help the customers who came and left during this time. Once Chen Guo installed the keyboards, she immediately began using one of them. She immediately entered the game and quickly went to the Arena, feeling that she would be invincible with her new epic keyboard and mouse. However, she was crushed in her first match and then wrecked even harder in the second match.

Chen Guo sat dumbly at her computer as if she had been splashed with ice-cold water.

“I say. Did you think that switching to a better keyboard and mouse would suddenly make you a lot better?” Ye Xiu saw this while finding change for a customer. He continued speaking: “Your own skill is the most important point. If you want to improve, switching your keyboard and mouse won’t even be as useful as playing with that whack-a-mole I gave you!”

“Who are you talking to?” A customer wasn’t sure.

“To that noob over there.”

Chapter 248 – Guidance

“Who’s the noob?!” Chen Guo yelled impolitely and slammed the keyboard to go for another match.

“So heartless! You’re going to hit it if it can’t help you?” Ye Xiu mumbled to himself.

Angry and anxious, Chen Guo lost for a third time. She felt like pushing the table away and leaving, but she didn’t want to be taunted by Ye Xiu again, so she clenched her teeth and went in for round four.

Tang Rou finished carrying the bags over to her room. After tidying up a bit, she came down with her new keyboard and mouse. She also wanted to try them out, when she saw Chen Guo furiously tapping on her keyboard.

“What’s wrong?” Tang Rou was astonished. In yesterday night’s game, Team Excellent Era had swept their opponents away and once again won almost every round. Chen Guo’s mood today had been extremely good. Why’d she suddenly get so heated up after only such a short while?

“She lost six times in a row.” Ye Xiu said.

“Mind your own business! If you don’t handle the bills correctly, I’ll nail your head to the wall!” Chen Guo roared.

“You got her angry again!” Tang Rou was helpless and more or less figured out the root of Chen Guo’s anger. Today, she had just heard Chen Guo say how amazing she’d be with a new high-end keyboard and mouse. But when she returned, she was losing like this.

She silently walked to Chen Guo’s side and watched her play as she installed her new keyboard and mouse. Tang Rou had the mechanics down now, but her observational skills still weren’t too great. She could only tell that, judging from the differences between their two health bars, Chen Guo was undoubtedly going to lose.

“Calm down. What are you so impatient for?” Ye Xiu’s voice drifted by again.

“Huh? Why’s this guy so noisy? Should we go find somewhere more quiet?” Chen Guo said to Tang Rou.

“I thought you liked the noise, no?” Tang Rou laughed.

If they really wanted to go somewhere quiet, then they’d just go to the VIP rooms on the second floor. But as the Internet Cafe’s owner, Chen Guo wanted to stay on the first floor because she liked the atmosphere around here. She had grown up in this type of environment her entire life.

Chen Guo kept on tapping her keyboard and mouse as if she were nailing Ye Xiu’s head to the wall. This time, her playing went pretty well and the tides seemed to have turned.

Tang Rou was currently logging into the game, when she suddenly heard Chen Guo say “Woah!” She turned her head and looked. Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze had been launched into the air and was currently being trampled on.

“Just use an Aerial Fire to get out!” Ye Xiu said.

“I don’t need you to say it!” Chen Guo began firing. However, her angle was messed up and she fired up into the air. The recoil knocked her down and she crashed into the ground.

“Tsk tsk, you went a bit overboard, no?” Ye Xiu said.

“Hey hey hey, how can you see from so far away?!” Chen Guo decided that she’d stop playing. She got up furiously and stomped over to find Ye Xiu.

At this time, Ye Xiu didn’t have any customers and was clear. He laughed: “You can’t be an expert without good eyes!”

“If you’re an expert, then teach me something! You’re always making stupid, sarcastic remarks!”

“How’d I not teach you? I told you to not randomly hit your keyboard. I told you to stay calm. I told you to play slower, but you just had to ignore it and yell at me. I told you to use an Aerial Fire to get out, but you shot it towards the sky………”

“I can’t make a mistake?” Chen Guo interrupted.

“But you can avoid this kind of mistake. Look, I had warned you that the Heavy Metal suits you, but you just had to use the Seventh Edition Light Wind. It’s too light for you!” Ye Xiu said.

“I…….” Chen Guo couldn’t say anything. Had Ye Xiu really been helping me the entire time? But he still makes me too angry! Chen Guo felt like that kicking him once or twice would make her feel calmer and make her play better.

“Switch to a “Heavy Metal” and try it out!” Ye Xiu handed her the Heavy Metal mouse. Chen Guo stared in doubt at this extremely stupid and heavy mouse and hesitated on whether she should take it or not.

“You might not be used to it in the beginning, but don’t be impatient and slowly try it out! Also, your recent opponents might be better than normal..” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?”

“You’re famous. Everyone wants to challenge you.”

Chen Guo immediately understood and almost died from anger: “And that’s your fault! I won’t let you borrow my account next time!”

After Ye Xiu borrowed her account to instantly kill off Poplar Beach, Chasing Haze’s name became extremely famous. Outsiders saw it as the main account of a great expert and went over to admire her. Players from all over came to pull her in, ask to be students, challenge her, or try to make friends with her.

Chen Guo felt extremely sad. She didn’t feel famous at all. That guy just slapped his butt and ran while leaving her with this mess. How annoying!

“Uh, I was a bit inconsiderate at that time and I feel like I should have played a bit more modestly, so you wouldn’t be so troubled.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah…… it wasn’t too much trouble……” Chen Guo had a hard time accepting Ye Xiu’s apology.

“But if you keep playing like this in the Arena, then everyone will know the truth, right?” Ye Xiu continued.

“Go die!” Chen Guo grabbed the Heavy Metal mouse and left. She had been too naive to think that he had any sort of confession to make.

“I’ll continue teaching you from afar!” Ye Xiu yelled from behind Chen Guo. Tang Rou had been laughing on the side the entire time.

“So talkative!”

Chen Guo switched mice. She took the Heavy Metal and moved it twice. It was very heavy and would take some time to get used to. Even so, she started a new match.

This time, she was more calm. Now that she was more focused, Chen Guo wasn’t so bad. She wasn’t top-tier by any means, but she was at least at the skill level of Seven Fields’s group. Plus, she had had this account for several years, so her equips were quite good, giving her the advantage in most cases.

During the match, Chen Guo discovered the Heavy Metal mouse’s advantages. Compared to the Seventh Edition Light Wind, the heavy mouse was much easier to control. It was a bit heavy, but saying that moving the mouse was too tiring was clearly an exaggeration.

“Is that guy lying or telling the truth……” Chen Guo muttered. She was already quite satisfied with this mouse. The more she used it, the better her playing flowed. She finally won this round.

“Hmph, let’s see what you have to say now.” Chen Guo was delighted. She turned her head to look at the front desk and immediately turned furious. She had finally won a match, but that guy wasn’t there. He was busy playing on his own computer.

Chen Guo was sad. She couldn’t just grab him and tell him to watch. She angrily entered to play another match. She glanced at Tang Rou’s screen and saw that she was in the game, too.

“What are you guys doing?” Chen Guo asked Tang Rou.

“We played all day yesterday and our equipment’s running out of durability. I’m going to get mine fixed.” Tang Rou said.

“You’re still being chased?”

“I guess so. Ye Xiu told me to be careful.”

“Where is he?” Chen Guo asked.

“He just got online. We’ll be dungeoning in a bit.” Tang Rou said.

“Oh….” Chen Guo replied and continued playing in the Arena.

Ye Xiu had gone offline for about half an hour. After coming back online, Cleansing Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion were no longer by his side. It still wasn’t convenient for them to stay in one place for too long.

“Have they killed the Fire Witch yet?” Ye Xiu sent a message to Su Mucheng.

“No news yet.” Su Mucheng replied.

“So slow!” Ye Xiu sighed. “We’ll dungeon and then you can go rest early!”

“Everyone’s here!” Su Mucheng saw that Tang Rou’s Soft Mist and Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash were on.

“They need to fix their equipment.” Ye Xiu replied.

“I hope they’ll be able to finish doing that before they kill the BOSS and return.” Su Mucheng said.

“Fire Forest isn’t that far, but a lot of people will be coming from Congee City after dying.” Ye Xiu said.

The three killed a few nearby monsters in Line Canyon while they waited for Tang Rou and Qiao Yifan to come. Finally, after a long time, a system announcement popped up. Fire Forest’s Fire Witch Cashew had been killed by Tyrannical Ambition.

“Oh oh, not bad!” Ye Xiu sent to Cold Night: “What’d it drop?”

“What? Why should you care?” Cold Night replied.

“Depending on your pace, I want to give you a new updated list for the bet.”

“Hell no!” Cold Night refused.

Chapter 249 – Leave It To Nature

It wasn’t easy for Tyrannical Ambition to take down the Fire Witch. None of the other guilds would let up and they were all afraid of others taking the prize away. If not for the other guilds, killing off the Fire Witch would have been easy.

In the beginning, no one had a huge advantage. Tyrannical Ambition was actually on the worse end. However, when backup arrived, Tyrannical Ambition’s superiority emerged.

Jiang You’s group were upper-tier in mechanics and had vast amounts of experience. In comparison to non-pro players, they were the elite of the elites. Don’t look at how they were nothing in Lord Grim’s eyes. Against normal players, the five players’ confidence reignited.

After a long and bitter battle, Tyrannical Ambition relied on these five to come out victorious. For Tyrannical Ambition, which had endured so much for the past few days, this victory could have made them feel much better. But right as they were celebrating, Lord Grim shamelessly approached them.

Change the list? Did he believe that they killed the BOSS for him? Cold Night was very unhappy.

“Absolutely not!” Cold Night hated how he wasn’t sharp enough.

“Really? Then, that’s too bad.” Lord Grim casually replied and then went silent. Cold Night scratched the walls. What was with this guy’s train of thought? He couldn’t understand him.

After killing the BOSS, the guild took a list of their casualties. They checked to see which opponents had taken them down and recorded their names.

Many years of fighting with one another had made the guilds act less impulsively and more rationally. In situations where they had the absolute advantage, they absolutely wouldn’t negotiate with you. However, in situations where their strengths were equal, they would find ways to get revenge in the future. Day after day, their list of enemies to enemies was in a mess. Today, I’ll kill your people. Tomorrow, your people will kill my people. The cycle will never end.

Right now, the guilds were calm, or at least, they appeared calm on the outside. For example, Samsara’s tenth server guild leader, Lonely Drink, went on to congratulate Cold Night, who replied with his own show of respect. In reality, the two had just finished their casualties list and many of their players had died by the other side’s hands. This was the old players’ way of conducting business. Only new players would become hostile and begin enacting revenge at this moment.

Chen Yehui had rushed back after dying. They hadn’t gotten the BOSS and were feeling very gloomy right now. However, after seeing that the atmosphere wasn’t too bad, he immediately reminded them of Lord Grim.

As a result, the other guilds gathered up again like nothing had happened and began discussing how they would conduct the movement.

“Where’s Lord Grim right now? He’s gone again.”

“The dungeons have reset. Maybe he went to Line Canyon to dungeon?”

“How about this.” The delighted Cold Night made a suggestion: “Always chasing Lord Grim with so many people is too wasteful of our resources. Why don’t we all just go and do our own thing for now. As soon as any one of us find him, we’ll send each other messages and we’ll gather again.”

Cold Night was trying to work half-heartedly. Their pro team was about to come out. How were they unable to take down Lord Grim? This was why he was too lazy to participate. He just wanted to find a reason to leave.

As for the other guilds, Cold Night’s suggestion was pleasant to hear. Whether it was guarding the Line Canyon entrances or guarding the city entrances, it was incredibly tiring. It wasn’t fun to play like this.

They had originally thought that stalling Lord Grim would have been a small matter. Who would have imagined that, even with so many people after him, there would be such miniscule results to show for it. Their own progress had taken a hit. It had been an unsuccessful plan and it wasn’t worth continuing.

When Cold Night’s suggestion came out, the crowd all applauded and immediately showed their support. However, there were two voices of opposition.

One was Chen Yehui. He had other motives. How could he let the guilds reduce the amount of resources they were putting into this!

The other was, unexpectedly, Herb Garden’s Plantago Seed.

Herb Garden’s attitude had been unorganized and easygoing the entire time. Chen Yehui felt that his current actions were a bit suspicious. Seeing Herb Garden’s attitude, it was very possible that Herb Garden was thinking the same thing he was. They hoped that Lord Grim would make both sides suffer.

However, from this point of view, how could they know that both sides would suffer? This meant that Herb Garden must know that Lord Grim was the God-level player, Ye Qiu!

“How could he have known this?” Chen Yehui wasn’t sure.

“Everyone, Lord Grim is our biggest enemy right now! Putting in our resources to fight him is just a temporary movement. After all this, our development in the tenth server will go unobstructed.” Plantago Seed was trying to persuade the people.

“Ha ha, you’re correct, brother. We’re not backing out. We’re only slightly changing our means of doing things. Right now, we’re placing too much importance on Lord Grim. He’s been leading us by the nose. Lord Grim exposed himself just recently, but we still weren’t able to catch him. The guards at the entrance have found him, but what was the use of that? So from the looks of it, we should just let nature take its course for now. With our eyes everywhere, we just need to gather together from time to time to give some trouble to Lord Grim. It’ll be enough to stop him from going to places with too many players and he’ll have to duck and hide every time he hunts down monsters, does quests, or goes dungeoning. Most of his time will be wasted from doing this. The time will add up and our goal will have been reached.” The one who spoke with confidence was Blossom Valley’s guild leader, Backlight Bomb, who perfectly supplemented Cold Night’s random excuse.

The ones who had been supporting Cold Night were doing so mostly because they wanted to escape as well. But after Backlight Bomb made such an assuring argument, many players nodded their heads and reaffirmed their positions.

“Sounds good!” Even Lonely Drink nodded his head. These guild leaders weren’t only doing this to have fun. Most of them had to consider what was good for their guild’s interests. This was work and their performance was important.

And thus, Cold Night and Plantago Seed had no way of persuading the masses. They looked at one another and had no other choice but to oblige.

In game, their characters couldn’t really make direct eye contact, but the two were able to read each other’s attitudes. Chen Yehui couldn’t figure out how Plantago Seed had gotten knowledge of Lord Grim’s identity, but Plantago Seed didn’t feel anything out of the ordinary from Chen Yehui. Ye Qiu was from Excellent Era. How could Excellent Dynasty be unaware?

After Ye Qiu retired, no one knew where he went to. Club Excellent Era also said they didn’t know. Ordinarily, it should have been very easy for a God like Ye Qiu to find game-related work after retiring. Had Ye Qiu specially run to the game to make trouble and prepare to lead Excellent Dynasty?

Plantago Seed had made many guesses after knowing Lord Grim’s identity. He thought that this was the most likely case.

“Okay, then from now on, we’ll be a bit more natural with carrying out our measures against Lord Grim.” Backlight Bomb continued, “It’s very likely that Lord Grim is in Line Canyon right now and a lot of us will be heading to dungeon too, so we’ll go see if we can find Lord Grim’s whereabouts. If we find him, then we’ll immediately report it.”

“That’s the way it should be.” Someone replied.

Chapter 250 – The Situation Isn’t Clear

The guilds decided on this plan and then dispersed. The majority of them headed towards Line Canyon.

At Line Canyon, Ye Xiu easily found Tang Rou and Qiao Yifan and proceeded to dungeon as well. The players from those seven guilds wanted to bump into Ye Xiu’s group, but the only time that would happen was during the moment they exited and re-entered the dungeon. Some luck would be needed.

The guilds now had a new plan. They only needed to watch out for any signs of Lord Grim. The night passed by gently and there wasn’t much pressure on them.

As for Ye Xiu’s side, they didn’t know that their opponents’ plans had changed. They continued with their careful and roundabout routes. Tang Rou hoped that they would meet a few players that they could kill, but she was left disappointed that night. Every time they left the dungeon, nothing ever happened, and even after going around in a circle to switch entrances, nothing happened and they easily re-entered the dungeon.

Backlight Bomb’s prediction had been correct. Under this type of situation, as long as they kept up the pressure on Ye Xiu, Ye Xiu would waste time taking detours. The amount of time would add up and their leveling speed would slow down. After finishing their three runs, they had spent around an hour more than they normally would have spent. Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan logged off, while Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, and Steamed Bun Invasion continued on with their detours. No one followed them and no BOSSes appeared.

After learning about the advantages of the Heavy Metal mouse, the number of matches Chen Guo won grew higher and higher. She was currently violating her rules of work and rest and refused to leave the computer. The only thing that made her unhappy was the fact that there would sometimes be people who would ask her for advice because they thought she was that great expert from before.

It was getting late and Chen Guo wasn’t able to continue. She had yawned countless times and after almost falling asleep in one match, she finally decided to stop and go to sleep. She put away her new keyboard and mouse and temporarily stowed them away at the front desk.

“Since your advice wasn’t bad, i’ll gift you this mouse!” After stowing them away, she handed her extra “Seventh Edition Light Wind” to Ye Xiu. She waved good night a few times and then went over to her room to sleep.

“What are we going to do now?” Ye Xiu heard Tang Rou ask.

“Level up! Let’s hurry and level up. That’s the most effective way of fighting back against these guilds.” Ye Xiu said. Fighting back and forth wasn’t very exciting for Ye Xiu’s group and didn’t benefit them in any way. On the contrary, these types of fights wasted a lot of their time. He didn’t want to fall for such a mistake.

This reasoning was similar to what Liu Hao had realized after wasting his time fighting with Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu wouldn’t be troubled so easily. After teaching the big guilds a lesson, he wouldn’t continue to tangle with them.

‘Then are we going to Desolate Land?” Tang Rou asked.

In terms of efficiency, running dungeons was much faster than killing monsters in leveling areas. However, Desolate Land couldn’t compare to Line Canyon. There would be a lot of players over there, so it wouldn’t be convenient to go there right now. In the end, the three left Line Canyon and ran to Fire Forest.

The day passed by like this. Ye Xiu gradually began to realize that the guilds had changed their strategy. They had suffered sneak attacks three times, but it looked like the attack had been made on the spot. Two of them had been towards Lord Grim, which Ye Xiu easily escaped from, while the other attack was against Steamed Bun Invasion, in which they succeeded and sent Steamed Bun Invasion back to the city. Fortunately, they had changed their respawn points to Bulls Town. If not, then it would have been troublesome to leave Congee City again.

Hearing of the news, Ye Xiu could only comfort Steamed Bun Invasion.

Steamed Bun Invasion said that he had been through a lot worse. Dying once or twice was just a small matter and not worth mentioning.

Not worth mentioning? Then who had been the one to immediately report his death when he came online?

That’s what I was worried about! Ye Xiu didn’t say it, but he silently sighed in his heart.

The other side was no longer intent on chasing them down forever, but they would continue to put pressure on them. Ye Xiu had no way of knowing when the other side would suddenly surround and kill them, so their only choice was to stay on the safer side. At this moment, the other side was safely leveling up, but Ye Xiu’s group didn’t have that sort of luxury.

The other guilds could put in 20% of the effort into chasing them, but Ye Xiu had to stay on alert 100% of the time. If not, then they’d end up like Steamed Bun Invasion and be killed off.

“What do you think of killing them every time we see one of them?” Steamed Bun Invasion suggested.

“If we got experience from killing them, then I’d have strongly recommended it already.” Ye Xiu replied.

“We should set another record to take revenge!” Tang Rou proposed.

Ye Xiu didn’t agree.

Right now, everyone else was at a roadblock in Line Canyon. The Level 33 players were about to hit Level 34 and there still wasn’t any final result in Line Canyon. Records were still being set, but it would only be improved by a miniscule amount each time.

Even though they currently held the record, the other guilds were very close. Lord Grim’s team was only faster than the second place, Tyrannical Ambition, by two seconds. The third place, Herb Garden, was only four seconds behind. Their record could be overtaken at any time. All the guilds, who were watching the rankings, knew this. What was Lord Grim’s group waiting for this time? Were the records going to keep on going back and forth like this? Or were they waiting for a guild to declare themselves as the winner and then completely crush them?

This type of situation had given Tyrannical Ambition some time to win back some face. Players could at least see that they could compete with Lord Grim.

After last week’s match, Boss Chen had been very happy. Today, when Ye Xiu got up, he saw Chen Guo directly open up three stations for personal use. Her reasoning was that the Internet Cafe would never be full enough that only three stations would be left.

“Three stations? You’re not planning on giving one to me right?” Ye Xiu suspicously asked.

“Don’t worry. You can say you’re happy.” Chen Guo said.

“I don’t need it. I stay at the front desk during the night.”

“Uh…….”

“I also have to smoke during the day. Would you be able to stand me sitting next to you?”

“Uh……”

“But that’s good too. I’ll have a seat to sit in whenever I come over to teach you.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why don’t you go die!?” Chen Guo glared and immediately called someone over to shutdown the computer meant for Ye Xiu.

Chapter 251 – Dismantle

Time gradually passed until it turned nine. This was the time that Tyrannical Ambition had agreed upon for the second match. Ye Xiu was sitting there and gaming in the smoking area as usual.

“Have you gathered all the materials yet?” Ye Xiu messaged Cold Night. He was controlling Lord Grim to head towards Bulls Town.

Cold Night almost replied with a “Ready”, when he suddenly realized, why was he acting so obediently?!

“You hurry up.” Cold Night bluntly replied.

At nine o’clock sharp, Lord Grim arrived at the Arena entrance. He entered the Arena, created a room, and then told Cold Night which room he was in.

After a brief moment, the other side entered. It was the same five characters from last time, but now, the players behind them were very different. The Striker had become the leader. The Cleric, next. And then the Elementalist, Blade Master, and Sharpshooter.

Ye Xiu smiled.

The Striker was undoubtedly Han Wenqing. The Cleric was obviously still Zhang Xinjie. The Elementalist, Crowd Lover, was probably Bai Yanfei, and the Sharpshooter was probably Wang Chixuan. How could Ye Xiu not know who was in Tyranny?

Though, out of these five characters, there were only three pro-players who were actually subbing in.

Han Wenqing’s Striker, Zhang Xinjie’s Cleric, and Bai Yanfei’s Elementalist. Ye Xiu had guessed these three correctly. However, the Blade Master and Sharpshooter weren’t Tyranny’s pro-players. These two accounts weren’t in Tyranny’s area, so how did those players get them so quickly?

Though, if they wanted to find other suitable accounts, it was possible, but Han Wenqing believed that the three of them would be more than enough.

“The whole pro team? Do you want us to lose even more face?” When Han Wenqing said it, no one else dared to answer back.

Right now, the three were in the studio. No one in the room dared to speak. Jiang You’s, Endless Night’s, and the Striker’s accounts were also being used. The other computers were being used by others, so they could only go spectate the match.

“What…… what’s the meaning of this?” When Jiang You looked, he was immediately startled by the arrangement of Lord Grim’s team.

The Blade Master, Flowing Tree? Not there.

The Launcher, Cleansing Mist? Not there.

The Battle Mage, Soft Mist? Not there.

The Brawler, Steamed Bun Invasion? Not there.

The Ghostblade, One Inch Ash? Not there either.

Not a single one of them was there. None of their classes matched the four other members in Lord Grim’s team and they didn’t recognize any of their usernames. Jiang You turned around in astonishment and saw Han Wenqing look at Zhang Xinjie: “Where are the players you were talking about?”

“The bet didn’t require them to be here…….” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Can we start?” Lord Grim asked.

“This guy……. did he find another team of hidden experts again?” Jiang You feared. He was absolutely confident in the pro-team, but the problem was that only half of the team came. The Sharpshooter and Blade Master weren’t going to hold them back right?

The Sharpshooter and Blade Master were even more nervous than Jiang You was. The two were originally somewhat nervous when they heard that they were going to play with the Gods. After seeing Lord Grim’s unexpected team arrangement, their hearts immediately tightened.

“Start.” Han Wenqing replied to Lord Grim.

Jiang You was too busy thinking. The screen he was looking at changed to spectator mode, and the match began. The random map that was chosen was the circular arena.

It was a very simple and plain map. The map was a bit bigger than the 1v1’s basic four-sided ring; it was round and flat. If this were a pro-match, they most certainly wouldn’t pick this type of map, where there was no advantage for either side.

“The map isn’t bad.” Han Wenqing said. With such a simple map, there weren’t any weird tricks or underhanded methods that could be used. Coordination and mechanics would be the only deciding factors for this match.

“You guys deal with those four. I’m going to meet with this Lord Grim and teach him a lesson.” Han Wenqing simply ordered.

Even though Zhang Xinjie possessed the title of Master Tactician, it didn’t mean he was always the shot-caller during a match. The person who made the decision the most was still undoubtedly the team leader. Of course, Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie had very good synergy with one another. They would switch roles depending on the situation and help one another adjust. Two shot-callers in a single team was usually taboo in team battles, but for Tyranny, their team was in extreme harmony. What happened if both their calls clashed? Up until now, such an occurrence had never occurred for them.

After Han Wenqing made the order, his Striker quickly rushed forward.

“Arrow Formation! Follow him.” Zhang Xinjie shouted and the four moved out.

Arrow Formation was a formation where one person led the way as the tip of the arrow. The remaining people would be on either the left or right and form a cone-shaped formation. It was very effective when charging in. However, the requirements needed for the person at the front was high. While charging, the person at the front would be the target of incoming attacks.

Tyranny was very familiar with this type of formation, and Han Wenqing was always at the front.

They began with their most used strategy. The Sharpshooter and the Blade Master felt their hearts surge. In game, they often copied this type of formation, but how could they have imagined they’d have the chance to do it with Han Wenqing in the lead?

The five maintained their formation and began observing their opponents.

The other side was in complete chaos. Zhang Xinjie had no idea what type of pathing they were taking.

Zhang Xinjie wasn’t panicked. He immediately thought of the cheerleader from the previous match, Zero Kills.

“No way, right?” Zhang Xinjie was astonished. Lord Grim had directly found four random strangers? He was being too confident, no? Or did he just directly give up on this match? However if that was his intent, then why’d he agree in the first place? Could he be…….

There was no time to think. The two sides clashed. In this type of simple map, the two sides didn’t need to waste their time closing in on each other. The battle began after only ten seconds.

Han Wenqing didn’t care if the other side was weak or strong. He focused on his own movements. He always went all out.

His right leg flew out, as he attacked with a “High Kick”, launching the player in front of him into the air. His right hand whistled forward with a “Collapsing Fist”, blowing away players on either side of him, while sending an attack towards his target.

The battle had only just begun, yet the other side had knocked back two players and knocked up another one. The spectators weren’t sure if it was because Han Wenqing was too good, or whether it was because the opponents were too bad.

Han Wenqing said he planned on encountering Lord Grim and completely ignore the players he knocked aside. His character continued forward and welcomed Lord Grim.

Han Wenqing attacked!

He initiated with a Dashing Jab, which Lord Grim leapt back to avoid. His Striker immediately switched from a punch to a kick. His Front Kick seemed to have borrowed the momentum from the Dashing Jab and tore through the air ferociously towards Lord Grim.

A light cloud of smoke dispersed. The Front Kick had only connected with Lord Grim’s Shadow Clone.

The spectating Jiang You almost shouted it out. He had seen the moment Lord Grim had used his Shadow Clone Technique and flashed behind the Striker.

Han Wenqing’s character passed through the light smoke and turned around. Lord Grim’s battle lance stabbed towards him like a viper.

In this type of situation, being able to dodge this attack would make you feel lucky, but Han Wenqing wasn’t normal. He didn’t dodge and instead, immediately stepped forward. He still planned on attacking.

His two hands crossed and pushed forward to block the incoming lance. Level 30 Striker Dismantle Skill: Empty-Handed Blade Block.

Dismantle skills were a type of special attack. The skill was split into two parts: using a parry against the opponent’s attack, and then a counter-attack.

When the Dismantle skill appeared, the Block and Counter were one. Once the player successfully blocked the opponent’s attack, the following part of the Dismantle would definately hit. In other words, as long as the first part of the skill succeeded, then there was a 100% chance to interrupt the incoming attack and make a counter-attack.

However, using a Dismantle skill wasn’t that easy to activate successfully.

First, the precondition was that the player had to Block the attack, so the Dismantle could only be used when the other player attacked. If the Block failed, there would be no second activation of the Dismantle. If the other side didn’t move, your Empty-Handed Strikes the Blade would be wasted.

Han Wenqing wouldn’t retreat and instead continued forward. He was planning on Dismantling Lord Grim and striking back with the greatest power he possessed.

Chapter 252 – Strike First

Han Wenqing’s Striker put both his hands together. At this moment, Lord Grim’s lance stabbed forward and there didn’t seem to be enough time for him to draw it back. However, the lance suddenly swooshed and the umbrella canopy opened outwards. Lord Grim tugged backwards and the front half of the lance was withdrawn this way.

The Striker’s two hands connected with nothing but air. His “Empty-Handed Blade Block” had failed. Even an experienced expert like Han Wenqing wasn’t able to react in time to the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s sudden transformation.

The Thousand Chance Umbrella was lifted and the tip faced forward, exposing a black muzzle. A spark flew out and three Anti-Tank Missiles flew out.

Anti-Tank Missiles at this range would make most people feel hopeless, but Han Wenqing was someone who didn’t know the word hopeless. At this moment, his choice was the same as it was before, attack!

As the gun fired the Anti-Tank Missiles, his Striker moved forward.

Bang!!

The smoke and the fire from the explosions quickly dispersed, but Han Wenqing’s Striker hadn’t stopped or dodged. His Striker tore through the smoke and continued to rush towards Lord Grim. The three Anti-Tank Missiles had been struck down by his punches.

The Anti-Tank Missiles’ explosions should have caused a slight knock-back and a brief stun effect. The reason Han Wenqing’s Striker was able to continue pushing forward was because of a certain Striker skill.

Striker Level 15 skill: Reinforced Iron Bones.

The skill lasted twenty seconds and during those twenty seconds, the character’s physical defense would greatly increase and the character would enter a Super Armored state.

Correct. the Super Armor state made the character immune to knockbacks and stuns. This was the reason why his Striker wasn’t affected by the Anti-Tank Missiles crowd control effect. However, Super Armor wasn’t an invincible state. The increased physical defense would only reduce the damage slightly. Yet, even then, Han Wenqing didn’t hesitate to use Reinforced Iron Bones.

What he needed was not to retreat, but to advance forward!

His tough attitude made Jiang You and the other spectators go into a frenzy. They had tried their hardest to resist shouting, but they were all hating how they couldn’t fight alongside Han Wenqing.

They were filled with hope and hoped that his punch would teach Lord Grim a lesson.

In the end, Lord Grim had anticipated Han Wenqing’s punch. When he used the Anti-Tank Missiles, his character jumped slightly and flew back slightly, using the recoil to gain momentum. The Striker’s fists had missed.

While the spectators sighed in regret, Han Wenqing didn’t seem to notice. His character continued to rush forward. It looked as if he wouldn’t be able to catch up to the flying Lord Grim, but then his hands suddenly shot forward and threw out a Sand Toss.

Sand Toss was a Brawler skill. Both the Brawler and the Striker were of the Fighter class. Any skill that was learned before changing classes could be kept. However, because the number of skill points was limited. Players had no way of learning all the skills. Since they couldn’t even max all of their own class’s specialized skills, which skills, Level 20 and below, to learn was under constant debate. Which ones to learn, which ones not to learn, and which level was good enough were all common issues.

This Striker had chosen to learn Sand Toss and for Lord Grim, it wasn’t going to be easy to dodge. The damage from this skill wasn’t high, but the troublesome part was the bonus Blind effect. Even though the opponent could turn his camera to avoid it, in a battle between experts, turning away for even a split second wasn’t any different than a short Blind.

Ye Xiu obviously didn’t want to give Han Wenqing this type of opportunity. His Thousand Chance Umbrella opened up and the Sand Toss only hit his umbrella. When he looked again, Han Wenqing’s Striker pushed his hands forward and a Qi Bullet flew out.

“Oh?”

Qi Bullet was a Qi Master skill. Sand Toss was probably learned because of its Blind effect, but Qi Bullet was just a normal flying projectile. The damage itself wasn’t bad, but the problem was that it did magic damage. Qi Master is a class that mainly dealt magic damage, and since Strikers relied on physical attacks, they couldn’t use the skill to its full potential. Such an uncommon skill was completely out of Ye Xiu’s expectations.

The Qi Bullet was shot out quickly, but its movement speed wasn’t too fast, so Ye Xiu was able to dodge it, but the Striker used this opportunity of time to close in and continued with his plan of taking the first strike.

He initiated with a Front Kick, which Lord Grim sidestepped to dodge, but unexpectedly, the Striker immediately turned his hand over and followed up with a palm strike.

Ye Xiu hastily leaped backward and just barely dodged the palm.

Slap was a low-leveled Brawler skill and most other classes wouldn’t choose to learn it, however, this Striker did.

The Slap missed but the Striker shot forward with a Dashing Jab, following closely behind Lord Grim. Han Wenqing deserved to be called a God. His kick, slap, and punch, three skills, were linked together perfectly without any pauses in between.

Lord Grim’s movements weren’t slow either. A normal step, a small hop backwards, and then a side roll. These were three movements done perfectly to avoid the three attacks.

Jiang You and the other spectators stared at each other. It was becoming more and more evident just how skilled Lord Grim was.

Even though Lord Grim was currently being pressed on by the God Han Wenqing, he hadn’t taken any significant damage yet. Speaking of this, how many players wouldn’t feel pressed when fighting against Han Wenqing? Han Wenqing was an extremely aggressive player. Using Reinforced Iron Bones to take the hit and continue forward was his style.

Lord Grim rolled back up but Han Wenqing’s Striker had already closed the gap. Han Wenqing jumped forward, just barely off the ground, and kicked.

This was the Striker’s Eagle Stamp. The effect was similar to Huang Shaotian’s Falling Light Blade. The two had both used their respective skills as soon as their characters left the ground to execute the skill extremely quickly.

Lord Grim had only just gotten up and was finally unable to dodge. The Eagle Stamp connected with his head and he was quickly kicked twice soon after.

Eagle Stamp’s damage wasn’t bad, but if the consecutive stamps weren’t done quickly or accurately enough, the opponent could escape from it. Han Wenqing obviously wouldn’t make such a mistake. When Han Wenqing or a God-level player did such actions, such difficult aerial maneuvers could be done perfectly.

Han Wenqing continued with his fierce attacks. As soon as his Eagle Stamp finished, he immediately used a Collapsing Fist since Eagle Stamp couldn’t cause the opponent to become dizzy. As soon as Lord Grim saw the fist fly towards him, his Thousand Chance Umbrella immediately split into Tonfas. His right hand shot out and reached out towards the Striker’s fist.

The Striker was grabbed, lifted onto Lord Grim’s shoulder, and then thrown backwards onto the ground.

Grappler Level 20 Dismantle skill: Receiving Throw.

Chapter 253 – To Retreat By Advancing

“Ah!!”

This time, quite a few of the spectators shouted in astonishment.

In their eyes, Han Wenqing had been pressing forward extremely hard. It was already quite amazing that Lord Grim was able to endure for so long. Finally, when Lord Grim had been Eagle Stamped, they thought that victory was in hand. But just now, Han Wenqing’s Striker was suddenly hit by the opponent’s Dismantle.

The Receive and Throw’s damage couldn’t compare to Eagle Stamp’s, but receiving the opponent’s attack and then throwing him onto the ground looked much more devastating than Eagle Stamp’s movements.

Lord Grim didn’t throw the Striker out with his Receive and Throw. He instead kept the Striker near, not allowing him time to Quick Recover.

“If I don’t leave you with some black and blue to look at in the mirror then you’d be too arrogant.” Ye Xiu said after throwing Han Wenqing onto the ground.

“So it really is you.” Han Wenqing replied. He wasn’t surprised.

As rivals, they were really too familiar each other. After fighting for a bit, Ye Xiu was already completely certain that the Striker was Han Wenqing. And even though Ye Xiu wasn’t using his signature Battle Mage, his pathing, decision-making, and other battle habits had already been seen through by Han Wenqing, who was also certain that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu.

“Who? Who??” Jiang You and the other spectators began muttering amongst each other.

They couldn’t hear the opponent’s voice in-game, but they could hear what Han Wenqing said because he was in the same room as them.

Lord Grim is someone their God recognizes? Jiang You and the other spectators trembled.

Meanwhile, on the screen, Lord Grim didn’t follow up on the fallen Striker and instead waited for Han Wenqing’s Striker to get up.

Are they not going to fight? The spectators were puzzled.

From start to finish, they had been locked onto Han Wenqing’s and Lord Grim’s 1v1. And what about the other players? They hastily checked the rest of the fight, and they only had one thought in their hearts: disaster.

An utter disaster. Lord Grim’s four teammates had been flattened so badly they probably didn’t know which way north and west was anymore. The Sharpshooter and Blade Master even looked powerful and mighty in front of them, which made Jiang You quite jealous.

It wasn’t hard to see that Lord Grim’s four teammates were the same as the previous Zero Kills. They were easily cleaned up.

‘Who exactly is Lord Grim? What is he trying to do?” Jiang You wasn’t able to understand. When they looked back, Han Wenqing and Lord Grim were once again fighting. But so what? Once those four cheerleaders died, they would just gang up on him…….

“Why fight so seriously?” Ye Xiu chuckled.

Han Wenqing didn’t reply and kept on attacking ferociously.

After a few rounds, one of his strikes connected with Lord Grim again.

Jiang You and the other spectators’ hearts had leapt into their throats. But in the end, Lord Grim didn’t counter and was then beaten up by the Striker.

Seeing Lord Grim being beaten up so badly should have been something to celebrate. Jiang You didn’t know why, but currently he didn’t feel anything from it.

Han Wenqing comboed and then suddenly stopped mid-way.

Lord Grim’s body fell. To everyone’s surprise, he didn’t even Quick Recover. He just lay there, not moving.

It was strange that an expert like Lord Grim wouldn’t move.

Was he already dead? But when they looked at his character’s health, Lord Grim was still far from dying!

The spectators were bewildered. They stealthily glanced at Han Wenqing and discovered that his face was like the calm before a storm. They held their breaths.

The spectators were trying to figure out what was going on, when Lord Grim finally jumped back up.

“Sorry, I had to leave for a sec. Huh, why aren’t I dead yet?” Ye Xiu said.

韩

Han Wenqing didn’t say anything and then immediately pounced forward. He had felt it before, which is why he suddenly stopped.

At this moment, the other eight players’ battle had ended. How could some random players be an opponent for two pro-players and two in-game elites?

After the four cleaned up the cheerleaders, they rushed over and arrived at where the other two were dueling. But none of them moved to surround Lord Grim.

Should they move? Seeing that Zhang Xinjie and Bai Yanfei weren’t moving, the Sharpshooter and the Blade Master did the same and just watched in silence.

Since they were fighting next to their God, they weren’t negligent in the slightest against the cheerleaders. They had been completely focused on their battles and hadn’t been paying attention to the battle here.

The two prepared to enter the battle at any moment, but it didn’t seem like they needed to! Under Han Wenqing’s fierce attacks, Lord Grim looked to be struggling to stand up. It didn’t look like he had any chance of fighting back.

“That was to be expected! In front of Han Wenqing, what was Lord Grim?” the Sharpshooter and Blade Master thought simultaneously.

But Jiang You and the other spectators didn’t think like this. Their minds were still pondering over of that sudden Receive and Throw’s speed and accuracy. Except, after that, Lord Grim never really showed up again. He had been taking a beating the entire time. He even stopped moving for a bit. But after standing up, nothing changed.

It was just a matter of time before Lord Grim lost. But Jiang You still felt uneasy. He felt that the loss was too unusual. It seemed like he was losing on purpose.

Right before Lord Grim’s health bar ran out, Han Wenqing stopped his attack once again.

‘What are you doing? Just a bit more. Hurry up.” Ye Xiu said.

“What are you trying to do?” Han Wenqing asked.

“Old friend Han, your attitude is certainly deserved. But it’s just a small match…… Of course I know that you always like to go all out.” Ye Xiu continued, “It’s just that, at our age, we should slow down a bit. You’ve probably felt it.”

“Sorry, I only know how to go forward. I don’t understand what “slow down” means.” Han Wenqing said.

“Then, hurry up.” Ye Xiu had Lord Grim step forward into Han Wenqing’s attack range.

“If you’ve already recognized that you’ve lost, then leave the stage yourself!” Han Wenqing said.

“Leaving doesn’t mean I recognize that I’ve lost.” Ye Xiu laughed. Lord Grim left and the system proclaimed Tyrannical Ambition’s team as the victor.

Jiang You and the other spectators in the room as well as others who were watching in-game all felt a bit puzzled, but all in all, they won and their happiness instantly washed over their bit of doubt. Their biggest worry now was whether Lord Grim would do as he said he would.

“You’ve lost!” Cold Night immediately messaged.

“Yeah, in the future, I won’t touch your guild’s records.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ha ha ha, that’s good. Then, we’ll continue to be friends. If you ever need anything, then you can come talk to us.” Cold Night was incomparably happy.

Ye Xiu simply replied with a smiley face.

“What do you say we take Line Canyon’s record tonight?” Cold Night asked Jiang You.

“It’s finally over.” Jiang You let out a sigh of relief, “If the other guilds want to compete with Lord Grim, then let them. We’ve finished our matters. In the future, we’ll keep good relations with Lord Grim. This guy seems to have some sort of background. I’m going to ask the team captain about it in a bit.”

“Okay, that’s what I thought, too.” Cold Night said.

Meanwhile, Ye Xiu opened up his friends list and messaged someone.

“Are you interested in Line Canyon’s record?”

“Of course….. but we can only rely on ourselves, God. We can’t look to you for help anymore.” Blue River replied.

“I know. I won’t be moving. I have a guide with me here. Would you like to take a look?”

Chapter 254 – By Proxy

“Guide? What guide?’ Blue River was somewhat puzzled.

“A guide for setting the record.” Ye Xiu replied casually. The guide was based on Concealed Light’s version. After a few days of hard work, Concealed Light finally finished an accurate guide for how to set the record. Ye Xiu had checked it seriously and didn’t find any problems with it. It could be said that if you followed the guide step by step with a team without any equipment issues, then anyone could participate in the competition for the dungeon record. Afterwards, it just depended on who carried the guide out the best.

However, Concealed Light’s guide wasn’t anything out of the box. In other words, Concealed Light’s guide was detailed and precise, but it wasn’t anything new. It wasn’t that Blue River and the other experienced players didn’t understand the strategy the guide used. It was just that they hadn’t played a low-leveled dungeon in a long time, so they were unfamiliar with it. Concealed Light’s guide let them save time by researching the things they had forgotten or weren’t used to, allowing them to directly practice with a complete strategy.

But the guide Ye Xiu presented wasn’t the same as Concealed Light’s guide. He had made a few revisions on Concealed Light’s version.

These revisions were new strategies that had never been talked about before in Line Canyon. They were similar to the new strategy Ye Xiu had come up with for Boneyard. This type of new strategy wasn’t something that Concealed Light, who didn’t have any actual experience, could come up with.

“A guide for setting the record?” Blue River was still suspicious.

“Correct. As long as you follow it, then I can guarantee that you guys will stand on top of the record boards.” Ye Xiu was very confident.

“Really? Then, let me study it.” Blue River said.

“Bro, there’s a tuition fee.”

Blue River stared blankly. In that instant, he understood what was going on.

Thise God had changed his approach!

Currently, it was very difficult for him to continue substituting in and setting the record for the guild. This was because Lord Grim was too good and was too famous. Whenever a record came out with his name, he would be the only person the players would see, and thus, no one would recognize that record as a reflection of the guild’s strength.

Looking for Lord Grim to set the record for them wasn’t a viable route anymore. But the guilds still needed records and Lord Grim had become a large obstacle for them, which was why seven guilds had allied together to chase down Lord Grim. Blue River knew what had happened in the past few days. He was glad that Blue Brook Guild hadn’t participated. God had made the seven guilds suffer miserably.

However, Blue River understood that this God wouldn’t relax. No matter how skilled he was, he was still only a single person and had to divide some of his attention to avoiding the guilds’ pursuit. The battle wasn’t easy for either side.

In Blue River’s eyes, the battle would still be decided by the dungeon records.

If this God was still able to continue forcefully pressing on the dungeon records even while being chased, then the guilds would be forced to compromise. It was very possible that they would eventually have to pay him to not set the record.

Forcefully pressing down on the records wasn’t a problem for this God.

And dealing with the pursuers from the guilds didn’t seem to be much of a problem for this God either.

Using power to subdue the big guilds sounded ridiculous, but it was actually possible for him. That was what Blue River thought after knowing Lord Grim’s identity.

As the guild leader in the new server, he understood the progress of each of the guilds. At this moment, the elite teams were about to reach Level 34. Line Canyon’s final record would be set tonight.

And currently, it was very possible that the not yet Level 33 Lord Grim would level up later and then take down the record that would be set tonight. It was also possible that he would set another astonishing record right now at his current level.

Blue River hadn’t completely given up on setting new records. He had only given up on competing with this God. In other words, Blue River was prepared to pay him to not set new records. It was just that they had to take down the record first.

And amidst this, the God came to him to try and sell him some guide……

He deserved to be a God. His line of thinking was clear and he knew that the dungeon records were still the only solution to the current conflict. However, he hadn’t thought of forcefully subduing the guilds with his records and had instead chosen a different method to help the guilds set the record.

Lord Grim didn’t care about having his name on the records, but he needed the materials. As a result, he chose to sell his strategies.

Too smart! Blue River couldn’t help but praise him. By doing this, he would drop the guilds’ enmity while making a profit. His method was too beautiful.

Blue River completely understood what this God was trying to do. He also knew that this God wasn’t hiding anything from him.

“I understand.” Blue River replied.

Blue River didn’t doubt the reliability of the guide. This was because he knew Lord Grim’s identity. It would be an easy task for God Ye Qiu to make a guide. Before, everyone had been puzzled about how he had set those astonishing records. And now the answer was almost in front of them.

“Can I ask a question?” Blue River suddenly asked.

“What question?”

“Why did you choose Blue Brook Guild?” Blue River asked.

“Choose? That’s not right. I just picked a random guild to ask. If you don’t want it, then I’ll ask another one.” Ye Xiu replied.

“So it’s like that. I do want it.”

“Then let’s discuss the price.”

“But I can’t take it this time.” Blue River said again, “Before this, we made an agreement with Tyrannical Ambition that they wouldn’t touch Desolate Land’s dungeon record, while we wouldn’t touch Line Canyon’s record.”

“So it’s like that! Then you’ve lost a good opportunity. I’m very sorry.”

“Can I ask for the guide for the Fire Forest dungeon record in advance?” Blue River asked.

“Hmm……. let’s talk about it later!” Ye Xiu replied.

Blue River was sad. He was afraid of the words “let’s talk about it later”. Previously, when he was still looking for Lord Grim to set the record for them, he had gotten “let’s talk about it later” as replies. And every time, a different guild had taken the opportunity. If he knew that the situation would come to this, then he wouldn’t have made the agreement with Tyrannical Ambition.

“What a pity.” Ye Xiu felt sorry for Blue River and then chose a different target on his friends list.

These other guild leaders longed for the records. Sure enough, Ye Xiu messaged Misty Castle’s guild leader, who immediately replied back saying he was interested.

Knowing that there would be a price, the guild leader sent an emoticon with its cheeks streaming with tears and then asked for the price.

Ye Xiu’s asking price was very reasonable, so there was no haggling over the price. In any case, neither side would have budged.

After just a few words, they finished discussing about the price. But because it was their first time collaborating, both sides needed to communicate a bit more.

After all, this time, Ye Xiu wasn’t going to personally substitute in. If he was going to, then the record was guaranteed. As for buying the guide, Ye Xiu could only guarantee that there weren’t any problems with the guide; he couldn’t guarantee that Misty Castle’s players could completely follow the guide’s requirements. This wasn’t something he had control over.

Misty Castle’s guild leader wanted to pay the materials after they had successfully set the record. Ye Xiu continued to say that there were absolutely no problems with the guide and he would receive the pay as soon as he gave them the guide. As for whether or not they could set the record, that depended on themselves.

The two argued for a long time over this issue, yet no conclusion was made.

Chapter 255 – What Does He Gain?

Misty Castle’s guild leader was indecisive. After pondering over it for a while, he still hadn’t come to a decision. Ye Xiu could only patiently explain to him his guide.

Before, when Ye Xiu went to look for Blue Brook Guild, he had said that he just picked a random guild. In reality, that was a lie. Selling the guide was different from personally setting the record for the guild. No matter what guild it was, as long as he subbed in, Ye Xiu would take down the record – guaranteed. But the guide was different.

The guide was only something on a piece of paper. Whether or not you could complete what was on the paper was a completely different matter.

Why were most of the records held by the Three Great Guilds? Strength! Even with the guide, the buyer still had to perform.

Top-tier guilds undoubtedly had the advantage when it came to the number of talents they possessed. For example, the group of five that Jiang You lead had good mechanics and were outstanding in their ability to implement a guide. With Ye Xiu’s guide, they would certainly be able to set an incredible record.

And what about the big guilds who had slightly fewer talents? They would be the same as Misty Castle. They would hesitate over whether they should buy the guide or not.

Misty Castle’s guild leader didn’t doubt that the guide was real. He was just worried that their guild’s players weren’t talented enough. If their guild acquired the guide, but weren’t able to take the record, then wouldn’t that be like drawing water with a sieve?

This was why he hoped that they could have the right to return the product. Even though Ye Xiu refused it, Ye Xiu understood what the other side was thinking. At this moment, if this was some other guild, then they would probably be the same. Misty Castle was already considered one of the stronger guilds.

“Don’t worry about the guide. There aren’t any complicated or unfamiliar maneuvers you have to do. If you find a few experts and practice, then there definitely won’t be a problem.” Ye Xiu tried to ease Misty Castle’s guild leader’s anxiety.

After another long pause, Misty Castle’s guild leader reluctantly replied with an “Alright then.”

Thus, Ye Xiu immediately asked the other side for his e-mail address and sent the revised version of Concealed Light’s guide to him.

Misty Castle’s guild leader impatiently opened it.

“So long!” He just saw the article’s page length and was already astonished. He then checked the detailed directions for the final BOSS. He didn’t see anything that was extremely difficult and it really was within their abilities. Only after checking this did he scroll up and take a look at the rest of the guide.

Misty Castle’s guild leader was an expert among the experienced players as well, so his vision was quite good. After quickly skimming through two pages, he didn’t find anything wrong with it.

“I’m going to keep reading.” Misty Castle’s guild leader tabbed back to the game and called out to Lord Grim.

“Take your time.” Ye Xiu wasn’t worried. The guide didn’t have any problems and Misty Castle was a guild backed by a Club who valued their image greatly, so they definitely wouldn’t go back on their word.

Afterwards, Misty Castle’s guild leader asked a few questions about parts he was uncertain about. Ye Xiu explained each one to him. After a few rounds, he finished looking at the guide.

Misty Castle’s guild leader didn’t find anything wrong with it, so he sent Ye Xiu the materials. After the trade was finished, Ye Xiu looked at the time. It was almost time to change shifts, so he logged out of the game. With a few minutes to spare, he randomly browsed around the internet.

On the forums, Concealed Light had already posted his Line Canyon guide.

It was even longer than the previous Idiot’s Guides, making many intimidated with their first glance at it. However, the amount of mocking lessened and many began to seriously comment on it.

Club Tyranny.

Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie, Bai Yanfei. After finishing their match in-game, they didn’t stay in their guild’s studio and went back to do their own business.

Without a doubt, the match had been utterly boring.

Zhang Xinjie’s and Bai Yanfei’s fight against the four cheerleaders didn’t need to be talked about.

Even though Han Wenqing fought against his old rival, Ye Qiu hadn’t been trying at all. If Ye Qiu had only fought like this previously, then Han Wenqing would have confirmed his status as fully retired. However, Ye Qiu clearly proved himself with the Receiving Throw, which Han Wenqing was unable to defend against. Ye Qiu just hadn’t been taking it seriously.

“Why?” Zhang Xinjie didn’t understand, “Looking at his performance today, he was clearly planning on losing.”

“He would never do something that had no purpose. This means that him losing was in his interests.” Han Wenqing said.

“That’s why I say that he had already decided to lose this match long ago.” Zhang Xinjie said.

“If he loses, then he won’t touch Tyrannical Ambition’s records. But at the same time, Tyrannical Ambition won’t make trouble for him, too. This might be what he wanted to achieve.” Han Wenqing said.

“What does he gain from this?”

“Time.” Han Wenqing answered bluntly.

Zhang Xinjie stared blankly, though he sort of understood.

“You don’t actually think that guy truly plans on retiring for good, do you?” Han Wenqing said, “In maybe another year, we might meet him in an official match.” Han Wenqing suddenly lowered his head and looked at his right hand, which then clenched into a fist.

When Han Wenqing and the two other pro-players left the studio, Jiang You mustered up his courage and asked who exactly Lord Grim was.

“Ye Qiu.” Han Wenqing threw down the name and left.

Jiang You and everyone else in the room were obviously dumbstruck. The thought that Lord Grim was such a person hadn’t come across their minds before.

But they didn’t revere Ye Qiu in any way. He was Tyranny’s archenemy. Of course, they completely understood their archenemy’s strength. After finally knowing who they had been up against, their hearts relaxed a little.

Losing to a God wasn’t shameful in any way. Plus, their team captain had helped take revenge for them.

But because of this, they still had to change some of their plans. Jiang You contacted Cold Night: “Maintain contact with Lord Grim, but there’s no need to rope him in.”

“Why?”

“Do you know who Lord Grim is?” After knowing that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu, Jiang You couldn’t imagine what type of conditions he’d have to give to rope in such a God.

“Who?” Cold Night asked.

“Ye Qiu.” Jiang You bluntly replied like Han Wenqing had. Saying the name in such a way was just as if he was the team captain. Jiang You wanted to copy him, but unfortunately, he could only type it out. He hoped that Cold Night would be able to see some of his demeanor from these words!

After a long while, Cold Night finally replied with a single word: D*mn.

“That’s why you don’t need to bother with roping him in!” Jiang You said.

“I understand.” Cold Night replied.

“Tonight will go just as planned. We’ll take down Line Canyon and then go back. The rest is up to you.” Jiang You made a great concluding speech.

“Don’t worry!” Cold Night was full of confidence. Without Lord Grim against them, he wasn’t worried about anyone else.

At midnight, Jiang You’s group gathered together at Line Canyon and headed towards the dungeon.

This was their last night in the tenth server. The five all felt a little nostalgic.

“Playing in the new server is quite fun, too.” The Blade Master said.

“The new server is pretty crazy this time.” The Striker added.

“I’m currently wondering that when Ye Qiu comes to the Heavenly Domain, what will happen then?” The Sharpshooter said.

Everyone fell silent. In their end, they all exposed a somewhat pained expression.

“F*ck. You just had to say that when we were all so happy.”

“My bad…..”

“Okay, let’s take down the record first. Let’s take it down!” Jiang You yelled.

“Understood!!” The four replied.

Even though Ye Qiu’s shadow made them surprised, the five were in high spirits.

After only one run, they broke the Line Canyon dungeon record.

Chapter 256 – The Purpose of a Game

If it was just Tyrannical Ambition setting a dungeon record, then no one would be amazed. After all, the big guilds were going all out at Line Canyon’s dungeon tonight. No guild would let this opportunity go by. And even though Tyrannical Ambition had suffered under a bit of mockery due to Lord Grim’s subbing in, it didn’t affect their fundamental strength. The fight for the dungeon records was as competitive as ever. Every guild understood this, so they weren’t surprised that Tyrannical Ambition’s name was up on TV.

But after seeing Tyrannical Ambition’s time, they couldn’t help but suck in a cold breath.

27:41:24.

In the past few days, Line Canyon’s dungeon record had occasionally changed, but it was always only by a few seconds. When the first place team’s record was only within five seconds of the fifth place team’s record, it indicated that the record had reached a certain limit.

Tyrannical Ambition’s record this time though gave the other big guilds a fright.

Compared to the previous record, their record had improved the time by a full two minutes.

Was this actually Tyrannical Ambition? Quite a few players had their doubts and checked the team’s roster on the leaderboards, searching hard for Lord Grim’s name. Everyone failed to find it, though. Tyrannical Ambition. It was the real Tyrannical Ambition. All of the big guilds had a spy network. They had information on the five Tyrannical Ambition names. They were true members of the guild.

However, with a sudden move, they actually improved the time by two minutes.

Normally, it was very rare for players to leave room for improvement for dungeon records. After all, these required perfect playing. A single small mistake could even cause them to restart. And this type of mistake wasn’t something that they could avoid. Everyone made mistakes. As a result, whenever it was time to set a record, every team would go at it their hardest. Whichever team could achieve the most perfect run would set the final record.

But Tyrannical Ambition’s record showed that they had the strength to beat the record by over two minutes, which they hadn’t shown until now. Two minutes was a lot. Making up for this time with a few less mistakes wasn’t easy. In Tyrannical Ambition’s run to achieve the record of 27 minutes, if they had made mistakes here and there, then they probably would have been in the 28-29 minute range.

But they didn’t. Previously, there hadn’t been any records under 29 minutes.

Tyrannical Ambition’s record was truly astonishing. Was it something they were always capable of doing or was it because they had run the dungeon perfectly? Even if they knew the answer to this, it was pointless. From now on, all the guilds would have to attempt to beat this record.

Two minutes after Tyrannical Ambition set their record, new records began showing up on the leaderboards. Two guilds had surpassed their previous records and one of them had even entered below the 30 minute mark.

But compared to 27:41:24, the two records were too far off. They obviously wouldn’t be shown on TV; they could only silently take the second and third place. No one could deny their efforts, but the greatest applause would be reserved for those who took first place. The second, third, and even the fourth and fifth places would increase a guild’s reputation a bit, but they couldn’t compete with those who took first place.

First place and second place were sometimes only off by a second. But the titles “first”and “second” made others feel that the distance between the two placers was miles apart.

The guilds had all done their research on how to run the dungeon. They all knew just how difficult it was to achieve 27:41:24.

When Tyrannical Ambition’s record came out, one third of the competitors immediately gave up. Another one third continued to run the dungeon as planned, but none of them knew if they could achieve such a record. They could only pray towards the heavens. Apart from this, the remaining one third clenched their teeth and continued to batter at the records. They felt that there was no reason they couldn’t achieve Tyrannical Ambition’s record.

Herb Garden, Excellent Dynasty, Samsara…… the guilds that had allied against Lord Grim didn’t give up. This wasn’t a coincidence. These guilds had clearly spent much effort chasing down Lord Grim for the benefit of all. Just by looking at how they joined in on such a movement showed their desire for the records. How could they give up now?

27 minutes! The elites from every guild stared at the number…..

“27:41 by Tyrannical Ambition. It looks pretty good!” Tang Rou noticed it the instant the announcement was made. She remembered most names of the guilds she had encountered. In the beginning, she hadn’t taken them seriously. But after chatting with Chen Guo, she discovered that these were all top-tier guilds in Glory. Chen Guo, who had been playing the game for a long time, was more clear on how strong each of the guilds was. All in all, Ye Xiu hadn’t played in the normal servers for a long time, so he was picking up a lot of new things as he played.

Tyrannical Ambition was extremely strong. Ye Xiu had never said this, but Chen Guo had talked a lot about them. Even though Tang Rou couldn’t see how Tyrannical Ambition was strong, since Chen Guo said so, she should just listen…….

“Eh, it’s okay.” Ye Xiu wasn’t too impressed with Tyrannical Ambition’s record.

“If it was us, how fast could we do it?” Tang Rou asked.

“25 minutes!” Ye Xiu said.

“Are we going to try now?” Tang Rou asked.

Midnight was the high point for running the dungeons, so it wasn’t convenient for them to cause a commotion at this time. There were guild members everywhere at this time. It was very likely that if they were found entering a dungeon, they’d be surrounded as soon as they exited. It had taken them ten minutes to arrive and some more due to caution. As a result, the guilds had already finished running the dungeon once and had just entered for their second try.

Seeing that Tyrannical Ambition had set a relatively impressive record and seeing that Ye Xiu hadn’t talked about the records, Tang Rou couldn’t help but ask.

“There’s no need for us to set records anymore!” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?” Tang Rou asked.

“Because competing for the dungeon records was never our goal! Think about why you play the game.” Ye Xiu said.

“Uh…….” The simple phrase had stumped Tang Rou.

Ye Xiu didn’t care if they weren’t going to set a record. Setting records was just a way for him to gather uncommon materials. He now had other ways of gathering materials, so he didn’t need to clash against the other guilds for the record. With his identity, if word came out that he was competing against these normal players for the dungeon record, then he’d become a laughingstock.

Ye Xiu didn’t care. Su Mucheng obviously didn’t care. Qiao Yifan’s motivation didn’t need to be spoken of either. He came to the new server for personal instruction from a God-level player. After playing with the God for a few days, he already felt he had made a lot of improvement. In the beginning, he wasn’t used to playing a Phantom Demon, but he was becoming more and more familiar with it now. Dungeon records? Qiao Yifan obviously didn’t care about these. He was still a pro-level player. His reason for coming here was to improve. Beating some normal players couldn’t be considered as any improvement in his eyes.

And consequently, only Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion cared a bit more about these records.

Steamed Bun Invasion was more pure. He liked to play the game and he played for fun. With his good attitude, he always found something fun about the game. Setting a record was one of them. But without it, there were still many other things to enjoy.

In the end, the only person who really cared about the records was Tang Rou. This girl was extremely competitive and liked the feeling of competing and surpassing other people. Just as expected, while the others were indifferent about Tyrannical Ambition’s record, Tang Rou asked more about it.

Purpose……

Ye Xiu’s question had made Tang Rou feel at a loss for words.

“To beat you.” After a few moments, Tang Rou blurted it out. It was the original reason she had played Glory, the game she hadn’t found interesting. The game had a lot of content, but Tang Rou’s original reason hadn’t changed. Whether it was in dungeoning or PK, she frequently paid attention to Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, constantly comparing each other’s performance.

Even though she was getting more familiar with the game, she only felt how large the gap between them was. This didn’t make her dispirited, though.

She first had to figure out where their differences were and how great the differences were.

To her, it had only just begun. The ever impulsive and rash Tang Rou had already gotten rid of the idea of continuously challenging him until she beat him. She was now preparing a plan to surpass him.

She learned from Ye Xiu while watching the distance between them. She would then fix whatever she needed to fix. Tang Rou had her own plan in mind. She wasn’t like Steamed Bun Invasion who said this and that and stupidly laughed.

Tang Rou didn’t relax when she played, which was very different from Steamed Bun Invasion’s playing for fun.

However, for Tang Rou, this was what made her feel that the game was fun. If it was something that was just for her to relax, then she’d only feel bored.

After reminding Tang Rou her purpose for playing the game, Ye Xiu then casually said: “Then why are you setting records?”

Chapter 257 – Appropriate Handling

Why am I setting records?

Tang Rou didn’t know the answer. The question stumped her! Wasn’t Ye Xiu the one who brought them over in order to set records? He had even made them undergo practice every day for each of the dungeons, yet he’s suddenly asking why she’s setting records?

“Why were you setting records?” Tang Rou asked back.

“I was doing it for uncommon materials. Everyone knows that. What about the rest of you?” Ye Xiu asked again.

“To learn from senior and improve.” Qiao Yifan replied without any hesitation.

“Ha ha ha, playing with senior’s more fun.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Ha ha.” Su Mucheng only laughed. She didn’t say anything.

“Mu Mu……” Tang Rou tried to win over a comrade-in-arms. The two were quite close with one another.

Su Mucheng could only say the truth: “I did it to help him get materials.”

The cruel reality was displayed in front of her eyes. No one on the team had really cared about the dungeon records.

“It’s still dungeoning. Even if we just casually set it, it’d be good too!” Tang Rou struggled.

“That’s true.” Ye Xiu said, “But in our current situation, if we continued to monopolize the records, then those others guilds won’t stop bothering us. It’s not worth it to get caught up with them.”

Ye Xiu brought the discussion to the main point. This was his true reason for not setting records.

With his experience and skill, he wasn’t scared of the threat from these guilds. If he was only playing the game for fun, he probably would have chosen to play around with the other guilds. But that wasn’t the case. Even if he killed all of the players from these guilds, what would be the point?

“There’s nothing wrong with setting dungeon records, but in our current state, the result from setting a record would just cause us to waste a great deal of our time. We aren’t scared of these guilds, but fighting with them isn’t our reason for playing the game.” Ye Xiu said.

“Senior! Senior! I find stealing their BOSSes to be quite fun.” Steamed Bun Invasion energetically said.

“Steamed Bun ah, this is only the new server. Stealing these low-leveled BOSSes is too unstylish! Let’s hurry up and level. When we get to the Heavenly Domain, there will be more BOSSes and more experts. The guilds over there will also be stronger so you tell me, doesn’t that sound more fun?”

“Hm…..” Steamed Bun Invasion replied and after thinking for five seconds, he yelled: “Let’s hurry and level up, everyone!”

Tang Rou was speechless. This Steamed Bun was a little bit too easy to sway.

“Yeah! Let’s hurry and go to the Heavenly Domain.” Ye Xiu said, while sending Tang Rou a personal message: “Our boss is waiting for you there!”

This guy!

Tang Rou was startled. Her treatment towards Chen Guo, due to playing like crazy, really was a secret worry of hers for these past few days. She wanted to play with Chen Guo, but the two were in different servers. Even if they sat together, they were still only playing on their own and couldn’t party up with each other.

Ye Xiu looked as if he was even more crazy about the game than she was, but he was still able to pay attention to all of this. The guy had been trying to reason with her at first and now he was trying to play the emotional route…..

However, it really was a good point! After hearing all this, Tang Rou discovered that her desire to level up grew stronger. Setting dungeon records or whatever had been pushed to the back of her mind.

Tang Rou thought for a bit and then replied: “Okay, then let’s hurry and level up!”

“Good! That’s what I wanted to hear!” Ye Xiu said.

“We’ve got to level up quickly. Everyone dungeon faster!!” Tang Rou yelled.

“Wha?” Ye Xiu stared stupidly. Leveling faster did mean that they should dungeon faster, but didn’t dungeoning faster mean that they would be trying to set dungeon records? He looked at the following message and saw an evil smiley face from Tang Rou. Ye Xiu knew that she was intentionally teasing him. He replied with a sweating face.

“Try hard. It doesn’t matter what your goal is.” Tang Rou replied again.

“You have to try harder. Your goal is to beat me, but the difficulty is too great.”

After some time, Ye Xiu received another message from Tang Rou: “I looked for a long time, but there’s no emoticon that describes what I’m feeling right now.”

“Ha ha.“ Ye Xiu laughed. He was finally able to get her to accept it and his opinion of her went up. This girl wasn’t someone who only acted on her own.

Tang Rou didn’t reply, but Ye Xiu was still busy typing. As he dungeoned, he continued to chat with two people.

One of them was Concealed Light. His newly issued Idiot’s Guide had been received quite well, but there were still quite a few criticisms. One of the commenters had even criticized him without even looking at the guide. Concealed Light looked at the comments the entire day. He would even argue with some of them and all that came out of it was concealed anger. He was now pouring out his grievances at Ye Xiu.

“There will always be people like this. You don’t need to worry about them. Your guides don’t have any mistakes in them and if they don’t believe that, then it’s their fault.” Ye Xiu replied.

“But some of them clearly hadn’t read it, yet they still criticized it.” Concealed Light gloomily said.

“If they didn’t even look at your guides, why are you even looking at their comments?” Ye Xiu said.

“I only found out after I finished reading their comments!” Concealed Light said.

Ye Xiu didn’t know what to say. Why was it that this kid so one-track minded like Steamed Bun Invasion?

“If they didn’t see your guide, then there’s no point taking note of their comments.” Ye Xiu plainly said.

“Sigh sigh sigh…….” Concealed Light sighed. God’s words had made him feel a bit better, but his anger wouldn’t go away so easily. Concealed Light told Ye Xiu that he agreed with him, but still couldn’t help looking at the comments.

“But it’s true that your guide hasn’t reached its limit.” Ye Xiu messaged again.

“Ah?”

“It’s not your fault. With your circumstances, it’s already incredible that you’ve reached such a level. It’s very difficult to come up with something new only by watching videos and reading other guides. Coming up with something new requires actual experience and testing, which are two things you lack. I made a revised version of your guide that you should take a look at!”

“Ah? Your version?” Concealed Light asked.

“Yeah!” Ye Xiu said, while sending Concealed Light his version via QQ.

Concealed Light immediately received it and quickly looked at it. He then replied: “Ah! So you could do it like that! I should have thought about that!!”

“Of course you’ll suddenly see it now.” Ye Xiu said.

Concealed Light continued to look, while discussing with Ye Xiu.

“How do you usually level up?” Ye Xiu asked Concealed Light.

“Quests…….”

“You can’t find anyone to party with?” Ye Xiu asked. Summoners, especially new Summoners, have a hard time finding parties. When Summoners fought, if they summoned too few creatures, their damage would be too low; If they summoned too many however, their control over them would be poor, and then it’d only become a mess with the other team members, which was extremely irritating. As a result, fewer and fewer players liked Summoners. In the end, it caused so many Summoners to stand outside the dungeon entrance that they earned the nickname “Dungeon Guards”.

“Yeah……” Concealed Light replied, confirming Ye Xiu’s assumptions.

“Actually, for a five-player dungeon, Summoners have the ability to solo it. Even though it’ll definitely be a lot slower than it would be with five players, your experience gain will be a lot greater. If you get good, your experience gain speed won’t be any lower than one person in a five-man party.” Ye Xiu possessed the skill to solo a five-man dungeon with any class. But for a normal player, Summoners were good for soloing.

“Uh, I’ve…. tried it before.” Concealed Light replied. Most Summoners would research how to solo a dungeon. Some were able to persist while others failed. Concealed Light seemed to be in the latter category.

“In a bit, if you have time, I’ll bring you along for a run!” Ye Xiu said. With Concealed Light’s mechanics, Ye Xiu reckoned that soloing probably couldn’t be done.

“Ah, that’s great. Thanks, God.” Concealed Light was naturally very happy. He then asked: “God, are you planning on posting your version?”

“No, it’s for sale.”

“Ah?”

“I’m selling it to those guilds who are setting records to earn some materials.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ha ha ha, too good.”

“So keep it a secret for now or else it won’t be valuable anymore.”

“I understand.” Concealed Light replied. He was able to understand the guide, so naturally he understood the guide’s value. Even though Ye Xiu had only changed the guide a little bit, it was clearly much better than it was before. If people wanted a guide for setting a record, then Ye Xiu’s was the real deal.

Chapter 258 – Guide Easter Egg

While Ye Xiu talked with Concealed Light, he was also privately chatting with someone else.

Misty Castle’s tenth server guild leader, Hazy Mist, immediately sent Ye Xiu a massage after seeing Tyrannical Ambition’s record: “Brother, can we beat 27:41?”

“The guide can, but can you?” Ye Xiu replied.

“It seems……. not too likely……” Hazy Mist was quite honest.

“You have to beat it. Right now, everyone’s watching the record. It’s your time to shine.” Ye Xiu said.

“If we don’t set it, can we return it?” Hazy Mist asked.

“I already said no……” Ye Xiu bluntly said.

“Half?”

“Stop bothering me, brother.”

“Aww. Tyrannical Ambition’s too fierce.” Hazy Mist condemned.

“If you still have time to be sad, then hurry up and gather some experts to practice what the guide says!”

“Where am I supposed to find people this late at night? And also, your guide uses a certain class setup. I still haven’t gotten the team together yet!”

“Impossible. You’re lying. I don’t believe you can’t form a team with such a large guild like yours.” Ye Xiu said.

“Alright, I was lying, but it really wasn’t easy to get them together. Is there anything else tricky about it?” Hazy Mist asked.

“None. There really isn’t any. It’s all in the guide.”

“There aren’t any focal points in the guide?”

Ye Xiu suddenly understood and replied: “So that was what you were asking about. Why didn’t you just say it!” Ye Xiu had been wondering what Hazy Mist wanted. He didn’t think that they would suddenly be so close after only talking with each other once.

“You’ve already seen through it? The guide has a few focal points. As long as you do those well, then you might not need to follow every step exactly. If you take those focal points and integrate it into your familiar strategy, then it should work, too. How many of these focal points have you found?” Ye Xiu followed up. For these top-tier players, they already had their own step-by-step method. They didn’t really need such a detailed guide.

“Uh, seven.” Hazy Mist said.

“Which seven?”

“I’ve highlighted them in the file. Can I send it to you to look at?”

“Sure.”

Hazy Mist quickly sent it over. Ye Xiu opened it. The focal points Hazy Mist had found were all the new revisions Ye Xiu had done on Concealed Light’s guide. The ones Hazy Mist had highlighted were all correct. He had found the most important parts of the guide.

“These seven are correct.” Ye Xiu replied, “But there are still two more. I’ve highlighted them and sent it back to you. Go and take a look!”

“Okay, thank you.” Hazy Mist replied. This was the reason he had contacted Lord Grim. When he first looked at the guide, he had noticed a few different points. He then talked about it with the guild and found these seven focal points. But he was worried that they hadn’t found them all, so he ran to ask Lord Grim.

Hazy Mist received the file and then went silent. However, after a short while, Hazy Mist suddenly sent another message: “D*mn! A record came out!!”

“Where?” Ye Xiu didn’t see any announcements. He opened up the leaderboards and it was still Tyrannical Ambition at the top.

“In the seventh server! Holy sh*t!” Hazy Mist sent a going-crazy face.

“What’s the time?” Ye Xiu stifled a laugh as he replied. He obviously understood that Misty Castle wanted to practice using the guide and try it out, but they didn’t want to waste the tries in the tenth server, so they went to a different server to practice. It hadn’t been easy for Hazy Mist. To be able to gather up the people and borrow accounts in under an hour was a testament to his ability. However, they had only been practicing and they had already set a record. If they had known that it would happen like this, then they wouldn’t have gone through the trouble of practicing.

“26:11:45!”

“Not bad! If you brought that over to this server, then you’d shake the server. Are there any reactions on the seventh server?” Ye Xiu asked.

“We earned the “Idling Headache” achievement.” Hazy Mist replied. In the old server, setting a low-leveled dungeon wouldn’t garner much attention.

“Come to the tenth server and run the dungeon!”

“Who knows if we’ll be able to do it this run?”

“I don’t think there will be any problems.” Ye Xiu said. The record they had just set couldn’t have been from following the guide step-by-step. There was no way they could follow and fully understand such a long and tedious guide in such a short amount of time. No one could do that. But the guide was fixed, while people were creative. By grasping the focal points of the guide and then applying it to their regular strategy, that was the most efficient method.

Misty Castle’s experts clearly understood this. They quickly grasped the focal points and combined Ye Xiu’s new guide with their usual strategy to break the record on the seventh server.

“I hope so!” Hazy Mist replied. He seemed very worried, but in reality, he wasn’t worried at all. After finding out how incredible the guide was, he was already full of confidence.

As he chatted, Ye Xiu continued to dungeon. They weren’t pursuing a record, so they weren’t so tense. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion did their limited practice, while Qiao Yifan practiced fighting in different scenarios.

After Tyrannical Ambition’s record came out, a lot of discussion was brought up by normal players. Many guessed when Lord Grim would come out and stomp on the record. A lot of players were even betting on how much he would beat it by.

This run took them 33 minutes, which was very ordinary. But so far, Ye Xiu didn’t see any new announcements.

After a short while, Hazy Mist sent another message saying that they had failed the first run.

“You can do it.” Ye Xiu could only encourage them.

“It’ll definitely come out tonight!” Hazy Mist was extremely confident. Ye Xiu reckoned that the guy had gathered more than one team. They probably had six or nine tries.

The dungeoning continued. Ye Xiu calculated the time and guessed that the guilds should be done with their three runs. Ye Xiu checked the leaderboards. The second and third place spots had been changed, but Tyrannical Ambition was still in first.

Ye Xiu wasn’t surprised by this. The competition was fierce, but Jiang You’s group truly did stand out from everyone else.

News of the guilds began appearing in the world chat. After running the dungeon three times, a lot of the guilds had hit Level 34 and were currently congratulating or bragging to each other. And after this, they were going to compete for the Fire Forest first clear.

A first kill wasn’t as amazing as a dungeon record. But if they still had the chance, it was still worth going for. The members who had just reached Level 34 gathered together and left Line Canyon.

Jiang You’s group should have been part of this group. But unfortunately, after being killed by Lord Grim twice, their experience had decreased and they were still stuck at Level 33.

However, seeing that their record wasn’t even close to being beat, the five felt very happy.

Chapter 259 – Misty Rain

12/24, 2:03 AM.

Tyrannical Ambition’s overall guild leader, as well as the other famous top-tier experts that he had brought over, gave their final blessings after struggling in the tenth server’s pioneering battle.

Jiang You’s group had come to set the record in order to save Tyrannical Ambition from their predicament. At the same time, they had unexpectedly also resolved the Lord Grim problem. They took down Line Canyon’s dungeon record without a hitch. Their mission had been quite successful.

Even after running the dungeon three times, they still weren’t able to beat the record that they had set at the end of the first run. Once they had finished, their mission ended. The reason that they were staying for a while longer was to celebrate with the tenth server’s players and also to see whether Lord Grim would keep his promise to not touch their record.

At this moment, over half an hour had passed since they had exited the dungeon and there hadn’t been any announcements. They had all relaxed. Lord Grim hadn’t beaten their record and hadn’t set a ridiculous record beforehand; nothing bad had happened.

“Okay, the tenth server will now be in your hands.” Jiang You said to the tenth server’s guild leader, Cold Night, and its core members, such as Endless Night. The four elites that had come over were all old core members of Tyrannical Ambition, so the guild members that had come over to pioneer in the tenth server knew them. The four were talking with members one on one, encouraging them.

Just as the friendly ceremony was proceeding, an announcement suddenly popped up. Tyrannical Ambition’s hadn’t noticed it in the beginning. It was only after the announcement had passed by did they realize what the announcement was about……

Not good!!!

Practically everyone realized this simultaneously. In that instant, Tyrannical Ambition’s players all made the same movement: they moved their mice in order to check their messages and read the message that had just been received.

But in reality, they didn’t need to.

While Tyrannical Ambition’s players had been distracted and missed it, the other tenth server players had all seen the message clearly.

The players who had seen it already then began to discuss it amongst themselves. The discussion had caused Tyrannical Ambition’s players to miss the announcement message. But right now, the discussions in the world chat were all talking about what they didn’t want to see.

A new record……

They saw these three words. Tyrannical Ambition’s players hadn’t seen wrong. In that instant, a dungeon record announcement had been made.

Their excited and joyous guild suddenly turned deathly.

Correct, deathly. Even though everyone was sitting in front of their computers looking at their screens, they had all felt as if their souls were leaving them.

Doubt and disbelief……. floated in the air.

“Who was it?” Jiang You suddenly asked. His words were full of bitterness and pain.

Who was it? Wasn’t that an easy thing to check? If a record had come out, then it would show up on the leaderboards. However, Jiang You seemed to have forgotten this and didn’t go and check. Why? Did he not want to see a particular name on there?

Jiang You didn’t look, but others did.

“Misty Castle……” Cold Night said, carrying a hint of disbelief. However, it was true. He had checked the name three times. It really did say Misty Castle.

“Misty Castle?” Jiang You repeated the name in even greater disbelief.

Misty Castle. It was true that the guild was backed by a Club, but Tyrannical Ambition rarely saw that guild as an opponent.

Misty Castle along with Team Misty Rain were strange entities.

They were actually quite good, but their strength was always neglected by others, which seemed to be because of their temperament. Their temperament was greatly influenced by their ace player.

Team Misty Rain’s ace player was a girl.

She was a girl who loved to watch all sorts of random Twilight-type TV shows and loved to talk about random gossips.

Of the twenty teams in the Alliance, Team Misty Rain was the only one whose ace player was a girl.

Of course, Chu Yunxiu’s skill level wasn’t low at all. As the team’s ace player, she was good enough to be considered one of the Alliance’s top-tier Gods. But compared to male players, Chu Yunxiu’s performance never felt tough enough. In tense situations, her win rate was very low and in those matches she lost, many saw that it appeared as if she had modestly declined to fight it out.

In those matches, it appeared as if she should have been able to continue for a bit longer, but for some strange reason, she always silently lost.

No one knew if this was due to her temperament or personality. But as a result, a lot of people on the outside said things like “She’s just a female player, after all.” in order to explain it.

ESports was different than traditional sports, where players directly competed with their bodies and physical strength. As a result, it seemed as if males and females were on equal grounds in eSports. But because girls generally weren’t interested in these types of intense fighting games, there were a lot fewer female players in eSports than males and their skill levels were usually worse than male players by quite a bit.

Chu Yunxiu was a rarely seen female God-level player. But because of this reason, a lot of people thought that she lacked competitiveness.

Ace players often decided the team’s style and their temperament. Thus, Team Misty Rain was seen as a team that lacked competitiveness.

Their achievements reflected this as well.

After Chu Yunxiu joined the team, Team Misty Rain had entered the playoffs three years in a row. But no matter how amazing they performed in the regular season, they always lost miserably in the first round of the playoffs. Team Misty Rain didn’t seem to fit in with the playoffs’ serious and fierce competition.

In their first playoffs, maybe it was because they weren’t experienced enough. But the second and third time? They couldn’t always use a lack of experience as an explanation for everything.

Thus, Team Misty Rain and its players were labeled as such.

Since the team was relatively ignored, their in-game guild was ignored as well. Misty Castle wasn’t small by any means and they had many experts, but they never looked outstanding when competing against others. Perhaps it was because they weren’t performing well or perhaps it was because they didn’t even try, but their rare good performance usually lasted only for a brief period or sometimes didn’t even appear.

Soft! Too soft!

That was what many players saw Misty Castle as, which suited the team as well as their ace player, Chu Yunxiu.

But since Chu Yunxiu was a girl, everyone understood if she was a bit softer than others.

The guild was mostly filled with males, yet they were also soft, making a lot of people look down on them.

Tyrannical Ambition, on the other hand, was different. From their ace player to their team to their guild, they possessed tyrannical strength and a strong character. Yet they had unexpectedly been stomped on by the soft Misty Castle. This type of dramatic development was too hard to accept.

“Misty Castle? IMPOSSIBLE!!” Jiang You’s voice suddenly rose. He personally checked the leaderboards. The first place name really was Misty Castle and their record: 25:21:78.

Tyrannical Ambition had stepped on the entire server’s records by 2 minutes and now, Misty Castle had stepped on theirs by 2 minutes.

Jiang You’s complexion changed. He, who had personally researched the low-level dungeon, had no idea how Misty Castle had beaten their record by a whole 2 minutes.

“

“Are these players actually from Misty Castle?” Jiang You tried hard, but didn’t see Lord Grim as any of the five players’ names. Perhaps they had invited a few experts to sub in? Or maybe some recently retired pro-players came to mess around in the new server?

“They’re all from Misty Castle.” Cold Night confirmed after looking at the leaderboards.

“Their characters might be, but the people playing on them might not be. How shameless.” Jiang You said.

“Cough!” Cold Night coughed in embarrassment.

Jiang You heard the reminder and then immediately felt even more embarrassed.

He had played in the tenth server with this Elementalist, Crowd Lover, for too long. Jiang You had even forgotten that he wasn’t the original user of the character. He was also one of those “shameless” players.

Luckily, besides Cold Night, no one had noticed Jiang You’s error.

Everyone was still dumbstruck by Misty Castle’s record and began looking at the world chat.

They all wanted to cry, but no tears came out.

Right now, ignorant noobs were saying: Tyrannical Ambition is so bad! The record they set didn’t even need to be beaten by Lord Grim. Misty Castle? What guild was that?

A lot of naive players didn’t know of Misty Castle’s background. They took the guild to be a small guild that showed Tyrannical Ambition’s inability. And a lot of noobs believed it all, discussing just how weak Tyrannical Ambition was.

Weak?

Even when Tyrannical Ambition had their team wiped out, no one ever dared to call them “weak”.

The experts were furious. Everyone in the guild was furious.

Not waiting for their guild leader’s orders, Tyrannical Ambition’s players had already begun arguing with these players on the world chat.

Jiang You’s group watched in pain…… Their guild’s players had clearly come off worse. Those noobs’ words had clearly pricked their skins.

There was nothing they could say! They had no grounds for an argument!

Their first kill and record had all been done with Lord Grim’s help. And their hard-earned record had been crushed “without the help of Lord Grim by some random guild”.

Misty Castle was just some random guild…… Tyrannical Ambition really wanted to cry. How were they going to argue against that?

Chapter 260 – Returning to Desolate Land

Tyranny brawls. Tyranny falls. Tyranny’s record just got mauled.

Amidst the arguing, a poetic verse suddenly appeared. The attackers cheered and began to chant the verse over and over again. Quite a few players continued the poem and the world chat exploded into a poem competition with Tyrannical Ambition’s demise as the main topic. Traditional poems, rhyming poems, limericks… All sorts of poems were presented.

How could Tyrannical Ambition’s players not be angry? Jiang You couldn’t stay calm. He opened his messages and took note of the player who had written the starting verse.

“Spearless! Shut your mouth. If you have the guts, 1v1 me in the Arena or out in the wild. The loser eats his account card. Do you dare?”

Jiang You was the guild’s main leader so his words and actions represented the guild. He hadn’t acted independently in a long time. But since no one recognized him in this server, he stopped caring and went directly to the world chat to fight with the attackers. The loser eats his account card was a slang in Glory, which meant “delete your account” in the early days of gaming.

Not long after Jiang You issued the challenge, the player named Spearless replied: “Tyranny brawls. Tyranny falls. Tyranny’s record just got mauled.”

Jiang You wanted to pull out his hair, but his world chat messaging was still on cooldown, so he pushed someone off their computer and typed: “Do you dare 1v1 me? If you don’t dare, then shut your mouth!!!”

This time, the other side had his world chat messaging on cooldown, so he was quiet for a while. But once the cooldown came off, the other side immediately repeated: “Tyranny brawls. Tyranny falls. Tyranny’s record just got mauled.”

“F*ck!!!” Jiang You was about to go crazy. The people nearby saw that he was angry and didn’t dare utter a word. But in their eyes, Jiang You’s actions were quite childish. As the guild leader of one of the Three Great Guilds, he was actually arguing with some random noob. That was too shameful!

This random noob looked to be quite experienced as well. By repeating his annoying message over and over again, he succeeded in making Jiang You more and more furious.

“Guild leader! Calm down! If you get angry, it’ll be your loss!” Everyone finally surrounded and consoled him.

“Calm down? What’s the use in calming down? The record’s been stepped on again! What am I supposed to do?” Jiang You roared. The players, both inside and outside of the game, heard him. True! What were they supposed to do? They all looked at the attacks on the world chat as if they were eating a bitter fruit.

Right at this moment, Ye Xiu’s group finished their third run. Compared to others, they had used almost an hour more. Almost all of it was due to running and hiding.

When Misty Castle’s record was announced, Ye Xiu saw it and immediately received a message from Hazy Mist, asking Ye Xiu for Fire Forest’s guide.

“I’m still studying Fire Forest. There’s no rush. You should go to Fire Forest and gather some materials, or else, when I come out with the price, I won’t be able to help you.” Ye Xiu replied.

“What’s your asking price?” Hazy Mist asked.

“That depends on how things turn out.” Ye Xiu replied.

“How evil! Are you planning on revealing that our record was only achieved because we bought your guide and then having the other guilds scramble over it?”

“I don’t agree with you, saying that I’m evil. But the rest of it is true. It’s not a false advertisement.”

After a short moment of silence, Hazy Mist messaged again: “Then can we have priority?”

“I can give you a priority price!” Ye Xiu said.

“…….”

During this time, the poem competition had begun and student Jiang You had already leapt up to fry the noobs. Tyrannical Ambition’s enemies took out their popcorn and watched in glee as the events unfolded. Steamed Bun Invasion read Spearless’s verse twice and laughed out loud.

As for Ye Xiu, he didn’t have any sort of reaction. As someone who was once in the pro-scene, he was used to being opponents with the players on-stage and being friends with the players off-stage. Of course, “friend” was more of a polite term. Some of these players were considered friends if they ever nodded their heads as a greeting. That meant that they wouldn’t bring their rivalries on-stage, outside the stage.

“What are we going to do next?” Tang Rou asked. After giving up on setting records, the girl deliberately ignored new of records. She was afraid that if she kept on looking at the records, she’d want to set one.

“We’ll go to Desolate Land’s dungeon!” Ye Xiu said.

“Desolate Land? Isn’t that place that’s inconvenient to go to?” Tang Rou doubted.

“It’s different now.” Ye Xiu smiled, “The previous Level 33 players have hit Level 34, which means that a lot of players, who were previously under Level 30, have now entered the Level 30 domain. That meant that there will be more players at Line Canyon, no?”

“If you say it like that…… then I guess so.” Tang Rou looked left and right, “So you’re saying that a lot of players from Desolate Land have now gone to Line Canyon, which means that Desolate Land is now empty?”

“It’s not empty, but the danger level has lessened, so we can go and take a look.” Ye Xiu said.

“We’ll be leaving then.” Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan prepared to leave.

Everyone said their goodbyes. Ye Xiu privately messaged Su Mucheng: “We’re not going to be setting records, so you don’t need to play so diligently.”

“I want to play though.” Su Mucheng replied.

“Okay! If you want to play, then go ahead.”

“I’ll be leaving then.”

“Go ahead!”

After the two went offline, the rest of the group cautiously exited Line Canyon. Outside the canyon, Ye Xiu called for Concealed Light. The four partied up and headed towards Desolate Land.

After setting the record for Desolate Land, Ye Xiu hadn’t partied up with Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon for quite a while. Even though they still talked with one another, after being involved with the big guilds’ pursuit, Ye Xiu didn’t want to call them over. He was afraid that they’d get caught up in it too.

While Level 33 players were reaching Level 34 and Level 29 players were reaching Level 30, Ye Xiu’s leveling speed had slowed down. They still hadn’t broken through so Concealed Light was actually winning in this regard. His Level 32 Summoner was the highest level among the four of them.

“We’ll dungeon as a party of four. Concealed Light, play with us for now and I’ll have you practice when I find an opportunity.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Concealed Light said.

“Who would have thought! You’d actually have the chance to get instructed by Senior! Senior, what qualifications does he have? I don’t see it.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“His theoretical knowledge is solid. Even though he lacks actual experience, if you have nothing better to do, you should carry him along.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re really making things complicated for me but if Senior says so, then I’ll do it.” Steamed Bun Invasion reluctantly replied. He turned his head and majestically called: “Hey! Little Concealed Light, from now on, I’m your Senior. Come here and let me hear a ‘Senior’!”

“B*stard!” How could Concealed Light act kind to Steamed Bun Invasion?

“Oh my! The nerve! Do you dare 1v1 me? The loser eats his card.” Steamed Bun Invasion used the new knowledge he had just learned from reading the world chat.

“Tch……” Concealed Light obviously couldn’t agree and sent him a beneath-me face.

They continued to argue all the way until Desolate Land, where they entered a relatively quiet dungeon entrance.

When they entered the dungeon, Ye Xiu set up a plan for each of them. As a result, a weird scenario appeared. There were clearly four players running the dungeon, but it looked as if they were all doing their own thing. None of them were working together and one wasn’t even fighting monsters. He was just standing on the side shouting and directing.

This person was obviously Ye Xiu. At this moment, he was mostly worried about Concealed Light.

Teaching this guy was much harder than teaching Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion. After all, those two had solid mechanics. As soon as Ye Xiu taught them something, the two would immediately learn it after practicing it two or three times. But Concealed Light was very different.

Let alone, using summoned creatures to aggro monsters, block monsters, gather monsters together, surround monsters, etc… He wasn’t even able to move five summoned creatures in one direction.

Ye Xiu was patient though. He continued to teach him, but Concealed Light was somewhat disappointing. Not long after, he was forced to retreat after accidentally aggroing a few monsters, forcing Ye Xiu to help him out.

Starting from zero is truly difficult! Ye Xiu sighed.

“Concealed Light, do you seriously want to improve your mechanics?”

“Of course!”

“On the internet, there are a few programs that can help you train. Have you ever tried them before?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I’ve downloaded a couple, but they’re all too hard! Isn’t it too early for me to do those?” Concealed Light said.

“No. I’ll send you some elementary ones. You should practice those slowly!” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah, really? Thanks, Senior!” Concealed Light had argued with Steamed Bun Invasion for a long time, so he learned what Steamed Bun Invasion called Ye Xiu.

“Hm? What’d you call me for?” Steamed Bun Invasion shamelessly joined in.

“You b*stard!” Concealed Light cursed.

“Thanks, God.” He didn’t forget to revise his previous address.

Chapter 261 – You Have to Love the Game!

In the blink of an eye, the day had grown bright and Ye Xiu stretched his arms.

At this time, no one in his group was still playing.

Tang Rou had gone off the earliest. After running Desolate Land three times, she went to sleep. Ever since the day that where she and Chen Guo went shopping, she had changed her sleep schedule. She wouldn’t stay up all night until day came like Ye Xiu did. She would go to sleep earlier, but wake up earlier than Ye Xiu also. Whenever Ye Xiu woke up, he would always be able to see her and Chen Guo sitting together and playing Glory up until 3 o’clock in the afternoon, which was when Tang Rou had to take the shift.

After Tang Rou went offline, Concealed Light, finally, was unable to continue arguing bitterly with Steamed Bun Invasion and decided to duel Steamed Bun Invasion in the Arena. Ye Xiu was dragged along by Steamed Bun Invasion and forced to spectate the match.

Ye Xiu really didn’t need to watch to know the results. With Concealed Light’s skill level, there was no way he could fight against Steamed Bun Invasion. Concealed Light fought ten matches and lost ten matches. Nothing unexpected had arisen.

“Ha ha ha ha, now you know my strength! Being your senior is actually quite troublesome for me, not you.” After exiting the Arena, Steamed Bun Invasion was absolutely delighted, while Concealed Light was completely silent. For Steamed Bun Invasion, who could find fun during any moment, beating up a noob clearly didn’t make him feel bad in any way.

“Steamed Bun, don’t be too complacent.” Ye Xiu felt that he had to say a few words: “You started training earlier than he did. Bullying Concealed Light, who just started learning, isn’t something you should be too happy about.”

“Ha ha, I was prepared to teach him well, but this little boy refused to accept me, so I had to teach him a lesson. How about it, little Concealed Light? Am I good enough for you? Ha ha ha ha…….” Steamed Bun Invasion continued to be proud of himself. Who would believe that he actually wanted to teach someone? He was clearly feeling good about beating up a noob.

“Alright, that’s enough. You, go and play!” Ye Xiu shooed away Steamed Bun Invasion. He turned around and saw that Concealed Light was still standing there stupidly.

“Don’t be discouraged. You’ve only just begun.” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah, I know.”

“That’s good. Gimme a sec and I’ll send you some stuff.”

“Okay!”

After that, he spent two hours searching, arranging, and categorizing. The materials he had gathered weren’t only useful to Concealed Light. Any other player who liked Glory would find them useful too, however, these types of specialized drills were extremely dull. Normal players wouldn’t be able to persist, and if you didn’t persist, no type training was effective.

The materials Ye Xiu had gathered were especially fitting for a beginner such as Concealed Light. Actually, these types of specialized drills were a bit difficult for beginners. However, in Ye Xiu’s eyes, for a beginner like Concealed Light to have such a solid grasp of theory meant that he was very tenacious and wanted to improve his own skill.

When Steamed Bun Invasion bullied the noob, Ye Xiu watched with one eye open and one eye closed. He wanted to see just how motivated Concealed Light was to improve.

After receiving the materials, Concealed Light thanked Ye Xiu, who reminded him about the important points. As for how to use them, Ye Xiu felt that it wasn’t necessary to tell someone who studied things so meticulously.

After sending Concealed Light his portion, Ye Xiu glanced at some more documents. While arranging the materials, he also found a few programs that could be specially used for Tang Rou’s and Steamed Bun Invasion’s training.

However……. when Ye Xiu thought of Steamed Bun Invasion’s misdeeds, Ye Xiu felt that these types of drills didn’t suit him.

Steamed Bun Invasion liked the game because the game brought him happiness. However, when this type of happiness stops existing, Ye Xiu wouldn’t know what type of attitude Steamed Bun Invasion would take.

The reason pro-players become pro-players, besides having talent, working hard, etc., was because they loved the game.

For example, for Ye Xiu, he had played the game for ten years, but his love for the game hadn’t died down. It wasn’t just him; every pro-player that struggled to be a part of the Alliance all did so because they loved the game.

As for normal players, some would play for two or three months and then switch to a different game. These types of players weren’t suitable to become pro-players. Even if their mechanics were good enough, if they didn’t have the passion, their performance would be vastly different from those that did and they wouldn’t be able to become anything great.

Steamed Bun Invasion found the game fun, which was why he was interested. New, in-game content would naturally interest him. However, how long would he stay interested? Ye Xiu felt that he didn’t understand Steamed Bun Invasion well enough. Normally, all he heard was the guy spouting random nonsense. He should have at least understood his previous gaming experiences. Ye Xiu had no idea where the guy got his mechanics from.

Regardless, he still wasn’t sure whether or not he should give specialized drills for Steamed Bun Invasion. He was afraid that it might cause him to lose interest towards the game and create conflicting feelings. Perhaps it was better to make him understand his own problems on his own right now and then for him to happily look for help later.

The other set of materials was for Tang Rou.

The reason this sis wanted to improve her mechanics so she could beat him. Ye Xiu originally didn’t believe that such a ridiculous reason would hold for much longer. However, from the looks of it, this sis’s stubbornness far exceeded that of normal people. Before she beat him, it really didn’t seem like she’d give up.

The good thing was that as she improved and as she continued to understand Glory, Tang Rou gained a greater understanding of just how far apart they were and would feel that the game wasn’t as “easy” as she had said before. This sis’s interest in Glory was slowly forming.

She would eventually be able to accept this type of practice.

Ye Xiu thought this way and checked the materials again. He decided that he would give it to Tang Rou tomorrow. As for Steamed Bun Invasion, he would put it off for now!

After tidying everything up, he closed the folder. There was still half an hour left until seven. Ye Xiu didn’t have anything else to do, so he logged into the game.

The game was the quietest at this time. No one was really talking on the world chat. The previous dispute between Tyrannical Ambition and the other players had died down awhile ago, so many had already seen their daily dose of drama for the day.

Those players, who had argued with Tyrannical Ambition, might not have any enmity towards Tyrannical Ambition. They just did it for the sake of roasting them. For example, the players that had written verses were only doing it in order to add fuel to the fire.

For an experienced player like Jiang You, he should have understood this very well. Unfortunately, his mood had been very bad, which was why he suddenly went off like that and almost became a new meme.

The world had finally quieted down. Ye Xiu conveniently checked the Line Canyon record. In first place was still Misty Castle and second place was still Tyrannical Ambition. Nothing had changed.

He checked his friends list and saw that the guild leaders were still on. Though among these, some of them were happy while others were worried.

Those that hadn’t set a record yet were a bit worried. As for the guild who was the most worried, that would have to be Tyrannical Ambition.

Ye Xiu obviously wouldn’t add fuel to the fire. He didn’t have any sort of enmity with the guilds. It was just that his interests conflicted with theirs. And had lost the game because Lord Grim was simply better than they were.

Ye Xiu was using the last of his shift to check in on the situation. He was just sitting there idly with nothing to do, when suddenly, he received a message from Tyrannical Ambition’s Cold Night.

“God!” Cold Night sent him an icon of cupped fists. He already knew of Lord Grim’s identity. But as a fan of Tyranny, there was no way he would truly worship their enemy, Team Excellent Era’s former ace player.

“Yes?” Ye Xiu replied.

“I want to know if you helped Misty Castle with their record.” Cold Night went straight to the point.

“Sure. I sold them a guide, which should have been of some help to them!”

Chapter 262 – Dungeon Tollbooth

Cold Night asked directly, so Ye Xiu replied the same way.

“So it really was you……”

“It was me.”

“It seems like you’re the only one who’s capable of making such a record.” Cold Night said.

“Don’t worry! I won’t be setting records personally anymore. I’ll only sell guides.” Ye Xiu said.

“You don’t even need to move to kill people. That sounds evil enough.”

“Don’t say it like that, everyone needs to eat. If you won’t let me set records, then I’ll sell guides. You won’t even let me sell guides? How do you want me to live?”

Cold Night didn’t know what to say. Since they weren’t able to beat Lord Grim, they allied together to kill him. In truth, there wasn’t anything honorable about this.

Even though he spoke this way, he didn’t have a bad impression of Lord Grim. However, if their guild were to develop, they would need the dungeon records. Methods such as pursuing and killing were methods that took place out in the open. However, there were even darker methods out there, which Cold Night had seen before. The game’s virtual reality brought out the darkness within people.

“Oh, it’s nothing. I just didn’t want to believe that we’d lose so badly, so I wanted to confirm things with you. I understand now.” Cold Night replied.

“If you want to win, it’s not like there’s no chance.”

“What methods are there?” Cold Night replied extremely quickly.

“Buy my guide!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Sweat……” Cold Night had already realized that the buying and selling of guides might even be more terrifying than having Lord Grim personally subbing in or holding the records hostage. This was because the buying and selling of guides wasn’t only limited to in the game. This time, the guilds had no way of stopping it.

In Tyrannical Ambition’s current situation, directly taking back the record was the most effective way of coming back and would even give them a thrill that would definitely attract attention. As a result, Cold Night was very interested in these guides.

“What type of guide is it?” Cold Night asked.

“The guide that Misty Castle used to beat your record.”

“The same?”

“Of course.”

“Then how can you guarantee that we’ll beat their record?”

“I shouldn’t be able to guarantee anything, right? I only said that it was a chance.” Ye Xiu said.

“So you’re saying that since we’ll be using the same guide, everything else depends on how we perform?”

“Exactly.”

Cold Night immediately pictured a scene: from here on out, every guild that wanted to fight for the dungeon records would first have to buy a guide from Lord Grim. If not, then any guilds that didn’t buy it would have no chance…….

This guy! He’s no longer a kidnapper. He’s transformed into a tollbooth. From now on, his guides are the tickets needed to set records!

“Can I take a look at the guide first?” Cold Night asked.

“No.”

“Why not…..”

“Because our relationship isn’t too good. I’m afraid that you won’t give me any materials after looking at it.” Ye Xiu said plainly.

“Then what happens if we were to give you the materials and you didn’t give us the guide?” Cold Night asked in return.

“Then you’d have lost big time.” Ye Xiu replied.

“You…..” Cold Night was speechless. He clearly needed the guide. If he wanted to buy the guide, then he would need to give materials to Lord Grim. There was no other option besides that.

Cold Night felt very gloomy. He didn’t like this sort of thing, but there was no way he could depend on his strength.

“I’m going to log off at seven. You have 15 minutes to consider it.” Ye Xiu messaged. “Of course, if you’re patient, then you can wait until I log in in the afternoon or even until next year. You can buy my guides at any time as long as you pay enough materials.”

“What materials?” Cold Night asked for the price.

Ye Xiu sent him the list.

“These…… are all Fire Forest materials.” Cold Night skimmed over them and said.

“We’ve only just started dungeoning in Fire Forest, so we don’t have these materials gathered up yet.” Cold Night didn’t object to the asking price. Ye Xiu had estimated it. It was similar to the deal between him and Misty Castle. He had changed the materials, but their value was still about the same. Cold Night knew that the price was lower than it would cost for Lord Grim to personally sub in, but in reality, since they had only just started running Fire Forest, they truly didn’t have the materials.

“Oh, but you should at least still have some of them, right? Maybe you can tell me what’s in your guild’s inventory and let me choose from it?” Ye Xiu said.

“One sec…….” Cold Night replied. He wasn’t sure.

After pondering it over for a few minutes, Cold Night felt that he should discuss it with his boss. However, he didn’t know if Jiang You had calmed down yet. If he suddenly told him that Lord Grim was still the holder of the tenth server records and that his situation was even more stable now, he was truly afraid that Jiang You would actually cough blood and have to be rescued by an ambulance.

“Wait just a bit longer!!” Cold Night hastily messaged Lord Grim and then hurriedly went to contact Jiang You. Simply speaking, he was anxious for Jiang You’s reply.

“So this guy actually had all this planned from the start? Was that reason why he decided to drag along four random cheerleaders and lose?”

Cold Night was startled. Now that Jiang You had said it, it did appear to be true.

“What do you say?” Cold Night felt that Jiang You had calmed down.

Jiang You went silent for a full minute before finally saying: “Give him the materials!”

“OK!” Cold Night decided. Their current plight was truly difficult. If they continued to fight with Lord Grim, Lord Grim wouldn’t care and they’d be the one losing out.

After receiving Jiang You’s reply, Cold Night contacted Lord Grim and said: “I agree!”

“What materials do you guys have?” Ye Xiu asked.

Cold Night checked the inventory and asked the guild for a materials list. After a while, he suddenly came up with a plan: to hide a few of the materials that Lord Grim wanted.

This trick was kind of pointless. With Lord Grim’s ability, it was just a matter of time before he got his hands on the materials that he wanted. But Cold Night wasn’t happy right now so if you want something, we don’t have it. We’ll give you something you don’t need!

Ye Xiu looked at Cold Night’s list and didn’t say anything. He picked a few materials and then replied back. Cold Night looked and saw that there wasn’t any problem. The materials were traded and Ye Xiu sent them the guide.

Cold Night opened up the document as if he was looking at a treasure. Just as he was about to say something else to Lord Grim, he found that Lord Grim had gone offline.

Cold Night suddenly panicked. What if they had been tricked? What if the guide was a fake? He hastily checked the guide and looked at the page count. Why was it so long?

He continued to read and discovered that it was different from normal guides. This guide was extremely detailed.

“F*ck, is he selling it based on the word count?” Cold Night disdained. But after looking at the highlighted portions and then reading them carefully, he immediately realized their significance.

“So it’s like this!” After reading a section, Cold Night suddenly understood.

“Did you get the guide?” On the other side, Jiang You was urging him.

Chapter 263 – Christmas Event

Cold Night sent Jiang You’s group the document. They all opened it and began studying it. After reading it through, they discovered that in order to break the record, they still needed to consult with Lord Grim. If they had known this earlier, then they wouldn’t have done so many tricks.

There were no words to describe what they were feeling right now. The only thing that made them feel a bit better was that they knew who Lord Grim really was.

Ye Qiu. It was an identity that wouldn’t garner any love in Tyrannical Ambition.

At least against such a strong opponent, losing wasn’t shameful.

They were all comforted by this thought to some degree. They tacitly agreed not to mention Ye Qiu, nor Lord Grim, and focus only on the guide’s content.

They were all experts, so they quickly understood the guide’s value. The highlighted portions were the guide’s most important points. The guide had originally required the use of five fixed classes, but…… by learning the most important parts of the guide, the classes didn’t need to be fixed. Jiang You’s group discussed this issue about how they could integrate the strategy into their class setup.

Meanwhile, Ye Xiu had already logged off. Ye Xiu was now off from work, so he went out to eat breakfast. While coming back, he saw Chen Guo standing outside of the entrance, ordering a few employees around.

“Oh? Are we going to celebrate Christmas?” When Ye Xiu walked over, he saw that a small pine tree was standing erect at the Internet Cafe’s entrance. Chen Guo was currently putting on bright lights and presents.

“Oh? You actually know the date? You didn’t make a mistake, did you?” Chen Guo said. For people like Ye Xiu who had their days and nights flipped upside down, in her eyes, it was very easy for them to lose track of time.

“I accidentally noticed it.” Ye Xiu circled around the small pine tree.

“Not bad!” Ye Xiu praised.

“Of course.”

“Is there actually stuff in here?” Ye Xiu pointed to the small presents hanging on the tree.

“Of course.”

“What’s inside?”

“Raffle prizes, coupons, etc.” Chen Guo said.

“Oh, oh.” Ye Xiu understood. Clearly, Chen Guo was like a lot of business owners and used this holiday as a marketing scheme.

“I say, boss! When you set up events, you should pay more attention to it! You should buy a Christmas tree. What’s up with this tree? Did you make it yourself with wires?” Ye Xiu circled around the Christmas tree again. Ye Xiu could tell that this Christmas tree wasn’t real and had been made entirely by hand.

“A handmade one isn’t good enough?” Chen Guo walked over and said.

“It’s not that it’s not good. It’s just that it can’t compare to an actual tree. It also looks kind of old. Was it from last year?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chen Guo shook her head: “I made it with my dad ten years ago.”

Ye Xiu was startled.

He had worked in the Internet Cafe for almost a month. Even though he hadn’t heard Chen Guo say it personally, he had heard quite a few stories about her from other employees. He had heard that Chen Guo had taken over the cafe by herself after her parents had passed away.

This rough-looking, hand-made Christmas tree wasn’t just used by Chen Guo for advertisement, but it was also a reminder of her memories with her parents. This Christmas tree definitely had a lot of history behind it.

“Your dad’s craftsmanship is pretty good. The tree looks really good.” Ye Xiu said.

“Thanks.” Chen Guo faintly smiled and didn’t argue with Ye Xiu’s obvious change in attitude.

“Do you need me to help you with anything?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No need. Go ahead and sleep!”

“Okay……” Ye Xiu returned to his room to rest. Chen Guo stood next to the Christmas tree, entranced.

Ten years……. This Christmas tree had accompanied her for ten Christmases.

Her father was still there on the first Christmas. The tree had been made by him as a Christmas present to her. But for the other nine years, only she and the tree had remained!

“Boss, can I hang this here?”

Chen Guo had been distracted, when someone suddenly interrupted her thoughts. An employee was asking her if it was okay to hang a decoration there.

“A little higher!” Chen Guo came back to the present and continued to direct.

Ye Xiu went to bed, but he didn’t sleep long and got up before noon. When he left his room and went downstairs, he saw that the Internet Cafe had a complete Christmas makeover.

The handmade Christmas tree was loaded down with presents and ornaments and looked as if it was about to bend over.

Apart from this, all sorts of bright lights and Christmas posters were put up. The most eye-catching headline was the announcement for Happy Internet Cafe’s Christmas raffle.

“Not bad, not bad. I can feel the Christmas spirit.” Ye Xiu looked around and praised Chen Guo.

“Yeah.” Chen Guo replied. She didn’t even lift up her head.

“The Christmas events are going to start soon. Shouldn’t you hurry up?” Chen Guo said. She and Tang Rou were at the computers playing Glory. The events she was talking about were directed towards the game, not the Internet Cafe.

The game obviously wouldn’t miss an opportunity like Christmas to promote sales. Every year, Glory would come up with new events for all sorts of holidays.

For every new server that was opened, the very first holiday event would be Christmas. And these events were always great opportunities for leveling and equipment. For old servers, there wasn’t much point in leveling. But for the new server, leveling was much more important than equipment. During these events, every minute and every second was precious.

“Aren’t I here now?” Ye Xiu smiled. He obviously wouldn’t miss this opportunity. This was also why he got up early today.

“Sit here. There aren’t any other empty stations.” Chen Guo pointed to a computer next to them.

“Oh?” Ye Xiu looked around again and noticed that business was going exceptionally well. He didn’t know if it was because of the game’s events or because of the Internet Cafe’s holiday promotions.

The computer Chen Guo pointed to was undoubtedly left open for Ye Xiu, even though she didn’t directly say it.

Without any other choice, Ye Xiu sat down and logged into the game.

“Wow. There’re so many people……” Ye Xiu noticed as soon as he got on.

“Yeah……” Tang Rou said, too.

Compared to the old servers, there would only be more players in the new servers. In the old servers, players were scattered all around the entire world, while in new servers, players were limited to Level 30 and below maps. As a result, the player population wasn’t spread out evenly and they were mostly crowded together. Even though technology had improved and the number of players wouldn’t cause lag, having a lot of players still caused delays because this year’s event had a competitive element to it.

Hunt down the Christmas thieves.

That was this year’s Christmas event. The plot was extremely simple. Thieves had stolen gifts from Santa, so it was up to the players to get them back. Depending on the gift the player returned, Santa would reward the player with a Christmas present. Each Christmas present would give a certain amount of experience, as well as an unknown reward.

The quest could be done repeatedly and a special ranking was created for the event: Christmas Hunting Leaderboards.

Clearly, it was a ranking based on the number of Christmas thieves hunted. When the event ended, Santa would give a different final present depending on your ranking.

That was the main quest, but there were also a few details.

For example, when stealing back the gifts from the Christmas thieves, the gift might be a piece of equipment, a potion, or some other random item. Players could choose to keep these items instead of returning them to Santa. If the gift wasn’t returned, then you wouldn’t receive rewards for it. But it was possible that players could become stronger through these items and, as a result, do the event quests more efficiently. All of these items that were gifts would expire after the event ended, but during the event, they could be extremely useful for competitions between players.

Apart from this, because player levels were different, there were several Christmas thief leaderboards that depended upon a range of player levels.

The range was five levels. Players would only compete on their respective leaderboard. The rewards gained also depended on the player’s level range. If you leveled up into a different level range, then your previous achievements would carry over into that new level’s range on the leaderboard.

Chapter 264 – Luck Is Very Important

Not long after Ye Xiu logged into the game, the clock hit twelve and the events began..

Players had naturally studied the event’s rules beforehand. Players didn’t need to accept any quests. They just needed to look for the Christmas thieves scattered around the map.

However, Christmas thieves had levels like normal monsters. The higher the level, the more points it would give. Besides this, there were also Elite Christmas thieves. They would score more points than normal thieves and would also give better quality presents.

“Ha ha, my luck is good. I’ve found one!” Ye Xiu heard Chen Guo laugh. He turned his head and saw Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze firing towards a Christmas thief. The thief immediately turned its head and pounced towards Chasing Haze. Meanwhile, nearby players also noticed this Christmas thief, but no matter how hard they attacked, the thief’s only target was Chasing Haze.

This was one of the special attributes of Christmas thieves: the first aggroed target was locked in. In order to prevent players from fighting amongst each other, whoever attacked the Christmas thief first had priority. Aggroed Christmas thieves would still be hurt by other players’ attacks, but no matter how much damage was dealt, it would only help the player who aggroed it first.

Seeing that Chasing Haze had already aggroed the Christmas thief, they stopped attacking and began searching again. The Christmas thief was nimble. It clearly wouldn’t be so easy to kill. Christmas thieves had different classes just like players did. They were called thieves, but it didn’t mean their class was that of a Thief. The monster that Chen Guo aggroed closed in on her and slashed at her; it was a Swordsman Class: Berserker.

Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze used an Aerial Fire, dodging and attacking the Christmas thief.

“Not bad!” Ye Xiu praised. Using Aerial Fire to widen the distance while attacking the target was a basic Launcher maneuver. He could see that Chen Guo was quite proficient in this area. Her movements had been very clean.

Chen Guo was absorbed in the killing. She was focused on her battle with the Christmas thief and hadn’t noticed Ye Xiu praising her.

Ye Xiu watched for a bit and then went back to his own game. His Lord Grim had logged off in the wild. At this moment, players were running around everywhere around him. As soon as a Christma thief spawned, who knew how many attacks flew at it.

Ye Xiu stretched his neck and looked towards Tang Rou. Tang Rou’s situation was similar to his. Players were everywhere. Finding a thief to kill was quite difficult. In this event, luck was an extremely important factor.

As Ye Xiu maneuvered his Lord Grim, he opened a message and saw that it was from Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist.

“You’re on time!” Su Mucheng said.

“Why are you on, too?” Ye Xiu was surprised.

“There’s an event! Of course I’m going to participate.” Su Mucheng explained as if it were obvious.

“It seems like you’re not busy. Have you captured any thieves yet?” Ye Xiu helplessly asked.

“Not yet. There’s too many people. I’m going to go to Fire Forest to take a look.” Su Mucheng replied.

Due to the rules, there would be fewer players in higher-leveled maps. After all, higher leveled players could go to lower-leveled maps, but for lower-leveled players, it could be dangerous for them to go to higher-leveled maps.

“I think Fire Forest is probably the same.” Su Mucheng said.

“I think so, too.”

Other Level 30 players might not be as skilled as Ye Xiu’s group, but they could still wander around Fire Forest. It wasn’t that they were unable to kill the monsters in Fire Forest. It was just that it wasn’t as efficient for leveling purposes.

“Maybe we should try aiming higher? What do you think about Sin City?” Su Mucheng said.

Sin City was a Level 37-39 area.

The entire leveling area was a city. The layout of the map wasn’t too different from a main city, but the NPCs there weren’t friendly and their only form of communication towards players was to attack them.

“There might be people there too, but there shouldn’t be as many.” Ye Xiu said. Players who were confident about surviving in Sin City were all probably heading over there.

“Then let’s go take a look!”

“Okay.”

Ye Xiu didn’t forget to call for Tang Rou. He checked his friends list and Steamed Bun Invasion was unexpectedly offline. As for the others, Seven Fields and Sleeping Moon were online. But for them, going to such a high-leveled area was probably too dangerous, so Ye Xiu didn’t call for them.

On their way there, Ye Xiu picked up two Christmas thieves. Christmas thieves had a certain strength to them. Their classes indicated that they had those class’s skills. At the very least, they were much more difficult than normal monsters of the same level.

Ye Xiu was able to kill two Christmas thieves. But he had already seen five players die from the Christmas thieves.

Currently, he didn’t recognize most of the names on the leaderboards. It seemed like the experts weren’t having very good luck. No matter how skilled they were, if they didn’t see any Christmas thieves, then what was the point?

Though he did recognize one of the names.

Thousand Creations!

The guy had unexpectedly placed on the Level 31-35 leaderboards. He clearly hadn’t gotten the achievement through luck, but rather by kill stealing the monsters.

Due to Christmas thieves locking onto their first target, most kill steals were avoided, but it couldn’t entirely be avoided. Under this condition, it made kill stealing a lot more difficult. There might not be a way to kill steal the monster by attacking it, but you could kill off the player it was aggroed onto. That would cause the Christmas thief to turn neutral, which you could then attack in order to take it down.

But doing things like this would only make you into a street rat. Ye Xiu didn’t doubt that if Thousand Creations continued to stay on the leaderboards through this method, then today the world chat’s main topic would be towards attacking this shameless kill stealer.

Speaking of this, this guy should have already kill stolen quite a few. Were there no angry shouts at him? Ye Xiu looked at the world chat and saw that it was filled with complaints about the event being too difficult to kill Christmas thieves.

Seeing the world chat, Ye Xiu couldn’t help but think of Tyrannical Ambition’s plight yesterday night. Even though he didn’t care who held the dungeon record, Ye Xiu still checked it.

The leaderboards hadn’t changed. After Misty Castle had bought the guide, they had set the record after one or two hours. Ye Xiu didn’t think that Tyrannical Ambition would lose to them. But there was no trace of them on the leaderboards.

It was possible that Tyrannical Ambition didn’t have the suitable accounts, so they were waiting for tomorrow to set it.

“Tsk tsk, they’re probably hurting inside, while waiting for the day to go by.” Ye Xiu didn’t care and didn’t need to side with any guild.

And in front of him, Sin City finally appeared.

Chapter 265- Sin City

Sin City. After entering the leveling area, the sky’s color changed. The sky was covered in dense, black clouds and thin rain drizzled down.

The entire city had a sinister and dark hue around it. Enveloped in both rain and fog, players had limited visibility. The rain’s dripping sound and the occasional thunder challenged the player’s hearing.

As soon as Lord Grim entered the city’s streets, thunder roared and lightning flashed down from the sky, illuminating the entire street in a deathly pale light in that instant. Ye Xiu suddenly moved his hands. His mouse shifted and Lord Grim stabbed towards his left with his Thousand Chance Umbrella.

The umbrella flipped inside out.

“Pu!” The Dragon Tooth connected with the target.

The lightning revealed his pale and mean face, dripping with rain. His hands held a cold dagger which stabbed towards Lord Grim, but he was hit first by Lord Grim’s attack.

This was a Sin City resident, one of the monsters in this leveling area. Glory’s drawings were extremely detailed. NPC monsters were randomly generated through character models. Their models were different from one another which made them appear realistic and vivid.

Sin City’s unique environment and weather made it troublesome for players. The residents here were also extremely hostile. Their faces looked like fiends and their sneak attacks were sudden. If Ye Xiu were a normal player, he would have most likely been hurt by the sneak attack.

Fortunately, Ye Xiu was Ye Xiu. His Dragon Tooth struck, followed by a Sky Strike.

Ye Xiu was a pro player. He had to be familiar with every type of map. Many of the maps used in Glory’s competitive matches were based on maps made in-game. After playing for so many years, how could he not be familiar with this type of environment?

Sin City?

When new players first arrive here, the reduced visibility and noisy background might make them feel repressed and the residents’ sudden attacks were likely to scare them. But for Ye Xiu, this was all too ordinary.

After using a Sky Strike, Lord Grim switched around with different forms and used different skills. But the high Level Suppression greatly weakened Lord Grim’s killing potential. Even though the fight was without any suspense, it still took him quite a while to kill off the resident.

Ye Xiu didn’t want to waste his time on this resident. After killing it, he began paying attention to the surroundings.

Residents were moving around in the 9 o’clock, 11 o’clock, and 1 o’clock direction. These residents’ aggro range had obviously been researched by players long ago. For Ye Xiu, he was good enough that he could estimate the distance with his eyes.

These three residents blocked the street he was on. No matter which way he went, he would inevitably enter their aggro range. Ye Xiu saw this, but his Lord Grim continued forward.

Charge forward!

After seeing the resident at the 9 o’clock direction step twice, Ye Xiu used the opportunity to make Lord Grim rush forward.

Leap back!

The resident in the 11 o’clock position suddenly stopped and turned back. Ye Xiu hastily had Lord Grim leap backwards twice, just beyond the edge of the resident’s aggro range.

To the right, 30 degrees!

After confirming the residents’ positions, Ye Xiu made his decision and rushed forward diagonally.

As he moved, his camera constantly moved, observing the three residents’ movements. He would immediately make any adjustments based on their movements. Finally, after twisting and turning, Lord Grim ran past them without being noticed.

The process had been somewhat complicated, but it saved him a lot of time.

“Are all of you here?” After getting past the blockade, Ye Xiu opened his friends list and asked Su Mucheng and Tang Rou.

“Here.” The two replied in succession.

The three didn’t form a party after meeting up. Even though the event rules allowed for the formation of parties, the Christmas thieves would be mutually shared, which meant that each person would receive a lot less points for each one. From Ye Xiu’s experience, parties were there to make the fights easier. If the individual was good enough, then going solo was more efficient than forming a party.

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Tang Rou were without a doubt good enough to solo these monsters, so there was no need to party up.

After encouraging them, Ye Xiu told Tang Rou the places she had to be careful around in Sin City so that she didn’t make a blunder due to her lack of experience.

“You have to listen carefully. Even though there’s a lot of background noise, the monsters’ attacks won’t be completely covered up. You will have to get used to screening out the necessary sounds from all of the noise.” In Glory, lots of dangers behind the player could be found through experience and screening. It was an important game skill that had to be grasped.

“Got it.” Tang Rou replied.

Chen Guo glanced at Tang Rou’s screen and immediately gasped in surprise: “You’re going to Sin City at that level?” While looking towards Ye Xiu’s screen, she said: “You too!”

Not waiting for Ye Xiu’s answer, Chen Guo began to bubble with excitement. Her hand pointed towards Ye Xiu’s screen: “A thief!!!!”

“I see it!” Ye Xiu had no choice but to talk with her.

“Hurry up and attack it!”

“I don’t want to aggro the other monsters!” Ye Xiu said. He had seen the Christmas thief long ago, but the guy was standing next to two Sin City residents. If he attacked now, the two residents would be aggroed. Ye Xiu wanted to wait for an appropriate time.

Chen Guo understood what Ye Xiu meant. As a result, she ignored her own character and helped Ye Xiu watch the thief.

That Christmas thief crouched into a corner and stopped moving. The two Sin City residents incessantly paced back and forth.

“Oh, oh, oh! Hurry up and attack!” Chen Guo suddenly hit Ye Xiu.

“The right one is still off by one position!” Ye Xiu said.

“Really?” Chen Guo muttered, “If you’re going to keep wasting your time like this, then you might as well just kill them all, no? You’re good enough to do that, right?”

“Don’t rush me.” Ye Xiu didn’t move and looked as if this was his only option.

“Let’s see how long you’re going to wait!” Chen Guo said, when the two residents moved one step sideways. Right at this moment, Lord Grim lifted his weapon and fired.

The bullet moved extremely quickly. All Chen Guo saw was the blood that blossomed out when the bullet hit the Christmas thief’s head. The Christmas thief immediately leaped up and charged forward.

During this moment, the two residents turned around, but the attack had already ended and only the Christmas thief headed towards Lord Grim, which wasn’t something that they really cared about.

Ye Xiu had actually grasped that short window of opportunity. He had probably calculated the distance between them as well as the bullet’s speed and the timing. Was that something she could do as well?

Chen Guo realized long ago that Ye Xiu wasn’t any ordinary expert, but after witnessing this scene, Chen Guo weighed herself against him and suffered a blow to herself. As for how Ye Xiu was going to kill the Christmas thief, Chen Guo had no interest in watching. That was because Chen Guo wouldn’t be able to understand anything while directly watching Ye Xiu’s screen.

Chapter 266 – Escaping Outside of the Aggro Range

Chen Guo stopped looking over at Ye Xiu’s screen. She then turned her head and glanced at Tang Rou’s screen. But the scene that she saw made her even more dumbstruck.

These two people’s circumstances were polar opposites.

On Ye Xiu’s side, he carefully planned and didn’t arouse even a single Sin City resident. But on Tang Rou’s side, now that was a commotion. Her Soft Mist ran like mad the entire way. Her character glanced around every few seconds and Chen Guo already saw that there were at least ten residents chasing after her already! Tang Rou’s movements were truly extraordinary.

In addition, she looked as if she would gather more. As she sprinted down the road, not a single resident that she passed by didn’t notice her and added itself to the growing number of troops.

Tang Rou didn’t want to provoke them, either. It was just that their aggro range was just too large and they were just too aggressive. If she were here to level up, then that wouldn’t be a bad thing and would actually be convenient for that purpose. But in her situation, avoiding these monsters’ aggro required experience and awareness. It didn’t matter how good her mechanics were.

Tang Rou clearly wasn’t at Ye Xiu’s level. She had only recently entered Sin City and she had already gathered up so many residents.

In the beginning, Tang Rou had killed them off. But after killing a few, she saw that she wasn’t getting much experience. It was a complete waste of time. As a result, she didn’t want to keep wasting her time. But in front of these Sin City residents, they weren’t going to just not fight you if you didn’t want to fight. It wasn’t that convenient.

Chen Guo watched for a bit and felt that Tang Rou was in a lot of danger. She hated how she wasn’t able to help her, so she hastily went to grab Ye Xiu.

“Hey, hey, don’t pull! Don’t pull!!” Ye Xiu was currently attacking a Christmas thief. He was unable to withstand the drag and made a slip-up. Lord Grim was hit by the thief’s blade, which also disrupted Lord Grim’s combo. This Christmas thief was an actual Thief class. After doing that, the thief rolled backwards and immediately began to wander off.

“Oh no”!” Chen Guo looked and also knew that the situation was bad. This was a commonly used tactic by Thieves. They would wander off and place traps everywhere, restricting your movements. It seemed like the AI for these Christmas thieves were different than in the past. They moved as if they were real, like actual players.

When a player accidentally set off an explosion, a spike, or a poison gas bomb, it was always a mood destroyer. A lot of players didn’t lose to Thieves in mechanics, but in their psychology. When affected players continued to fight in an imbalanced state of mind, their movements turned panicked and they would make more mistakes, causing them to lose.

For people like Chen Guo, who were easily instigated, this sort of strategy was something that they feared intensely. Who knew how many times they had lost to Thieves because of this? Seeing this situation, she accidentally put herself into the situation and panicked. She apologized for messing up Ye Xiu.

But….. it was a groundless fear.

The Christmas thief put down the first trap and then sidestepped, ready to put down a second. But before he could do so, three Anti-Tank Missiles fired at him. The Christmas thief had nowhere to run. The thief was hit directly and failed to set the trap. Lord Grim rushed forward with his Thousand Chance Umbrella in its battle lance form. He swung up with a Sky Strike, launching the thief into the air.

The battle instantly returned to the original scene. The Christmas thief was stuck in Lord Grim’s combo and was unable to get out. Ye Xiu continued to play, while asking : ”What is it?”

“Ah?” Chen Guo had been so worried that she had almost forgotten about Tang Rou’s situation. She turned around and saw that Tang Rou’s situation looked even worse now, so she replied hastily: “It’s about Little Tang. She’s being chased by a lot of monsters!”

Ye Xiu heard this and glanced over to Tang Rou’s side: “I’ve told her how to escape the monsters’ line of sight before!”

Ye Xiu didn’t have hopes that Tang Rou had the ability to not alarm any residents like he was doing now. As a result, he reminded her of how to quickly escape from the monsters’ aggro.

Escaping from their line of sight was one way to get rid of their aggro. Simply speaking, when you ran, you would turn more and wind around walls more. The aggro would quickly drop and the monsters would lose their line of sight and stop chasing. In Sin City’s streets, running away in this way was very easy.

“She was doing it, but……”

But what? Whenever she escaped from old residents, she would always bump into new ones, aggroing them. Tang Rou was stuck in this type of loop. In addition, now that she had pulled so many of these residents, it was too late to turn back and fight them all.

“What are her coordinates?” Ye Xiu asked Chen Guo. Tang Rou was very focused and didn’t know that the two of them were talking about her.

Chen Guo checked, when she suddenly saw a figure in front of Tang Rou’s character.

A figure appeared on one of the rooftops. Tang Rou immediately focused on her. Chen Guo immediately recognized the equipment on the character: a Launcher! It was the class she was most familiar with. It was a female Launcher too, so her familiarity increased by 100%.

The character’s class was the same and the equipment were ones that she recognized, but there was one thing that was very different. This female Launcher chose to have long hair that fluttered in the fine rain. The cannon in her hands lit up and flashed, shooting out a Laser. The female Launcher gently leaped backwards, utilizing the Laser Rifle’s recoil.

Tang Rou’s camera followed the Laser, which directly hit the dozen or so residents behind her. These monsters were only chasing her because she had entered their aggro range. Compared to that, an attack drew much more aggro from them. Simply speaking, the Launcher created an OT and most of the residents switched their targets to the female Launcher, except for the three or four that hadn’t been hit by the laser.

“Oh!” Chen Guo heard Tang Rou suddenly say. The female Launcher had probably said a few words to her.

Soon afterwards, more artillery shells were fired and those remaining residents were aggroed onto the female Launcher. The dozen residents stopped chasing Soft Mist and began chasing after the Launcher.

But the female Launcher had already disappeared. She had clearly jumped down onto a different street. She was escaping from the monsters’ line of sight. The residents climbed up the walls quickly though, which was something players couldn’t do. The group of residents climbed over and onto the other street. Not longer after, the Launcher jumped onto another rooftop and down onto a different street.

After a few rounds of this, their aggro was wiped clean. The dozen residents stayed on the streets and were no longer interested in their escaped target.

This type of method for getting rid of aggro was simple and effective. But unfortunately, Tang Rou was unable to use it. Mages didn’t have high jumps and weren’t able to jump onto the rooftops.

Those that could had to use speicla moves. For example, the Gunner had Aerial Fire. Witches could use their Brooms to fly up. Assassins could double jump, etc. Battle Mages could do it through equipment effects and skills, but currently, they weren’t able to, yet.

The Launcher returned to the original street and walked towards Soft Mist.

“Thanks.” Chen Guo heard Tang Rou say. She also saw the Launcher’s name: Cleansing Mist.

“You recognize her?” Seeing that Tang Rou was no longer in danger, Chen Guo went to ask her.

“Yeah. She’s Ye Xiu’s friend. She dungeons with us a lot.”

“She seems really good?”

“She is!” Tang Rou said.

“Is she better than me?” Chen Guo laughed.

“That…. uh……. uh……” Tang Rou wasn’t sure how to answer.

“What?”

“You asked if she’s better. She says ‘uh’, which means that she’s better than you!” Ye Xiu couldn’t but explain to Chen Guo.

Chapter 267 – Christmas Hunting Leaderboards

“Hmph!” Chen Guo wasn’t as competitive as Tang Rou. It was only because the female character was playing the same class as she was, as well as her heroic entrance, which caught her eye, that she had jokingly asked such a question. In the end, Ye Xiu seemed certain that that female Launcher was better than she was, immediately making her depressed. She was completely capable of doing what that Launcher had done, too! Why was that Launcher better then?

“I think I’ll try again.” Tang Rou was clearly talking in-game.

Su Mucheng had just happened to pass by when she noticed that Tang Rou was in trouble. The trouble was now solved, but if Tang Rou continued, she would most likely fall into the same situation again. As a result, Su Mucheng had suggested that the two party up.

But Tang Rou wasn’t so soft. The only reason why the situation had occurred was because she hadn’t been prepared enough. She kept on aggroing them until she couldn’t deal with them anymore. But now that she had a fresh start, Tang Rou felt like if she paid a bit more attention, then the situation shouldn’t go as badly as before, which was why she had said to Su Mucheng that she wanted to try again by herself.

“Okay, that’s fine!” Su Mucheng said and sent a smiley face. Thus, the two split up and headed in opposite directions, one heading east and the other heading west.

Tang Rou had Soft Mist run a few steps forward and stop. She stretched her neck towards Ye Xiu’s screen to steal his techniques.

Ye Xiu’s progress was going smoothly. He quickly found another Christmas thief and, just like before, he aggroed it without disturbing any of the other residents. Ye Xiu saw Tang Rou out of the corner of his eyes. He attacked the thief, while saying: “There’s no point in looking. You won’t be able to learn how to do what I’m doing in an instant.”

“Why not?” Tang Rou was pondering over the method Ye Xiu had just used to avoid the monsters, when she heard Ye Xiu talk to her.

“Expert, you explain to her.” Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo.

“…….” Chen Guo was speechless. Usually, when someone called her an expert, she’d become happy. But being called an expert by someone who was clearly better than she was made her feel as if she had been called a noob!

Chen Guo glared at Ye Xiu, while still giving Tang Rou an explanation. She told her that Ye Xiu’s methods didn’t involve any special techniques, but it relied on experience and intuition, which could only be gained through time. This was something only experienced players possessed.

Tang Rou heard this and could only nod her head. As a new player, she had no way of replicating that. Just how far apart were the monster and herself? Tang Rou looked a hundred times, but couldn’t tell!

Since she had no way of copying Ye Xiu, Tang Rou was forced to use her own clumsy method. If the monster seemed easy to avoid, then she’d simply go through without arousing the monster. If the monster didn’t seem easy to avoid, she wouldn’t risk it and would find somewhere else to go —– she was basically just wandering around the city randomly. If there was nowhere to hide and no way of easily getting through, then her only choice would be to force her way through.

Tang Rou relied on her own ability and struggled through Sin City. She found a few Christmas thieves on the way and killed them off conveniently. To her, fighting was a lot simpler than finding her way around the city.

In the end, the saddest person was Chen Guo.

She had luckily bumped into a Christmas thief at the beginning of the event, but ever since then, she hadn’t encountered any others afterwards. Whenever she saw one, it was always taken away by someone else first. Chen Guo could only admire Tang Rou and Ye Xiu as they killed Christmas thieves from time to time.

The new server truly was better! For there to actually be Christmas thieves that no one was scrambling for… As for the Heavenly Domain, which Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze resided in? There were crowds of players everywhere she went. The players’ enthusiasm was too scary.

If the Heavenly Domain was like this, then that meant that the older servers were also like this. In addition, the Heavenly Domain had its own server leaderboard. Points gained from the old server and points gained from the Heavenly Domain wouldn’t be combined. Chen Guo had already decided that she would stick with the Heavenly Domain server. She didn’t have the ambition to get onto the leaderboards. She just wanted to kill a few thieves and then earn some of the rewards. But one hour after the event began, poor Chen Guo was only able to kill three Christmas thieves.

However, the rewards from catching three Christmas thieves was better than the gains one normally made in an hour. When max-leveled players turned in the stolen gifts from the thieves they had killed to Santa, the experience they gained would automatically be turned into money, in addition to a whole bunch of other rewards.

But the ones who were truly excited were those on the system announcements.

In the global chat, there would be messages about some players earning a rare reward.

In order to get on TV, the rewards had to be a Purple or higher ranked equipment, an uncommon material, a hidden dungeon map, a BOSS summoning scroll, an equipment enhancement scroll, or even skill books…..

All of these rewards were things that everyone wanted. It didn’t even matter what the probability of getting those were; everyone rushed like ducks to try and grab one.

Messages of joy, sobbing, bragging and cursing appeared in the global chat. It didn’t matter since no one would give up on the event.

Seeing how a few players were grumbling in grief about how they hadn’t been able to kill a single thief, Chen Guo’s three thieves looked quite promising. At the very least, her hour hadn’t been wasted. But for these types of events, the scariest part about them was comparing your results with others.

Compared to those crying players, Chen Guo was very lucky. However, compared to the two people beside her, Chen Guo really wanted to punch them.

On her left, Tang Rou had killed nine Christmas thieves in an hour.

On her right, Ye Xiu was even crazier. He had killed fourteen Christmas thieves in an hour. Chen Guo wasn’t even close to them.

For her, every time she caught a Christmas thief, she would impatiently run to Santa and exchange it for a present. But them? Their inventory had lots of stolen gifts in them, but it seemed as if they wouldn’t go back until their inventories were full.

Chen Guo was extremely sad! Fill up her inventory? That was only a dream for her!

Ye Xiu and Tang Rou focused on searching for Christmas thieves and hadn’t paid any attention to the person that was between them, who had only killed three in an hour.

Aside from searching for Christmas thieves, they had also paid attention to the leaderboard.

The Christmas Hunting Leaderboards. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was 261st place after an hour. As for Tang Rou’s Soft Mist, she was quite far from Lord Grim, at 784th place. The two were also able see Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist, which was at 319th place, way ahead of Tang Rou and fairly close to Ye Xiu.

But the biggest difference was that, while Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist were still rising up in the leaderboard, Soft Mist was beginning to hover around the 800th mark. Clearly, at this ranking, she was killing off Christmas thieves at the same rate as those at the 800th mark. The competition was fierce but Ye Xiu’s and Su Mucheng’s skill levels truly were higher than everyone else’s by a whole level.

The leaderboards clearly showed their gap, but for Tang Rou, these rankings only fired up her spirit even up more. As soon as her name showed up on the leaderboards, she rushed up to the 800th mark. But after that, she was unable to move forward any further. This achievement hadn’t come easy. She had been running around Sin City like crazy. In that hour, she had killed nine Christmas thieves, but had also killed eighteen Sin City residents. Those battles had consumed a lot of her time.

The Level 31-35 Christmas Hunting Leaderboard caught their attention, but they didn’t pay too much attention to other leaderboards.

For example, the Hunting Leaderboard for guilds.

This leaderboard didn’t distinguish between the different skill levels. It looked at the total number of points from all the players in the guild. Without a doubt, guilds with more members and higher-leveled members would have the advantage, but it also could be argued that this was a representation of a guild’s strength.

At this moment, the guild that placed first on the tenth server’s Christmas Hunting Guild Leaderboard wasn’t Herb Garden, Blue Brook Guild or Tyrannical Ambition.

Excellent Dynasty!

Excellent Dynasty was impressively placed first by a large margin, too. The number two was Herb Garden, who was followed closely behind by Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition. In reality, the rankings between these three guilds were a messy battle. The placings between them constantly shifted.

For all of these big guilds, who had failed in the competition for the dungeon records, this Christmas event was a huge chance for them to prove themselves. This competition this time seemed to be unrelated to Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu glanced at it for a second and then stopped paying attention to it.

Chapter 268 – Deviously Stealing Monsters

The players continued to work hastily at their task. As for the leaderboards, the majority of players looked at it with one third envy, one third jealousy and one third pain.

The players on the leaderboards were definitely earning more presents and rewards than the other players. In addition, whether it was due to skill or luck, these players would only continue to grow stronger with more presents, making others feel truly helpless at their situation.

The players who were on the leaderboards followed their placing carefully in order to maintain it or rise further. Only by doing this long-term would they gradually begin to guarantee their spots.

Being able to hunt Christmas thieves in Sin City was undoubtedly a reflection of a player’s skill. Tang Rou continued to work hard and her ranking began to gradually rise as a result.

Finally, when some of the luckier players, who had found Christmas thieves consecutively, began to run out of luck, they gradually started falling off as players, who relied on their skill, such as Tang Rou, steadily pushed ahead.

774……

767……

751……

749……

Every time Tang Rou killed a Christmas thief, the number of points she earned increased and her name would go up a few rankings. And just like this, Tang Rou continued advancing step by step, improving her spirit with each step. Her left hand tapped her keyboard, while her right hand held her mouse and her two eyes stared intently at the screen, unwilling to shift away for even a single second.

Leaderboards possessed this type of mysterious attractive force.

Another one!

Tang Rou was getting more and more used to Sin City’s atmosphere and was also getting better and better at finding targets while having a hazy field of vision. Out in the distance, amidst the rain and fog, a blurry figure could be seen. Tang Rou determined that it was a Christmas thief and immediately rushed towards it.

At the same time, another figure flashed out from the other side of the street, sprinting towards the same Christmas thief. In the figure’s hands was a bright lightsaber that stood out in the rain.

Tang Rou saw the figure and immediately understood the person’s intent. After being in Sin City for so long, she had seen many other players, but this was the first time she had set her eyes on the same target as another player.

Tang Rou obviously wouldn’t back down. She chose the shortest route to the Christmas thief and sprinted towards it. A Sin City resident that she had been planning to avoid was alerted. She didn’t have the time to bother being careful.

The Sin City resident naturally wouldn’t be nice to Tang Rou. Soft Mist’s figure dashed past his eyes as the resident pounced forward coldly with a knife in his hands.

The opposing Blade Master also noticed the incoming Battle Mage. The majority of the players who were currently in Sin City were veterans in Glory and were far more experienced than Tang Rou. Judging from the distance between the two to the Christmas thief, the Blade Master determined that he was one step faster than her. Just as he thought that he had won, he saw that the Battle Mage had alerted the monster, which made him feel even happier, reinforcing his confidence in snatching this Christmas thief.

When the resident closed in, Tang Rou didn’t hesitate. Her right hand swiped her mouse and Soft Mist sent a Sky Strike, launching the resident into the air. Soft Mist stepped sideways and then used a Falling Flower Palm. The force from the palm scattered the rain, creating a ripple. It all looked very tyrannical.

“Not good!” When the Blade Master saw the direction of the palm, he panicked. The Battle Mage had unexpectedly used the monster to profit from the disaster. She had originally been a bit slower, but now with the Falling Flower Palm, the resident had accurately crashed into the Christmas thief.

After the Christmas thief climbed up, the thief nimbly ran towards Soft Mist. The Blade Master quietly watched and could only curse out loud.

Tang Rou heard the player curse, but ignored him. Soft Mist went forward and met with the Christmas thief and that resident.

It was a 1v2, but Tang Rou wasn’t scared. She had killed quite a few Christmas thieves and residents already. Attacking two of them at the same time wasn’t too difficult for her, which was why she wasn’t afraid to alert the resident and use it to her advantage.

The Blade Master originally planned to get ready to leave. However, at this moment, the two players moved a bit closer to one another, allowing him to see the blurry ID that had been hidden by the mist and rain.

Soft Mist.

Seeing this ID, the Blade Master halted.

He put his sword next to him as the Blade Master quietly watched Soft Mist fight.

Level 31. The Blade Master looked up the ID and confirmed Soft Mist’s level. At this level, she would suffer from Level Suppression in Sin City. Yet, it looked as if the 1v2 was going smoothly, confirming Soft Mist’s strength. The Blade Master couldn’t deny that she deserved to be a member of Lord Grim’s dungeon team.

The Blade Master thought to himself for a bit and then quietly left.

Tang Rou had noticed the player watching her and was prepared for a fight.

But after seeing the player leave, she relaxed. She guessed that the player was thinking about whether or not she was able to deal with both a Christmas thief and a monster at the same time. If she wasn’t capable of doing so, then he would have picked up the scraps. But after seeing that the situation wasn’t going to happen, he naturally left. This type of thinking wasn’t anything noble, but it was at least better than directly killing the opposing player and forcefully stealing the monster.

Tang Rou clearly wasn’t having any trouble with the two monsters if she still had the ability to think about other things. After collecting her thoughts, she focused on the fighting. But to her surprise, the Blade Master returned not long after and was running like crazy, too. Behind him were ten or so Sin City residents.

With around ten people running along the wet ground, the footsteps were able to be heard clearly. Tang Rou heard the noise so turned her head to look and saw that the guy was running towards her with the mob of monsters.

Tang Rou stopped smiling. This guy was in the same situation as she was before! Even though she sympathized with him, Tang Rou couldn’t do anything to help. She was afraid of this, too.

In the blink of an eye, the person reached her. Tang Rou looked closer and was suddenly startled.

Wind Following Sword!

Wasn’t this ID the same as that Blade Master she had just seen? He had only just run off, so why did he suddenly gather so many monsters? That wasn’t normal, right?

Even if Tang Rou was inexperienced, she could still tell that something wasn’t right. Just as she brought up her guard, this time, Wind Following Sword wasn’t as nice and a sword wind sliced towards her.

A sword light flashed amidst the dusky rain and fog. The sword wind carried the rain, beautifully soaring towards Soft Mist.

It looked good, but it didn’t make her feel good.

Tang Rou immediately had Soft Mist dodge to the side, but the thief and resident didn’t care about her situation and continued to attack.

Sword light flashed once again. Wind Following Sword used a Sword Draw and then followed up with a Triple Slash to close in. In that instant, three opponents were attacking her, but Tang Rou didn’t panic. She dodged to the side and sent out a Sky Strike.

Wind Following Sword was a bit slow. He wasn’t able to dodge the attack in time and was launched into the air, not high up, but still knocked up. Tang Rou wasn’t polite in the slightest and followed up quickly with a Falling Flower Palm.

Palm hit!

Wind Following Sword was hit directly by the Falling Flower Palm and was sent flying backwards. Tang Rou suddenly cried out, “Oh, no!”

“Ha ha ha ha, girl, you really like using this trick!”

Wind Following Sword wasn’t acting like the loser and was unexpectedly laughing. His body flew and crashed into the giant mob of Sin City residents.

These residents had grouped together. His crash was even more thorough than Su Mucheng’s Laser Rifle. Every single resident was hit.

And their aggro counted towards Soft Mist.

Against a devious opponent, Tang Rou’s lack of experience had finally cost her.

Chapter 269 – It’s Not That Simple

The ten or so Sin City residents climbed up from the ground; their gazes were all directed towards Soft Mist. They hissed and then swarmed forward.

Wind Following Sword slowly got up at this moment. On top of his head was a word bubble with an “evil” smiley face in it.

Tang Rou felt extremely disdainful of this player. This time, she was actually angry. She hadn’t been this angry even when the big guilds had ambushed her.

She didn’t say anything and then suddenly pounced directly towards the ten residents. However, her Scarlet Moon Lance was pointed towards the peaceful Wind Following Sword.

Wind Following Sword was startled by Tang Rou’s manner, but after seeing the ten residents between them, he immediately calmed down.

This sister. It’s hard to even say if she’d be able to run away from these monsters, yet she actually advanced forward instead of retreating. It looked very silly.

Wind Following Sword didn’t move and watched Soft Mist clash with the residents. He wasn’t planning on leaving. He wanted that Christmas thief behind Soft Mist. Of course, if he also killed off Soft Mist, then that’d be good, too.

Soft Mist once again used a Falling Flower Palm. Her palm hit the center of the mob and the energy rippled through, spreading out in a series of crashing explosions. It was as if a bomb had been set off inside the mob. The monsters were immediately split up and sent into a state of confusion.

Wind Following Sword looked and saw that Soft Mist was better than he had originally thought. But even though the Falling Flower Palm had been done well, if she wanted to directly charge forward, it wouldn’t be that simple.

Because of the Level Suppression, Falling Flower Palm’s blow-away effect would be greatly weakened. The palm really had been executed beautifully, but the effects didn’t reach Tang Rou’s expectations. The distance that the monsters were blown away wasn’t far enough. Tang Rou was just about to have Soft Mist charge forward and attack Wind Following Sword, but two of the residents that hadn’t been blown away suddenly pounced towards her.

Wind Following Sword laughed coldly. In this type of situation, he didn’t think that Soft Mist would dare to battle with these two residents. If she did, the other residents would surround her, and by that point, even if she were given wings, she’d have difficulty escaping.

In the end, Soft Mist swung her Scarlet Moon Lance and actually attacked the two residents.

Wind Following Sword stared blankly and then sneered: “Idiot!”

The two residents were launched into the sky by the Sky Strike. Closely following, Soft Mist extended her hands and stabbed forward at one of them with a Dragon Tooth, sending one of them towards Wind Following Sword. Soft Mist stepped forward, stabbed forward again, picking up the other resident, and threw it in a half circle. That resident was thrown behind her, causing a shockwave, knocking the monsters that had just gotten up back to the ground.

This time, Wind Following Sword was truly shocked!

Under the Level Suppression, Sky Strike’s knock-up effect wouldn’t be too high, but in that short amount of time, Soft Mist had actually completed a Dragon Tooth and a Circle Swing, with extreme accuracy as well. That hand speed made Wind Following Sword re-evaluate her.

Wind Following Sword dodged the resident, but then saw a Fire Chaser fly towards him and strike the resident.

The Fire Chaser exploded and Wind Following Sword was caught in the explosion. Fire Chasers did Area of Effect damage.

She had even sent out a Fire Chaser at that moment? She had controlled it perfectly as well to catch both of them in the explosion. It definitely wasn’t a coincidence.

This girl! Her mechanics were incredible!

Wind Following Sword was thinking on turning, when Soft Mist closed in. Her Scarlet Moon Lance sliced towards him as if it were about to cut him into a meat patty.

But Wind Following Sword wouldn’t be beaten as easily as those monsters. He sidestepped and countered with his own attack. He then jumped backwards twice, causing Soft Mist’s next two stabs to hit nothing but air.

Tang Rou was startled. For the competitive her, this type of situation excited her. Whether it was her hand speed or her microing, they would all be better than normal when she was in battle. Her Double Stab had been performed quite quickly, but the opponent had unexpectedly anticipated it and jumped backwards.

Wind Following Sword chuckled and returned with an “Upward Slash”. Tang Rou jumped back without thinking. Pow! The Christmas thief had caught up and whacked her.

The thief’s aggro was still on Soft Mist’s body. The thief wasn’t planning on running!

At this moment, Sin City’s residents had climbed up and pounced forward. But even in this situation, Tang Rou was even more intent on carrying out her program than those NPCs and continued to attack Wind Following Sword.

Her lance pricked up with a Sky Strike, which was once again easily dodged by Wind Following Sword.

She turned and her left hand struck. A tyrannical Falling Flower Palm shot forward, but unfortunately missed.

Missed? Why can’t I hit him?

Tang Rou didn’t feel like there were any problems with her playing, but the opponent seemed to always be able to predict her moves. Under this tense situation, Tang Rou was unable to calm down. The only thought in her head was to fight!

Even if she was going to end up being surrounded by the monsters, she would drag that evil guy to hell with her.

With her fighting spirit risen, she fiercely attacked.

This time, she only used normal attacks. Tang Rou’s hands moved even faster than before, sacrificing precision to do so. All she knew was that her attacks were headed in the general direction towards Wind Following Sword! Even if she died, she was going to kill that guy.

Stab, slash, slice! These basic attacks brought about an unexpected effect.

Wind Following Sword wasn’t as calm as before. The three consecutive attacks had thrown him off guard. He failed to dodge the slice, which hit his waist, causing his character to stagger to the side two steps. He didn’t seem to be having as easy of a time dodging as he had before.

Tang Rou suddenly understood what was going on.

Ye Xiu had taught her about this before. Pay attention to the skills that were used. And that Wind Following Sword was using this method.

Before this, Tang Rou had used a Falling Flower Palm, Sky Strike, Dragon Tooth and Circle Swing in quick succession. After that, those four skills were on cooldown and the Chasers would be shot out only when hitting the target. Finally, since Soft Mist was a Level 31 Battle Mage, her only skill left was a Double Stab.

Wind Following Sword had calculated this, which was why he was able to easily predict the Double Stab. Soft Mist then used her skills one after the other once the skills went off cooldown, which Wind Following Wind predicted and dodged easily.

It was because her hand speed was quick that the opponent could predict her moves so easily. The instant that she finished all her skills, she would use them again as soon as they could be used.

This Wind Following Sword wasn’t so simple either. Tang Rou had obviously practiced this before under Ye Xiu’s guidance, but even though the theory was simple, doing it in practice wasn’t. Tang Rou was still learning to pay attention to her own skills’ cooldowns and was far from being able to pay attention to the opponent’s skill usage and cooldowns. But this Wind Following Sword, even if it was only because Soft Mist only had a few skills and was predictable, was still able to do something that Tang Rou wasn’t able to.

But this time, Tang Rou’s quick normal attacks finally made it so that he was unable to keep up. Normal attacks didn’t have cooldowns, so Wind Following Sword had no way of predicting them. And since Tang Rou was faster than he was, he had no way of dealing with them.

He hadn’t yet stabilized himself, when a scarlet light flashed in front of him again. Soft Mist’s Sky Strike had struck again. This time, Wind Following Sword wasn’t able to dodge and was launched into the air.

Circle Swing!

The lance stabbed through Wind Following Sword and then threw him towards the ground. The monsters that were now surrounding her were knocked to the ground by the following shockwave.

However, Tang Rou wasn’t able to completely protect herself from every direction. During that time, she had also been hit by the monsters.

Chapter 270 – Battle Spirit

Tang Rou finally hit Wind Following Sword, but the price in doing so had been extremely high. During that time, the monsters were hitting her, dropping her health by a third. Unfortunately, due to the Level Suppression, the damage that she took was also greater.

In comparison, the damage that she had inflicted onto Wind Following Sword was not even close to that high.

It definitely wouldn’t be good for her if they continued to exchange blows like this.

Even though it was a fact that Battle Mages were a part of the Mage class, they had a Strength growth rate of 3.5, which was the same as Blade Masters. However, for their defense, they maintained the same value, a weak 2.5 Vitality growth rate, just like the other Mage classes.

And for their equipment, Battle Mages were proficient with Leather Armor, while Blade Masters were proficient with Light Armor. Battle Mages also had weaker Defenses.

Battle Mages had the disadvantage in Vitality and Defense. How could Battle Mages trade blows with Blade Masters?

Even more so, Wind Following Sword’s level was higher than hers and Soft Mist was the only opponent he had faced. On the other hand, Soft Mist also had the ten residents, as well as the mighty Christmas thief, as opponents.

It was extremely difficult, but compared to beating Ye Xiu, Tang Rou felt that it was still doable.

Soft Mist brandished her lance and guarded against the monsters. She fished out a health pot and downed it.

In an endurance battle, you had to grasp the timing for when to drink potions. As soon as your health and mana began to fall, you had to start paying attention to them. The things Ye Xiu had taught her were now appearing clearly in her mind. Tang Rou knew how difficult this battle would be so she focused her attention on the battle.

Dragon Tooth! Her Scarlet Moon Lance stabbed forward, brushing past the two residents, and headed directly towards Wind Following Sword, who hastily dodged it. Soft Mist then followed up with a Falling Flower Palm. The monsters ahead were blown away, blocking Wind Following Sword’s left and right escape routes.

Wind Following Sword immediately jumped into the air and allowed the flying monsters to pass through. Seeing that there was a huge opening in Soft Mist’s defenses right now, Wind Following Sword grabbed his sword and, just as he was about to use a Falling Light Blade, he suddenly changed his mind and canceled it.

The skill hadn’t come out, but since he had already activated it, the skill went cooldown. It looked like a waste, but in a high-skill battle, faking an attack was common.

Wind Following Sword didn’t have any intentions of faking an attack. When he landed on the ground, he laughed coldly: “Are you trying to trick me? Girl, you’re still too naive.”

The Falling Light Blade might have hit Soft Mist, but the shockwave would have also hit the surrounding monsters. At that moment, Wind Following Sword had figured out Tang Rou’s intent: to trick him into aggroing those monsters.

“You go and play with them on your own!” Wind Following Sword laughed. He used a Triple Slash to retreat far away.

Seeing that Wind Following Sword hadn’t been duped, Tang Rou’s plan fell through. After seeing him run away, she became even more aware that the situation she was in wasn’t looking good. That guy was too shrewd. Compared to how he played, she really was too simple.

Perhaps the only way for her to win is to charge forward without looking back!

Soft Mist’s Neutral Chasers provided her with a movement speed buff and the Fire Chasers buffed her Strength. Her condition flourished as she rushed towards Wind Following Sword.

Wind Following Sword had pretty much figured out her plan. He walked around and decided that he wouldn’t tangle around with her. Soft Mist had the advantage in movement speed, but Wind Following Sword was able to walk around freely, while she had to deal with the monsters. She was able to hit Wind Following Sword sometimes, but she had no way of following up on it. If she ignored the pursuing monsters, she would definitely be the first to fall.

They continued to run around like this and Wind Following Sword’s health slowly whittled away. However, Wind Following Sword didn’t panic. He took out a health potion and downed it right in front of Soft Mist and looked at her as if he were the emperor.

How to fight in a prolonged battle was a course that every expert needed to take. Wind Following Sword clearly knew about this. At this moment, he had calmly drank a potion, and arrogantly too. He had naturally wanted Tang Rou to lose hope.

Wind Following Sword hadn’t been paying attention to the time. When he checked, he suddenly jumped up in fright. He had been messing around with Soft Mist for 20 minutes already!

Soft Mist had spent 20 minutes being chased by monsters, who were six to eight levels higher, while chasing him. This girl was a bit too fierce!

Wind Following Sword arrogantly drank another potion. As his opponent chased after him, she also drank a potion.

She didn’t waver and hadn’t admitted defeat yet. This type of person could be knocked down, beaten, and killed! However, it didn’t look as if it were possible to make her give up.

“You really do possess skill.” Wind Following Sword began speaking, “But, this truly is too boring!”

Tang Rou ignored him and continued to have Soft Mist rush forward. Wind Following Sword continued to dodge her attacks.

“Watch my sword!” Wind Following Sword suddenly shouted. Soft Mist immediately halted.

“Ha ha ha ha, I was just playing with you.” Wind Following Sword laughed, as if he was looking for some fun in something that was very boring.

After 20 minutes of playing like this, Tang Rou’s condition finally seemed to be declining. Her continuous charging forward without looking back momentum was affected and the monsters had caught up with her. It didn’t look as if she possessed the ability to deal with Wind Following Sword anymore.

“F*ck.” Wind Following Sword was finally able to stand still and relax.

“If you knew this was going to happen, why’d you have to dawdle around! Hurry up and die already. You’re wasting my time.” Wind Following Sword shouted at the struggling Soft Mist.

“Blade Masters really liked spouting nonsense!” Tang Rou, who had been silent the whole time, suddenly shouted.

Her voice sounds quite nice!

That was the first thought that appeared in Wind Following Sword’s mind. But, he could also hear the coldness and murderous intent in her voice. To be toyed around like this, it’d be weird if she wasn’t angry.

“Aren’t you bored of talking so much?” Accompanying this was a loud explosion. A lightning bolt crashed down from Sin City’s skies. The monsters that were surrounding Soft Mist were suddenly blown away. A Falling Flower Palm, along with a coincidental thunder boom, made the scene look extremely impressive. Wind Following Sword suddenly felt weird. Under the Level Suppression, why was her Falling Flower Palm able to have such an effect?

He didn’t have the time to think carefully because Soft Mist had already pounced forward towards him.

“You really are stubborn.” Wind Following Sword sounded a bit helpless, but his sword wasn’t. A Sword Draw sliced through the air. The girl had fought against the monsters for quite a while, so him doing some damage wouldn’t aggro the monsters.

Soft Mist jumped into the air and dodged the Sword Slash.

Dragon Tooth! Soft Mist immediately stabbed forward.

Wind Following Sword calmly jumped backwards.

Pow! He was hit!

“What?” Wind Following Sword was astonished. How did that attack hit? Did her attack speed increase?

He didn’t have the time to think about this problem. Wind Following Sword was suddenly in a Stunned state. He couldn’t help but notice that his health was dropping a bit too fast.

It was just a Dragon Tooth. How did it do so much damage?

Another scarlet light flashed.

What? Is it actually faster? Wind Following Sword thought as he was launched into the air.

The following two stabs directly pierced through him. Double Stab!

He flew outwards, but the third stab grabbed him in midair and swung him around.

“That can’t be right! Why is my health dropping so quickly?” Wind Following Sword began to panic.

Dragon Tooth. Sky Strike. Double Stab. These three moves had dropped his health bar to half.

As he was Circle Swung around in the air, Wind Following Sword glanced at Soft Mist’s body. A light, golden glow surrounded her body. He hadn’t noticed before because of the rain.

Wind Following Sword was immediately stunned. He, who was experienced, obviously recognized this skill.

It was the Battle Mage’s Level 50 Awakening Skill: Battle Spirit!

How could this skill appear now???

Chapter 271 – Seventh Stage Battle Spirit

A Level 50 Awakening Skill obviously couldn’t appear on a Level 31 character. However, the glow around Soft Mist, as well as her sudden increase in attack speed and strength, was without a doubt from Battle Spirit.

Battle Spirit continuously buffed the Battle Mage as they fought. The buff applied was based on the number of consecutive combos done by the Battle Mage.

At a 10-hit Combo, the attack speed would increase by 0.5, the movement speed by 2%, and the Strength stat by 30.

At a 20-hit Combo, the attack speed would increase by 1.0, the movement speed by 4%, and the Strength stat by 50.

At a 30-hit Combo, the attack speed would increase by 1.5, the movement speed by 6%, and the Strength stat by 70.

And like this, there were a total of seven stages. On the seventh stage, the buff would be even greater than the previous jumps.

The seventh stage required the Battle Mage to Combo 120 hits, but the attack speed would increase by 6, the movement speed by 24%, and the Strength stat by 260. Compared to the sixth stage, it required twice as many combos, but also doubled the buff.

How strong were these buffs?

An attack speed of 6 was similar to the difference between the slowest Greatsword and the Tachi.

A movement speed increase of 24% was 4% more than the buff from a max-level Neutral Chaser.

As for a Strength stat increase of 260, that was even more terrifying. The Ghostblade’s Sword Boundary would only increase the Strength stat by 150 at max level.

A Battle Mage at the seventh stage of Battle Spirit was extremely terrifying.

Wind Following Sword was an experienced player. Soft Mist was moving faster, attacking faster, and also hitting harder! He was well aware that she was at the seventh stage of Battle Spirit. That golden glow around her was quite distinct.

The seventh stage was indeed extremely strong, but in reality, it was practically impossible to achieve. If she had comboed Wind Following Sword 120 times, then he would have died long before that. If that happened, she wouldn’t even have the opportunity of getting to the seventh stage.

The seventh stage could, in reality, only be achieved in a chaotic battle where there were many targets, allowing the Battle Mage to quickly rack up a high combo. Soft Mist had used these surrounding monsters to accumulate a 120-hit combo. After reaching the seventh stage, she turned to Wind Following Sword to attack him.

As for where the Battle Spirit came from, Wind Following Sword knew the answer.

Event. It was due to the Christmas event.

The items from Christmas thieves could be used. After using the item, the item couldn’t be used to exchange for gifts with Santa. These items couldn’t be traded and weren’t worth any money. They would also expire after the event had ended.

Smart players weren’t likely to use these items, but Soft Mist had been forced to use one of the items that she had received from a Christmas thief.

Skill Scroll!

Skill Scrolls allowed a skill to be added onto an equipment. The Skill Scroll would then add one level to the skill. The level of the skill could even go over the max-level. In other words, if a skill was at max level 10, then after using a Skill Scroll, it added a level to that skill, making the skill go to level 11. However, there was a limit to the amount of times a skill scroll could be used, so it wasn’t possible to level up endlessly through this method.

In order to level a skill, the character first had to have learned it already. If the character hadn’t learned it yet, the Skill Scroll would only be used on the weapon, which would allow the skill to be used at a skill level of 1.

All of this was explained on the Skill Scroll. Tang Rou had put the Battle Spirit Skill Scroll on her Scarlet Moon Lance, which allowed her Level 31 Soft Mist to learn the Level 50 Awakening skill: Battle Spirit.

The Christmas event was even more generous. With this scroll, Soft Mist was able to directly learn a maxed Battle Spirit. Of course, this would only be temporary and the game wasn’t afraid of it messing up the game’s balance. They wanted to let new players personally have a taste of what high-leveled skills were like. And due to this, it helped Tang Rou out tremendously.

Tang Rou didn’t really understand all of this. She had heard from Chen Guo that Battle Spirit was the Battle Mage’s signature move, so she understood that quite well. After seeing this scroll in her inventory, she didn’t hesitate to add it to her weapon.

In ordinary circumstances, a normal Skill Scroll would only allow her to use a level one Battle Spirit, which would only allow her to reach the first stage and the first stage wouldn’t be enough power. But because of the event, a max-level Battle Spirit allowed Soft Mist to explode with power.

A sudden increase of 260 Strength at Level 31 was much more terrifying than having that increase at Level 50 or Level 70 because the proportional strength gained was completely different.

Wind Following Sword quickly understood, but it was already too late. Even though he was experienced, there was no way that he could have anticipated this situation.

Wind Following Sword was thrown onto the ground. His health rapidly decreased and he was only at ⅓ health now. Attacks with a 260 Strength increase were way too difficult to bear.

Wind Following Sword immediately drank a potion. He wouldn’t give up so easily. The seventh stage was terrifying, but it wasn’t without a weakness.

Battle Spirit was a passive skill. After a Battle Mage learned it, they would grow stronger with more combos. However, the buff depended upon the combos and wasn’t as stable.

For example, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had reached a 120-hit Combo from the monsters. If she stopped attacking, she would still have the seventh stage buff and if she kept on fighting, she would still be fighting at the seventh stage. But her next attack would reset the Battle Spirit’s combo count. If her combos stopped at 10 in the next round of attacks, her seventh stage buff would wear off and she would only have a first stage buff.

In other words, if she wanted to maintain her seventh stage buff, then every time she did a round of attacks, she would have to keep doing 120-hit combos.

When Soft Mist rushed forward, she used all of the skills she had at her disposal in order to create a combo. If she stopped comboing, her seventh stage buff would immediately wear off and Wind Following Sword understood this better than Tang Rou did.

As a result, as long as he dodged or interrupted the next attack…….

A scarlet light flashed.

Wind Following Sword was still thinking the plan through, when Soft Mist’s attack connected. The previous Circle Swing knocked him down, disabling him from using a Quick Recover.

Wind Following Sword was suddenly scared. In terms of mechanics, he never was fit to be her opponent. And now that his opponent had the seventh stage buff with an attack speed increase of 6 and a 24% increase in movement speed, along with the movement speed buff from the Neutral Chasers, how was he going to dodge her attacks?

Just as he was thinking about Neutral Chasers, one of Soft Mist’s Neutral Chasers slammed into Wind Following Sword’s head. Luckily, the Neutral Chaser did magic damage, so it wasn’t affected by the Strength boost and the damage was normal. However, as the Neutral Chaser exploded, Soft Mist swung her lance and launched him into the air with a Sky Strike.

“I can’t escape!” Wind Following Sword cried. If Soft Mist used all her skills, his life would certainly end! However……. if Soft Mist killed him, then she’d also die as well due to the attacks from the oncoming monsters.

Wind Following Sword knew it was over, but he still held a bit of hope.

As Wind Following Sword thought of this, he suddenly saw an item roll towards Soft Mist’s feet.

Wind Following Sword immediately laughed madly. He turned his camera mid-air and saw a person’s hand pulling back.

“Bang!” A grenade exploded under Soft Mist’s feet, knocking her aside. Even though she quickly used a Quick Recover and didn’t get knocked to the ground, Soft Mist’s seventh stage Battle Spirit immediately wore off.

“Ha ha ha! Girl, you and I aren’t the only ones playing the game!” Wind Following Sword laughed in glee.

Tang Rou felt depressed. She had already seen that there was someone on a rooftop nearby and there were also more players coming from the far end of the street. She knew that, this time, she was out of luck.

“You’re quite right.”

At this moment, Tang Rou suddenly heard a voice. The voice was very close, as if it were coming from next to her……

Chapter 272 – Ups and Downs

“Who is it?” Wind Following Sword turned his camera around to find the speaker.

“It’s a game! Calling for help if you’re in trouble isn’t anything shameful. Look at this bro. He has the advantage and he’s asking for help. That awareness and that decision-making is something you should learn!”

Tang Rou had already figured out who the speaker was. She looked at Ye Xiu, who was talking to her. His voice had spread out both from outside and inside the game.

Between these two, Chen Guo was focused on her own screen and didn’t seem as if she intended on moving. But, this didn’t fit with her personality. Her current dignified look only made it seem even stranger. Tang Rou immediately guessed that Chen Guo had seen that her situation wasn’t looking good, so she had gone to find Ye Xiu, who rushed over to help.

“What are you looking at? The monsters are coming.” Ye Xiu said.

Tang Rou hastily turned her head. The swarm of monsters were still targeting her. Soft Mist didn’t have much health left and her potions were on cooldown. Before this, it had been very difficult to find an opportunity to attack Wind Following Sword. After finding the opportunity, she had ignored everything else. As long as the monsters didn’t interrupt her, she wouldn’t care. Even if she herself died, she had to bring Wind Following Sword down with her.

It had originally been possible, but then a helper had suddenly appeared. This splash of cold water had caused Tang Rou to become somewhat dispirited. But to her surprise, Ye Xiu had also arrived at this moment.

She liked to solve her problems on her own. But she now found out that during a crisis, someone pulling her out of it felt wonderful. She had never felt this sort of up and down feeling before.

Tang Rou was distracted by her feelings. The monsters had once again pounced on her and her health was almost red. The monsters had already surrounded her. It was true that Ye Xiu had come, but could he get her out of this mess?

She had these types of thoughts in her head, but Tang Rou wouldn’t give up so easily. A Falling Flower Palm, which was originally meant for Wind Following Sword, instead hit several monsters in front of her and blew them away.

At this moment, loud bangs exploded nearby. The monsters on her left and right had been thrown tumbling into the air by the explosions. In the previous second, they had her surrounded. In the next second, they were sent into a mess.

A white light fell onto her body —- Lord Grim’s Heal. Next, Lord Grim jumped down from the rooftop and landed next to Soft Mist. The sound of a gatling gun came from the rooftop. The flying bullets headed directly towards the rooftop of the opposing Spitfire.

The Spitfire immediately dashed along the road. The Gatling Gun chased after his footsteps. The tiles on the rooftop shattered into pieces, but not a single bullet landed on his body. At this moment, he felt as if his dodging had been extremely beautiful, but then he heard three shots and saw three Anti-Tank Missiles whistling towards him. The Spitfire had thought that he had dodged well, but in reality, his opponent had fired in that way in order to lure him into firing range.

The three Anti-Tank Missiles had been out of his expectations and were in a triangle formation too. Locked into a certain area, he had nowhere to run.

The Spitfire jumped down to the side. But as soon as he jumped, the explosion sent out a shockwave, sending him flying to the other side of the street.

“Hurry up and kill your Christmas thief. I’ll help you block them.” Ye Xiu said to Tang Rou.

Tang Rou looked around her. The Christmas thief had been in the middle. It had just been knocked down. After getting up, it headed directly towards her. Tang Rou immediately had Soft Mist meet up and give it a beating. The other monsters also tried to rush forward, but Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist threw down a charged-up Cannonball, scattering them into the wind like kites.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had already joined their party, so she wasn’t affected by the blast. Even though it was still a situation of few versus many, with Su Mucheng’s help, the remaining monsters were few enough for Tang Rou to deal with.

As for Ye Xiu, he was controlling his Lord Grim and heading towards Wind Following Sword.

Wind Following Sword saw him clearly. His enthusiasm died down and, instead of fighting, he turned tail and ran.

Within moments, Tang Rou was no longer in any great danger. Chen Guo let out a sigh of relief, but her feelings were complicated.

This was because Wind Following Sword’s style and name were very similar to someone whose ID she recognized.

Heavenly Domain. An old veteran of Excellent Dynasty, Aura Following Sword. When Chen Guo joined Excellent Dynasty, she often heard of his treachery.

Correct, Chen Guo was also a member of Excellent Dynasty. She had always been a loyal fan of Excellent Era, so of course she had wanted to join Excellent Dynasty. Her Chasing Haze wasn’t bad and Chen Guo’s skill level was decent. She was good enough to join these guilds and had gotten into Excellent Dynasty quite smoothly. She had been a member up until now, so she had a few friends in there.

Aura Following Sword was a very famous expert in the guild. Chen Guo and her friends with their normal accounts never really had the chance to ever play with these experts. But these experts’ activities were often the topic of their discussion.

Aura Following Sword often performed devious deeds against other guilds’ players. To guild members like Chen Guo, it was very fun to hear about, so she had a good impression of him.

But today, when she saw his treachery in action, it was towards the friend sitting next to her. Chen Guo suddenly felt that this person wasn’t very nice. Her concept of treachery had already turned completely negative.

Chen Guo hadn’t seen the reason that it had all started, but Soft Mist had to deal with a large mob of monsters, while Wind Following Sword just ran around, not leaving. Tang Rou ground her teeth and tried to kill him. This scene was enough to make Chen Guo make a few guesses.

Chen Guo understood Tang Rou’s personality. Even though an expert like Ye Xiu was nearby, she knew that Tang Rou would never ask for help, so Chen Guo asked for help in her place.

One side was a member from her guild, while the other side was her friend, which made Chen Guo feel a bit awkward on the inside. Due to her close friendship with Tang Rou and from a justice viewpoint, Chen Guo didn’t hesitate to stand by Tang Rou’s side. Now that she was looking at things from a different angle, her only desire now was to see that Wind Following Sword whose treachery she used to adore have his head splatter against the wall.

“Huh! Why’d he run!” Chen Guo pretended to be playing, but in reality, her character was running randomly around the map. She glanced sideways from time to time at Ye Xiu as he was about to teach the devious Wind Following Sword a lesson. But how could she know Wind Following Sword would suddenly turn tail and run? Chen Guo was disappointed and blurted it out.

Seeing that Tang Rou was looking at her, Chen Guo hastily adjusted her seat, while hitting her keyboard as if she was playing: “You’re not going anywhere!”

Tang Rou was currently fighting a few monsters, but couldn’t resist chuckling: “What are you acting for?”

“Ha ha!’ Chen Guo saw that she had been found out and didn’t explain herself. She openly watched the battles on the two screens. She wanted to see the situations on both sides, so her head was constantly turning left and right like a pellet drum.

Wind Following Sword was heading towards the street ahead in order to pick up his friend because he knew of Lord Grim’s identity.

Chen Yehui had to manage such a large guild and in the end, he still needed a few trusted aides. In Excellent Dynasty, he didn’t dare mention that they were going to fight against Ye Qiu. However, as his trusted aide, Wind Following Sword still knew about this reality.

No matter how experienced or how devious Wind Following Sword was, he doubted that he had the ability to fight with a God like Ye Qiu. Seeing Lord Grim come towards him, and without a helper at his own side, Wind Following Sword was trembling. He trembled out a turn and tapped the keyboard to sprint away and wished that he had a skill like Battle Spirit to hasten his movement.

However, running away was a hope of his. Whether he could actually do it was a different matter.

Ye Xiu used the Shadow Clone Technique. Lord Grim immediately teleported a distance, lifted his hands and threw out a Grenade. He didn’t throw it at Wind Following Sword’s feet and instead threw it in front of him. Wind Following Sword knew that if he kept going forward he would be sent flying back by the Grenade. His only choice was to go around the explosion. But going around it cost him time and the distance between them immediately closed by a few steps.

Triple Slash! Wind Following Sword wanted to use this skill to move faster. But then he heard a hum from behind him. He turned his head and saw Lord Grim coming in with an Assassin’s Shining Cut, which was faster than Triple Slash’s movement speed.

Wind Following Sword panicked. He was about to be caught and he was still some distance away from his friend. Ah, Ye Qiu! The person who was about to catch him was Ye Qiu!

“Bang!” A gun sound rang out from behind him. The distance was too close. Wind Following Sword didn’t have any time to react. Even if he couldn’t dodge it, he had to keep running! Wind Following Sword continued to tap his keyboard like mad, but discovered that his character wasn’t able to move.

“Sh*t! A Stun Bullet!”

The Stun Bullet’s stun didn’t last long. Shortly after, he began running again.

“Bang!” Another gun sound, even closer this time. There was even less time to react. Wind Following Sword was launched into the air by the bullet.

“Floating Bullet…….” Wind Following Sword muttered in his head.

Chapter 273 – A Measure of an Expert’s Skill

No matter how badly Wind Following Sword wanted to escape after being launched into the air, it wasn’t going to happen. All he heard was a bang and the blast which lifted up the rainwater and looked as if it would splash him from inside screen onto his face.

Wind Following Sword was sent flying away. He adjusted his camera and prepared to Quick Recover in order to land safely. But right when he turned his camera, he discovered that there was a monster in the direction he was flying towards.

Wind Following Sword was brimming with joy. If he hit that monster, it would count as Lord Grim’s attack. The monster would then naturally go and return the blow. And as a result, his would have a higher chance of escaping! The heavens had truly blessed him today.

Wind Following Sword continued to dream and then, in the blink of an eye, his character reached the monster.

But……. but when his body flitted across, the two didn’t bump into each other. They were off by just an inch.

“F*ck!” Wind Following Sword fell into despair. He immediately prepared to Quick Recover. His character rolled onto the ground and when he got up, he saw a cold glint flash across his eyes.

So quick! Wind Following Sword was startled! But in the next second, he saw the situation clearly. The incoming attacker wasn’t Lord Grim, but rather, it was that monster.

Wind Following Sword stared blankly. At this moment, he wanted to cry, but no tears came out.

When he flew by, he hadn’t hit the monster, but instead, he had landed in the monster’s aggro range, which was why the Sin City resident had locked onto him.

Wind Following Sword immediately rolled again in order to dodge the attack.

With his skill, dealing with a single monster was very easy. However, the bigger problem was, what was Lord Grim going to do next? Wind Following Sword turned his camera to look. Sure enough, Lord Grim was dashing towards him. His dream, where the monster would aggro onto Lord Grim and let him escape, didn’t happen. On the contrary, the monster had aggroed onto him and had given Lord Grim a chance to kill him.

Wind Following Sword was in an even more panicked state now. He saw Lord Grim lift up his weapon and shoot. If the bullet was another weird Spitfire bullet, then if he was hit, the damage he would take as a result of the status effect wouldn’t be good for him. Wind Following Sword had to avoid it. Panicked, he sidestepped in a random direction in order to dodge the shot and then he heard a “he he” chuckle from behind him.

Wind Following Sword immediately turned around to look. A figure that had originally been crouching at the corner stood up and headed towards him.

Wind Following Sword wanted to cough up blood. He hadn’t been very careful when he dodged the bullet and, as a result, he had unexpectedly stepped into the aggro range of another monster and aggroed it as well.

Wind Following Sword hastily tried to get out of its range, but after only taking a few steps, he heard footsteps closing in. His hesitation had allowed Lord Grim to close in.

He couldn’t beat him one on one, but he had to do something to delay him. Wind Following Sword grinded his teeth. He turned around and sent out a Sword Draw!

“F*ck me!!!” Wind Following Sword cursed.

Behind him, Lord Grim jumped up into the air. The Sword Draw swept under his feet, missing him. But behind Lord Grim were another two monsters and those two monsters were hit.

The two monsters had originally been aggroed onto Lord Grim. But after being hit by the Sword Draw, their attention turned to Wind Following Sword. They brandished their blades and pounced on him.

Four!

Now that things had escalated to this, how could Wind Following Sword not know what was going on? Accidentally stepping into a monster’s aggro range and Lord Grim bringing two monsters behind him wasn’t just a coincidence. This was pure revenge. Lord Grim was using the method he had used previously to play around with Soft Mist back at him. However, Lord Grim’s method was superior. Being able to blow him away into the aggro range was a reflection of his skill.

Sweat could be seen on Wind Following Sword’s head. He could still deal with four monsters, but Lord Grim? He looked at him and discovered that Lord Grim wasn’t in a rush to attack him.

Does he want to attract even more monsters? Wind Following Sword immediately thought this and began paying more attention to his surroundings. This was originally a leveling area, so there were monsters every few steps. Wind Following Sword looked around and saw that any one of them could turn into his enemy at any time.

Careful. Careful!

Wind Following Sword observed his surroundings and observed Lord Grim’s movements. But Lord Grim didn’t seem to have too much interest in any of these monsters. He didn’t actively aggro them. For a moment, Wind Following Sword wasn’t sure what the opponent was thinking. What was Ye Qiu thinking?

Wind Following Sword looked at the end of the street. His friends were rushing over to his rescue. Truthfully, Wind Following Sword didn’t believe they could beat Ye Qiu, but he did believe that, with more people, things would become more chaotic and his chances of escaping would be greater as a result.

Just as he thought this, he suddenly saw a figure on the rooftop move. The Spitfire who had been knocked down by Su Mucheng previously had finally climbed back up. He looked over the street’s circumstances and immediately headed towards Wind Following Sword in order to help him.

He held a grenade in his hands and after taking a few steps forward, he quietly threw it behind Lord Grim.

Wind Following Sword’s heart was about to leap up to his throat. If the grenade hit, then he’d have some hope in escaping!

The grenade arced down. As long as it hit the ground, it would explode. But who would have thought that, at this moment, Lord Grim would suddenly turn around and draw his sword simultaneously. The grenade that had been thrown downward was sliced by the sword light and immediately exploded.

Wind Following Sword felt that it was a pity. Soon after, he saw the sword being sheathed. Lord Grim changed his weapon once again and flames spouted out of his gun.

The Spitfire on the rooftop was still changing his ammunition in order to get ready for his next attack. By the time Wind Following Sword warned him, it was already too late. Lord Grim had fired Anti-Tank Missiles at him. The Spitfire didn’t have time to dodge and the explosion blasted him onto the streets once more.

Wind Following Sword looked on, dumbstruck. He still knew what was what. Everything that had happened in that instant showed Lord Grim’s incredible skill.

The number of players who could hit a grenade in mid-air wasn’t high. And the Anti-Tank Missiles had used the grenade’s light and noise as a cover. This was why Wind Following Sword was able to understand what had happened, while that Spitfire had no idea what had happened. For that Spitfire, Lord Grim’s shots had been completely covered up by the grenade’s explosion. By the time he saw the missiles, it was already too late to dodge.

Using such a small detail wasn’t easy.

It meant that he completely grasped the opponent’s position, the opponent’s field of view, the effects of the grenade’s explosion, and his extremely quick hands ensures that he could complete his attack at the moment of explosion.

Wind Following Sword once again decided to turn tail and run. The more experienced you were, the better you would understand how terrifying this was. Wind Following Sword understood this. He no longer desired to try and block Lord Grim. Whether he could escape now depended on his luck!

Wind Following Sword didn’t even look back when he ran. Run. Run forward. He didn’t care what was happening behind him. He didn’t want to know how far away Lord Grim was from him or whether or not he had aggroed more monsters. The only thought in his mind was to run and to continue running.

Gun sound!

Wind Following Sword didn’t look back. He only shifted his direction slightly. Whether he could dodge or not depended on his luck!

Another shot!

Wind Following Sword twisted his body, but he still didn’t turn his head.

Gun sounds continued to ring. Wind Following Sword continued to zigzag. His health hadn’t gone down and he hadn’t been hit. Wind Following Sword’s hopes were once again reignited. Could he have somehow awakened his true potential in a moment of crisis? Was his potential so great that he could dodge like this?

Bang bang bang bang!

Amidst these gun sounds, Wind Following Sword’s health still hadn’t gone down. He felt as if he was sliding over the water.

So graceful! Wind Following Sword complimented himself. Soon after, from another point of view, he saw that something didn’t seem quite right.

It didn’t matter. All he had to do was keep running! Wind Following Sword didn’t want to waste any time. Another gun sounded and, from the corner of his eyes, he saw a flame.

A figure appeared in Wind Following Sword’s field of view. It was Lord Grim, who was currently flying backwards along the road. This was because he was using Aerial Fire.

Wind Following Sword cried.

Lord Grim had been using Aerial Fire the entire time to catch up to him. He had been twisting around as well because of the noise. That had probably made him look as if he had gone crazy, right?

“Your twisting looked pretty good.” Wind Following Sword quickly heard him praise.

Wind Following Sword stared at Lord Grim. He was ready to fight. It didn’t matter who his opponent was. No matter how terrifying Lord Grim was, he didn’t plan on just letting himself die. He wouldn’t go down without a fight.

Bang! Another stream of bullets.

It had already become a reflex. When he heard the sound of bullets being fired, he couldn’t help but twist…..

But these bullets weren’t directed at him.

“It seems like you’ve gotten addicted.” The other side laughed. Wind Following Sword felt embarrassed. He used a Sword Draw and finally acted against Lord Grim. And so what? Even if he died, it was only a 10% experience loss. He could get that back in a day.

“Fight!” Wind Following Sword shouted.

His slash gently flitted past Lord Grim. “You even messed up who your opponent is. How sad.” Ye Xiu said.

Wind Following Sword was startled. He had been too absorbed in listening to the gun sounds. He now noticed that he could hear footsteps quickly closing in…….

“This is?” Wind Following Sword immediately turned around.

A scarlet light flashed in front of his eyes and he saw an ID on top of the opponent’s head: Soft Mist.

Chapter 274 – Fight to the End

Tang Rou and Su Mucheng combined their efforts and brought the dozen high-leveled residents and the Christmas thief to their end. In the process of doing so, using the highest stage of Battle Spirit, Soft Mist did the majority of the damage.

After clearing away the monsters, Tang Rou had Soft Mist chase after Wind Following Sword.

She was again in the seventh stage of Battle Spirit. The combination of the Neutral Chaser’s movement speed buff and Wind Following Sword’s twisting and turning caused Soft Mist to quickly catch up.

Wind Following Sword had thought that Ye Qiu’s Lord Grim was his opponent, but instead, Lord Grim had gifted him with four monsters to play with. At this moment, the player who was going to embarrass him was the player that he had originally played around with, Tang Rou.

A scarlet light flashed in front of his eyes! By the time that Wind Following Sword saw it, it was already too late to dodge.

The Scarlet Moon Lance slashed upwards with a Sky Strike. Wind Following Sword was launched into the air. His body was still in the motion of turning his head.

The lance quickly returned, but came back with an even greater force. The lance pierced his stomach, lifted Wind Following Sword, and threw him onto the ground.

The direction of the swing had been calculated. Tang Rou learned from her mistakes. She executed a Circle Swing perfectly and the shockwave hadn’t aggroed any of the monsters chasing after Wind Following Sword.

As soon as Wind Following Sword was thrown to the ground, those four residents took the opportunity to pounce on him. They surrounded and stabbed him while Wind Following Sword was on the ground. In game speak: this was a true sweeping attack.

Wind Following Sword looked as if he was food for hungry wolves. In an instant, the residents surrounded him. Only his head could be seen and he looked powerless.

Wind Following Sword struggled to swing his sword. He slashed at a monster and then rolled away and got up. During that short moment, his health had already dropped to half from the four monsters’ bullying. But before he could relax, Soft Mist’s lance arrived in front of him. This time, Wind Following Sword was prepared and jumped back to dodge. But how could Tang Rou give up? She quickly followed up with another attack.

Wind Following Sword watched as his health was extorted. There was no way he could beat her and nowhere to run either. His camera turned left and right and then looked up towards the heavens, praying for some flying immortal to save him.

In the end, all he heard was a bang. Wind Following Sword’s camera turned and saw someone on the rooftop. However, that someone wasn’t his friend, but Cleansing Mist.

His Spitfire friend had been blown back onto the streets, but he didn’t give up and Aerial Fired his way back up to the rooftop. However, his attempt this time was even more of a failure than the previous two times. As soon as he landed, he saw a black barrel directly in front of his face and was directly blasted away. He was hit by consecutive explosions. Unable to even stand up straight, he was once again sent back down to the streets. And, this time, Su Mucheng no longer paid attention to anything else, concentrating on killing him.

Meanwhile, on Ye Xiu’s side, his Lord Grim had moved up and blocked the players, who were coming to support their struggling friend.

These players were obviously from Excellent Dynasty as well and knew of Lord Grim’s strength. But they didn’t know that he was Ye Qiu. If they had, then they definitely wouldn’t have come to kill themselves.

How large was the difference between normal players and pro players? It was hard to answer because every player was at a different skill level. But during events hosted by a team, the pro players would sometimes give a performance. They would invite normal players to fight against them. One pro player would fight against several normal players and the results of these exhibition matches didn’t need to be said.

However, these five Excellent Dynasty players didn’t know that they were up against a top-tier God. They only knew that Lord Grim was good, but there was no way they could have predicted that. The difference in their skill levels wasn’t something that they could make up for by being careful and cautious.

In this battle, Ye Xiu was up against five, but he took the initiative to attack. Lord Grim sprinted forward and easily dissolved the long-ranged characters’ attacks. The speed at which he closed in was out of their expectations. The melee players hastily attacked, but Lord Grim had already sent out a Sword Draw.

The sword aura swept over. To jump over the Sword Draw like Ye Xiu did required quick hands and fast eyes. It wasn’t something that just anyone could do. For normal players, the most common method of avoiding this attack was to move backwards.

To think of jumping backwards to dodge this attack meant that their reactions weren’t too slow, but Ye Xiu had already predicted what they would do. His attack had been placed just right. The jumping backwards method was just a bit worse than Ye Xiu’s. Most people wouldn’t be able to see the distance of the attack extremely accurately. The players thought that they had dodged it, but in the end, they were hit. The sword aura swept at them and looked as if it had jumped a bit farther than usual.

Since they were in Sin City, they definitely weren’t bad players. After being blown away, their Quick Recoveries had been completed beautifully.

But in the next second, they saw a blue light surround their bodies. The blue light rose up into the air as well as their bodies.

Rising Emblem!

By the time they realized it, they searched for Lord Grim, who wasn’t moving. It was clearly a Shadow Clone, but where was the real body?

The real body was obviously below them. Lord Grim held his weapon and fired twice, sending one of the players away. Following after, the weapon changed to a battle lance. He raised it up and stabbed forward, sending another one flying away. He then turned around and raised his palm. A deafening noise followed, blowing away another. The battle lance then returned back into the gun form. Bang, bang, bang. Three shots pushed another one away.

During the time that they were launched into the air by the Rising Emblem, the originally clustered allies were suddenly split apart into different directions. The sole remaining member landed at his original position. This member was a long-ranged class and was quickly beaten up by Lord Grim.

As for those other four members, they experienced what Wind Following Sprit experienced. Next to them were Sin City residents, who quickly attacked them. Each of them now had another partner.

At this moment, should they get rid of their new partners? Or should they quickly rescue their long-ranged friend? Or should they continue trying to rescue the almost-dead Wind Following Sword?

They didn’t have to think about it for too long because Tang Rou quickly helped them eliminate one of their options.

Truthfully, if Wind Following Sword was in a true 1v1, with his experience and skill, he might not lose to Tang Rou.

Unfortunately, he just had to play around. Now that Ye Xiu had taken revenge, he had to worry about the aggroed monsters. As for Tang Rou, she was at the seventh stage of Battle Spirit. Her attacks were faster and stronger. There was no way that he could 1v1 her, let alone her with four helpers.

“Fight!” Wind Following Sword thought.

He had already made the decision before, but he had mixed up his opponent. This time he decided again, but his energy had already withered away. He did fight, but as expected, he died fighting.

With Wind Following Sword’s death, the five players who had come no longer had a purpose. They had quickly charged forward to save the friend whom Lord Grim was beating up and now wanted to run away. But how could it be so easy? Leaving was going to be even harder.

Tang Rou had cleaned up Wind Following Sword and Su Mucheng had killed off that Spitfire as well. Now it was a 3v5 fight, something that the five players didn’t notice.

In a short moment, the first player on the other side fell. Quickly, the second and third players followed……

Wind Following Sword had died and none of the friends he had called for help had survived either. Amidst the rain, Soft Mist stood up valiantly like before. She was the last to stay standing because she had two friends beside her.

“Amazing. Amazing!!” Chen Guo commented. She had watched the entire course of action. Not just the culprit, but his other helpers were also all killed. And the entire process had been a steam roll! It really made her feel good.

Chen Guo was extremely happy. She only regretted that their allied Launcher wasn’t her. She was already looking forward to playing with Ye Xiu and Tang Rou.

And these two? These two must be happy after such a beautiful battle, right?

Chen Guo looked to the right and all she saw was Ye Xiu as calm as ever. No, it looked like he was bored. The guy didn’t look energetic at all and the way he looked sitting there made her angry.

“It’s all good now. You can continue questing!” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay!!” Tang Rou replied.

That’s it? Just like that???

Chen Guo didn’t want to believe it. A great fight had just ended. They didn’t even talk about it for a bit. They were just going to quietly move on and continue questing? If this had been her, such an intense battle, where she had finally won in the end, was something that she could talk about with her friends for an entire week.

Chapter 275 – There Must Not Be Losses on the Leaderboard

Wind Following Sword revived in Congee City.

None of his equipment had dropped, but the 10% experience drop was enough to make his heart ache. But what made him even sadder was the turning point mid-battle. He had originally thought that taking the Christmas thief was absolutely safe. How could he know that so many side issues would pop up? In the end, not only did he die, but his friends who had come to save him had also all died.

Not long after Wind Following Sword died, he saw his friends come one after the other. They all revived next to him. The characters stood there stupidly and not a word was said.

Go back and take revenge?

With just them, Wind Following Sword didn’t dare try. After all, he knew that Lord Grim was Ye Qiu and obviously knew that Cleansing Mist was Su Mucheng as well. In addition, that Soft Mist was also strong too.

There was no use trying with just them. The only way was to rely on many and the only way to do that was to rely on the guild. But right now, the entire guild was working on the Christmas quests. Wind Following Sword had only done the kill stealing on a whim. He hadn’t talked about it with Chen Yehui. Chen Yehui also never told them what to do if they encountered Ye Qiu and his comrades.

In the end, Wind Following Sword acted for himself and left dejected and depressed. He didn’t even know how he would report it to Chen Yehui yet.

And the players next to him weren’t his close friends, either. They were simply a part of the hunting group. At that time, they were nearby and had been called over by Wind Following Sword to their deaths.

“Lord Grim really is incredible!” someone finally said.

“He is.” Wind Following Sword parroted. Exaggerating Lord Grim’s strength could ease their thoughts!

“If we knew earlier, then we should have called more people over.” another said.

“He wasn’t there in the beginning!” Wind Following Sword hastily excused himself. But he wasn’t wrong. When he called them over, Lord Grim wasn’t there yet.

“What do we do now?”

“Call for more brothers!” One of them clearly wasn’t happy and wanted revenge.

Wind Following Sword was also thinking about this issue. Just as he was about to answer, a new message came. Wind Following Sword opened it and saw that it was Chen Yehui: “What happened?”

“You know about it already?” Wind Following Sword felt awkward. Power leveling in the new server was extremely important. The team’s deaths had caused them to lose experience and morale, which was completely against what they were going for.

“It’s being talked about in the chat!” Chen Yehui replied.

“Oh, no!” Wind Following Sword immediately checked the guild chat. The bros next to him were all talking about it angrily! No wonder none of them had been talking when they had revived. They had been chatting in the guild’s chat room.

“I encountered Soft Mist……” Seeing that the guild leader already knew, Wind Following Sword could only explain. He stressed that at that time, he felt like he had it 100%, which was why he had acted out. He didn’t think that Soft Mist would be so tenacious and hold out for so long. When he had discovered that he was in trouble, he then called people over. But the other side had also called for help and then they all got wiped out.

“How could you guys be their opponents?” Chen Yehui said.

“Yeah……” Wind Following Sword felt gloomy.

“Ye Qiu! He really is bringing trouble to us wherever he goes!” Chen Yehui said.

“Yeah, yeah!” Wind Following Sword added, while still being gloomy. Trouble? It was more like he was the one who had caused trouble and then their opponents had taken revenge, right?

“Did you look at the Christmas Hunting Leaderboards?” Chen Yehui asked.

“I saw it. We’re way ahead.” Wind Following Sword said.

“I’m talking about the individual one, Level 31-35.”

“Oh?” Wind Following Sword immediately went to check. The first page showed the first twenty places, with the rankings making Wind Following Sword feel pleased. Of the first twenty places, their Excellent Dynasty held the first 15, with him at ninth place.

Wind Following Sword obviously knew the reason they were able to hold the first 15 places. This was something they had created. For example, for Wind Following Sword’s party, the other party members would gather all of their Christmas thieves to him. As a result, this let him easily take a high placing. As for the other fourteen players on the leaderboards, they were all the same.

This time, Excellent Dynasty’s advantage in manpower was finally showing. The other guilds also had their first-string players come to Sin City, but they didn’t have nearly as many players as Excellent Dynasty did.

The current Excellent Dynasty was quite weak in the Heavenly Domain though, because many of their experts went to the tenth server.

In the Heavenly Domain, the competition there was in a deadlock. There was no way of breaking it in a short amount of time. Chen Yehui had put everything at stake and invested heavily into the tenth server. They had to be in a leading position.

Currently, things weren’t going too well. Even though they took down Frost Forest, Liu Hao stopped helping them and the later top dungeon records had come under the monopoly of Lord Grim. However, Chen Yehui had learned from this. Now whenever they moved out, they would always weigh the pros and cons first and wouldn’t act out on impulse.

“Check the eleventh page.” Chen Yehui messaged Wind Following Sword.

Wind Following Sword checked and immediately understood what the guild leader wanted him to see.

Lord Grim, 218th place.

“This guy’s rising so quickly!”

“Correct. He wasn’t even on the leaderboards an hour ago. But now, he’s already risen to the 218th place. Even though the difference in points is still very large between him and us, I’ve calculated it and, at his speed, after three hours, he’ll have entered our ranks. And you know who Cleansing Mist, the one on the fourteenth page, is, right? She’ll also rise up, sooner or later. But for her, she probably won’t have the time to maintain her record, so we don’t have to worry too much about that. However, it’s hard to say about that guy.” Chen Yehui replied.

“But…… even if they rise up, we still have the majority!” Wind Following Sword said.

“Do you still not understand? As long as he rises up, the public will be entirely focused on him. No one would care about how outstanding our achievements are. All they would pay attention to is the fact that Lord Grim has once again stepped all over us again. You look at any dungeon record from any other server. Can you say that the second place record is bad? But what about in the tenth server? All of the records he tramples over are all terrible compared to his! The entire guild immediately looks like trash. Has this ever happened in any other server? He’s the entire reason for this unhealthy trend.”

“So you’re saying……” Wind Following Sword was starting to understand Chen Yehui’s intent.

“That’s why we definitely can’t let him climb up the ladder. We can’t let this little rat spoil our porridge.” Chen Yehui’s message seemed to have sound and color to it.

Wind Following Sword saw Chen Yehui’s determination. He was someone very close to Chen Yehui in the guild and understood the relationship between Chen Yehui and Ye Qiu. This time, Chen Yehui had thought the plan through, but were there some personal reasons mixed in? Wind Following Sword didn’t ask. Perhaps this was for the better. The guild’s and his own personal interests were in alignment.

“What do you think we should do?” Wind Following Sword asked.

“I’ll give you some players. You deal with it. That doesn’t necessarily mean that you have to fight him. As long as you delay him, that’s enough. You think of a method!” Chen Yehui handed the task to Wind Following Sword. Wind Following Sword’s craftiness was famous in the Heavenly Domain. Against Ye Qiu, fighting him with brute force clearly wouldn’t work. It would require lots of effort and time.. and it might even end up biting them back. But through more secretive methods, letting Lord Grim silently suffer a bit would be better. Wind Following Sword was undoubtedly the most suitable choice. Even if he was the one to personally move out, he might not be as cunning as Wind Following Sword.

“Alright. I’ll do it!” Wind Following Sword wanted to take some revenge, too. He was quite confident in himself here. Ye Qiu was undoubtedly a top-tier God, but his many years of playing had been aimed towards the way professionals played against each other. In the game, things weren’t as simple as just winning and losing matches. Wind Following Sword decided that he would have this God taste the wisdom and tricks of an in-game player.

As he thought, Wind Following Sword checked the Christmas Hunting Leaderboards.

Terrible! They had only talked for a bit and Lord Grim had already risen. He had been at 218th place before. Now he was at 211th.

There was no time to delay! He had to hurry up and start moving.

Wind Following Sword went on his way towards Sin City, while contacting the helpers Chen Yehui had given to him.

Chapter 276 – The Web’s Lord Grim

Sin City. Thunder and lightning continued to flash in the sky from time to time as the rain continued to pour down.

Lord Grim and Soft Mist were split up in the city. Both of them were searching for Christmas thieves. Ye Xiu and Tang Rou quietly tapped their keyboards and clicked their mice. Apart from their typing, there was no other sound.

Chen Guo was sitting between these two. She was running around with her Chasing Haze in the Heavenly Domain. She was running and running…….

Plunk!

Chasing Haze fell into a hole.

“F*ck!” Chen Guo immediately had Chasing Haze jump out of the hole. She wasn’t able to focus. In the previous PK, she had been the most excited one there, even though she was a spectator.

Helpless, Chen Guo drank a sip of water and continued to run around aimlessly without a destination. Four Christmas thieves… this was her progress up until now. In the previous hour, she had killed three of them. But during this hour, she hadn’t made much progress. Because she was watching the two of them play, she was still a bit distracted. Whenever she found one, another player would always snatch it first.

When someone else got to it first, Chen Guo would always quietly walk away. But this didn’t mean that such situations were always peacefully resolved. Killing another player and stealing the monster was a common tactic that was taking place all over.

The Heavenly Domain was truly a survival of the fittest world. Danger could come from anywhere. Since there wasn’t any penalty for PKing here and the experience as well as the item drops were larger, killing other players for their items was a common occurrence.

Perhaps not everyone liked the Heavenly Domain’s atmosphere, but the Heavenly Domain wasn’t a place that players were forced to go to. The players had a choice. However, the Heavenly Domain had better equipment, better materials, stronger BOSSes, and harder dungeons, which were enough incentives to make players constantly enter. If that enticement wasn’t strong enough, most would probably stay in the normal servers to play.

Chen Guo had once been attacked and had her equipment drop. She had been so angry that she had stopped playing for a whole week and had even wanted to go back to the old server. But not long after, she had climbed back onto the Heavenly Domain. This place had this type of magic to it.

But currently, Chen Guo didn’t feel good about the Heavenly Domain at all. She rigidly pressed forward. Her hands were almost numb. As for the two players beside her? Both of them were clicking and tapping furiously. She didn’t even need to look to know that they were constantly busy. In the new server, in Sin City, there were too many monsters and not enough players. They never needed to walk far to see a Christmas thief. As a comparison, how could she like playing on the Heavenly Domain?

Running and running……. she just couldn’t snatch any Christmas thieves for herself. Chen Guo would sometimes measure herself against the two of them on her left and right. Gradually, she discovered that Ye Xiu had quieted down, too.

He was just like her. He seemed to only press forward and turn left and right stupidly.

Chen Guo once again switched her attention to Ye Xiu’s screen instead of hers.

Lord Grim went through the street into an alley, looking everywhere. There seemed to be fewer Christmas thieves now. Or perhaps.. were there were more players now?

Wherever Lord Grim went, either the Christmas thieves had already been killed or there were already players fighting them.

Ye Xiu obviously didn’t go and kill others to steal their monsters like Wind Following Sword did. All he could do was turn around and keep looking. But it always seemed to be this way.

Chen Guo watched for half an hour. He had only killed 2 Christmas thieves in that time.

In an advantageous place like Sin City, where Ye Xiu had previously killed 14 in an hour, killing 2 in half an hour was too strange. This could be seen from the leaderboards. During the half hour, Lord Grim’s name continued to fall.

“The system probably changed because you guys were too savage, no?” Chen Guo suddenly said.

Ye Xiu turned his head and looked at her. He lightly shook his head and said: “Something’s not right.”

“What’s not right?” Chen Guo asked.

Ye Xiu didn’t answer. He continued to patiently have Lord Grim look around.

Chen Guo obviously knew that the system couldn’t have changed. Tang Rou was still busy fighting. It couldn’t be that the change was only directed at Lord Grim, so that it would only change wherever he moved, right?

Chen Guo continued to watch.

Another half an hour passed. It was even worse this time. He had only killed one. Three Christmas thieves in one hour was Ye Xiu’s achievement.

Chen Guo didn’t take the chance to take delight in his misfortunes. She also felt that something wasn’t right either.

“I’ve been surrounded.” Ye Xiu said in response to Chen Guo’s doubtful gaze.

“Surrounded?”

“Yeah, there’s always people nearby.” Ye Xiu pointed to a place not far away to a character who was killing a Christmas thief. “They’ve set up a net around me, moving along with me. They’ll have gone to all the nearby areas ahead of time. If there are Christmas thieves, then they’ll either lead them away or kill them. That’s why I rarely find any I can kill.”

“Is that even possible?” Chen Guo stared blankly.

“There’s quite a lot of them. I just counted. There’s 24 total.”

Chen Guo now understood that Ye Xiu hadn’t been blindly searching, hoping for some luck. After figuring out that something wasn’t right, his movements about were to examine the situation. Through this half an hour of examining, he was able to come to a conclusion.

“Kill him!” Chen Guo said.

“That evil?” Ye Xiu laughed.

“If they don’t hurt me, then I won’t hurt them.” Chen Guo told him her reasoning.

“Then should I go and try?” Ye Xiu asked for her opinion.

“Go!” Chen Guo said as if she was in charge.

As a result, Lord Grim rushed forward. But before he could even get anywhere close, the player turned tail and ran. The Christmas thief obviously followed behind the player. No matter how good of a player Ye Xiu was, it would be very difficult for him to catch and kill it.

Chen Guo watched, dumbstruck.

“They’ve prepared well!” Ye Xiu sighed. He checked the Christmas Hunting Leaderboards and saw that his rank had gone down by a lot.

Ye Xiu checked the first page of the leaderboards.

“Woah, Excellent Dynasty is so mighty!” Chen Guo blurted out. The first fifteen places were held by Excellent Dynasty.

Ye Xiu smiled, but didn’t say anything. A fan of Excellent Era would obviously be a fan of the in-game Excellent Dynasty.

But Chen Guo understood.

This type of painstaking work trying to make sure Ye Xiu didn’t kill any Christmas thieves was clearly because of the competition between the two sides. The competition was for the ranking positions on the leaderboards.

And the only people who had that type of power was undoubtedly in a guild. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim didn’t have a guild, so he was on the individual leaderboards. A guild still needed to suppress an individual? When Chen Guo saw the first fifteen places, Chen Guo began to understand.

Lord Grim’s name was rising up rapidly. He might soon knock one of them down, but the other fourteen would still be there. Did they have to maintain all fifteen places?

Chen Guo couldn’t understand this point because she didn’t know the details of the tenth server. Chen Yehui’s worries weren’t groundless, however. If Lord Grim really did step all over the leaderboards, then it was very possible that Excellent Dynasty’s placings would immediately turn into nothing. When that time came, who knew what those stupid noobs would say?

Blue Brook Guild and Tyrannical Ambition had encountered it. Which guild wasn’t afraid of that happening? Chen Yehui hadn’t personally run over to the tenth server in order to witness a tragedy.

“Are these players from Excellent Dynasty?” Chen Guo was somewhat unsure.

“Seems like it.” Ye Xiu said.

“What type of enmity do you guys have with each other?” Chen Guo didn’t understand the tenth server’s situation, so she could only think that Ye Xiu had some sort of quarrel with them.

“It’s a long story.”

“Then what are you going to do now?” Chen Guo asked.

“Hm, let me think.” Ye Xiu said.

“Not bad!” Meanwhile, Chen Yehui was also paying attention to the leaderboards. Lord Grim’s ranking was falling and he knew that it was the result of his actions. Seeing that the effects were still going on after an hour, Chen Yehui happily sent Wind Following Sword a reward.

“Ha ha, it’s nothing.” Wind Following Sword said modestly, though he was secretly extremely delighted.

“How is he reacting?” Chen Yehui asked.

“After running around blindly for an hour, he seems to have just figured out that something isn’t right.” Wind Following Sword was already looking down on Ye Qiu’s intelligence.

“Then he’s probably going to move out soon. Be careful.”

“Okay. I’ll be waiting. One of Glory’s four famous Master Tacticians. Actually, I’ve always wanted to test myself against them. I want to see for myself just how godly their tactics are.” The clear achievements after an hour had put Wind Following Sword in high spirits.

Chapter 277 – Spinning Spiderweb Formation

“Have you thought of a solution? Have you thought of a solution?” Chen Guo was even more anxious than Ye Xiu was.

“I’ve thought of a very dependable method, but I need someone who’s brave and smart enough for it.” Ye Xiu said.

“What’s the method?” Chen Guo asked.

“Go to Club Excellent Era across the street and cut the lines. What do you think? Can you do it?”

“F*ck off!” Chen Guo wasn’t happy. He was clearly having fun with her.

“Ha ha.” Ye Xiu laughed, but his hands had already begun moving.

As Lord Grim began to move again, he went into the alleys and ran around.

Chen Guo didn’t understand his intent. He seemed to be doing the same thing as he had been doing in the previous hour. He was just running around stupidly. Just as she was going to say something, Ye Xiu suddenly pointed his hands at her screen: “Thief.”

“Ah?” Chen Guo immediately turned around and looked. Sure enough, there was a Christmas thief where Ye Xiu was pointing at. Without hesitating, she had Chasing Haze lift up her cannon and accurately fired at it. Chen Guo cheered and continued to fire, but still looked at Ye Xiu’s screen from time to time. She wanted to know what the situation was like.

“Go and fight your thief. I’m going to be running around like this for awhile!” Ye Xiu said.

“Running around and doing what?” Chen Guo asked.

“Observing their formation.”

“Oh……” Chen Guo actually wanted to keep asking, but she discovered that that previously lazy guy had disappeared. Right now, Ye Xiu was extremely focused. His eyes spun and spun, chasing after his extremely quick-moving character. He was clearly researching something seriously. Chen Guo decided not to say anything. She wouldn’t bother him and went on to focus on her Christmas thief.

Ye Xiu never stopped moving.

Lord Grim looked around in a small circle. The situation was still the same. The Christmas thieves that could be found had already been snatched away.

After winding past three streets, Lord Grim suddenly jumped up. He raised his weapon and used an Aerial Fire, jumping to the rooftop. After this, he jumped off with another Aerial Fire, and headed directly towards the other side of the street.

He had never done this before. When Wind Following Sword received the report, he didn’t think much of it: “That’s it? His thinking is too simple!”

“What are his coordinates?” Wind Following Sword followed.

The member had been prepared and sent him Lord Grim’s coordinates.

“This……” Wind Following Sword saw the coordinates and was immediately startled. Originally, after receiving Lord Grim’s coordinates, he would set up adjustments for their formation. But this set of coordinates was too familiar to him. This was because this set of coordinates was very similar to the set of coordinates he had just been at.

Lord Grim is nearby!

When Wind Following Sword became aware of this, his character immediately began to move. He turned around and sprinted towards the street. At the same time, he lifted his camera and checked the rooftops.

Sure enough! Wind Following Sword really did find Lord Grim. He was standing on the rooftop, looking down at him.

How could Wind Following Sword dare delay? He immediately used a Triple Slash to run. He was the same as his other team members. As soon as they saw Lord Grim, they wouldn’t wait until he got close to them! This was Wind Following Sword’s orders.

No one posed a chance at facing Ye Qiu one on one. Having thoughts of fighting would only hold them back. After all, their guild’s main mission was still to fight Christmas thieves.

“Is he chasing? Is he chasing?” Wind Following Sword didn’t want to turn his head. He was afraid that turning his head would affect his movements. He listened closely. He didn’t hear any footsteps or gun sounds. After a while, Wind Following Sword finally turned around to take a look.

He hadn’t. There was no sign of Lord Grim. There was just an empty field.

Wind Following Sword let out a sigh.

As for his previous position? Wind Following Sword recalled it and then quickly sent orders to the other team members.

Not long after, another teammate reported back, sending him Lord Grim’s new coordinates. Wind Following Sword looked and saw that he was still in their formation’s range. He couldn’t help but laugh coldly. Running around on the rooftops truly made things a bit more difficult, but was that it? “Ye Qiu isn’t anything much!” Wind Following Sword said to himself.

Just as he closed the message, he glanced at his own coordinates.

Huh! Why did it look familiar? These coordinates……. were very close to the ones that the team member had reported for Lord Grim.

Wind Following Sword was startled again. He immediately wanted to run, but a figure suddenly landed in front of him. If that wasn’t Lord Grim, then who else could it be?

“So you know who I am!” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Ye Qiu!” Wind Following Sword called out the name. He was feeling a bit panicked. Since they were a bit too close to each other, it was very possible that he wouldn’t be able to get away. But luckily, the formation wouldn’t fall apart with just one death. Even if he died, the formation would still continue on.

Thinking of this, Wind Following Sword calmed down and laughed: “So you’ve actually caught up. But so what? I can’t 1v1 you, so I’ll die. But I’m sure you’ve already figured it out, right? Our goal isn’t to PK with you.”

“Ha ha, it’s just a Spinning Spiderweb Formation.”

“Oh, you really deserve to be called God Ye. You know your stuff.” Wind Following Sword’s voice contained a bit of mocking in it. So what if he knew what it was? Wasn’t he still helpless in front of it? Wind Following Sword was delighted.

“But you don’t. Did you know that I was the one who created the Spinning Spiderweb Formation?” Ye Xiu was still smiling.

“What did you say?” Wind Following Sword was startled.

“Do you have a map with you? When you go back to the city, clean up your teammates’ positions!” Ye Xiu said and then had Lord Grim dash forward.

Wind Following Sword brandished his sword in defense. However, he had been too startled by Ye Xiu’s words. His thoughts were no longer on the battle. When Wind Following Sword fell, he still hadn’t figured out what had happened. He immediately decided to revive and have his teammates report their positions.

Ye Qiu had created the Spinning Spiderweb Formation?

Wind Following Sword didn’t know that. He had accidentally discovered it while browsing around on the internet. It looked interesting, so he had studied it for a bit. He had also used it quite a few times over the years. If not, then he wouldn’t have been so familiar with it.

He really couldn’t remember who the authors of the materials he had gathered were. Maybe Ye Qiu was one of them. If Ye Qiu was, he wouldn’t be surprised! These types of Gods, who had been playing since the start of the game, had written many guides. Wind Following Sword really hadn’t paid attention to who had created the Spinning Spiderweb Formation.

Wind Following Sword couldn’t deal with all of this. After receiving everyone’s positions, he immediately found an online map outside of the game’s window.

The online map he had found was quite detailed. His mouse showed the coordinates. Wind Following Sword lit up everyone’s coordinates and, not long after, the formation was clearly shown. Lord Grim’s position had still been within the formation’s area of control. There weren’t any problems with it!

Was it just a bluff?

Wind Following Sword thought as he continued to direct everyone. He had everyone head towards his previous location and revise their position. Not long after, the team members reported back with Lord Grim’s new coordinates. Wind Following Sword no longer controlled his character and now focused only on sending messages and directing their movements.

The online map had many functions. Right now, Wind Following Sword felt like he was playing a strategy game.

“Ye Qiu, I want to see how you’ll escape.”

Wind Following Sword began to slowly recover from the previous scare. The corners of his mouth pricked up and he began laughing coldly again.

“Heart Needle, head east two blocks. Watch the right street.”

“Minar, go up to the roof on your left.”

“Sand, go back to that crossing behind you.”

Wind Following Sword casually directed them. The more he played, the happier he became. He felt like he was playing with the opponent. And this opponent was a top-tier God in Glory. That type of feeling was truly unprecedented!

More messages came. Wind Following Sword looked and saw Lord Grim’s coordinates again.

Wind Following Sword calmly checked the map and once again gave a string of orders.

And after deploying his team, he suddenly discovered that there was a huge hole in his Spinning Spiderweb Formation.

“How!?” Wind Following Sword’s feelings went up and down. He immediately had a team member head to fix that hole, but he quickly received new coordinates for Lord Grim.

Is he heading towards the opening? Wind Following Sword nervously looked at the map.

Chapter 278 – Break the Formation! The Guest Acts as the Host

Sure enough!

When he compared Lord Grim’s previous coordinates to his current one, he found that Lord Grim was heading directly towards the hole in the formation. Judging from the time that the coordinates were sent, it looked as if Lord Grim had changed directions very early on and very decisively. It seemed like he knew that there would be a hole here.

Wind Following Sword hastily messaged any nearby players to fix the hole. Judging by the distance, there was still enough time. However, his sudden dispatch caused another area without anyone there to appear. Based on the direction that Lord Grim was moving towards, Wind Following Sword decided that he should dispatch those who were far away from Lord Grim to fill the gap. That was how the Spinning Spiderweb Formation worked.

But as soon as he had sent out the messages and heaved a sigh of relief, he then discovered that he had received another report of Lord Grim’s coordinates. Wind Following Sword checked the report and immediately exploded.

Lord Grim had changed directions again!

He had just given a bunch of orders and now they were all pointless. Lord Grim was currently heading towards the gap they had left after adjusting their positions.

Wind Following Sword couldn’t pay attention to anything else but Lord Grim. He hastily sent another round of orders. And this time, in order to fix the gap, he had to adjust even more people, which meant he had to send out more messages. Wind Following Sword hastily moved his hands and increased his hand speed. But instead of using them on playing the game, he used it to type faster. His character stood still in Congee City. He didn’t have any time to take even a single step.

In Sin City, Lord Grim continued to advance, rushing forward in a straight line.

No one was more clear on the principles of the Spinning Spiderweb Formation than Ye Xiu. Actually, he didn’t know who exactly was giving out the commands, but during his hour of running around, which Chen Guo had assumed he was still searching for Christmas thieves, in reality, Ye Xiu was actually observing his opponents.

After an hour of observing, Ye Xiu understood how many players were on the other side’s formation. Every time he saw their positions, he gradually grasped the positions of everyone in the Spinning Spiderweb Formation.

The 24 Excellent Dynasty players and their positions were constantly revolving in Ye Xiu’s head. After this, Ye Xiu could predict what his opponents would do with every change in direction he made.

However, he still had to confirm it. After all, if the person executing the formation was different, then the person’s habits and adjustments might not follow his predictions. Ye Xiu was especially worried that the other side hadn’t learned the formation well. If that was the case, then his carefully made predictions would be thrown off. However, in that case, breaking out of the formation would also be just as easy. If that were the case, he wouldn’t need to do anything too technical.

By testing the reactions in the formation for a bit, Ye Xiu discovered that his opponent knew what he was doing. His opponent had already grasped and understood the Spinning Spiderweb Formation extremely well.

But unfortunately, even so, the Spinning Spiderweb Formation wasn’t unbeatable. As the creator of the Spinning Spiderweb Formation, even if there weren’t any holes, Ye Xiu could create one.

This type of hole couldn’t really be considered a hole, but an innate flaw of the Spinning Spiderweb Formation.

This flaw laid in the commander. Because the orders given had to be extremely precise, every time there was a change in direction, the commander had to give almost every character in the formation an order. When the situation changed too quickly, the commander would have a hard time keeping up.

And Lord Grim, the Spinning Spiderweb Formation’s prey, was causing this to happen.

After grasping the other side’s formation, Ye Xiu immediately began to execute his plan. Killing Wind Following Sword was the plan’s first step.

Wind Following Sword was already killed, thus that area temporarily became empty. The commander had to make up for this and, from then on, the formation came under Ye Xiu’s lead.

Even though he wasn’t the commander, in a sense, he was the guide for the formation. How they moved depended entirely on him. And from here on out, Ye Xiu became the guest that acted as the host. By following the movements he had planned out beforehand, he would ultimately drive the other side’s movements and continuously hasten his speed, creating an opening and allowing him to break through.

A hole? There was one, but the hole wasn’t big enough, yet. Continue!

Even though Ye Xiu didn’t have an online map that he could use to grasp the entire situation, the map he had in his head was even clearer. The points on the online map were static, but in Ye Xiu’s mind, the points were constantly moving.

“F*ck!!” When Wind Following Sword received another set of coordinates, he wanted to rock the table in frustration, but he was too busy moving.

Lord Grim once again headed towards the fault in the formation.

There shouldn’t be a fault in the Spinning Spiderweb Formation, so why was there one here?

Wind Following Sword hastily gave orders as he pondered. He was reflecting back step by step to find where the problem had occurred.

Finally, Wind Following Sword’s reflection found an answer.

He locked onto the moment when he had died.

The problem started there! Wind Following Sword suddenly understood. The Spinning Spiderweb Formation didn’t require a precise number of players to work. If there was one fewer or one more, the movements were the same. However, the instant that he died, a blank space appeared in their 24-player formation.

When he revived, he immediately went to fix it. The appearance of the crack was only for a brief moment.

But now that he looked at it, he had lost. He hadn’t been able to fix it and, instead, the more he tried to fix it, the greater the opening became, all the way until you could clearly see the opening if you looked at the map.

Up until then, Wind Following Sword was still somewhat clueless. But now, he finally understood it after seeing Lord Grim accurately rush towards the opening time and time again .

This wasn’t a coincidence!

This was a scenario that the other side had created.

Ye Qiu! He had originally been the prey in their net, but now he had already become the host. Right now, he was completely dictating how the net was being woven.

And he himself? Even after understanding the situation, he still couldn’t fix it.

Wind Following Sword hastily gave out more orders. It was the same as before. He was pulling down one wall only to put up another. The opening in his Spinning Spiderweb Formation was growing larger and larger.

Not good!! Sweat had already started forming on Wind Following Sword’s head. He wasn’t fighting, but his two hands sounded like they were tapping the keyboard even more furiously than they were in a battle.

I can’t keep up!!

Wind Following Sword discovered that with so many adjustments to make, by the time he sent them all out, would there still be enough time to keep Lord Grim in the middle?

Wind Following Sword grew nervous and worried, but his hands never stopped moving.

Just a bit more! Just a bit more!!

Wind Following Sword encouraged himself repeatedly.

Of the 23 players, Wind Following Sword was only able to give out 17 orders this time.

He had to look at each player’s position, determine each player’s movements, and then give them an order. This wasn’t as easy as it sounded. After sending the 17 orders, Wind Following Sword felt his hands becoming fatigued and his head ached.

And then another message came…..

No way!!

Wind Following Sword fell into despair. Whenever an adjustment was made, someone would report Lord Grim’s coordinates. After this, he would go into a frenzy once again. How many times had he done this now?

Wind Following Sword’s fatigued hands opened the message and tears immediately began streaming down his face.

And sure enough!

Lord Grim once again changed routes. Wind Following Sword didn’t even need to look at the online map to confirm it, because he already had experience with this. Lord Grim must be going towards the opening. Where was the opening? How could Wind Following Sword not know? He didn’t want an opening to be there, but there was nothing that he could do about it. This was because ever since the first crack in the formation had appeared as a result of his death, Lord Grim had led the way to widen the opening.

Wind Following Sword hoped that he could have some time to fix it, but he didn’t. Lord Grim’s movements never gave him the chance to. In other words, up until now, Wind Following Sword hadn’t been able to switch from a 24-player formation to a 23-player formation yet.

Everything began when he died.

But Wind Following Sword continued to persevere.

Thinking, making the decision, and giving the orders. His head hurt and his hands almost felt like they weren’t his own. This time, Wind Following Sword gave orders to 19 players.

This was a contest! Wind Following Sword clearly understood that even though he couldn’t see his opponent, the movement of the red dot on his map was in a struggle with him, as if they had fiercely clasped hands together and were arm wrestling. This was no longer the casual and easygoing leading that he did in the beginning. At this moment, Lord Grim was repeatedly battering and tearing down his net.

He won’t break out!!

Wind Following Sword finished 19 messages! He had done it! In that instant, he felt extremely satisfied, because he had completed a difficult challenge. Before this, he hadn’t believed that he could accomplish such a feat in such a short amount of time. It was all simply a miracle.

Sure enough, his true potential only came out against a worthy opponent. Wind Following Sword looked at the red dot on the map as well as the opening that had appeared again. Lord Grim once again headed towards it. He wouldn’t be flustered this time, because he had already accomplished a great feat. He was confident that he could continue on with this situation. He was completely prepared.

Wind Following Sword’s spirits roused. He waited for the report back and waited for those coordinates. This time, he had built up his confidence and suddenly began to enjoy this type of challenge.

Wind Following Sword waited and waited. But this time, the prompt report never came.

Wind Following Sword began to ask for it himself. He asked the players in front of Lord Grim, one, two, three….. He asked them all, but none of them had seen Lord Grim.

Wind Following Sword fell dumbstruck.

If the Spinning Spiderweb Formation couldn’t grasp the prey’s location, then that could only mean one thing: the prey had escaped the web.

Chapter 279 – I Can Persuade Them!

The feeling of falling from the heavens down to the earth was something that Wind Following Sword understood now.

Letting Lord Grim escape wasn’t too bad, but the worst part was that Lord Grim had crushed Wind Following Sword’s confidence. He had just built it up and was filled with tremendous self-confidence, only for it to be destroyed in an instant.

He had originally thought that what he had been doing was amazing, but it had actually been pointless work. When he pulled off the feat, Lord Grim had already rushed out of the opening. In the end, he had been able to escape.

Wind Following Sword’s fingers had turned numb for real this time.

Spinning Spiderweb Formation. The word spinning pointed to maintaining a constant circle around the target. Even if the target didn’t react intensely, the players in the formation had to keep on moving. Especially since, this time, Excellent Dynasty’s goal was to clear away all the Christmas thieves around Lord Grim, which required them to move even more.

Having not received any orders for a while, some of the players were beginning to message him, asking what was up.

“Lord Grim is already gone.” Wind Following Sword replied without any embarrassment, only disappointment.

“Ah?”

Wind Following Sword sent another round of orders, but this time, it was to have the players pull back and monitor the entire area. The visibility in Sin City wasn’t good. Maybe Lord Grim had intentionally stopped moving in some spot?

This seemed to be their last line of hope, but Wind Following Sword wasn’t expecting anything.

The reality was as Wind Following Sword had predicted. Lord Grim was already outside of the Spinning Spiderweb Formation. Where did he go? He didn’t know at the moment and would have to look.

“We failed……” Wind Following Sword messaged Chen Yehui.

“What?”

“Lord Grim escaped from our control.” Wind Following Sword said.

“That doesn’t matter. You guys were still able to delay him for an hour. In this hour, his ranking has been dropping. This is all because of your efforts. Keep up the good work!” Chen Yehui said.

Wind Following Sword was startled. Clearly, Chen Yehui didn’t care that Ye Qiu had broken out. Even if he did, it had still delayed him for an hour. If they kept on doing this and maintained this type of delay, then Chen Yehui’s goal would be reached.

Wind Following Sword understood this too, but he was no longer in the mood to continue doing this. In his heart, he was already the loser. And now, the loser had to keep on getting trampled by the other side. How could that be fun?

But he would still accomplish their goal…… Wind Following Sword forced himself to look from Chen Yehui’s point of view. After replying to Chen Yehui, he renewed his spirits and rushed towards Sin City, while sending his players to search for Lord Grim.

If he was going to do it, then he would try his hardest to do it well. Wind Following Sword changed his attitude and his line of thinking.

Sin City.

Even though Ye Xiu had successfully escaped from the Spinning Spiderweb Formation, he knew that it wasn’t over. He understood Excellent Dynasty’s goal: to hinder his progress in the event and prevent him from messing with Excellent Dynasty’s lead.

“They’re too crazy! Such a large guild intends on competing with you?” Chen Guo was filled with disbelief.

“There’s a lot of pressure as an expert. Even if you don’t want to, you can’t help but become another person’s obstacle.” Ye Xiu sighed, making Chen Guo really want to smash his head into the table. Even though he really was an expert, couldn’t he be a little bit more modest?

“As an expert, you obviously won’t concede, right?” Chen Guo asked.

“Concede? How? Not do the Christmas quests?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Try a different angle! For example, you can join Excellent Dynasty! For an expert like you, if you’re willing, then I’m sure they’ll accept.” Chen Guo felt that her suggestion was quite good. After all, Excellent Dynasty was her guild.. and having her guild get into a fight with her friend didn’t seem right, so Chen Guo finally concluded on this. If he joined, then wouldn’t everyone be happy?

Ye Xiu turned his head to look at Chen Guo: “Don’t tell me you were sent by Chen Yehui?” Ye Xiu had used Chen Guo’s account, so he obviously knew that Chen Guo was a member of Excellent Dynasty.

“Huh? You even know the guild leader?” Chen Guo was astonished.

“Of course! He’s the one leading the work in the tenth server!” Ye Xiu said.

“Really? Even the guild leader went to the tenth server to pioneer? No wonder I haven’t been seeing him very often. A lot of experts have been coming on less too. Could they have run to the tenth server, too?” Chen Guo mumbled.

“Oh? That’s a thing?”

“Yeah! Look.” Chen Guo opened up her Chasing Haze’s guild interface. On the guild list, she pointed out a bunch of grey names to Ye Xiu. She also proudly gave them a short introduction.

Ye Xiu only quietly listened. He had actually heard of some of these names before. He was once Excellent Era’s team captain after all. If there were any experts in the guild, then the guild would definitely report to the team. This was the most established way of finding new players: choosing from the experts in-game.

Testing the guilds’ experts was a task that Ye Xiu had frequently done. All of Excellent Dynasty’s top-tier experts had a datasheet of them in the club. Some of them had even been done by Ye Xiu. These types of characters left some impression on him.

\

“So it’s like that.” Now that Ye Xiu saw Chen Guo’s guild list, he knew that Excellent Dynasty come to the tenth server in full force. But unfortunately, their guild with their high ambitions met him, who oppressed all of the guilds. Of course, with oppression, there would be resistance. Ye Xiu didn’t think that the reactions from the guilds were weird. However, he would also compete against them like so. Shrink back? If he had that thought, then from the very start, Ye Xiu wouldn’t have brought out his Lord Grim with the Thousand Chance Umbrella.

\

“So it’s like what?” Chen Guo was still asking.

“They’re so far ahead in the Christmas event that they dominate the first fifteenth places in the leaderboard. It turns out that Excellent Dynasty had sent out so many experts. No wonder!” Ye Xiu said.

“You could also be one of them!” Completely unaware of the situation, Chen Guo was still trying to persuade him.

“If I really can’t go on any further, then I’ll consider it.” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Do you want me to talk to them for you? I’m actually pretty familiar with a few experts. I can persuade them.” Chen Guo didn’t say it without pride.

Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry.

“Okay okay. If I need to do it, then you have to help me!” Ye Xiu didn’t make fun of Chen Guo’s good intentions.

Chen Guo nodded her head in satisfaction. She then looked at Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, who was still running around randomly. She couldn’t help but ask: “From the looks of it, you should hurry up and consider it! It’s been almost two hours and how many Christmas thieves have you hunted down?”

“Relax! You can still help.” Ye Xiu laughed, “When the entire Excellent Dynasty is crying, you can tell Chen Yehui that you can come to my place and persuade me.”

“Your place? You’re too arrogant! I’ll kick you out!” Chen Guo reminded Ye Xiu to pay attention to his status. She was the boss, after all. An employee dares to order her around? If I tell you to go east, then you go east. That’s the way it should be!

“Yeah yeah yeah yeah!” Ye Xiu nodded his head repeatedly. In the end, Chen Guo pointed at his screen and yelled: “Christmas thief! Hurry!”

“I see it.” Ye Xiu replied and fired at it. The Christmas thief immediately rushed towards Lord Grim, but Lord Grim didn’t meet with the thief. Instead, he jumped into the air with an Aerial Fire and flew onto a rooftop.

“What are you doing?” Chen Guo didn’t understand.

“Aren’t Christmas thieves designed in this way? The thief is very evil and merciless. He hid his identity and stole Santa’s carefully prepared presents. So as soon as he’s been discovered, in order to continue hiding his identity, he will attack the player that has found him to shut his mouth.” Ye Xiu said.

“Sounds right.” Chen Guo said.

“I plan on testing this setup.”

“How are you going to do that?’ Chen Guo asked.

“I want to see if he’ll continue chasing to try and kill me.” Ye Xiu said and, at this moment, the Christmas thief chased after him up onto the roof. This Christmas thief was an Assassin class. He was good at jumping and didn’t even need to climb the walls. At the highest point of his first jump, he jumped again.

The Christmas thief leaped onto the roof. Ye Xiu didn’t fight. He had Lord Grim turn around and run and jump to the other side of the street. On this street, there was unexpectedly a Christmas thief sneaking about. Lord Grim opened up his Thousand Chance Umbrella and fired at it.

“How many Christmas thieves do you think there are in Sin City?” Ye Xiu suddenly asked Chen Guo.

Chapter 280 – Gathering a Mob!

“What are you planning on doing?” Chen Guo’s tone carried a hint of disbelief. Ye Xiu had aggroed two Christmas thieves, but he hadn’t gone to fight them, making her feel like he had gone insane.

“Should we count them?” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re crazy.” Chen Guo watched, dumbstruck.

“Right now, I count two of them.” Ye Xiu actually started counting, while Chen Guo continued to watch in disbelief. Is this guy planning on aggroing all of Sin City’s Christmas thieves onto his body? Why would he try to commit suicide?

Two Christmas thieves chased behind Lord Grim. The Christmas thieves’ levels, classes and stats were different, so they moved at different speeds as well. The newly-aggroed Christmas thief held a Greatsword and really did look like a Berserker. His movement speed was relatively normal, but the Assassin Christmas thief was clearly faster.

However, because Ye Xiu was using Aerial Fire to fly backwards, he held the advantage in movement speed. Not only were they not getting any closer, they were growing farther and farther apart, up until the point where the Berserker had been left behind. If this was any normal monster, Ye Xiu would have already escaped from the thief’s aggro range and would then stop being chased by the thief. However, this Christmas thief wasn’t going to give up. The thief was quite similar to a dungeon’s elite monster.

“Bang!”

Lord Grim once again fired another round, hitting a third Christmas thief, who immediately took out his weapon and began chasing after him.

“Three.” Ye Xiu turned his head towards Chen Guo and reported the number he had counted.

Chen Guo had completely turned to stone. She didn’t have any reaction. Her head seemed to have already turned into a broken machine. Seeing Ye Xiu act like this, was he serious? There was no information on how many Christmas thieves were in a leveling area. However, the number of monsters in a leveling area had a limit. For example, if the limit was 100, then if there were 100 monsters, a 101st monster wouldn’t spawn. If the 100th monster died, then another monster would spawn after a certain amount of time.

Chen Guo had guessed what Ye Xiu was trying to do.

She had also guessed what the result of his actions would be.

However, was it even possible to do what he was planning? Could he guarantee that he could survive having so many Christmas thieves, all of different classes, chasing after him? Wasn’t that too much pressure?

“Number four.” Chen Guo was still thinking, when Ye Xiu reported that he had counted to four.

Because of the differences in movement speed, the four monsters were chasing after him in different places, but they were still quite a bit of distance away from Lord Grim.

Aerial Fire’s movement speed was determined by the character’s firearm. The higher the physical attack on the firearm was, the greater the recoil would be and the faster its movement speed would be. Ye Xiu’s Thousand Chance Umbrella was considered a Rifle with a recoil second only to the Handcannon. It was also a Level 25 Silver weapon, so its stats were equivalent to a Level 30 Orange weapon. The movement speed from its Aerial Fire was exceptional. In addition to his skilled playing, his Aerial Fire never seemed to stop, except only whenever he needed to land on the ground. It looked as if he was moving backwards in a perfectly straight line.

Chen Guo had no way of seeing this type of result through Ye Xiu’s first-person camera though. Otherwise, she would have definitely been astonished. All she could see was that Ye Xiu’s playing was quite quick and precise.

“Five.” Ye Xiu continued to count. The number of Christmas thieves that he had gathered became five.

Six.

Seven.

Eight.

The population in Sin City was sparse. Since Ye Xiu was only looking and not killing, his speed was naturally faster. Not long after, a long line of Christmas thieves were chasing after him, which caught the attention of any players who saw him.

“That many Christmas thieves in one mob? Lord Grim’s so greedy!”

“Sure, he’s greedy, but he’s good if he can actually kill them all.”

No one had yet to figured out Ye Xiu’s crazy idea. The players who had seen him had only thought that he was gathering a mob and then proceeding to killing them all at once, which was a common technique for leveling. However, Christmas thieves were quite strong and their respawns weren’t concentrated in one area, so most players decided to kill them one by one.

Only Chen Guo understood everything.

The train that Lord Grim had created was growing longer and longer. Right now, there were already eighteen Christmas thieves.

Lord Grim was completely safe, which was Chen Guo’s greatest astonishment. Among these Christmas thieves were long-ranged classes who were firing bullets and magic at him… But, none of these attacks affected Lord Grim’s movement speed.

While dodging these attacks, Lord Grim shuffled through streets and alleys in Sin City. While doing this, he had aggroed several Sin City residents as well, but these normal monsters weren’t as persistent and, after chasing for a while, they were shaken off.

The train was still expanding. As the train passed, Ye Xiu had even met Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist.

Su Mucheng didn’t know about the situation and thought that Ye Xiu had encountered some trouble. She immediately fired at the mob of Christmas thieves. However, these Christmas thieves had the setup where only the first attacker counted, so they wouldn’t aggro onto her. The Christmas thieves continued to chase after Lord Grim and Su Mucheng was still attacking, so Ye Xiu messaged her.

“Stop attacking. Stop attacking.”

Su Mucheng stopped: “What are you doing?”

“Gathering a mob!” Ye Xiu replied.

“You’ve already gathered so many. That still isn’t enough?”

“Not enough. I’m going to gather all of the Christmas thieves in the entire city.” Along with this, he sent an arrogant smiley face.

“Why?”

“It’s a competition! A competition to see who kills the most Christmas thieves.”

“So it’s like that. Then, it looks like there isn’t any point to staying here?” Su Mucheng wasn’t surprised like Chen Guo was, because she didn’t doubt that Ye Xiu could do this.

“Seems like it.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Though staying here to watch the chaos doesn’t sound too bad.” Su Mucheng also sent a smiley face.

“Then you can go and grab a good spot in advance.” Ye Xiu said.

“Where?”

“At the clock tower.”

“Oh!” Su Mucheng immediately understood, but she didn’t immediately go. Her Cleansing Mist ran in the opposite direction of Lord Grim. Soon after, she sent a message with her coordinates.

“Do you want to play, too?” Ye Xiu obviously understood what the message was for.

“I’m afraid that I’d mess it up so it’s better if you did it on your own!” Su Mucheng replied.

Ye Xiu led the train to the coordinates and saw Su Mucheng guarding a Christmas thief, which hadn’t yet been attacked.

Another carriage was added to the train and Su Mucheng was now running around helping Ye Xiu find new targets.

Thirty!

Ye Xiu had stopped counting out loud, but Chen Guo was still silently counting.

Thirty Christmas thieves were following behind Lord Grim now. The train’s momentum was growing larger and larger. The footsteps from the train shook half the city block with every road he passed through.

Meanwhile, on Excellent Dynasty’s side, Chen Yehui had finally received a report.

In the beginning, he didn’t know about this. He had only been looking at the leaderboards and had seen Lord Grim’s name continue to drop. He had thought that it was because of Wind Following Sword’s actions, but he didn’t know that, up until now, Wind Following Sword hadn’t been able to find Lord Grim’s whereabouts.

Only now did someone in the guild talk about Lord Grim’s train.

“He’s gathered around twenty or thirty Christmas thieves.” a player reported.

Everyone thought that he was only gathering up a mob. Even Chen Yehui, who knew of Lord Grim’s real identity, didn’t even think of such a crazy idea.

“Has he gone mad from our methods? Is he planning on gathering a bunch of monsters and then killing them?” Chen Yehui thought. “Should we go and mess things up for him?”

The Christmas thief train continued to expand.

Forty. Fifty.

The spectating players finally felt that something wasn’t right.

There should be a limit to how many monsters he would gather, right? If he continued to gather them, wasn’t he just asking to to be killed?

No one continued to think that he was only gathering them for the sake of gathering them and killing them all at once. However, none of them had any clue what his actual purpose was.

Time continued to pass. Lord Grim’s placing on the leaderboards continued to drop, but the number of Christmas thieves behind him continued to increase.

Chen Guo was already in complete disbelief. Tang Rou had also noticed and was speechless, too.

One hundred.

Two hundred.

Three hundred……

The number of Christmas thieves continued to increase. The number of passengers in the train were enough to fill up an entire street.

A full six hours had passed.

Ye Xiu hadn’t left his seat the entire time. He hadn’t eaten dinner, nor had he had a drink of water. He hadn’t gone to the restroom yet, either. All he did was continue with his insane plan and winning Chen Guo’s special approval, who personally helped him light up a cigarette.

Chen Guo didn’t dare interrupt him. Now that things had reached this far, she wanted to see just how far Ye Xiu could take it. Just how many Christmas thieves were there in Sin City?

Chen Guo had already completely forgotten about her own character. She was only focused on Ye Xiu’s situation now. The pressure of three hundred Christmas thieves was quite enormous. Ye Xiu’s expression was completely focused. His gaze never left the screen and he had maintained this concentration for a long time already.

Chapter 281 – Confusion

Christmas Eve.

Even though Chen Guo had decorated the Internet Cafe in a Christmas fashion, it had only been done for attracting business. Her dinner was even simpler and cruder than usual. She took her bowl to the computer and finished eating it there. She still had to count how many Christmas thieves Ye Xiu would eventually end up gathering!

The count continued to grow. Chen Guo stopped being astonished at every increase. She currently felt like she was watching a thriller. Just how many Christmas thieves would be gathered? That was the answer she was waiting for.

Meanwhile, the other experts in the tenth server’s Sin City were no longer able to sit still any longer.

The number of players who came to spectate grew larger and larger. With such a long train running around in Sin City’s streets and alleys, no matter how bad the visibility was in the city, it was still possible to see an abnormal situation like this quite easily.

What everyone had thought was impossible was slowly becoming a reality.

“What is he trying to do?” The leaders of the big guilds were all discussing this.

The most sensitive among them was Excellent Dynasty. They could already see the effects from Lord Grim’s movements from the data: their hunting progress in Sin City had slowed down. Christmas thieves continued to accumulate under Lord Grim. No matter how hard Excellent Dynasty searched, it was becoming harder and harder to find available Christmas thieves to kill.

Even worse, none of the Christmas thieves Lord Grim pulled were dying. If they weren’t dying, then they wouldn’t respawn, which meant that the number of Christmas thieves the other players could kill in Sin City was becoming less and less.

Excellent Dynasty was leading on the Christmas Hunting Leaderboards and needed Sin City to form a solid foundation. But now, their foundations were slowly crumbling. Their advantage in experts was unable to be displayed.

Chen Yehui obviously didn’t want to lose their advantage. After sending out Wind Following Sword and his troops, he picked other experts to react as well. And this time, they weren’t going to just hinder him. If they found Lord Grim, then they were to immediately kill him!

After Lord Grim died, they would then be able to gather many Christmas thieves. This profit was enough to make Chen Yehui excited.

Chen Yehui wasn’t the only one with this thought process. In front of such a profit, killing others was bound to happen.

Everyone understood that Lord Grim was a skilled expert, but under this type of situation, what did it matter if he was a god-level expert?

As the driver of the train, he didn’t have the opportunity to pause for even the slightest bit. With that type of pressure, how was he going to fight with other players? They didn’t even need to fight him directly. If they just stalled him, the mob of Christmas thieves would eventually swarm him and crush him into a pulp.

The guilds had created their own beautiful plans and then sent out their players to accomplish it. The number of players coming out wasn’t few, either. After eliminating Lord Grim, they would immediately scramble for the Christmas thieves.. so, the more players, the better!

But the reality of the situation wasn’t as beautiful as they had anticipated.

Wind Following Sword, who had been chasing after Lord Grim’s whereabouts the entire time, had discovered the issue long ago.

It wasn’t hard to find Lord Grim’s general whereabouts. The train parading through the streets was pretty easy to see. However, the train was way too chaotic. Finding out where exactly Lord Grim was in the train was extraordinarily difficult.

Different Christmas thieves ran at different speeds, so there were gaps in their chase. Those who were farther away could no longer even see where Lord Grim was, but with their AI’s automatic searching, they were able to still know where Lord Grim was. When they chased, they chose the most convenient route, which might not necessarily be Lord Grim’s original route.

Players would often see these Christmas thieves chasing Lord Grim, but the problem was, these thieves’ movements were completely out of sync. Some were running east, some were running west, some were climbing over walls……

Wind Following Sword compiled the reports from the players he had sent out and then used the map to determine where Lord Grim was located.

Every time he directed players to a location, they would always reply that there was nothing there.

This was already his fourth time of receiving “nothing there”. Wind Following Sword’s confidence had been struck once again. He was already feeling embarrassed about having the players continue running nowhere.

“Ye Qiu is moving too quickly.” Wind Following Sword reported to Chen Yehui, “He’s using the Christmas thieves’ random running movements to create a very confusing situation. We can very easily chase after the thieves, but.. we can’t verify his exact location.”

“What do you mean? You can’t find him?” Chen Yehui’s mood immediately turned sour.

“Only by luck……” When Wind Following Sword’s Spinning Spiderweb Formation had been broken through, his confidence had already dissipated. After a single match, he had already understood the distance between him and his opponent. After this, even though he continued to persist, the reality was just too cruel. Ye Qiu was still a level higher.

Luck wasn’t something that anyone could control. Ye Xiu used his movement speed and terrain to cause the Christmas thieves to cause chaos, but if you had good luck and randomly bumped into him, then there was nothing he could do about that.

Currently, there really were a few players like that. When they ran past a street, they turned their cameras.

“Lord Grim!!” The players were surprised to discover him.

Even though they weren’t able to see his ID, with a single person in front and countless Christmas thieves behind, if that person leading the mob wasn’t Lord Grim, who else could it be?

They then saw Lord Grim jump and, with a gunshot, hop onto the roof.

After three seconds, all they saw were a bunch of Christmas thieves climbing up the wall. The players immediately ran to the nearby street.

Huh? There were thieves climbing up the walls by the nearby street too.

Lord Grim was still on the roof!

And that rooftop wasn’t a place that just anyone could reach. Those who could go, went up. Those who couldn’t, ran along the two side streets and hastily called for help.

After that, they saw Lord Grim run onto the street and then jump onto another roof. After doing this several times, the majority of players immediately lost him.

A Gunner was able to catch him though. He was also very familiar with going up and down like this and was able to chase Lord Grim onto the streets.

Lord Grim began using Aerial Fire.

The Gunner began to sweat. When they used Aerial Fire, they were flying backwards, so they wouldn’t use Aerial Fire to chase. Because if they chased while going backwards, their backs would then be exposed to the opponent’s gun. So if you used Aerial Fire and the opponent used Aerial Fire, you’d be hit by the opponent’s bullets. Under this type of situation, chasing would be very difficult.

Everyone knew that Lord Grim was a great expert. The Gunner didn’t dare play anything difficult in front of Lord Grim, so his only choice was to run instead, while reporting the situation to his boss. Those Christmas thieves were also following closely after. From this, the gunner was able to personally feel just how chaotic Ye Xiu’s train was.

Lord Grim rushed to the end of a street and then made a right turn, disappearing from the Gunner’s line of sight.

The Gunner immediately turned back and used Aerial Fire to increase the speed. How could he know that Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim would turn around and glance at him? Seeing the Gunner use Aerial Fire, Ye Xiu immediately took advantage of the fact that they were still far from each other to sneakily slip away to a nearby street.

This type of trick might not be enough to trick the opponents, but these small details were what allowed Ye Xiu to create such a confusing situation.

The orders from many guilds were very simple: follow the Christmas thieves. Because of the Christmas thieves’ AI, they didn’t need to see Lord Grim to know where he was. Their paths would never be wrong and they would always head towards Lord Grim.

However, these Christmas thieves’ movement speeds couldn’t be compared to Lord Grim. If players only followed them, they would never be able to catch Lord Grim.

Just from movement speed alone, Ye Xiu was faster than the majority of players. And this was a huge advantage for Ye Xiu.

With a Silver Weapon as a gun, along with his stable and adept playing, no Gunner could beat him. As for other classes, their movement skills had cooldowns and they couldn’t last as long……

After six hours of persistence, Ye Xiu had already gone past the most difficult part of the plan. The more Christmas thieves behind him, the greater his advantage was and the more difficult it was for players to find his position.

322 Christmas thieves.

No guild knew of this terrifying number. The only person who knew of it was Chen Guo, who had been quietly counting the entire time.

Chapter 282 – Dark

“323…..” Chen Guo watched as Ye Xiu pulled another Christmas thief. The 323rd quickly joined the flood of Christmas thieves behind Lord Grim and was instantly submerged.

Ye Xiu controlled Lord Grim and, under his plan, the actual number of Christmas thieves he was facing wasn’t as crazy as others had imagined it would be. If Chen Guo hadn’t been counting the entire time, then if she looked at Ye Xiu’s screen, she wouldn’t have even thought that he was facing a terrifying 323 Christmas thieves.

As he pulled 323 Christmas thieves, the number of remaining Christmas thieves decreased, which made it ever more difficult for Ye Xiu to find new ones. But he wasn’t done yet and Lord Grim continued to rush about. The game’s settings had changed to a windowed screen. Alongside the windowed screen was a map of Sin City, similar to what Wind Following Sword had done.

If he was just running around randomly with the Christmas thieves, it wouldn’t anything difficult for Ye Xiu. But as the guilds began to react, Ye Xiu had to implement more variables into his plan. Chen Guo saw his look of concentration, so she didn’t bother him and only watched quietly as he played.

The map was filled with Christmas thieves running around. These Christmas thieves could obviously be attacked, too. However, those players wouldn’t gain any points from killing these Christmas thieves, so doing so was equivalent to doing free labor for Ye Xiu.

Players could only watch as the grandiose flood of Christmas thieves swept past them, since killing them wouldn’t benefit them. It made the players truly feel gloomy. They continued to search for Lord Grim’s whereabouts and also looked for any Christmas thieves that had escaped from the net.

The progress with the Christmas thieves hunting for the guilds grew more and more disheartening, but there was nothing they could do. They had already been working hard at it for several hours, but Lord Grim was still as alive as ever. Quite a few had seen him, but not a single one was able to follow and block him.

“But if we kill them, then at the very least, there’ll be new Christmas thieves that’ll respawn. We shouldn’t be just standing around without any monsters to kill!” On Blue Brook Guild’s side, Blue River and his friends were discussing amongst each other. They hadn’t made any progress in the past hour. What was happening in Sin City was completely unimaginable.

“But so what if we kill them? When new ones respawn, won’t Lord Grim just gather them again? If he can do it once, then he can do it twice……” Blue Brook Guild’s Bound Boat said.

“Kill Lord Grim!” Flower Lantern was more impulsive.

“Do you think that no one else has thought of that yet? And what are their results?” Bound Boat said. Blue River also let out a long sigh.

“Then what do we do? Are we just going to watch?” Flower Lantern said.

“I’m thinking……. that he’s doing this to create a situation where there’s nowhere for us to go, so we’ll have no other choice but to kill the Christmas thieves. But if we can restrain ourselves, he’ll also be in a situation where it’ll be too late to stop. With so many Christmas thieves, how was he going to kill them?” Bound Boat said. He also knew Lord Grim’s true identity, so he didn’t doubt Lord Grim’s skill. However, Lord Grim killing the mob by himself was still impossible.

“Oh……” Everyone felt that Bound Boat’s analysis made sense.

Blue Brook Guild wasn’t the only guild bound in a knot. Herb Garden, Tyrannical Ambition, Samsara, Misty Castle… Which guild wasn’t scratching at the wall helplessly? In the end, every guild came to the same conclusion as Bound Boat’s analysis.

No guild wanted to help Lord Grim by working for free, especially Excellent Dynasty. They didn’t know how many Christmas thieves Lord Grim had accumulated exactly, but if they helped him kill all of them, then Chen Yehui didn’t doubt that Lord Grim would immediately jump onto the top of the leaderboards, stepping on their Excellent Dynasty’s first fifteen places.

This was something that Chen Yehui didn’t want to see, even more so than not being able to kill Christmas thieves. At the very least, their Excellent Dynasty would be in the lead. Why would Chen Yehui personally help him just for him to step on them?

Every guild entered this type of overcautious state.

Even though Ye Xiu’s routes were mapped out and planned, the pace at which he was gathering monsters was getting slower. He was gradually entering the stage where he could no longer move forward.

341……

After achieving this number with great difficulty, another half an hour passed, but Ye Xiu still wasn’t able to find any new ones.

How many Christmas thieves were in Sin City? It was just something that he had said. How could a single person figure this out? The guilds were all gloomy, but they would sometimes still sometimes be able to find a fish that had escaped from the nets. When these Christmas thieves were killed, another would then randomly spawn. It was just that the number of Christmas thieves that spawned were very few now, so it was already no longer possible to find one just by casually strolling around.

“They’ve all been stolen by him. I haven’t killed one in a long time.” Tang Rou was also one of those in Sin City struggling for a penny. She was also affected by the situation and her progress was becoming more and more miserable.

“Pretty much.” Ye Xiu suddenly said.

“What are you going to do now?” Chen Guo excitedly asked. She had wanted to ask this question for awhile.

“Tsk. I originally thought that these guilds would move out. However, it seems like this time, they’re very reserved!” Ye Xiu sighed. The guilds had clearly determined the pros and cons of the situation this time. Even though they had been chasing to stop him the entire time, none of them had attacked the running Christmas thieves.

“If they’re not going to move, then I’ll have to do it myself.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“How…. how are you going to do that?” Chen Guo asked. She felt as if she waiting for the final climax in a suspense film.

“Just keep watching and you’ll know.” Ye Xiu grinned.

Still stalling! If you weren’t busy, then I’d have beat you to death already! Chen Guo was gloomy, but she didn’t do anything. She mindlessly attacked monsters as she glanced at Ye Xiu’s screen from time to time. Her day had been wasted. The majority of the time was spent watching Ye Xiu play. Especially true when those players had come to stop him, which had made Chen Guo extremely nervous.

Meanwhile, Lord Grim had already shifted directions. After Aerial Firing for a bit, he turned around and rushed straight forward.

In that direction was an enormous clock tower. Under the flashing lightning bolts, it appeared extremely menacing.

“Hey hey!” Tang Rou called for Chen Guo.

“Hm?” Chen Guo turned around. Tang Rou was tapping her screen.

“Oh!” Chen Guo returned back to reality. She had been watching Ye Xiu the entire time and her Chasing Haze was now surrounded by monsters.

She quickly dealt with the monsters. When Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu’s screen again, Lord Grim had already run to the bottom of the clock tower.

“Are you planning on……”

While still in mid-sentence, she saw Lord Grim jump up and fire. Gunshots rang out and Lord Grim flew diagonally, landing on a protrusion on the clock tower.

“I’m going to jump up.” Ye Xiu grinned.

“D*mn, do you think you’re Su Mucheng?” Chen Guo called.

In Glory, there were a lot of these types of high buildings, weird trees, and precipices. Under normal circumstances, it wasn’t possible to climb them. But it was possible to challenge this through one’s skills and through meticulous research. The methods for doing this were something the game developers had never anticipated.

Sin City’s clock tower was one of these buildings. The clock tower didn’t have any stairs. In order to climb up, your only choice was to jump. But so far, very few had been able to accomplish this. There was a video of a successful climb of Sin City’s clock tower on the web. It was a video from long ago, in which Su Mucheng used Aerial Fire to do it and it was recognized as the peak of the usage of Aerial Fire. And now, Ye Xiu just said that he was going to do it too. How could Chen Guo not jump to her feet at this?

“Oh? You watched the video? I’m going to do the same thing.” Ye Xiu nodded his head and expressed his approval to Chen Guo.

“Let’s see you do it!” Chen Guo startled. Chen Guo had also tried to climb Sin City’s clock tower before and clearly understood the difficulty of this task. The footholds weren’t meant to be footholds. Some of them were just a small bulge from the wall. Landing steadily on them required extremely precise playing. Chen Guo had already recognized that she didn’t have the skill to do it, which only made her respect Su Mucheng, who could do it.

But now? Ye Xiu was going to do it?

Chapter 283 – To Live High and Look Down

By the time Chen Guo finished saying this, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had already jumped twice and began to fire. His character flew through the air in a perfect arc, landing steadily onto the required place.

How was the clock tower climbed? In theory, Chen Guo knew the answer. She had studied Su Mucheng’s video quite a bit. When she watched Ye Xiu’s playing, sure enough, it was the exact same as that video. Every foothold that he took was the exact same as how she knew it. However, every time she tried, she would always fail. Ye Xiu, on the other hand, had already succeeded twice.

Chen Guo began to grow nervous again. She understood very clearly that, for this type of jumping, if a single mistake was made, then all of the previous efforts would be wasted. She had experienced this many times before.

“Guo Guo, look here.” At this moment, Tang Rou pulled at her. Chen Guo turned her head and looked. Soft Mist had also run to the bottom of the clock tower. Her camera was directed towards Lord Grim.

Jump, shoot; Jump, shoot…….

There was almost no pause between Lord Grim’s jumping and shooting. Apart from the times that he needed to turn his body, every time that he landed, he would then immediately begin to jump. His character looked like it was sliding along the wall of the clock tower. After only a short while, he had already reached a quarter of the way up the clock tower.

Slow down! Chen Guo’s hands were sweating from nervousness. Her earphones felt like they were squeezing her head. She took them off, which let her listen to the sounds of Ye Xiu’s playing.

A stop, a pause. The clicking of his mouse and the tapping of his keyboard had a rhythm. With every beat, his character jumped. It felt as if she was watching a movie, where the sound perfectly synced together.

Beneath the clock tower, on the streets, were incoming Christmas thieves. 341 Christmas thieves had finally gathered at one spot. At this moment, more and more were accumulating underneath the clock tower. They surrounded it, restless and noisy. Then, one after the other began to climb the tower.

Chen Guo saw that Ye Xiu had no way of turning back. If he ever made a single mistake and fell down, then he would immediately be drowned in the flood of Christmas thieves and be killed instantly.

The suspense film turned into a horror film. Chen Guo’s heart had leaped up into her throat. She almost didn’t want to watch anymore.

Up! Up!

Lord Grim continued to ascend without any hesitation and without any mistakes. The difficult places that Chen Guo recalled were easily passed over.

And finally, just as he was about to reach the top, Chen Guo suddenly cried: “Ah!”

On the screen, Lord Grim jumped and fired like usual. Except this time, his character was off from the top by a little. He wouldn’t reach it!

Lightning flashed down. Chen Guo suddenly remembered that this final point was very high and required that the character had a certain level of recoil, jumping ability, and weight. The instant that Ye Xiu jumped, he might not have prepared for this most difficult point.

Chen Guo helplessly watched as Lord Grim failed to reach the top. He was already beginning to descend. Just as she was upset that she hadn’t reminded him in time, she suddenly heard Ye Xiu repeatedly tap his keyboard. Lord Grim raised his weapon and then opened it.

“What are you doing? A parachute?” Chen Guo whispered in puzzlement. But the Thousand Chance Umbrella didn’t stop there. The canopy of the umbrella receded back to the umbrella bones. Eight umbrella bones bunched together and then began to rotate.

“D*mn, no way!!” Chen Guo yelled. This time, she recognized it. This was the Mechanic skill: Rotor Wing.

Lord Grim’s descent immediately stopped. After hanging in the air for a bit, he suddenly began to ascend. Following this, Ye Xiu made another move and the Thousand Chance Umbrella returned to its original form, allowing Lord Grim to land on the clock tower’s top.

“This thing can even function as a Mechanical Box!!” Chen Guo said in astonishment.

Mechanical Boxes were special equipment, which were made for Mechanics. Even though Mechanics were considered Gunners, in reality, the majority of their skills didn’t use their guns, but rather a Mechanical Box. It didn’t have any attack stats, but it could increase the levels for skills.

As a result, for Mechanics, they held guns in their hands and carried a Mechanical Box along their waist. Only this setup allowed them to completely use their skills, a unique aspect of this class.

And even though Rotor Wing was a level 20 and under common skill, without a Mechanical Box, it couldn’t be used.

“Or are you carrying a Mechanical Box on you?” Chen Guo asked.

“No, the umbrella has a Mechanical Box function.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck. What a weird weapon!” Chen Guo was speechless.

Ye Xiu chuckled, but didn’t say anything. His character’s camera turned.

“Ah, there’s someone up here!” Chen Guo jumped up in fright, seeing that there was someone up at the top of the clock tower. But after seeing the other person’s name, Cleansing Mist, she recognized her as the person who had helped Tang Rou. This person was one of their friends.

“She also jumped up…….” Chen Guo muttered and felt her heart ache a little. This sister was also a Launcher like her and played with Tang Rou and Ye Xiu, too. Chen Guo couldn’t help comparing herself to this Launcher. Now she saw that this Launcher had actually been able to jump up to the top. Even if it was only for Aerial Fire, she couldn’t compare herself to this Launcher.

“Wow! There’s no need for all of this!!” Ye Xiu was talking with Su Mucheng, in-game. Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist and him had started a trade transaction. She had sent him a large amount of potions, which were all mana potions, instantly stuffing his Weight to the max.

“Just in case!” Su Mucheng said.

“I’m not used to having this much Weight.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s not like you need to move too quickly.” Su Mucheng said.

“That might not be true!” Ye Xiu had Lord Grim walk to the edge of the clock tower. The clock tower was very tall. The Christmas thieves looked like ants, which were swarming their way up the clock tower.

Tang Rou, who was beneath the clock tower, was looking at the top of the tower, but the fog made it difficult to see. When lightning flashed down and lit up the sky, she was able to see two figures on top of the tower.

The other guilds were bitterly searching for Lord Grim. Finally, when they reached here, it was too late. Those who were quicker were at least able to admire Lord Grim’s heroic feat of jumping to the top of the tower.

“This is…… hard to stop halfway?” After receiving this news, Blue River helplessly said to Bound Boat.

Bound Boat immediately turned silent.

They had already figured out that these Christmas thieves were probably going to be taken down by Lord Grim, who was now living high and looking down. And the other players, who didn’t know Lord Grim’s true identity, were still amazed at the fact that he had jumped up to the top of the clock tower.

Chen Yehui was extremely vexed. He wasn’t surprised in the slightest that Ye Qiu was able to jump up to the top. But why hadn’t he thought of this place? He had only thought that Ye Qiu wanted to spite them, forcing the guilds to kill his Christmas thieves. But he hadn’t thought that Ye Qiu actually had a plan that he could fall back to. If he had thought of this earlier, Chen Yehui would have been able to guess that he would use the clock tower for this purpose.

And now.. it was too late.

By the time that Chen Yehui had personally reached the clock tower, he fell dumbstruck just like every other player there. There were so many Christmas thieves that it was impossible to count them all. Now that they had all gathered together in one place, the sight was too strong.

The Christmas thieves were completely tunneled in. They didn’t care about the players behind them in the slightest. As if they were going to pay respects at a shrine, they bravely headed towards that clock tower. And the players? They could only stupidly watch.

Chen Yehui looked left and right and saw Plantago Seed, Blue River, Cold Night, Lonely Drink, Backlight Bomb, Hazy Mist…….

The guild leaders of every top guild in the tenth server were all gathered in the same place, staring stupidly…… staring up high at the figures that could only be seen when lightning flashed.

The Christmas thieves leading the character were just about to reach the top, when lightning flashed down, allowing them to see the real situation. On top of the clock tower wasn’t just one person, but two. The moment the lightning arced down, two streaks of flame roared out from the muzzles of these two figures.

Flames exploded on the clock tower’s stone walls. Everyone could hear the sad and shrill shrieks. The Christmas thieves that had been hit were blown flying. What were they going to grab onto in the air? If they weren’t going to fall to the ground, where else could they go?

“These were all points! These were all presents!” the players thought as their hearts ached.

Chapter 284 – There’s Still Hope

The damage from falling off the clock tower was much greater than the damage coming from players. If players were to fall down, then they would certainly die.

Hearing these Christmas thieves shriek and shrill as they fell made all the players there ache. They wouldn’t die from the fall, would they? Wasn’t that too easy for Lord Grim?

Just as they were thinking of this, they saw a giant beam of light shoot down from the top of the clock tower towards the ground. This was a Laser Rifle from Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist.

This attack was a spectacular sight, though the damage from it wasn’t as impressive as the visual effects. The thieves at the front of the charge ate the Laser Rifle and were pushed apart, falling down from the clock tower. Afterwards, the Laser Rifle’s damage gradually decreased. In the end, the attack had only pushed down three Christmas thieves. Even though the others had been hit, they were able to cling onto the clock tower’s walls.

Whether the monsters could be shot down depended on the skill’s effect. The most optimal skills were the ones with a strong Blow Away effect. Knockbacks, such as from a charged-up Laser Rifle, could knock the Christmas thieves into each other and push a few down. If the skill effect was weaker, then the Christmas thieves would be pushed, but they wouldn’t fall.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng naturally understood this well. All sorts of skills were shot down from the top of the clock tower. Layer after layer of Christmas thieves continuously plummeted. Some quickly fell to the very bottom, while some only fell halfway, and some only just began to fall. Gradually, the shrieks from the falling Christmas thieves combined into one like a chorus, accompanying Sin City’s sinister atmosphere. Players that heard this felt a creeping coldness climb up their spines.

The guild leaders got together again. Some shook their heads in helplessness, while others sighed. Some looked up towards the sky in shock.

The worst among them was Chen Yehui!

This was because his guild currently ruled the leaderboards. The other guilds had already begun to feel the effects from Excellent Dynasty’s huge investment in the tenth server.

Ignoring all else, the number of experts in the Heavenly Domain’s Excellent Dynasty had become fewer. Everyone was aware of Excellent Dynasty’s movements now.

Though even if they knew, every guild had their own plans for their development in the new server and didn’t immediately invest more into it in order to keep up with Excellent Dynasty. And this time, in the Christmas event, Excellent Dynasty monopolized the tenth server’s leaderboards as a result. The other guilds knew that they wouldn’t be able to compete with Excellent Dynasty. They saw this, but didn’t bother with it too much. From a different point of view, Excellent Dynasty may look great in the tenth server, but what about the Heavenly Domain? Without their experts, they were doing extremely poorly in the event. Their performance could even be compared to guilds that had been made by casual players.

As a result, even though everyone was watching Lord Grim show off his might, everyone felt differently about it. Other guilds would only profit a bit less because of Ye Xiu’s move, but no one felt worse than Chen Yehui.

“Should we go and kill them? At the very least, the Christmas thieves will begin respawning sooner. With his method, who knows how long it will take for him to kill them all? I sent some people to check. These Christmas thieves won’t die with a single fall and will even continue climbing. We really don’t know how many times it will take for one of them to die from falling.”

There were already players beginning to discuss whether they should kill the Christmas thieves or not. After realizing that there was no way they could reach Lord Grim, quite a few players were beginning to have this thought.

“Kill them and gift Lord Grim free points? After that, he’ll just gather up more of them and then we go and help him again? F*ck, disgusting!” There were also voices who disagreed, especially from those who detested Lord Grim.

Chen Yehui didn’t want to just do nothing either. He wanted to start another alliance to oppose Lord Grim. But this time, he failed. All the other guild leaders just laughed and cut off the conversation. Chen Yehui also knew that, in this Christmas event, their Excellent Dynasty had profited the most so far. If they were to oppose Lord Grim, their Excellent Dynasty would still profit the most from it. What guild would agree to that?

Chen Yehui was helpless. Lord Grim was at the top of the clock tower, but he had no way of dealing with him. Even though he had many experts under him, none of them could guarantee that they could climb up the tower in a single try. Even if they could, with Lord Grim guarding the clock tower, if they tried to jump, wouldn’t they be in the same situation as the Christmas thieves?

Chen Yehui was at his wit’s end. In the end, his only choice was to bitterly continue looking for Christmas thieves. As Lord Grim killed his thieves, more would begin to respawn in Sin City.

Most of the guilds were already beginning to move out. Quite a few had begun to disperse.

Help Lord Grim kill off the Christmas thieves to have them respawn faster? In the end, no one did this. For people like Chen Yehui and Lonely Drink, doing something like that would make them feel as disgusted as if they had eaten a fly. They truly couldn’t do it. Those who wanted to do this also gave up because, if they did it, their players would be left at the clock tower, while the other guilds who didn’t do this would disperse and start looking for the respawned Christmas thieves. Helping Lord Grim was tolerable, but to be taken advantage of by others wasn’t something that the guilds could tolerate.

“I say we should try to control Lord Grim. We should take advantage while he’s trapped at the top of the clock tower to have a few of our troops kill him when he comes down.” Blossom Valley’s Backlight Bomb said. His team had been killed by Ye Xiu before and he still remembered it well!

“Kill him? To where? He’ll just come back from Congee City.. and then what? Are you going to lock up Sin City’s entrance?” Hazy Mist refuted.

In everyone’s eyes, they couldn’t just chase him like before and split their forces again, right? The Christmas event only lasted for 36 hours. Who would use their limited time wasting their resources?

“F*ck! It’s everyone for themselves!” The guild leaders sighed and then dispersed.

In the square beneath the clock tower, the players had left. But in the nearby streets, some players would walk for a bit and then stop and turn their heads to look.

“In just a short moment, they’ve reached another level.” Blue Brook Guild was one of the guilds that hadn’t completely left. Right now, Bound Boat was looking at the clock tower and talking to Blue River.

Blue River’s character raised his hand and was clearly observing as well. After a short pause, he said: “You’re right.”

“Does this mean that it’s possible that Lord Grim won’t be able to hold on?” Flower Lantern said, while gulping.

If Lord Grim couldn’t hold on, then that meant that the instant he died, the Christmas thieves would return to their original state.

Blue Brook Guild obviously didn’t mind taking the thieves for themselves.

“I’m afraid that we won’t be the only guild to figure this out.” Bound Boat said as he lowered his head and looked around. With Sin City’s visibility, the only thing that they could see was the rain and fog. They couldn’t tell if there were other people around.

“With so many of them, we won’t be able to eat them all. Even if we split the pot up, it’ll still be good for us.”

Blue River laughed bitterly: “Our guild wouldn’t be able to finish the meal and that guy wants to do it all himself.”

“Let him die from overeating!” Flower Lantern said fiercely and hoped that the Christmas thieves would hurry and submerge the clock tower.

“What do you think? Can you hold on?” Chen Guo was worried about this. From the beginning of his resistance, Ye Xiu’s playing had become extremely quick. His character was constantly shuffling about the peak of the tower. But seeing Ye Xiu’s expression and seeing how he didn’t look nervous, Chen Guo couldn’t help but bother him and ask.

“Just barely!” Ye Xiu grinned.

He and Su Mucheng couldn’t stop to rest for even a single moment. The Christmas thieves had climbed up all around the tower, but they weren’t going one at a time. Luckily, the clock tower became narrower the higher up it went. At the very peak of the tower, there was only enough space for five thieves to climb. According to these five spots, Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng split the tower into five sections, which were A, B, C, D and E.

“B!” Su Mucheng called.

Lord Grim hastily rushed over. A Christmas thief was just about to climb up when Lord Grim swept it away with a Falling Flower Palm.

“D!”

Lord Grim turned around and ran back. This Christmas thief was a Gunner. As he climbed, he even fired at Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu hastily dodged. He extended his arm and threw a grenade at the Christmas thief. Bang!

“A!” Su Mucheng called again.

“Almost, almost……..” Below the clock tower, squatting under the darkness, countless players looked up towards the tower, nervously awaiting the future’s results.

Chapter 285 – We Can’t Let It Go To Waste

The clock tower’s peak was high and distant. From the streets, the only thing that could be seen was a vague, dark shape. Normally, the sudden flashes from lightning scared players. But right now, everyone looked forward to them. It allowed them see clearly, saving them some effort.

“They’ve gotten up!!” a player shouted. He saw a hazy figure leap onto the clock tower’s peak.

“GO!!” Chen Yehui yelled.

He hadn’t given up yet. He had also noticed a Christmas thief breaking in. He had plenty of players handy and immediately split them into two groups. Half of them were to disperse and look for the newly respawned Christmas thieves, while the other half were to prepare to scramble for the pile of Christmas thieves.

Hearing their guild leader’s orders, Excellent Dynasty’s players immediately rushed to the streets. With so many players flooding the streets, it was quite easy for others to take notice of them.

After all, all of the guilds were positioned in a circle, so everyone had a different viewing angle. When Excellent Dynasty saw the Christmas thief go up, the Blue Brook Guild’s players hadn’t seen it yet. However, once they saw the players on the opposite side of them rushing forward, even though they didn’t know which guild they were from, they easily figure out why they had moved out.

“Go!” Blue River also shouted an order and Blue Brook Guild’s players rushed forward as well.

And like this, they tipped off each other and, in a short moment, six different troops had rushed out from the surrounding six streets, forming a giant circle around the clock tower.

“Cough…..” Someone gently coughed. This scene was a bit awkward!

But many of them didn’t care about this at all and had their heads raised, watching the Christmas thieves’ movements. The Christmas thieves were still climbing though, which meant that Lord Grim was still alive.

“F*ck!” Someone cursed on Excellent Dynasty’s side. They watched as the blurry figure that had flipped onto the top of the clock tower made a distant shriek and then fell onto the ground.

“Were we too impulsive?” a player seized the moment to ask.

They had only seen a blurry, dark figure flip onto the clock tower and had rushed out simply because of that. It truly was somewhat impulsive. The players who had positioned themselves and prepared to press the buttons for their skills unhappily loosened up their hands.

Everyone waited a bit, but they didn’t see any other Christmas thief reach the top.

“Should we go back?” The guilds whispered amongst themselves.

“What do you mean, ‘go back’…” a player said, while looking left and right. Everyone was out in the open. In any case, they stayed. Everyone understood that there was no point in hiding things from each other.

As a result, everyone raised their heads in unison and watched.

“A!”

“C!”

“D!”

Su Mucheng was constantly calling out.

“I say, are your cooldowns really that long?” Ye Xiu figured out that there was a problem. Su Mucheng’s Launcher didn’t have as many skills as his unspecialized, so there was no way she could continuously shoot Christmas thieves down like Lord Grim could. A lot of her time was spent observing the thieves’ positions. However, why did it seem like she was attacking less and less?

“Ha ha ha, they’re not! I just thought that it’d be fun like this.” Su Mucheng laughed.

“Are you trying to mess with me?”

“Have you eaten dinner?” Su Mucheng asked.

“Not yet.”

“Really? How sad. Then, I’ll help you out!” Su Mucheng said. She sent an Anti-Tank Missile towards a climbing Christmas thief in Area C. The explosion that resulted from it brought down two other Christmas thieves as well.

“Have you eaten?’ Ye Xiu asked.

“I have!” Su Mucheng hadn’t been gathering monsters the entire time like Ye Xiu, who didn’t even have time to take a sip of water. She had first helped Ye Xiu look for Christmas thieves and after that, went to the main city to buy a bunch of potions. She then came back and jumped up to the peak of the clock tower and waited with plenty of time to eat some food.

After Su Mucheng started trying again, they moved like butterflies floating past flowers. After a short while, the Christmas thieves, which had almost been about to break through, were pushed back down once again.

This scene was something that the guilds didn’t want to see.

“Maybe it’s only temporary?” Everyone silently thought.

In the blink of an eye, half an hour had passed. It was a bit too long for it to be temporary now. Chen Yehui, who was looking at the Christmas Hunting Leaderboards, discovered that Lord Grim, who had fallen off the list, was now shooting up on it like a rocket.

The Christmas thieves that had fallen off from the clock tower might not be dead, but they were pretty much halfway to being dead. As a result, when they climbed up and fell two or three more times, they would eventually die.

Right now, it was time to seize the prize. Every time that Chen Yehui refreshed the page, he saw Lord Grim leap forward. Accompanying this was the repeated cries of the Christmas thieves falling down.

Chen Yehui refused to give up. He raised his head and prayed that the Christmas thieves would grow fiercer. The other guilds hadn’t backed out yet either. Everyone still had some hope and wished that Lord Grim wouldn’t be able to hang on.

They had seen Christmas thieves reach the top several times. They were all ready to attack, but they were quickly blown away, and even bringing a few of their bros along with them.

Another half an hour passed.

The amount of Christmas thieves was reduced significantly. Of the six guilds, only four remained. Two of the guilds had already retreated.

Every time a Christmas thief died, another one would quickly respawn in Sin City. As for them? They didn’t see any signs of Lord Grim’s defeat, so they didn’t want to waste any more time.

Four, three, two….. Finally only Excellent Dynasty was left.

It wasn’t as if Chen Yehui couldn’t see the current situation. It was just that he refused to accept it! From the looks of it, it didn’t seem like Lord Grim was going to have any trouble guarding the clock tower. But what if he suddenly made some sort of grave mistake? Chen Yehui was already betting on his luck.

Lord Grim’s standing on the leaderboards continued to rise faster and faster. Chen Yehui watched as he shot up, but there was nothing that he could do to stop him.

400th place, 300th place, 200th place……

Chen Yehui finally saw another familiar name rising up along with Lord Grim.

Cleansing Mist.

Chen Yehui hadn’t noticed it in the beginning because this name was unexpectedly placed higher than Lord Grim. When Lord Grim hit 200th place, Cleansing Mist was already in the top 200.

Chen Yehui was surprised and checked again and saw Soft Mist’s name, who was unexpectedly higher than Lord Grim as well.

Clearly, these three had partied up to hunt the Christmas thieves. If they were in a party, everyone shared the points from a Christmas thief. As a result, the three rose up quickly in the leaderboards together. Chen Yehui had only been paying attention to Lord Grim. When Lord Grim was gathering up all of those monsters, he hadn’t gained any points, while those two kept their rankings on the leaderboard.

At this moment, after working hard for several hours, it was finally time to harvest the fruits of his labor. As for Sin City’s other players, they were left with the slowly recovering Christmas thief population.

Players were dropping in ranks as they were surpassed by these three. Even though the three were sharing the points, it was still more than enough to surpass the players who had completely lost their advantage.

Midnight. On the tenth server’s Sin City clock tower, the two-hour-long battle finally ended.

Cleansing Mist, Soft Mist, and Lord Grim were now ranked first, second and third on the Christmas Hunting Leaderboards. Excellent Dynasty’s fifteen heroes had gotten stepped on in the end, and three times, too. Chen Yehui’s expression was so ugly that it looked like he could die at any moment.

The corpses of the Christmas thieves piled up beneath the clock tower. A large portion of them had already respawned, but the Christmas thieves that were still piled there made the clock tower look like a Christmas tree, even though there was a bit of blood on it.

The bloody Christmas tree was filled with the Christmas spirit, though. The tree was covered with presents; they were presents that had dropped from the dead Christmas thieves.

Soft Mist was currently climbing up the tree and worked hard to collect these presents.

Although the person controlling Soft Mist wasn’t Tang Rou, but instead, was Chen Guo. Soft Mist wasn’t able to jump up onto the clock tower, so she wasn’t able to do much in the battle. Chen Guo had only been there originally to watch, but now she wasn’t able to watch any longer because of these presents.

341 Christmas thieves. 341 presents. The system protected them. Those who weren’t in the party couldn’t pick them up. Leaving them there would be a waste.

Tang Rou didn’t really care and, in the end, was scolded by Chen Guo as a result. Chen Guo then pushed Tang Rou to the side and then personally went to collect the presents for her. Tang Rou didn’t know whether to laugh or cry and left Chen Guo to do it.

Chapter 286 – Harming Others for One’s Personal Gain

Midnight. Normally, Ye Xiu would have taken the shift an hour ago. But today, for the Christmas event, Ye Xiu had created such a crazy scene. Chen Guo was even more nervous about it than Ye Xiu was. She let him off with a break and randomly had someone else sub in for Ye Xiu.

Chen Guo had been controlling Soft Mist to collect the presents, when she heard several gun shots from her headphones. Lord Grim and Cleansing Mist had jumped down from the clock tower. Using their guns’ recoil, they reduced a portion of the damage taken from falling too far down. If not, if they had directly dropped down from the clock tower, they’d definitely die, which would then, just be a joke.

The two characters came down one after the other and also began to pick up their presents. However, while Lord Grim was picking them up, he was also throwing away potions. They were all blue mana potions. As he was doing that, he grumbled: “See, I told you that you bought too many!”

“More is better than less.” Cleansing Mist said and also threw away any excess items from her bag.

It had been about who knew how long it was since the first Christmas thief had dropped to his death. Actually, quite a few presents had already disappeared. But even so, the three still weren’t able to completely pick up all of the presents that hadn’t disappeared yet.

The three characters circled around and around the Christmas tree, picking up presents. All around the streets, several eyes stared at the scene.

The main force of the six guilds had withdrawn, but they had left a few players there who would report to the guild in case Lord Grim made a disastrous mistake. In the end, they watched till the very end as the corpses turned into presents, making their mouths water all over the ground.

The three quickly filled up their bags with presents. Seeing that there were still presents left, even Ye Xiu felt that it was a pity. In the end, he saw Soft Mist, who was being controlled by Chen Guo, turn around resolutely and leave without any signs of reluctance. Ye Xiu was admiring the boss’ heroic determination, when he heard Chen Guo shout: “Hurry up! Hurry up and exchange them. Maybe there’ll still be presents when we return.”

Ye Xiu quietly wiped away some of his sweat and followed from behind. Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist also followed behind them. But right now, the three characters were all burdened with a filled bag, so using Aerial Fire wouldn’t feel comfortable.

Santa could be found in every leveling area, making it convenient for players to exchange their presents. Sin City’s Santa was at the entrance of the city, so there was some distance between it and the clock tower, which was in the middle of the city. With their current movement speed, Ye Xiu didn’t have high hopes that they’d be able to exchange their presents and return in time before the leftover presents disappeared.

Ye Xiu calculated the number of points he had gotten in this hour, as well as his earnings from the presents.

For the top guilds, Ye Xiu had completely used up the thief resources in Sin City, so their gains weren’t much better than those in crowded places like Line Canyon or Desolate Land.

As for Ye Xiu, if he had been doing the quest normally, with his efficiency, he would have had around the same number of points as he had now from the shared 341 Christmas thieves. As for the presents, his losses were much greater. Normally, he wouldn’t have had to waste so many presents.

The end result however, was that the gap between Ye Xiu and the big guilds was huge, but by reducing the big guilds’ gains, Ye Xiu’s gains had been reduced as well. What he had accomplished was, in reality, harming others for his own personal gain.

And truthfully, this wasn’t what Ye Xiu wanted. He would have preferred to quietly gather up points and rewards. As for how much the top guilds profited, Ye Xiu didn’t care. Unfortunately, there just had to have been people making things difficult for him. Regarding this, Ye Xiu also felt bad. He hoped that, in the next 24 hours, everyone would eventually come to an understanding. For a rare event like Christmas, no one would gain anything from hurting each other.

As he thought about this, the three reached Santa. They naturally returned the lost presents back to Santa. Chen Guo hastily exchanged all the presents, turned around and dashed back to the clock tower, opening the rewards as she ran.

Her luck was quite good and, after opening up all of her rewards, she appeared on TV three times. She received two Purple equipment and even a skill book. Chen Guo had only realized this after she finished cheering that Soft Mist wasn’t her own account. Even so, she was still happy about her luck.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng’s luck unfortunately wasn’t as good as Chen Guo’s, although they both made it onto TV once. The two didn’t care as much, though. But while opening the presents, they leveled up from Level 31 to 32. This event was an amazing time to gain experience and earn money. It was hard to come by such a prosperous time in the cold game. Otherwise, why else would all the players be going crazy for the thieves?

Seeing that they leveled up, Ye Xiu opened up his friends list and checked. Steamed Bun Invasion still wasn’t online and there was no sign of Qiao Yifan either. Ye Xiu didn’t really know that much about Steamed Bun Invasion’s situation. As for Qiao Yifan, it was very likely that the pro team would host some sort of party or activity on Christmas to bond with each other. Thinking about this, Ye Xiu messaged Su Mucheng: “It’s Christmas Eve. Doesn’t the team have anything planned?”

“They do!” Su Mucheng replied.

“Why didn’t you go?”

“I’m sick!” Su Mucheng said.

“What happened?”

“There’s an event today, so I got sick. I had to participate in the event to cure it.” Su Mucheng quibbled.

“……”

The three quickly returned back beneath the clock tower, though they hadn’t rushed there for nothing. There were still a few presents remaining there that hadn’t disappeared yet. There were only ten or so presents, which were then split by the three of them.

With the presents gone, the corpses also went away. The area around the clock tower looked as if it would quickly return back to peaceful times. Chen Guo wanted to continue, though. She got up and let Tang Rou use Soft Mist again. She pushed Ye Xiu and said: “Hurry up. Gather them again.”

Ye Xiu laughed bitterly: “Boss, think about it carefully. If I did it again, what’s the difference between me killing them normally and gathering them all at once?”

Chen Guo stared blankly. She then thought about Ye Xiu killing 14 Christmas thieves in one hour. Gathering all of the thieves didn’t earn him much more and he earned even fewer presents, right?

However, the three of them were now way above everyone else on the Christmas Hunting Leaderboards! Thinking of this, Chen Guo felt happy. But as for Ye Xiu, he preferred earning more presents. Did he really care about being ranked against normal players? Did he need to stoop that low?

Ye Xiu pushed away Chen Guo’s hopes of him gathering the monsters all up again and then left his seat. Having been doing the same thing for so long, he had to do something new.

He used the restroom, ate, and drank some water. Thinking about how there were so many players harboring evil intentions towards him, Ye Xiu cautiously decided that he wouldn’t stay online and chose to log out instead.

Lord Grim logged off!

When the guilds suddenly noticed this, they were startled at first and then became excited. As the Christmas thieves at the clock tower were killed, the thief population in Sin City began to recover back into its prosperous state, as it had been before all of this. Everyone was actively plundering about. Knowing that Lord Grim had gone offline was unbelievably good news for them, especially for Chen Yehui. The news felt as amazing as if finally having a thorn removed. Chen Yehui immediately checked the leaderboards. Even though the three were still ahead of them, the distance wasn’t hopeless.

Ye Qiu had logged off, but they hadn’t, which meant that they had time to catch up and surpass him.

Chen Yehui excitedly gave the orders and formulated a plan to surpass Lord Grim in four hours. After five hours, their fifteen heroes would once again dominate the leaderboards and obtain the first fifteen places.

Unfortunately, the good news didn’t last long. After half an hour of joy and hope, a system prompt notified everyone and struck everyone’s hearts.

System notification: Friend Lord Grim is online.

Friend Lord Grim! Everyone wanted to dig out these words and eat them. He wasn’t a good friend! He definitely wasn’t one!

Some angrily gave him a tag, giving Lord Grim a nickname of lowly thug, robber, bandit, evil beast…

But how could these random things affect Ye Xiu? After entering the game again, Ye Xiu sat in a comfortable position and looked at Chen Guo strangely: “Boss, you’re still not going to sleep?”

“Event!” Chen Guo said as her Chasing Haze ran about the Heavenly Domain.

“Tsk tsk!” Ye Xiu lamented. He turned his head back to look at a message that had come through.

He checked it and saw that it was Blue River: “God, are you still planning on playing like that?”

After Blue River knew of Ye Xiu’s identity, he addressed him differently and no longer called him Brother anymore.

Chapter 287 – Collaboration

Blue River wasn’t the only one to message him. Cold Night, Plantago Seed, Misty Castle’s Hazy Mist and a few other guild representatives came over to ask as if they hadn’t been involved in Ye Xiu gathering up the Christmas thieves.

“It depends.” Ye Xiu replied to everyone with the same two words.

“God! If you stall like that, then it isn’t good for either of us!” Blue River replied. He had left a few players beneath the clock tower, so those players had seen that Ye Xiu’s group only consisted of three players. Many of the presents had disappeared and weren’t picked up. The scene truly made their hearts ache.

His one wave gathering was a rather heavy blow to them. Everyone was worried that Lord Grim would do it again, so they had to go and ask what he was planning on doing next.

Collaborate with Lord Grim?

It wasn’t as if no one had thought of this. With Lord Grim’s method, it was definitely possible to suppress the other guilds. When the time came, as long as their guild members were a part of the same team as Lord Grim, then they would guarantee a profit. However, when news of that came out, other guilds would certainly group together and attack them.

Thus, after weighing the pros and cons, the guilds that had originally planned on this decided not to and instead decided to urge Lord Grim not to gather the monsters again, so that everyone was on the same level playing field. By helping each other analyze the situation, it was as if everyone was good friends with each other.

Ye Xiu understood this way before they did. The guilds had come across an unexpected accident. They hadn’t had any plans on dealing with Lord Grim initially. When the other guilds saw that Excellent Dynasty held the first fifteen places and were way ahead of everyone else as well, they recognized Excellent Dynasty’s huge investment in the tenth server. Because of this, no one really planned on competing against them on the Christmas Hunting Leaderboards.

The only worried guild was Excellent Dynasty. Only Excellent Dynasty used the Spinning Spiderweb Formation to oppose Lord Grim and only Excellent Dynasty was unhappy with Lord Grim’s placing on the leaderboard.

The first three places had been snatched away, which was already enough to make Chen Yehui detest them to death. But what Chen Yehui didn’t know was that Ye Xiu had then exposed the whole story to the other guilds, instantly infuriating them. They felt as if they had been forced into Excellent Dynasty’s matters and were blamed alongside them.

It didn’t make them feel any better about what Lord Grim did, but their target had increased by one.

Excellent Dynasty!

And at this moment, Ye Xiu actively gave out a suggestion. Collaboration!

Ye Xiu suggested a collaboration, dispelling the guilds’ previous doubts. The guilds had wanted to collaborate with Lord Grim alone, so they had been scared that the other guilds would attack them. But Ye Xiu was asking everyone to collaborate to eliminate the troublemaking Excellent Dynasty.

After the guilds discussed with each other, they felt like it was something they should do. The suggestion called for everyone to work together. The only thing that they were conflicted upon was how the presents would be distributed.

The points from killing the Christmas thieves would be split evenly between everyone in the team. But the presents were free to pick up. Because of this, whoever picked up more or whoever picked up fewer could cause a dispute among them. After all, they weren’t from the same guild and were all enemies. No one trusted each other.

This issue was a very big obstacle. After talking for a while, no one had come up with a good solution.

“That’ll depend on your luck!” In the end, Ye Xiu proposed a suggestion, “We’re all in the same team anyways and can’t attack each other, so it’ll just depend on who’s faster!”

This was pretty much a suggestion to which nothing was said. But in any case, it was a solution which everyone could accept. Players who picked up less were those whose hands were slower. That was their own fault.

The plan was finally made and a team was created.

In Glory, the maximum limit for a party was ten players. Each team could hold ten parties. In other words, a team could house up to 100 players.

And the number of guilds participating was 12. In the end, every guild sent eight players, split between ten parties along with Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng and Tang Rou, for a total of 99 players.

The eight players sent from each guild were, without a doubt, the top players of each guild.

Excellent Dynasty executed a sea of people strategy. The other guilds followed the more elite route to counter this. Excellent Dynasty had the advantage in the number of experts they possessed. But the other guilds could concentrate their resources on training a more elite team. After all, only one team was needed to set a dungeon record.

Their collaboration was an opportunity to train their elite team.

If everything went smoothly, then their profits might not be any better than before. But, the important part was that the other guilds not involved would be greatly weakened by this and that Excellent Dynasty would be one of them. If Excellent Dynasty earned less experience in this event, then the experience gap between Excellent Dynasty and the twelve guilds would widen.. Their advantage in manpower would be greatly weakened by a level advantage held by the twelve guilds’ elite teams.

Without delay, the 99-player team immediately began to work together as soon as the plan was made. The players spread out all over Sin City and began searching for monsters.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, who was currently standing next to Soft Mist and Cleansing Mist, didn’t move.

After a short moment, the players that had rushed out had already come back with a Christmas thief behind them.

Ye Xiu controlled Lord Grim to meet them and then attack.

One after the other, the Christmas thieves aggroed onto Lord Grim. A team could be considered as an individual entity, so the Christmas thieves’ aggro could shift between teammates. If one player didn’t attack the thief, but another did, the aggro would be snatched by the other player.

After sending Lord Grim their thieves, the other players left. Ye Xiu easily shrugged off the Christmas thieves and began to wander around.

Soon after, a steady flow of Christmas thieves came. Whether due to his own actions or from other players, in the end, they were gathered behind him.

The train once again began. And this time, the train was growing much faster because Ye Xiu had more than 90 helpers.

“He’s started it again!” Chen Yehui didn’t know what the situation was. But as soon as he heard the report that Lord Grim had started the train, he immediately flared up.

“We have to stop him, no matter the cost.” Chen Yehui ordered.

Excellent Dynasty’s players bitterly began to carry out his orders. At the entrance of a street, a team of players had blocked off Lord Grim. Just as they were about to attack, a laser beam shot towards them. Su Mucheng had acted faster.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist also brandished her lance and rushed forward. Her movement speed frightened them. Battle Spirit. For the next 20 hours of the Christmas event, Soft Mist would possess this skill.

With this high-leveled skill that she usually wouldn’t have, the small troop of soldiers were easily blown away.

The players still chased after them, but then they saw a scene that made them dazed.

In front of them was a Tyrannical Ambition player with a Christmas thief. Lord Grim went up and then unexpectedly took the thief’s aggro.

The Christmas thief was set up so that they would only attack the first person that attacked it. For something like this to happen could only mean one thing: Lord Grim and Tyrannical Ambition were on the same team.

This report was quickly sent to Chen Yehui. Chen Yehui was startled at first, but quickly understood what was going on: “Tyrannical Ambition and Ye Qiu are working together?”

Ye Qiu was someone that Chen Yehui detested. Tyrannical Ambition was also their most detested rival guild. Now that two detested groups were collaborating, it made him feel twice the disgust.

“Hmph. The reckless fool.” Chen Yehui laughed coldly. He felt that collaborating with Lord Grim now would make the guild the target of everyone, which would give him the chance to ally with everyone else to take down Lord Grim.

Chapter 288 – Powerful MT

Right when Chen Yehui was figuring out how he would use this opportunity to create a movement within the top guilds, he suddenly received a new message: Blue Brook Guild’s Christmas thieves were taken away by Lord Grim. It looked as if both sides had formed a team.

“What? Blue Brook Guild?” Chen Yehui felt that, this time, not only would he take care of Lord Grim, he’d also take care of these two enemy guilds as well.

Chen Yehui opened up his friends list and was just about to send messages to the other guilds, when he received several similar messages.

Misty Castle, Herb Garden, 301, Blossom Valley, Howling Heights, Void Walk, Royal Heritage, Parade……

Guild names appeared one after the other. It was finally time for Chen Yehui to be stunned.

An attack from all sides? An unwise move? Chen Yehui discovered that he had gotten the target wrong completely. The lone target was his Excellent Dynasty.

New messages continued to arrive, although some were repeats. Not long after, Chen Yehui had figured out how many guilds were working together with Lord Grim.

12.

Not one of the Three Great Guilds was missing and the remaining powerhouses were all participating as well. Many of these guilds had even allied together with Excellent Dynasty to pursue Lord Grim before. But in a sudden turn of events, they immediately switched alliances to ally with Lord Grim for their own interests.

After counting these 12 guilds, Chen Yehui looked again. Among the big guilds, only Samsara hadn’t joined.

Samsara’s Lonely Drink had been influenced too much by his personal feelings for Lord Grim, which was why he hadn’t responded to him. Right now, he was feeling the same as Chen Yehui. He felt a cold chill run down his spine.

They had no strategy left to try and were powerless to stop the opposing guilds. Against an alliance between 12 guilds, how could they stop them?

Sin City’s Christmas thieves quickly flocked behind Lord Grim. The more than ninety players each carried at least one and sometimes more Christmas thieves when they returned.

Half an hour! After only half an hour, Lord Grim had already gathered 415 Christmas thieves, surpassing the number of thieves he had reached after seven hours by himself. At this moment, the number of available Christmas thieves had turned into a shortage.

The 99-player team all headed towards Sin City’s clock tower.

Without any pause, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim begin climbing with the Christmas thieves gathered below him. Except this time, Lord Grim hadn’t jumped to the top yet, when many surrounding players began to attack them.

The Christmas thieves turned a blind eye to them and continued to rush beneath the tower to begin climbing.

Because these players weren’t members of the 99-player team, the Christmas thieves wouldn’t switch their aggro to them.

The players attacking were players sent by the 12 guilds. Their attacks would do damage to the Christmas thieves, but wouldn’t aggro them. Even though they wouldn’t gain anything from this, as experts trained by the guilds, every guild gave them certain benefits and, in these moments, they had to pay the guild back.

No matter how fiercely they attacked, they wouldn’t cause an OT! Because of the Christmas thieves’ special aggro setup, these attacking players were able to enjoy this advantage.

Under these attacks, the Christmas thieves quickly began to fall and golden presents filled the ground. The 99-player team gazed at the prizes with their mouths watering, but none of them dared to move. While the Christmas thieves were being attacked, the majority of the attacks were from Elementalists, Spellblades and other classes with AoE skills. The entire area underneath the clock tower was in their attack range.

The players in the team could not enter the fields. If they rushed forward, it was very likely that they would fall just like the Christmas thieves, so their only choice was to watch. Once the attacks stopped, they would scramble for the dropped presents littered all around.

Under these attacks, very few thieves were able to climb up and chase after Lord Grim.

Those who were able to climb up were obviously struck down by Ye Xiu. After dropping to the ground, their only option was to turn into a corpse. Who knew how much more efficient this was than just Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng attacking. After only a short moment, the grounds beneath the clock tower were scattered with corpses.

This spectacular scene made Blue River somewhat dumbstruck. He suddenly thought of the first time he worked together with Lord Grim in a dungeon.

“One Wave Rush! It’s One Wave Rush again!” Blue River muttered to himself.

It was the same as the One Wave Rush that they had done in Frost Forest, and an important part of the strategy was that Lord Grim was the powerful MT once again. It didn’t matter that he had jumped to the clock tower, or whatever. Gathering the aggro of all these monsters was something completely unimaginable for most players.

This time the scene was even more spectacular. But Blue River’s amazement wasn’t as astonishing as it was before at Frost Forest. This was because he knew of Lord Grim’s identity now.

Ye Qiu. What such a revered God could do was something that they could never imagine.

There weren’t many Christmas thieves left. The players in the team couldn’t resist any longer and began to scramble for the presents. The guilds stopped their attacks as well in order to avoid damaging their friends. The final stretch would have to be done by the players.

Lord Grim also began to descend from the tower with an Aerial Fire.

With a God descending, the players couldn’t help but move out of his way.

These team members would have to fight amongst themselves, but for Ye Xiu and his two friends, their gains were fixed. After all, without Ye Xiu, they couldn’t do this method and he obviously had the qualifications for special treatment. The guilds had no choice but to agree to his conditions.

415 presents. The setup was that if the presents were split between 13 equal portions, then Ye Xiu’s group would earn one of them. In other words, around 32 presents were given to Ye Xiu’s group to split amongst themselves. The remaining presents would be fought for by the other 96 players. If everyone got an equal amount, then everyone would obtain around 4 presents each.

With the first wave over, the Christmas thieves respawned again. The 99 players immediately began to move again and those responsible for outputting damage sat at the clock tower.

Some players even suggested that Lord Grim shouldn’t leave the clock tower. They would just keep bringing him monsters and then have the monsters killed. After Ye Xiu heard this, he naturally shook his head. He wasn’t an actual God. If so many monsters came, he would definitely miss a few. How could he control hundreds of monsters in one spot? That was too unimaginable.

The second round was actually even more efficient than the first. The players returning would normally come back with two or three Christmas thieves.

If they had to fight two or three at the same time, it might be a bit difficult for them. But if they were just running with them, then let alone two or three, four or five wouldn’t be a problem for them.

As a result, they gathered around four to five hundred Christmas thieves in one round and then killed them and picked up the presents. The entire process took less than thirty minutes.

Everyone was extremely happy. Earning these points and rewards was unbelievably easy! Even better, the players in the 12 guilds were shooting up the Christmas Hunting Leaderboards, while Excellent Dynasty and the other guilds were already slowing down.

Originally, they had no way of competing against Excellent Dynasty. But with Lord Grim, everything changed. Not only on the Level 31-35 Leaderboard, but even on the Guild Leaderboard, the twelve guilds were beginning to catch up to Excellent Dynasty.

Excellent Dynasty and Samsara were painfully bitter.

Right now, it was as if they were picking up scraps off of the floor to eat. They had to wait for Lord Grim and those guilds to eat their fill and then take the few crumbs that had accidentally fallen to the floor to eat.

And these crumbs had to be fought for, too!

After the 12 guilds sent their members for the team and for the damage output, they even had a few left over! These players would run around Sin City, looking for these crumbs, infuriating Excellent Dynasty and Samsara.

If they wouldn’t even let up the pressure for those crumbs, was there still justice in this world?

Chapter 289 – A Night Without Sleep

The day of crumbs was difficult to bear, but Chen Yehui clenched his teeth and persisted. Even so, Sin City’s crumbs were much worse than the other leveling areas’ crumbs.

He could only watch as the distance between them and the first three places grow wider and wider and the numerous players behind them grew closer and closer. Chen Yehui was worried, but there was nothing he could do about it.

There was only a single ray of hope left for Chen Yehui.

The event lasted for 36 hours in total. Lord Grim wasn’t like their guild members with two or three players changing shifts; Lord Grim could only be played by Ye Qiu. Other players definitely wouldn’t be able to do what he was doing right now.

Chen Yehui planned how he was going to increase their advantages while Ye Qiu was resting and widen the gap so far that Ye Qiu would have no way of catching up when he got online.

But after seeing the other side’s rapid progress, Chen Yehui was afraid that when Ye Qiu went to rest, he would have to figure out how would keep up with the other guilds’ achievements.

No matter what though, he only had an idea. “Hurry up and go rest!” Chen Yehui prayed.

In the Internet Cafe, Ye Xiu, Tang Rou and Chen Guo were all brimming with energy.

It was already midnight and, even though there was an event going on, the game couldn’t replace real life. When midnight came, many players logged off. Whether it was in the new server, the old servers, or the Heavenly Domain, it was the same everywhere.

Those who were able to stay online undoubtedly won a lot of free space. At three in the morning, the complaints about not being able to find any Christmas thieves had clearly gone down and Chen Guo clearly had the results to show this. She had finally gotten out of the worst of it.

Sin City might be the only place in the tenth server that hadn’t really been impacted heavily by this. The highest leveled characters in the server from the big guilds were all online for 24 hours and all-nighters were very common.

Everyone online was busy playing. Ye Xiu was naturally busy, also. Tang Rou was together with Su Mucheng as usual and they were both helping him block any trouble. However, after handling Excellent Dynasty’s players a few times, they no longer saw them anymore. Chen Yehui had already recognized who he was up against. Ye Xiu was allied with 12 guilds. Chen Yehui judged the hour and sized up the situation and decided to stick with picking up the crumbs.

As a result, Tang Rou and Su Mucheng turned into accompanying Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim as he ran around. This was very boring for Tang Rou. After going with him two times, she saw that there really wasn’t anything to do, so she left and had her Soft Mist bring in monsters like the other players. But Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist stayed behind Lord Grim the entire time. The two talked when there were things to talk about and when there wasn’t anything to talk about, they quietly did their own things. Su Mucheng also had the ability to gather a few monsters, so whenever something sudden popped up, she could help Ye Xiu out.

The players from the various guilds were no longer as excited as they were before. Their moods gradually leveled out. But when they saw their names continuously rising up the ranks on the leaderboards, they still worked at it 100%.

The night was growing deeper and deeper. Even though numerous players had gone to sleep, the life of playing all night wasn’t going to disappear. In the new server’s leveling areas, the competition was as fierce as ever. In the global chat, there were still those cursing those stealing away monsters, as well as cursing the trash they got from the presents, all the way until the sun rose without any stopping.

At seven in the morning, this was usually when all-nighters went to sleep. Like Ye Xiu, Chen Yehui would usually go to sleep at this time, but the difference was that his character would be taken up by someone else to continue training.

But this time, when Chen Yehui dragged his exhausted body up, his eyes were still wide open. Right now, he was staring at his system messages. He didn’t have Lord Grim in his friends list, but that didn’t mean he didn’t have a way of knowing when the other side went offline. After observing Ye Qiu for a while, he knew that Ye Qiu often slept at seven. Chen Yehui had waited for this moment for the entire night. He decided that he would work a little harder and wait until Ye Qiu went to sleep. He would continue working and seize the opportunity while the guy was resting for a few hours to fight for the Christmas thieves.

Except, as time passed, no message came.

“This guy……..” Chen Yehui felt that something wasn’t right. He could persist and continue working, so didn’t that mean Ye Qiu could, too? This guy was someone who was known as someone who had plenty of energy. When he was still a pro-player, he would also pull all-nighters often. This was also one of the excuses he and Liu Hao had used to attack him.

“It looks like he doesn’t plan on sleeping for now…….” At eight, Chen Yehui saw that no message had come. His tiredness had multiplied and he was already yawning a lot.

On the Level 31-35 Christmas Hunting Leaderboards, Excellent Dynasty was already no longer on the first page.

Neither were they on the second or third page.

They weren’t seen all the way until the fourth page. The fifteen heroes were no longer standing together. They had been squeezed out. Some had even dropped to the fifth page.

With the current trend, the fifteen heroes might still have the chance to stand together. Although by that time, they would be on the sixth page.

On the sixth page, they would be out of the first one hundred places…… Chen Yehui hated it so much that his teeth were starting to ache.

When he looked at their guild’s placings. Excellent Dynasty was still number one. They still had the advantage in overall points, but the distance between them and the others was no longer far. The numerous guilds behind them were catching up. After a few hours, they would surpass Excellent Dynasty. The only good news was that Excellent Dynasty wouldn’t drop to the sixth page.

“Why hasn’t Ye Qiu gone to sleep yet?” Chen Yehui hated. After thinking for a bit, he called for the next in line for the shift: “Immediately wake me up when Lord Grim goes offline”. He then went off to bed.

He couldn’t stay for the entire 36 hours, right? Chen Yehui thought like this and believed that he could seize the opportunity while Lord Grim was off.

Could he last for all 36 hours? He still didn’t have an answer. Although, he was sure that Lord Grim would be able to at least last 24 hours. At noon, Ye Xiu was still in front of the computer and looked listless. However, he looked like that the majority of the time.

Chen Guo had just woken up and jumped up in fright when she saw this. She wasn’t able to hang on any longer at six in the morning and went to sleep. Remembering that the Christmas event only came once a year, she woke up and hurried over. But then she saw that Ye Xiu was still sitting there and it looked like he hadn’t moved.

“Did you sleep?” Chen Guo grabbed a chair and asked.

“Nope.” Ye Xiu shook his head.

“Are you not sleepy?” Chen Guo was astonished, although she wasn’t too shocked. Ye Xiu had only gone 24 hours without sleep.

“I’m still okay.” Ye Xiu replied.

“You’re not sleepy, either?” Chen Guo turned her head to ask Tang Rou. Tang Rou was still fighting!

“I’m still okay.” Tang Rou said in practically the same way Ye Xiu did.

“Are you two really okay?” Chen Guo turned on the computer while saying.

Meanwhile, on Club Excellent Era’s side, Chen Yehui kept the event close in his mind. He slept for four hours and then, after waking up tired, he thought of Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and immediately awoke clear-headed. He got up and then rushed over to the studio.

No one had called for him, which meant that Lord Grim still hadn’t gone offline. This guy truly was persistent.. But it should be soon, right?

Chen Yehui thought as he entered the studio. He then walked over to the player using his tenth server character.

“Is Lord Grim still on?” Chen Yehui asked.

“Yeah.” The other side replied. After seeing Chen Yehui arrive, he got up and gave him his seat. The player had been looking for crumbs in Sin City and really wasn’t too busy.

Chen Yehui sat down and the first thing he did was look at the leaderboards. He skimmed over it and discovered that his guild’s fifteen heroes had impressively risen up. This made him indescribably happy, because it meant that a miracle had happened. But after looking at things more closely, he wanted to cry. But no tears came out, even the gum in his eyes dropped out. Chen Yehui had even forgotten to take care of himself for his work. He had run over as soon as he got up and hadn’t even washed his face.

Why had their Excellent Dynasty players risen? It was because the other guilds in front of them had gotten more experience and risen to Level 36.

When they reached Level 36, they would automatically be placed onto a separate Hunting Leaderboard. These level 36 players would immediately switch over, while their players stayed in the Level 31-35 Leaderboard. Their rankings would naturally go up.

This situation made Chen Yehui extremely gloomy. Now that things had gotten this far, he no longer felt that he was living in the same world.

Chen Yehui calculated that with their current crumb-picking pace, when they finally reached the Level 36-40 Leaderboard, their fifteen heroes would be at the very bottom of it.

Seeing that Lord Grim was still on, Chen Yehui wasn’t interested in playing the game. He threw down an “Immediately call me when Lord Grim goes offline!” and then went to do the things he hadn’t had time to do after waking up.

Chapter 290 – Persistence Will Pay Off

It wasn’t as if Ye Xiu didn’t feel anything. Going through an entire day without rest, while playing relatively focused, made him feel somewhat tired long ago. But he persisted the entire time.

His persistence would eventually pay off with more rewards.

The experience gained from the Christmas thieves, as well as from opening the presents, allowed Lord Grim, Soft Mist and Cleansing Mist to rise to Level 35. The guild members also reaped the rewards and leveled up as well.

The most important part about this efficiency was that it was stable, which made the twelve guilds who were involved extremely satisfied. Right now, their biggest concern was the same as Chen Yehui. It was the issue of when Lord Grim was going to sleep.

Lord Grim, their super MT, was someone that no one could replace. During the night, he climbed the tower twice an hour on average and had yet to make a mistake. Such steady and solid playing made everyone gawk in awe.

There were many players in the twelve guilds that could jump up the clock tower. But being able to successfully jump up once after trying a hundred tries was also counted as being able to jump up the clock tower. As for Lord Grim? It seemed like he could jump up a hundred times and succeed a hundred times. That couldn’t be compared to those players who “could jump up the tower”.

Without Lord Grim, they had no way of conducting this sort of tactic, but staying up for 36 hours wasn’t an easy task.

Even though the guilds were worried, no one went up and asked him, in case Lord Grim was so absorbed into it that he forgot about sleep. They were afraid that, if they reminded him of it, he would immediately remember and hurry to sleep.

Everyone harbored this type of uneasiness in their hearts. Every time a wave of Christmas thieves were killed, they all worried about receiving a message from Lord Grim that he was going to stop.

“If you’re sleepy, go rest.” Within the game, Ye Xiu said this to Su Mucheng. He was the only one who was needed for the strategy. Su Mucheng and Tang Rou were really just there to leech experience.

“I’m not sleepy.” Su Mucheng replied.

“Aren’t you sick?”

“Yep! Insomnia!”

Ye Xiu laughed, but didn’t say anything more. He turned his head to look at Tang Rou. This sister looked like she was about to doze off. Before Ye Xiu had come to Happy Internet Cafe, Tang Rou was someone like Chen Guo who had a strict work and rest schedule.

Chen Guo, who was in between the two of them, noticed Ye Xiu’s gaze and turned her head. Tang Rou, who had only just recently said that she was fine, already had heavy eyelids. It was hard to even tell if she could see the screen clearly anymore.

“If you’re sleepy, then go rest. It’ll only be a few hours.” Chen Guo said to Tang Rou.

“I’m not sleepy.” Tang Rou put in great effort to widen her eyes.

“What do you mean not sleepy! Go. Take a nap and I’ll wake you up in a bit. If you don’t, you’re going to fall asleep eventually. The event will keep going until 12 midnight! Can you……. sleep for an hour and then, when you’re good again, you can continue until the end.” Chen Guo still hoped that they’d be able to balance out gaming and rest. She had originally wanted to say “Can you hang on until 12 without sleeping?”, but then quickly changed her words. It wasn’t a good idea to say this type of challenge to Tang Rou. If she did, then her competitiveness might just carry her through.

This time, Tang Rou really did look like she was sleepy. She had woken up even earlier than Ye Xiu did yesterday and had stayed awake longer than Ye Xiu.

“Then.. I’ll be going to sleep for a bit!” After hearing Chen Guo’s urge, Tang Rou finally gave in and went to log out of the game.

“You don’t need to log out.” Ye Xiu suddenly said.

Tang Rou stared blankly. Chen Guo immediately understood. She had been sitting between them for the entire day, so she obviously knew how they were killing the Christmas thieves. It was true, Tang Rou’s character didn’t need to log out. She could just stand there, under the clock tower, and leech experience.

“Yeah, yeah. You don’t need to log out. There’s no point in wasting the experience.” Chen Guo said.

Tang Rou nodded her head: “Then, you can have my share of the presents.” This was directed at Ye Xiu.

“Okay.”

Tang Rou left shortly after. Chen Guo turned her head to ask Ye Xiu: “And you?”

“Can I take a day off?” Ye Xiu said.

“For what?”

“Sleep.”

“You’re…… actually planning on staying up?” Chen Guo asked.

“You know that without me, it won’t work!” Ye Xiu pointed at the screen and said.

“Let’s see how long you can last.” Chen Guo wouldn’t try and persuade Ye Xiu.

“I still need to smoke. I hope you can last, too.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hmph…..” Ye Xiu had been smoking the entire night. Chen Guo had persisted through. Seeing Ye Xiu light another one, she humphed, but didn’t say anything.

day was even busier than at night. The event was growing nearer to the end and the players were all focusing harder.

Ye Xiu was still persisting. On the other side of the screen, many players were saying in their minds: “He’s still not sleeping!”

Some of these thoughts were filled with gratitude like the twelve guilds.

While others were filled with complaints like Excellent Dynasty.

Guild leader Chen had kept an eye out for a long time. It was already four in the afternoon. A new wave of sleepiness hit the tired Chen Yehui, but there were still no signs of Lord Grim going offline.

“This guy! He’s not planning on staying up for all 36 hours, is he?” Chen Yehui was in a terrible mood.

The more time passed, the more Chen Yehui felt like Ye Qiu was planning on doing exactly this. He began growing uneasy.

On the guild leaderboards, Excellent Dynasty had already been passed. They had recently fallen to seventh place and, as the six guilds in front of them passed them, the six guilds behind them were closing in.

What to do?

Happy Internet Cafe! Chen Yehui knew that Ye Qiu was staying there. Could he do something with that knowledge?

Cut their power lines? Make a fake emergency call? Do some sort of online attack? Send people over to act like they needed Ye Qiu for something?

What Chen Yehui was pondering over wasn’t in his area of expertise. He was just letting his imagination run wild and letting more and more ideas rise. Chen Yehui had already vetoed these options. Seeing how everyone around him were merely gaming nerds who played the game the entire day, he had no way of carrying these ideas out.

There’s no way out! The sun was about to go down. Chen Yehui hadn’t played the game yet and was circling about in worry.

The guild leaders had slept. When they woke up and returned to the game, they saw that Lord Grim was still there. They were in admiration.

In the afternoon, Lord Grim had finally made a mistake while jumping up the tower, giving everyone a false alarm. Just as he was about to fall from his mistake, amidst everyone’s cries, the Thousand Chance Umbrella turned into a Rotor Wing and he flew back up to a foothold.

Even with a mistake, Ye Xiu had ways of fixing it, making them feel like the strategy was even more solid than it was before.

At six, Tang Rou came down and began controlling her Soft Mist again. She looked at her bag and saw lots of presents. Someone had clearly helped her pick them up. The probability that Chen Guo did it was very high, but she acted like she hadn’t done anything.

At this time, Cleansing Mist was no longer moving. Ye Xiu had called twice and hadn’t gotten an answer. It seemed like she wasn’t able to hang on much longer. Her character was still in experience range though. It was just that no one could help her pick up presents. Ye Xiu called Tang Rou over for her share, but she refused, so Ye Xiu could only keep them for himself.

Su Mucheng had fallen asleep for three hours. At nine, she suddenly woke up and immediately began playing the game again, as if nothing had happened.

In the blink of an eye, midnight was closing in. Ye Xiu moved his Lord Grim to the top of the clock tower and let out a long sigh of relief.

Finished! Even though there was still a bit of time, there wasn’t any time to gather another wave. He had lasted for 36 hours. Ye Xiu had originally been extremely tired, but the instant everything was over, he suddenly felt his body relax. These 36 hours of playing hadn’t been wasted.

Chapter 291 – Crazy Rewards

Midnight. The system announced that the Christmas event was over. From this point onwards, Christmas thieves would no longer respawn. The Christmas thieves that were still alive would no longer drop any lost presents or count for any points after they were killed. As for presents that had already been dropped, they weren’t affected if they were picked up after midnight. They could still be exchanged for rewards since the exchange for rewards continued for the entire day.

The twelve guilds that had allied together with Ye Xiu were, without a doubt, the winners of this year’s Christmas event. The crowd underneath the clock tower in Sin City erupted in a cheer. Their cries of joy resounded throughout the air. But on top of the clock tower, Lord Grim simply stood there without any signs of movement.

The monster hunting had been completed and Lord Grim could finally come down. Tang Rou turned her head to look and discovered that Ye Xiu had already fallen asleep at his table.

Tang Rou and Chen Guo looked at each other. He had looked perfectly fine a few minutes ago! But in an instant, he dropped dead asleep.

“Hey, hey! You couldn’t hang on for a few minutes longer?” Chen Guo heartlessly shoved Ye Xiu awake.

“What?” Ye Xiu murmured, “Isn’t it over?”

“You haven’t picked up the presents yet!” Tang Rou said.

“You guys go ahead!” Ye Xiu said and then turned his body. He shifted positions and looked as if he was going to continue sleeping.

“Get up. Go back to your room and sleep.” Chen Guo lifted Ye Xiu up.

“Okay, okay, okay. I’m going.” Ye Xiu stood up and left his seat swaying.

Chen Guo watched and was also surprised. Staying up for 36 hours without sleeping wasn’t anything too serious for an adult. But looking at Ye Xiu’s attitude, he looked as if he would fall over at any moment.

Chen Guo thought again. During those 36 hours, Ye Xiu had been doing what others couldn’t do. In order for him to maintain his performance, Ye Xiu had to be focused the entire time. The exhaustion of his mind was something that players like them, who were simply running around and hoping for luck, could not feel.

“Hey!” Seeing Ye Xiu sway again, Chen Guo hastily got up and ran over to help him. But suddenly Ye Xiu steadied himself and shook his head, muttering to himself in astonishment: “I can even sleep while walking. I’m becoming better and better…….”

Chen Guo was speechless. She finally caught up: “Are you okay?”

“I’m fine, I’m fine. I’m going to go to sleep first. Help me log out!” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ll help you turn the presents in! What would happen if you accidentally slept for 24 hours?” Chen Guo happily said.

“Go ahead, go ahead!” Ye Xiu laughed. He then walked over to the stairs. Chen Guo was a bit afraid that he’d tumble down if he climbed up the stairs, but when she looked again, she saw that Ye Xiu’s footsteps were steady. His swaying from before might really have been because he hadn’t been awake and was sleepwalking.

When she got back to her seat, Chen Guo saw Lord Grim’s camera. Lord Grim was at the top of the clock tower with a bird’s eye view of the entire city. The other players were gathered underneath like a bunch of ants. The lightning that arced down made it seem like they could be picked off at any time.

Chen Guo controlled Lord Grim on the clock tower and looked around to the left and the right, feeling a bit reluctant to leave. She had never been here before!

This continued until Tang Rou gave her a look of doubt, making Chen Guo feel a bit embarrassed. She coughed lightly and asked: “Are there still any presents left to pick up?”

“There are! You should help him pick them up!” Tang Rou said.

“Okay.” Chen Guo nodded her head. She opened up Lord Grim’s equipment and looked. His Thousand Chance Umbrella happened to be stopped in Gun form. Chen Guo looked at the attributes and was unbelievably astonished. Thinking about how she was actually using a Silver weapon, Chen Guo could not calm down.

“I’m going to go down!” Chen Guo said.

“Go ahead!” Tang Rou said.

Chen Guo played a Launcher. Even though she was not able to jump up to the top of the clock tower, jumping down wasn’t a problem. She looked at the scene one last time and then had Lord Grim jump down.

Her character descended amidst the fine rain. Chen Guo aimed at the ground and grasped the timing. After shooting several times, Lord Grim finally landed safely.

The guild players surrounding the tower were still there. Their feelings towards Lord Grim were somewhat complicated, but when they saw him jump down, they weren’t sure what to do.

Chen Guo ran over to Soft Mist to help collect the remaining presents. The other players had already finished their scrambling. The pile over there had been left alone especially for Ye Xiu’s group.

After picking up ten or so lost presents, Chen Guo and Tang Rou didn’t talk with these guild players and ran off to find Santa.

“Where’d that sister go?” Chen Guo discovered that there was no trace of that Launcher.

“Oh, she logged off.” Tang Rou said.

The two didn’t say anything else and gave their presents to Santa. Even though Chen Guo wasn’t using her own character, she still looked at the system messages and repeatedly checked her rewards.

For players like Lord Grim and Soft Mist, with so many presents and so many rewards, they had already gone up on TV multiple times.

Going up on TV didn’t necessarily mean that the items they got were great. For example, Purple equipment would also be announced by the system, but their value was limited. Even if they were Orange equipment, they couldn’t be compared to skill books. Those were unable to be traded, so even if you had money, you still wouldn’t be able to get them. Ye Xiu’s group had found skill books in the entire course of the event but Tang Rou’s luck had been the best. She had gotten 55 points in total from skill books while Ye Xiu got a total of 45 points. Su Mucheng had been the most tragic. She had only found the two lowest skill books worth 5 points each, for a total of 10 points.

Aside from this, there were quite a few uncommon materials and a bunch of other stuff. Tang Rou had no idea what the value of these items were, so she kept them for now and decided to tidy them up after the event was over.

And the craziest rewards was experience. When the event finished, the three characters had risen to Level 37.

The other guilds’ players had started at a higher level and, after cooperating with Lord Grim, their efficiency went through the roof, as well. However, they had gotten quite a few less presents, so their rewards couldn’t be compared to Ye Xiu’s group. After exchanging their presents, they rose to Level 38.

As for the helpless Chen Yehui, he could only stare at the leaderboard. Their fifteen heroes’ levels couldn’t even compare to Lord Grim’s group now. When they originally arrived at Sin City for the event, those three were only Level 31 and were three levels apart from them! In the 36 hours of the Christmas event, they had leveled up six times, while Excellent Dynasty with their crumbs, were only able to level up twice.

Even though they did better than the majority of the players and were considered outstanding among the player base……… the majority of the players weren’t Excellent Dynasty’s opponents. Their competitors, the ones who they wanted to compete against, were already two levels above them.

Chen Yehui was helpless towards these results. Even though they were at the bottom of the leaderboard, they had fortunately made it onto the level 36-40 Leaderboards. As for Samsara, they had fallen to the middle of the Level 31-35 Leaderboard.

The higher leveled leaderboard had its advantages.

The higher the level, the greater the rewards of experience, gold, equipment, and material became. The rewards for the Level 36-40 Leaderboard was much better than the rewards for the Level 31-35 Leaderboard.

“It’s all over…….” Chen Yehui finally determined that the leaderboard wouldn’t change anymore. Chen Yehui let out a deep sigh. At this moment, he wasn’t too annoyed because he already recognized that he had been defeated this time.

Chapter 292 – The Aftermath

At the end of the Christmas event, the chat was filled with players announcing their rewards. After a wave of noisiness, things gradually began to calm down. When players received a notification that the event had ended, the majority of them finished exchanging their presents and then proceeded to log off.

Apart from the rewards exchanged from the lost presents, the greatest rewards came from rewards based on the total points accumulated.

Right after Tang Rou received her final Christmas present, she immediately opened it. With a flash of light, she earned a large amount of experience and Soft Mist directly jumped to Level 38. She also received a glowing red, Orange weapon: Battle Mage Level 40 Glowing Fire Halberd.

Glowing Fire Halberd, Level 40.

Weight: 3.3 kg. Attack Speed: 1.

Physical Attack: 470. Magic Attack: 355.

Strength +15. Fire Chaser Skill Level +2. Attacks have a 3% chance of Burning the target.

Looking at the weapon, Tang Rou compared it to her previous Level 30 Purple weapon, the Scarlet Moon Lance: Physical Attack: 330, Magic Attack: 250.

“How amazing!” Even Tang Rou could tell.

“You actually got an Orange weapon. Your luck isn’t bad!” Chen Guo also praised. For a player with a max-leveled account, a Level 40 Orange weapon wouldn’t make her go mad with envy.

Lord Grim also got his final present. But when Chen Guo saw the words ‘Christmas present’, Chen Guo hesitated before eventually closing it and logging out of the game.

She returned to her Chasing Haze. The amount of points she had accumulated naturally couldn’t compare to the amount of points Ye Xiu and Tang Rou had accumulated. Yet even so, she still looked forward to her final present. Chen Guo took in a deep breath and then opened up her present.

The sounds of rattling came out. She had opened a bunch of coins. But besides that, there was nothing else. Chen Guo clearly only got something very, very ordinary.

Seeing the money bag, Chen Guo realized that only Ye Xiu and Tang Rou had earned a profit today. Her Chasing Haze had always been average. She had done her best, but most of her time was used being excited for someone else. Thinking back, even she felt that it was a bit funny.

After opening her presents, there weren’t any more events, so Chen Guo stopped playing.

“It’s been a long day. You should go to sleep early!” Chen Guo said to Tang Rou.

“Phew…..” Tang Rou felt a bit at a loss. 36 hours sounded long, but it actually wasn’t that long. Apart from the short nap, the majority of her time was used on the busy event. Now that the event was over, she suddenly didn’t know what to do anymore.

Usually at this time, the dungeons were refreshed and she would party up and dungeon. But now, her usual party wasn’t there. Her character had leveled extremely quickly. In the blink of an eye, she went from Level 31 to Level 38. Where was she supposed to go now at this level? What was she going to do? Tang Rou had no clue.

She looked blankly at the game and then nodded her head to Chen Guo: ”Okay, I’m going to sleep.”

As a result, there was no Tang Rou in the corner tonight, nor a Ye Xiu at the front desk. Everything seemed like before Ye Xiu had come.

At nine in the morning, Ye Xiu woke up from his bed.

The sunlight shone through the pitiful window, leaving a ray of light in the dim storage room.

Dust hovered around in the light ray. Ye Xiu looked at it blankly and couldn’t help but think back to the rain in Sin City that had drifted like so.

The crazy 36 hours had ended! Ye Xiu had only realized this now. He rubbed his head and got up, putting on his clothes and then left the room.

The TV was on in the living room. Chen Guo was in her sleeping bag and was watching the TV from the sofa with her head wet.

“Boss.” Ye Xiu called. Chen Guo turned her head and said with a mouth full of foam bubbles, “Wu wu” —— a greeting. She then turned around and continued to watch TV.

Ye Xiu was speechless. Who would think that someone who was watching TV on the sofa like that would brush her teeth at the same time?

“Can I use the bathroom?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Wu wu wu.” Chen Guo got up and rushed into the bathroom. After gargling and rinsing out her mouth, she wiped her mouth clean of the white foam and walked out: “Go ahead!”

“Okay.” Ye Xiu went in.

“I didn’t open your Christmas present. Don’t forget to open it.” Chen Guo said.

“Okay.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

By the time he finished washing, Chen Guo had already turned off the TV and left. The door to Tang Rou’s room was open, but she wasn’t there. Ye Xiu walked out and went to the Internet Cafe.

“Morning!” He greeted the employees working in the Internet Cafe. Ye Xiu saw Tang Rou and Chen Guo sitting together at their special computer spots. Ye Xiu walked over and said hi, but didn’t sit together with them: “I’m going to the smoking section!”

“Okay.” Chen Guo obviously wouldn’t stop him. She was only been able to resist because it had been a special situation yesterday. Cigarette smoke wasn’t something that she liked.

The Internet Cafe in the morning was very empty. Ye Xiu randomly took a spot and swiped his card to enter the game.

As soon as he got online, he immediately received a message from Steamed Bun Invasion, who was crying to him!

“Senior, what happened? How did you guys suddenly get to Level 38 in one night?” Steamed Bun Invasion added a bunch of crying emoticons.

“Christmas event. Where were you the past two days?” Ye Xiu replied.

“I was at a Christmas event too!” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“What? How come I didn’t see you online?”

“Why would I go online? I went to drink with a few of my buddies. We got very drunk and I slept the entire day yesterday. I came onto to the game to look today and everything changed. How many days did I sleep? What day is it today?”

Ye Xiu was speechless. Steamed Bun Invasion’s Christmas event had taken place offline. He helplessly replied: “There was a Christmas event in game. It allowed you level very quickly. We leveled several times because of it.”

“There was something like that?” Steamed Bun Invasion was surprised.

“For these types of holidays, the game often has events.” Ye Xiu felt like Steamed Bun Invasion had played games before, so he should have known.

“That’s right! How could I have forgotten!” Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly realized and began crying as if his mother had passed away.

“Hurry up and catch up!” With such a gap, what else could Ye Xiu say?

“Senior, I’ll give you my number. If something like this happens again, call me!” Steamed Bun Invasion was very sad.

“Okay!” Ye Xiu replied. He jotted down Steamed Bun Invasion’s number and told the crying Steamed Bun Invasion to train.

Ye Xiu opened up Lord Grim’s inventory. He saw the Christmas present and opened it.

A flash of light. Lord Grim and Soft Mist’s points had been quite high, so the experience reward they received was about the same. With this experience, Lord Grim also leveled up to 38. Aside from this, he also got a reward that put him on TV, a Level 40 Orange weapon: Shadow Claw.

Claws were Fighter class weapons and were most commonly used by Brawlers. The Shadow Claw was an Orange weapon, so its stats didn’t need to be spoken. However, Ye Xiu didn’t need it to upgrade his Thousand Chance Umbrella. Ye Xiu immediately messaged Steamed Bun Invasion and gave him the Shadow Claw’s attributes.

“Ah, ah, ah, ah! Senior!!” Steamed Bun Invasion shouted.

“Hurry up and level! When you reach Level 40, I’ll give it to you.”

“I will! I will!” Steamed Bun Invasion yelled.

Ye Xiu smiled and then closed the chat window. His Lord Grim was still in Sin City and had a lot of items on him. He still had a lot of Weight on him and he had to get rid of it.

After returning to Congee City, he ran directly to the storage house. On the way there, Ye Xiu made sure to be careful, looking to see if he was being given any special attention from the big guilds.

Don’t look at how everyone had been so happy and harmonious at yesterday’s Christmas event. This chapter had already closed. What followed wouldn’t change. For enemies like Blue Brook Guild and Herb Garden, they definitely wouldn’t suddenly become friends after a single short alliance.

As for Ye Xiu, in the guilds’ eyes, had returned to being that dungeon record kidnapper, especially now that Lord Grim’s level could be compared to theirs, which would make them fearful once again.

Ye Xiu didn’t find anything unusual after observing his surroundings. When he went to the storage house, he quickly tidied it up. Even though he had a lot of materials, in order for him to level up his Thousand Chance Umbrella to Level 35, he still didn’t have enough. For the missing parts, should he run to the market or should he sell some more guides?

Ye Xiu thought and opened up the dungeon records leaderboard. He looked and was surprised. Line Canyon and Fire Forest. These two dungeons’ fastest times were quite frightening.

Chapter 293 – Lance Form! Level 35

Line Canyon’s new record beat the record made by Misty Castle, who had used Ye Xiu’s guide, by two minutes. The record holder was Tyrannical Ambition. Even though they also had Ye Xiu’s guide, the current record surpassed the limit that could be reached by Ye Xiu’s guide. Ye Xiu had no idea how they had done it.

Looking again at Fire Forest’s record, the current record holder was Blue Brook Guild. Their record was unbelievably high as well. Apart from this, not only were the top records astonishing, the first ten records were all enough to make players dumbstruck.

In the Christmas event, the players were all focused on the event. The announcements of records being broken would be washed away by the frequent notifications of rewards from presents. Ye Xiu hadn’t noticed the intense fighting for the records during those 36 hours.

Thinking of this, Ye Xiu figured out what had happened.

These records had appeared because of the Christmas event.

Similar to how Tang Rou’s Soft Mist could temporarily have Battle Spirit, the guilds’ record-setting teams clearly took advantage of the Christmas event to obtain skills that they shouldn’t have at this level in order to create an extremely strong team, temporarily.

This type of team would no longer exist after the event ended, but their records would stay.

Using this opportunity, Tyrannical Ambition dropped a ridiculous Line Canyon record. Even though no one noticed it at that time, there would definitely be ways to have people notice. And the ones who most urgently needed it was Blue Brook Guild, who was able to successfully seize the opportunity and take down Fire Forest’s record. The guild’s embarrassing crisis could finally be relieved.

After thinking of all this, Ye Xiu smiled. There was no longer anything of value that could be obtained from these two dungeons. Ye Xiu opened up Sin City’s dungeon records and checked them.

Sin City’s records were more normal. This dungeon required players to be Level 37-39. The only players who had reached this were those 99 players from Ye Xiu’s team. Excellent Dynasty’s high-leveled players were still in the Level 36 range and wouldn’t be able to participate in Sin City’s dungeon competition, for now.

The Christmas event awarded quite a few good pieces of equipment. The twelve guilds that had allied with Ye Xiu had already allocated their equipment to create an extremely strong team. After yesterday night ended, Sin City’s dungeon record was set. The current record-holder was Herb Garden.

Tyrannical Ambition, Blue Brook Guild, Herb Garden. Glory’s three top guilds fully utilized this event. It had to be said that their ability to surpass other guilds wasn’t without reason.

Seeing that the dungeon competition had already reached Sin City, Ye Xiu had to hurry. He hadn’t yet researched the dungeon. After all, there was no way he could have known that they’d hit Level 38 with this event. It would now be useful to begin his research for the guide he intended to sell.

Guides, videos…… Ye Xiu opened up a broswer to look up materials.

Ye Xiu wouldn’t create an Idiot’s Guide like Concealed Light. He had to find the crucial points and come up with something new.

He moved the game to one side. Ye Xiu flipped through guides and watched videos, while creating a new computer file to write things down in.

After coming up with a few ideas, he still had to go back to the game to test them.

Ye Xiu returned to the game, but didn’t go directly to the dungeon. He instead went to the game’s equipment editor. He didn’t have all of the materials necessary to fully upgrade the Thousand Chance Umbrella yet, but he could upgrade a few of the forms.

He had the rest of the materials from Line Canyon apart from Illusion Swordmaster Ahong’s Orange Weapon —— Scarlet Illusion Blade.

Forty Sandworm Silk were used to upgrade the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s canopy to Level 35.

The piece connecting the umbrella bones, canopy, and pole needed the extremely rare Amber Crystal, an uncommon material dropped by the wild BOSS, Cliff Ronin Alpine.

The connecting piece wasn’t very eye-catching, but it was extremely important. During the research for the Thousand Chance Umbrella, many of the tests were done for this piece. At that time, many materials were used. But after changing forms,, the Thousand Chance Umbrella would immediately fall apart after everything was put together. In order to find materials that could be used for the different levels, a lot of effort was put in.

And right now, Ye Xiu was adding the Amber Crystal into the template. After he disassembled the Thousand Chance Umbrella, he just had to replace the original piece with the new one.

After that, Ye Xiu used the Scarlet Scorpion Tails and the Scarlet Stingers.

Eight of each were needed. At this moment, they were used to replace the umbrella tip’s eight White Wolf Sharp Fangs.

On the newly changed umbrella’s tip was shown a pitch-black Scarlet Scorpion Tail. Along the barb-like structure’s back were streaks of black along with fine lines of blood-red, the Scarlet Stingers.

After exchanging everything, Ye Xiu saved the new edit and then went back to the game.

Currently, Lord Grim was still in Congee City. Even though it was a safe zone, changing the weapon formations to check the attributes could still be done. He took out the upgraded Thousand Chance Umbrella and changed it to the lance form. The umbrella tip was made up of Scarlet Scorpion Tails coming together. The backwards hooks were unevenly matched, but the eight Scarlet Stingers came together creating a single scarlet tip.

The attributes.

Thousand Chance Umbrella (Lance Form), Level 35.

Weight: 2.3 kg. Durability 23. Attack Speed: 5.

Physical Attack: 470. Magic Attack: 350.

A Level 35 Silver weapon had an attack that wouldn’t lose to a Level 40 Orange weapon. These stats were around the same as Tang Rou’s new Level 40 Orange weapon, Glowing Fire Halberd, but the Glowing Fire Halberd had an Attack Speed of 1, while his Thousand Chance Umbrella had an Attack Speed of 5.

An Attack Speed of 5 and an Attack Speed of 1 didn’t mean that there was 5 times the difference. In the early days of Glory, Attack Speed wasn’t represented by numbers. Numbers were attached in order to help players understand the concept of “Attack Speed +1 / 2” attributes to a weapon.

The difference in Attack Speed was only 1.25 times based on the data provided to the public. This number didn’t seem eye-catching, but in the game, a player could easily feel the difference. As for the difference between an Attack Speed of 9 and 10, the difference was miniscule and only a very skilled expert could tell the difference.

Apart from this, there was also a setup that made players sad. It was that the Attack Speed would only appear as a whole number. This meant that there were actually decimal places that were hidden. And this rounded (up or down) part could only be found through research.

But in any case, no matter the difference in decimals between the Attack Speed of 5 and the Attack Speed of 1, as long as the difference between the two Attack Speeds was greater than 3, it was enough for the majority of players to feel the difference. And compared to the Glowing Fire Halberd’s additional attributes, the Thousand Chance Umbrella was finally no longer completely blank.

The Level 35 Thousand Chance Umbrella had an 8% chance to Poison and an 8% chance to Bleed.

Chapter 294 – Creating a Blade

Up until now, apart from a Silver weapon’s Attack, the Thousand Chance Umbrella didn’t have any additional attributes. It was like a White equipment. Even those Green equipment from quests frequently added Strength, Intelligence, etc. But the Thousand Chance Umbrella? It never had any. Not until now.

At Level 35, the Thousand Chance Umbrella finally possessed additional attributes.

The Scarlet Scorpion Tails and the Scarlet Stingers added Bleed and Poison effects. Comparing it to the Glowing Fire Spear’s 3% Burn chance, it wasn’t hard to see how incredible the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s 8% chance was.

After inspecting that there weren’t any problems, Ye Xiu relaxed. The attributes of self-made weapons depended on the details. If the length of the eight Scarlet Scorpion Tails were different or if the eight Scarlet Stingers were assembled in a different way. It was possible that the weapon’s attributes would be negatively affected. The current results had only been made through countless experiments.

Seeing that the lance form was as he expected, Ye Xiu tapped his keyboard. Lord Grim’s hands shook and opened up the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s canopy, opening into an open umbrella. For the Thousand Chance Umbrella, this was the Shield form.

The Sandworm Silk didn’t add any additional attributes to the Level 35 Shield form, but the fundamental defense and ability to absorb damage had been upgraded. However, the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s Durability didn’t change. This meant that the higher the level, the more the Shield couldn’t be used. This Shield form could only be used at the most crucial moments.

The lance and shield forms had been upgraded well, but the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s other parts such as the umbrella bones, pole, sword, etc. couldn’t be upgraded yet because he didn’t have enough materials.

Besides the Scarlet Illusion Blade from Line Canyon, the other materials came from the Level 34-36 Fire Forest. There still weren’t many materials from Fire Forest in the entire tenth server, so it was quite difficult to gather them now.

As a result, Ye Xiu wasn’t too rushed about searching for materials yet. As for the Scarlet Illusion Blade, Ye Xiu had asked Tyrannical Ambition about it twice. The first time, it was left out because they didn’t accept his price for him not acting. The second time was in Zhang Xinjie’s bet, where the Orange weapon was put up. Unfortunately, Tyrannical Ambition said they didn’t have it and made up for it with other materials.

Whether Tyrannical Ambition really had it or not, Ye Xiu didn’t know, but he could at least see that Orange weapons truly were rare.

“I could try and buy the weapon.” Ye Xiu thought. He typed into the global chat asking to buy a Scarlet Illusion Blade.

The world was large, even if it was a rare Orange weapon, after so many days of countless players running the dungeon, Ye Xiu believed that there should at least be a few out there.

Sure enough, several friend invites were quickly sent to him. Ye Xiu added them one by one and asked. Of the five, one of them had heard wrong. The player thought he was selling the blade instead of buying it. With a quick flip, he became Ye Xiu’s competitor.

Ye Xiu ignored him and asked the other four.

Ye Xiu had an idea on what the cost of the Scarlet Illusion Blade was. He only hoped that he wouldn’t meet that type of stubborn noob, who wouldn’t let go of a high price. Even though Ye Xiu didn’t spare any expenses with his Thousand Chance Umbrella that didn’t mean he was going to spend more than what made sense.

Of these four, one of them was only curious about the price. He didn’t even say whether he had the item or not. As for the other three, two of them went up and asked for Ye Xiu’s price. Ye Xiu naturally gave them a fair price. In the end, one of them directly replied with a “Bye” as if he had met with a scammer. The other didn’t reply for a while after hearing Ye Xiu’s reply and was considering it. As for the last one, he directly gave a price to Ye Xiu. His starting price was much higher than Ye Xiu’s fair price. This was normal though. The seller would always try to sell it for more.

Ye Xiu didn’t hurry to reply and waited for the player who didn’t reply back yet.

In a short moment, the player replied: “A bit low!”

Ye Xiu didn’t say too much and made his asking price higher. He then replied with the same price to both of them. The price was higher than his original asking price, but compared to the price given by the other guy, it was lower.

In the end, the one who actively gave him a price defended his price, while the other now with a higher price hesitated again and then replied that he would accept.

Ye Xiu immediately made an appointment, while sending the other one a reply saying “Sorry, I’ve got another offer.” That player’s messages stopped and nothing else came. Whether or not he was regretting his offer, no one would ever know.

Ye Xiu didn’t have that much money, but he had materials. As a result, he messaged the seller for a negotiation to see whether he accepted materials. If this was a noob who didn’t know about the value of uncommon materials, then it definitely wouldn’t work. Luckily, it looked like this player understood and after a bit of discussion, he happily accepted Ye Xiu’s offer.

The two brought their items and met up at an agreed upon place. After opening the trade, they each put in their items and accepts. Like many other countless transactions, it ended peacefully.

The two said bye and then went to do their own things. Ye Xiu entered the equipment editor. All he had to do was make the material into the correct shape. Of course, to get to this point, countless trials and errors had been made.

Ye Xiu thought back on all of this with a tinge of emotion. The Scarlet Illusion Blade had already been made into the correct shape. He switched the sword and saved the editor.

He then entered the game and took out the sword from the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s handle. Apart from the red color of the blade from the Scarlet Illusion Blade, everything else changed.

Thousand Chance Umbrella (Sword Form), Level 35, Physical Attack 390, Magic Attack 440.

Apart from this, there was a Critical Strike chance increase of 2%. This was an additional effect that was originally in the Scarlet Illusion Blade and hadn’t disappeared after being put into the editor.

After this was done, Ye Xiu could only wait a few days for the tenth server to run more Fire Forest dungeons before he could do any more upgrading. He could then sell his guides for the items after they were gathered by the guilds. Gathering up all the materials by himself was impossible.

Lord Grim left Congee City and headed towards Sin City. Ye Xiu messaged Tang Rou, asking her if she wanted to dungeon.

Actually, Ye Xiu had the ability to solo the dungeon. However, when dungeoning solo, it wasn’t possible to encounter a hidden BOSS. Ye Xiu considered this and decided he needed a partner.

Tang Rou was currently following a guide and clearing some quests. Soft Mist had leveled from 31 to 38 extremely quickly. Among the load of quests within these 7 levels, there were naturally ones that rewarded skill or attribute points. Hearing Ye Xiu’s call, she immediately tossed the quests to one side and ran to play with Ye Xiu in Sin City.

At Sin City, the two met and partied up.

“Just us two?” Tang Rou looked left and right, but didn’t see anyone else.

“If not, then who else?” Ye Xiu said. Besides Su Mucheng, the other players he was friends with weren’t high enough leveled to dungeon in Sin City.

“Okay, then let’s go!” Tang Rou said. When she said “Just us two?” She wasn’t doubting that the two wouldn’t be able to clear the dungeon. It meant that if it was just them, then they should start at once.

Sin City’s dungeon was located in a prison.

Sin City’s residents were all criminal, escaped prisoners. This prison didn’t have any rules either. The prisoners were free to roam. The quest background and the story was that there was a prison outbreak where all of the guards were killed. Their jobs were to forcefully suppress these prisoners from escaping..

Ye Xiu and Tang Rou. One of them had looked at the plot ten years ago, while the other was feeling dizzy with mass of text. At this moment, how could she care to understand all this. The two went to the dungeon entrance and quickly entered it. They only had one goal: Kill!

Chapter 295 – Word Battle

The underground prison was dim and moist. As soon as the two characters entered, they stepped into a small puddle. Water splashed onto the ground. Not far from there were a few monsters, who immediately turned their heads and rushed over when they heard the sound.

The underground prison didn’t give players any time to prepare. As soon as they entered, they had to fight.

Tang Rou liked this briskness. Her Soft Mist had already dashed forward to meet with them in combat. In this dim environment, her Scarlet Moon Lance’s glow shone brightly.

The two of them were more than enough to deal with this dungeon. However, the two couldn’t think about creating any type of record. Ye Xiu had come to research the dungeon. Seeing that Tang Rou didn’t have any problems dealing with the monsters, he let her be and continued to walk forward until he reached his planned position, where he began to practice.

Tang Rou was just one person and needed some time to clear away the dungeon monsters. When she had finished doing so, she ran over to where Lord Grim was and discovered that he was unexpectedly even slower than her.. and by a lot.

“What are you doing?” Tang Rou asked curiously. Even though Ye Xiu normally never tried his hardest in dungeons, he had never been like this.

“I’m studying some things. You can continue killing.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Tang Rou continued forward. Although the two were both in the same dungeon, they were pretty much doing their own thing.

Tang Rou pushed forward. She turned around and saw that Lord Grim was still in the same place and with the same few monsters. In Glory, team members only shared experience within a certain range. Soft Mist was just about to leave that range so Tang Rou had no choice but to go back.

“You’re still not done?” Tang Rou asked after running over, though she didn’t have Soft Mist help out.

“Yeah, help me test it out……” Ye Xiu had Tang Rou help him.

As a result, in this dungeon, the majority of the monsters were killed by Tang Rou, while Ye Xiu was often stopped at some spot. Once he was stopped, he would be there for several minutes. With the two going back and forth like this, the dungeon took almost two hours to complete.

After the first run, Tang Rou didn’t say anything.

During the second run, Ye Xiu was no longer running and stopping like he was before. He began killing monsters extremely quickly, especially in the places where he had stopped at before. When he rushed forward in those areas, he was a lot more focused and more efficient.

“What do you think?” Tang Rou asked. She had helped Ye Xiu a few times and heard Ye Xiu’s explanation. She already understood that Ye Xiu was studying new strategies in order to clear the dungeon faster.

“Not bad.” Ye Xiu’s research had gone smoothly.

“Is it going to be used for setting records?”

“Yeah, though we won’t be using it.”

“Then what is it for?” Tang Rou asked.

“As a textbook to be sold to the big guilds!”

“They can’t do it themselves? They have to rely on you?”

“That’s hard to say.” Ye Xiu admitted.

Ye Xiu had pushed away the old and brought out the new in order to increase the dungeon-clearing efficiency. Was he really the only one who could do this? Ye Xiu understood that this might not be the case.

The dungeon was fixed. For many new players, as long as they spent some effort researching it, they all had the ability to come up with a new strategy.

Ye Xiu’s advantage was that he was able to use the shortest amount of time to find the most precise strategy.

In Sin City’s underground prison, Ye Xiu spent his morning and afternoon running the dungeon three times in order to determine the strategy. However, for others, the amount of effort and time they had to put in would be far greater than Ye Xiu.

For example, Tyrannical Ambition.

Tyrannical Ambition could see that the guide they had bought from Ye Xiu was mostly the same as the usual strategy. There were only a few places that had been changed. However, these few places immediately increased the efficiency of the entire guide. This type of strategy gave Jiang You a great enlightenment.

Jiang You obviously wasn’t confident that he could compare to God Ye Qiu. However, this was only a dungeon, which was their in-game experts’ area of expertise. Some of the reasoning in Ye Qiu’s guide gave him some enlightenment. Perhaps they didn’t need to exchange materials for his guide. They might be able to create their own guide.

Jiang You was currently doing just that.

From yesterday night till now, he had used all of the accounts he had on hand. He didn’t know how many times he had run this dungeon. Only just a moment ago, he had discovered something new again and was writing it down in a document. Jiang You’s mood was extremely good and the guide was almost done.

“Guild leader, it’s time to eat.”

When the call for lunch came out from an underling, Jiang You typed in the last punctuation mark. Excited, Jiang You erased the period he had put in and put in an exclamation mark to express his mood.

He saved it and then closed the document. Jiang You stood up with a glowing face: “What are we eating for lunch?”

Jiang You didn’t feel tired at all despite his all-nighter. It was all because he was feeling extremely happy. They had benefited a lot from the Christmas event and had used that opportunity to take back their lost Line Canyon record. And now, it was time to take Sin City’s record as well. Spring had already come for Jiang You.

“Guild leader, it’s going well in the tenth server, hm?” A subordinate asked.

“Yeah, it’s going well, it’s going well.” Jiang You smiled.

Everyone was happy. Ever since Jiang You’s interference in the tenth server, a dark cloud seemed to loom above the studio in Club Tyranny. Even those who weren’t involved in the tenth server were affected by the tenth server’s situation.

Jiang You’s repeated running into a wall in the tenth server had put forward an even harsher environment in the studio. These past few days, the atmosphere in the room had constantly been going up and down.

And now, finally, it seemed like in the most recent two days, the skies had cleared from the storm. The guild leader had a big smile across his face and he no longer admonished them as frequently. He would even say a few jokes for them to hear, even if they weren’t funny.

After lunch, Jiang You didn’t go to sleep. He directly logged into the tenth server and contacted Cold Night. However, at this moment, Cold Night himself wasn’t there. It was a different person who had taken the account to level.

Though in order to use the same account, the two people were definitely together. After a while, the real Cold Night switched over. Jiang You sent him the guide he had personally researched and had Cold Night hurry and choose players to practice it.

“From Ye Qiu?” Cold Night asked after receiving it.

“Ye Qiu? Aren’t we only going to use that when we have no other choice? I made this guide myself.” Jiang You said.

“Oh, oh…….” Cold Night didn’t dare say too much. In his eyes, Ye Qiu would definitely continue to sell his guides. The guild leader had gone to do battle with him and so he had also created a guide. Even though Cold Night respected his guild leader greatly… when comparing the two, no one in their right mind would think the guild leader was better than Ye Qiu, right?

Cold Night still called players to get ready to practice. They had to first understand the guide well.

Each member complied as they were informed. Cold Night received another message and saw that it was from Lord Grim.

“Brother, do you want a guide?”

“Sorry, we already have one.” Cold Night replied.

“Oh? From who? Zhang Xinjie?” Ye Xiu asked.

Cold Night didn’t reply for awhile. The other side thought the guide was from Zhang Xinjie. If he said that it was from Jiang You, it would clearly be lowering themselves. It was as if the other side asked if you had gone to a banquet. You couldn’t proudly say that you had actually eaten instant ramen. Instant ramen couldn’t help you win any sense of superiority.

“You don’t have to worry about that.” Cold Night replied. He felt a bit ashamed. He didn’t want to say that the guide came from the guild leader, because if he did, then he’d feel like he’d be lowering the guild leader’s name. It was a bit shameful.

Even though Ye Qiu was their Tyranny’s rival, he was still Ye Qiu. For them, Cold Night felt like they didn’t even have the qualifications to be his enemies…….

Chapter 296 – Can I Buy Out?

Tyrannical Ambition had made their own guide. Ye Xiu wasn’t too surprised by this. With a few prompts to guide their reasoning, it didn’t matter how good they were; anyone would want to try. After all, researching it was free.

Not only Tyrannical Ambition, but Misty Castle was the same. When he asked Hazy Mist, Hazy Mist also evasively laughed, meaning that they didn’t need it for now.

Ye Xiu understood and didn’t expose them. Even if the two guilds researched their own guides, it would only reduce the number of his clients. This type of secret weapon definitely wouldn’t be shared with other guilds or else they would be creating more competitors.

The two guilds that had previously bought Ye Xiu’s guide refused his new one. Ye Xiu chose another guild.

“Another one?” Blue River received the message and replied back.

“Yeah! Last time, you missed it. This time, you should take the chance!”

‘Last time it was Line Canyon. Did Misty Castle use that guide?” Blue River asked.

“Of course.”

“What’s the price!” Blue River said.

A list of materials appeared in front of him.

Blue River quickly skimmed over it and replied: “This…… Not just me, I’m afraid no one in the tenth server can fulfill your needs.”

The list was all Fire Forest uncommon materials. However, they had only begun running Fire Forest two or three days ago and really didn’t have many materials.

“It’s not a rush. It’s not our first time making a deal. We still have trust, right?” Ye Xiu said. What he meant was: ‘you can give it once you have it’.

Last time, when he peddled his guide, Blue River had refused it because he had made a deal with Tyrannical Ambition to give up on competing for the Line Canyon record. He was clearly someone who kept his part of the deal. Even if it was a time when his guild really needed to come back, he didn’t use any loopholes as an excuse to break the deal. How could he not trust someone like this?

“Okay, if you’re fine with it, then it’s not a problem. When we get the materials, we’ll hand them to you. Give me a guide.” Blue River replied.

“Give me your e-mail. I’ll send it to you.”

Blue River gave him his e-mail address and then asked: “Can I ask you something? How many guides have you already sold?”

Blue River was an understanding person. He wasn’t naive. He had completely understood the guide’s value and purpose last time. This guide wasn’t a guarantee for the record. It was only a ticket to the competition. It didn’t make sense for him to only sell one copy. Simply speaking, the tenth server records were once again being controlled by Lord Grim. However, Blue River knew that with Lord Grim’s identity, there was nothing he could do about it.

“Just you for now.”

“Oh? Then….. Is it possible to buy the guide out?” Even though Blue River knew the possibility wasn’t high, he couldn’t help but ask. If he sold these guides, he had ten or so guilds as buyers. Buy out? That would mean that the price would be ten or so times higher. It wasn’t something that they could pay.

“Ha ha…… buy out……”

“I’m going to check the mail.” Blue River saw that Ye Xiu was avoiding the topic, so he said something to break it.

Unexpectedly, Lord Grim messaged him again with a new list: “If you’re going to buy it out, then this is the price.”

Blue River was startled. He discovered that the buy out price which he had originally thought wasn’t possible, looked possible. Compared to the previous list, this buy out price only added a few more items. From the value of the list, it wasn’t ten or so times the price, but only two times the price.

Such a cheap price was completely out of Blue River’s expectations. “No way?” Blue River mumbled and scrolled up and down. That was it. There was nothing after it.

“Is there another message?” Blue River thought. After a bit, another message popped up. When he looked, he saw that it was from Lord Grim: “What do you think?”

“Just this?” Blue River couldn’t help but ask.

“Yeah.”

Blue River hesitated. It wasn’t because the price was high, but because the price was too low……. How difficult! If the price was high, he couldn’t buy it. If it was too low, he was hesitant because it seemed like there was a trap. Even though the other side trusted him, Blue River wanted to pay him back. But as the guild leader, he was responsible for the tenth server and couldn’t act out impulsively.

“Can I……. think about it?” Blue River asked.

“Oh? How long?”

“Is a day okay?”

“Alright!” Ye Xiu laughed in reply.

How could he not know what Blue River was thinking? If he was going to buy it out, then he had to look at the guide’s value. Blue River would probably test out the guide, especially when midnight came. By then, Blue Brook Guild would begin competing for the records in the 10th server. If he really could set an incredible record, then buying out the guide was the same as buying out the record.

Could the guide help Blue Brook Guild do that? Ye Xiu didn’t know. After all, Tyrannical Ambition and Misty Castle had already created their own guides using similar reasoning. Ye Xiu didn’t know how good their guide was, either. He was confident in one thing though: Tyrannical Ambition’s and Misty Castle’s guides could be no better than Ye Xiu’s.

There was no limit to player vs player battles because people could progress and change. However, dungeons were fixed. Some of the luck was fixed within a certain range. There was absolutely a limit. As long as the limit was reached, then there was no way the other side could surpass it.

Ye Xiu thought and then continued to play.

He had already finished with Sin City’s dungeon runs. As a result, Ye Xiu did the same as Tang Rou. He flipped through guides while doing the required quests from Level 31-38. Once again, he sat in the same place the entire day, only moving to eat.

At night, Qiao Yifan grabbed his One Inch Ash and got online. When he looked at God’s level, he also coughed up blood. Ye Xiu asked him and, sure enough, their Tiny Herb had their own Christmas event. As a small figure on the team, he couldn’t be so free like Su Mucheng, which was why he hadn’t been online for those two days.

Qiao Yifan knew about the Christmas event’s rewards. He had guessed that he would fall behind in levels, but he had never imagined that it’d be by so much. The God was already Level 38. The two would have difficulty playing with each other. He was currently regretting everything. If he had known earlier, then he would have handed his account over to have it leveled.

Qiao Yifan sighed, but was helpless. There was no way he could catch up on his own; he’d have to have someone level it for him.

As a result, Qiao Yifan didn’t really play much that night. He hastily greeted God and then logged off. He immediately contacted the substitute leveler and handed his account over.

In the blink of an eye, it was midnight again. The entrances to the dungeon areas were packed with players.

Ye Xiu was at his spot during the shift. Tang Rou was in her designated spot as usual. Chen Guo had gone to bed early.

“Are we going to dungeon?” Tang Rou asked. She had been completing quests the entire day. Her brain was fried.

“Let’s go!” Ye Xiu said.

Su Mucheng had already gone online. Ye Xiu and the other two walked over and partied up. Currently, only the elite teams from the big guilds were in Sin City. The wild teams still hadn’t reached here yet. At the entrance, he saw many familiar IDs; they were all players that had teamed up with him during the Christmas event.

They greeted each other half-heartedly and then went into the dungeon.

Three definitely couldn’t compare to five, but that didn’t mean the dungeon would be hard. The three pushed forward. As the time approached 12:30 AM, Ye Xiu began to pay attention to the messages up until 12:40 AM without any news of a dungeon record. Ye Xiu was currently thinking that the first round of running the dungeon has resulted in the guilds all having made mistakes, when he heard an announcement: Tyrannical Ambition had taken down Herb Garden’s Sin City dungeon record.

Chapter 297 – I Once Had a Guide

The Sin City’s teams from the top guilds were all undoubtedly from the Christmas event. Through their final present’s rewarded experience and a day of leveling, they were now Level 39. It didn’t need to be said that through the Christmas events, the guilds had obtained quite a few pieces of Level 35 equipment. The members of these teams already had a full set. It could be said that the competition in Sin City had reached a new level of intense fighting. The record previously held by Herb Garden had already been a fairly impressive record.

If it was simply a record being broken, then it wouldn’t be too astonishing. However, Tyrannical Ambition’s record of 29:34:71 had beaten Herb Garden’s by nearly three minutes.

Such a large improvement clearly wasn’t possible to achieve through luck. There had definitely been some sort of trick.

The world was shocked, but when Ye Xiu saw this, his heart relaxed.

“Was it through your guide?” Tang Rou asked.

“No.”

“Oh? Then how does it compare to your guide?”

“Slightly worse.” Ye Xiu said. This was his reason for relaxing. If Tyrannical Ambition hadn’t made any mistakes during their record-setting run, then Ye Xiu was sure that their guide had a few oversights and wasn’t at the limit yet. As long as Blue Brook Guild precisely did what the guide required, then breaking the record shouldn’t be a problem.

“Then, who bought your guide?” Tang Rou asked.

“Blue Brook Guild.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh.” Tang Rou had learned these names by now.

It was hard to avoid a discussion in the global chat. After all, three days ago, Tyrannical Ambition had been beaten full of cuts and bruises from public ridicule. But with two back-to-back astonishing records in Line Canyon and Sin City, they came back with a powerful counterattack. With such a record, Tyrannical Ambition’s voice sounded righteous and self-confident.

“Tsk tsk tsk, people from Tyranny are always like this.” Su Mucheng said. As someone from the pro scene, she was used to calling the team’s name this. To Su Mucheng, Tyrannical Ambition was the same as Tyranny.

“Yeah, they’re the type of people to never stop provoking others.” Ye Xiu said.

“If their record gets beaten in a bit, where will their face go?”

“Yeah, they’re too impulsive. They could’ve at least asked me!” Ye Xiu said. If Tyrannical Ambition’s players had come to ask him, he could have told them that their record wasn’t good enough. If they were going to brag, they still needed to try harder or else their reputation would quickly take a blow.

Su Mucheng laughed and then said: “Ask you? You’re the one person Tyrannical Ambition doesn’t want to acknowledge, no?”

“Uh…..” This question really stumped Ye Xiu. Whether it was Tyranny’s people or Tyrannical Ambition’s players, none of them liked Ye Qiu.

When Jiang You saw that the tenth server’s team had broken the dungeon record, he leaped up in joy and celebrated with the person next to him.

“The dungeon run was a success!” Cold Night reported.

“Yeah, I saw it.” Jiang You smiled in response. The guide had been made by him, so he naturally had an idea about what the record should be. Everything that could be done had been done. If they wanted to improve it even further, then it would have to depend on luck. In short, that was as far as it would go.

“We just don’t know about Ye Qiu…….” Cold Night wasn’t as excited as Jiang You.

“Ha ha, the dungeon is fixed. No matter how great Ye Qiu is, there’s a limit to how fast you can go. The record won’t be going anywhere.” Jiang You had put in a lot of effort into creating the guide and had held very high expectations for it. He was clearly a lot more confident in his guide than Cold Night was.

Cold Night saw that the guild leader’s reasoning made sense, but he was still uneasy. He wanted to ask Ye Qiu, but he also didn’t want to appear weak in front of him. Even though Ye Qiu was a great God, as someone from Tyrannical Ambition, he didn’t want to lower his head to him.

Another ten minutes passed from Tyrannical Ambition’s record. The world was still discussing it and no new record came. Ye Xiu’s group of three spent 50 minutes before finally finishing their first run. Without saying anything more, they directly went in again.

Not long after, Ye Xiu began paying attention to the messages again. If a second record was going to come, then it was about time.

Not long after, another announcement really did come out for Sin City. The new record was set by Misty Castle, time: 29:33:46.

1 second! They had only beaten Tyrannical Ambition’s record by 1 second.

Such a small difference was a bit frustrating, but it was common for this type of competition between experts. When Jiang You saw Misty Castle’s record, he wasn’t angry. On the contrary, he laughed out loud and sent Cold Night a message: “Look and you’ll know. His guide is the same.”

Misty Castle had bought the guide last time. Jiang You thought that they did the same this time, too. He hadn’t thought that Misty Castle would do the same as them and also try to create their own guide.

‘Keep trying!” Jiang You encouraged his tenth server comrades. When he thought of Misty Castle’s expense in buying the guide in order to set the record, while their Tyrannical Ambition had relied on themselves, Jiang You felt superior.

Tyrannical Ambition didn’t want to appear weak in front of Lord Grim, but Misty Castle wasn’t the same. Even though they had politely declined Lord Grim’s offer for the guide, with the new record, Hazy Mist sent Lord Grim a message: “How is it? Is this record good enough?”

“Yeah, it’s okay.” Ye Xiu replied.

“If we used your guide, how would it be?” Misty Castle asked.

“It would be better than yours.”

“Really?” Hazy Mist sent a grimaced emoticon. He was unsure if Ye Xiu was cheating him, so he used an emoticon to show his feelings.

“It’s true.” Ye Xiu replied with a sunglasses emoticon. Whether or not Hazy Mist believed him or not was all up to Hazy Mist.

“Uh……. then which guild bought your guide?” Misty Castle wasn’t believing it. If there really was a guide better than his, two records had already been made, so where was that better record?

But he didn’t need to wait for Ye Xiu to reply. An announcement quickly popped up.

Congratulations Blue Brook Guild for setting the Sin City dungeon record, time: 28:12:52.

At the same time, Ye Xiu received a new message from Blue River with two words: “Buy out!”

“Do you believe me?” Ye Xiu grinned.

“I believe you! I believe you! If the price isn’t enough, we can add more.” Blue River even asked to increase the price, showing how confident he was in the guide. The guide’s price had already been cheaper than Ye Qiu personally substituting in. The buyout price was also within Blue River’s acceptable range.

“There’s no need for that. It’ll be the same as that list I sent you in the afternoon!”

“No problem. When we get the materials, we’ll send them to you.” Blue River replied.

“Okay.”

He closed Blue River’s chat window. There were still new messages from Hazy Mist.

“Ah ah ah, is it Blue Brook Guild?”

“Sure enough, your guide really is better than ours!”

“What’s your price this time? Tell me it!”

“Hello hello hello hello? Is anyone there?”

Hazy Mist sent him four consecutive messages.

“The guides are sold out.”

“Sold out? You can sell out?” Hazy Mist quickly replied, but when he finished, he figured out the answer: “Blue Brook Guild bought it out?”

“There was once a copy for me, but I didn’t value it……” Hazy Mist left crying. Tyrannical Ambition’s Cold Night wasn’t as emotional. He had wanted to value it, but guild leader Jiang You was intent on fighting it out. Jiang You had even stopped caring about his work in the Heavenly Domain and focused on the tenth server.

When Blue Brook Guild’s record came out, Cold Night felt that things weren’t looking good. He had previously declined Ye Qiu’s guide. Should he ask him for the guide now? He didn’t want to lower his head to Ye Qiu, but he was always the one who had to do all the dirty work. Cold Night was depressed! However, he hoped that the guild leader would continue being stubborn and refuse to ask Ye Qiu for help. That way, he wouldn’t have to lose face.

Chapter 298 – Research is the Key to Efficiency

Club Tyranny. Game studio. Midnight was supposed to be these players’ time to work. But with another setback after only just a few days of happiness, quite a few instantly felt tired and gave up on tonight’s work.

Taking advantage of Jiang You’s currently heavy mood, the majority of the players escaped.

Jiang You was staring at his guide in shock.

This guide had been made with his sweat and tears. He had thought that he had created a guide at the limit. He had been full of confidence and had shown it to everyone around him.

But Blue Brook Guild’s record was like a slap to his face, so heavy that his face was red.

Cold Night was still worried whether Jiang You would tell him to ask Lord Grim for help. But at this moment, Jiang You was too embarrassed to give the order.

Complacency leads to loss. Modesty brings profit. Jiang You fully understood what this meant now. He was truly too sad.

Just what was he missing in his guide? Jiang You flipped through his document. Here was everything he had researched on Sin City’s underground prison.

He could only take the blow. As the grand guild leader, he had to be respected.

Where had he gone wrong? Jiang You anxiously thought. The more anxious he became, the messier his mind became. The messier his mind became, the harder it was to find the problem.

Don’t look for Ye Qiu and ask Blue Brook Guild? Jiang You even had this type of thought. He then thought again. Blue Brook Guild was competing with them! Why would they tell him their methods? How stupid was that? Jiang You discovered that this thought completely showed how much of a mess his mind was in.

I can only rely on myself…… Jiang You told himself. Cold Night saw that Jiang You didn’t call for him and was very happy. The two didn’t know what each other was thinking, but each of their actions complimented what the other wanted.

After Blue Brook Guild completed their buyout, Blue River let out a sigh of relief, but he didn’t relax. As an expert, he could also see that it wasn’t necessary that a top-tier God like Ye Qiu create the guide.

When they saw the guide, most of their thoughts were “Why didn’t I think of that?” If they had been the ones to create the guide, how long would it take them? Blue River didn’t know. But he did know that after breaking the record, they were in an advantageous position.

Guides could be considered as research and technical development for the dungeons. If Tyrannical Ambition and Misty Castle hadn’t set the record, then Blue River might not have bought it out. It was only after these two guilds set the record that Blue Brook Guild understood the value of the guide.

Even if it wasn’t absolute, currently, the buyout meant that they were in the lead.

In Ye Xiu’s guide, even if Blue Brook Guild tried to find places to improve, they wouldn’t be able to come up with anything new.

As for Misty Castle, they knew that there was no way they could obtain Lord Grim’s guide. With their strength, they possessed the ability to compete. But competing with the current fastest record wouldn’t be easy. The opportunity had been placed in front of them, but they hadn’t valued it. After losing it, they could only look back in regret.

As for Tyrannical Ambition, Jiang You refused to compromise and continued to research. However, from his confidence in his guide, he knew that the guide was already his limit. If he wanted to break his limit, how could it be so easy? Also, his reputation was on the line and he was too embarrassed to ask others for help. He pressed forward with brute force alone and tossed and turned, but no progress was made.

Ye Xiu was now much more carefree. After finishing the needed quests, Lord Grim was almost Level 39. And next, he was ready to research the next dungeon’s guide.

The selling of Sin City’s guide had gone by extremely smoothly. With a price that even Blue River couldn’t believe, he easily sold it out. It looked as if he could have earned more if he didn’t sell it out, but in reality that wasn’t the case. Just like how the top guilds didn’t dare look for Lord Grim to substitute in for them, buying these guides could only be known by a small portion of the guilds. It wouldn’t be good if news about it were to leak out.

If the players knew that the guilds were using his guides to set records and that the guilds weren’t doing it on their own, then it would be the same as before. The records would be meaningless and Ye Xiu would then have nothing to sell. This was why it was best that these guides were slowly being spread in private.

If he sold it openly, then if some evil guy waited for the guilds to set the records first and then let the secret out, it would be very bad. This time, when Misty Castle ran over to Ye Xiu to negotiate, even though he had guessed who the guide had been sold to, Ye Xiu never confirmed that the guide had been sold to Blue Brook Guild. The reason he did that was to guard against this.

At seven in the morning, Ye Xiu had finished his shift. The tenth server’s Sin City dungeon record stayed at that record that had been set a 1 o’clock.

After that, for the second, third, and fourth day, Blue Brook Guild, Tyrannical Ambition, and Misty Castle worked hard. Blue Brook Guild set new records, but the time difference between each of them wasn’t too great. They were all around the same time. As for Misty Castle and Tyrannical Ambition, even though they had some breakthroughs, the distance between their records and those of Blue Brook Guild were still off by a length.

From Level 20 onwards, when the fight for the dungeon records began, the fighting had always been bloody. Each dungeon had been beaten, wave after wave. But this time, the other guilds looked as if they had been completely beaten. Only Blue Brook Guild stood at the top without any competition. When the fourth day passed, the first ten places on the Sin City dungeon leaderboard were completely filled by Blue Brook Guild’s team.

And at this moment, the tenth sever’s top players were reaching Level 40.

Blue Brook Guild’s name shook far and wide in Sin City and they had learned the benefit of being the leaders in dungeon technology. At this moment, they reached Level 40 and were ready to prepare for the new dungeon’s challenge. The first thing they had to do was find Ye Xiu for a guide.

“God!” Blue River sent a respect emoticon.

“Yes?”

“We have the materials. How do we give them to you?” Blue Brook Guild finally gathered all the buyout materials from Fire Forest.

“You can just send them to me.” Ye Xiu said. The in-game mailbox could receive practically anything apart from players.

“Okay, okay. And….. uh, ha ha……. You understand.” Blue River laughed.

“Are you talking about the Thousand Wave Lake dungeon guide?”

“Of course, of course.” Blue River was somewhat nervous. He was afraid that the other side would have some unexpected reply.

When he looked again, he saw a new list of materials.

“Uh, this…… what about buying out?” Blue River looked. He recognized quite a few. They were Sin City materials. They didn’t have all the items on the list. Even though they had run Sin City several times, the problem was that there weren’t many teams running it, so they didn’t have many materials. However, when he looked at their previous experiences with Ye Qiu, Blue River felt that not having them for now shouldn’t be a problem. In any case, he trusted that the other side wouldn’t lie, so he directly asked for the buyout price.

“You want to buy it out again? This time, times ten.” Ye Xiu replied.

Chapter 299 – Big Sale

Ten times……

Honestly speaking, this wasn’t a surprising price for Blue River. After all, selling over ten copies of the guide wouldn’t be hard to do.

However, for Blue River, who had already tasted the sweetness before, he felt disappointed when he heard the price. The price was a bit too high for just a dungeon record.

Blue River had a certain understanding of Ye Xiu’s personality. He sighed, but he didn’t haggle over the price and simply replied: “Alright, give me a copy!”

“Are you buying it out?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No, no. I just want a normal copy…….” Blue River hastily said.

“Okay. I’ll send it to you right away.”

Blue River was a bit startled. Why did it suddenly feel like he had bought take out rice noodles?

As he thought of this, he opened up his mailbox and found the guide. Blue River immediately opened it and studied it. The dungeon’s science and technology had arrived. He had to hurry and understand it, before he could begin using it.

Blue Brook Guild was already working at it. Misty Castle wasn’t sitting idle. They had spent a large amount of time, but they hadn’t been able to create the most advanced guide. The dungeon competition was a fast-paced event. They had lagged behind in technology and they could no longer depend on it. As a result, after hitting Level 40, Hazy Mist also bought a guide. After buying it, he used the latest technology, while using it as a way to learn!

As for Tyrannical Ambition, Jiang You had spent four days studying the Sin City dungeon, yet he always lagged behind by one step. Who knew how many of his hairs had been pulled off. Because of the special relationship between him and Ye Xiu’s identity, Jiang You made things difficult for himself. When they reached the Level 40 domain, he hadn’t yet finished with Sin City, when the new Thousand Waves Lake dungeon had come……

As for the other guilds such as Herb Garden, they weren’t as stupid. They were all moving towards Lord Grim, asking him about the situation.

Ye Xiu remained calm and collected when he sold his guides. He didn’t let his guard down against those who inquired about other buyers’ situation. However, because there was a limit to how many high-leveled materials there were, Ye Xiu would only allow trusted guilds like Blue Brook Guild to pay these high-leveled uncommon materials at a later time. For those guilds he wasn’t familiar with, his list only contained materials that they had. First the materials, then the guides. If they didn’t have the materials, then they could substitute other materials to compensate.

In the blink of an eye, Ye Xiu sold ten copies of the Thousand Waves Lake dungeon. The ten guilds that had bought the guide began practicing. The record ever changing, making people watch them hurriedly, just like viewing flowers from horseback. When they saw their times, they all mutually understood. In order to not waste their guilds’ materials, all of the guilds practiced extra hard.

The competition for the Thousand Waves Lake dungeon was extremely intense, starting from the very first day. Tyrannical Ambition was still in a knot. How could it be so incredible? The records from these ten guilds had thrown everyone else competing aside. And their Tyrannical Ambition was among the obliterated crowd.

After a fit of teeth grinding, Jiang You finally reached terms with himself: “Forget about it. If everyone else has joined in, then what are we waiting for? Hurry and buy a copy!”

Cold Night didn’t wait any longer. When he saw that Jiang You had finally cleared his mind, he didn’t care about his honor. He directly contacted Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything more. If you want a guide, then you have to pay materials. It didn’t matter who you were.

Tyrannical Ambition took the guide and immediately began researching it. Even though they had started slower, everyone had the same guide. The deciding factor was no longer on who had the guide, but rather, the guild’s skill level. Lord Grim’s guide as the ticket to the competition was finally in operation.

Chen Yehui knew about the dungeon guide as well. No one cared as much about the tenth server records as Excellent Dynasty. He needed this dungeon guide. Because Li Hao no longer cared about the tenth server anymore, by only relying on their own guild’s strength to create a guide, they fell behind as well.

After thinking, Chen Yehui found a trusted aide who didn’t have the guild’s name to privately message Lord Grim and see if he could get a guide.

The result was beyond his expectations. This unknown character was able to add Lord Grim as a friend. After saying what he was there for, he also got a price.

The price list was sent to Chen Yehui. After looking at it, he didn’t see anything unreasonable and immediately sent the materials. When he looked at the guide, he saw that it wasn’t fake and secretly felt delighted. He felt he had played a clever trick, easily duping Ye Qiu. It made him feel quite good.

As for Ye Xiu? When he saw that an unknown player had asked to buy a guide from him, he wasn’t too surprised. He maintained his uncaring attitude and quoted the price.

Ye Xiu’s big sale had earned him quite a profit. As for who the records were set by, he didn’t care. It was still too early to see the results. He was currently paying attention to the official webpage. The new year was about to come and there would be an event soon. However, because the rewards from the Christmas event had been quite good, if things went as usual, then the New Year’s event wouldn’t be too great.

Today was the last day of the year and the day passed in the blink of an eye. The game announced a new event, which was a chain quest. Ye Xiu skimmed over the quest chain and saw that it was very complicated and was even a bit difficult. The rewards from this type of quest shouldn’t be too bad, right?

He immediately flipped to the rewards part. Ye Xiu looked and immediately felt disappointed.

Players who completed the quest would be entered into a lottery. The rewards weren’t bad, but the problem was.. the rewards were all real items!

In terms of rewards, Glory’s New Year event didn’t let players down. But to Ye Xiu, real items, whether it was a computer, mouse, monitor, cell phone, keyboard, account card, or in-game currency, held no interest for him.

At midnight, the calendar flipped to a new year.

Glory’s New Years event began. Analysts pointed out that, due to the event’s complexity and difficulty, even though it could only be done once, it might even take longer than the three days allotted to finish. The players didn’t dare be negligent. When the event began, the NPCs were flooded with players.

Ye Xiu really wasn’t interested in the rewards, but he heard that the experience from the quest chain wasn’t bad, so he also joined in.

No matter how difficult the quests were, if players like Ye Xiu couldn’t do it, then you’d have to suspect the game company’s intentions: are you planning on giving these rewards to players or not?

As a result, the quests, which the analysts had claimed would not be finished in less than three days, was finished by Ye Xiu in three hours. Soon after, he obtained his rewards: one yuan’s worth of in-game currency, making Ye Xiu seriously question whether the profits he had earned from the selling of his guides had used up all of his luck.

After finishing the quests, Ye Xiu helplessly went to continue leveling.

Ye Xiu had thought of taking advantage of the event’s quests. Should he make a guide to sell? Should he sell his services for the more difficult parts of the quest? The value of doing these were very low. There weren’t high prospects for it. Players could do it with help from their friends. Being unable to finish the quests in three days was complete nonsense.

The rewards from the New Year’s event really wasn’t bad. In these three days, there were frequently cries of joy in the Happy Internet Cafe. Some even won a computer, causing everyone to glare jealously at them.

During the event, the dungeon competition was as fierce as ever and leveling was as fast as ever. Among these, two more guilds had looked to Ye Xiu for a guide. With the materials he acquired from sales of his guide, the Thousand Chance Umbrella had been fully upgraded to Level 35.

The day the event ended, Ye Xiu did his usual. He got up and was about to go to the smoking area to play, when he was suddenly stopped by Chen Guo.

“Come with me on a trip this weekend!”

“Trip?” Ye Xiu was surprised. Even an Internet Cafe manager had to do this type of thing?

“Yeah, to City S.” Chen Guo said.

“City S?” Ye Xiu stared blankly, when he suddenly thought of something.

Chapter 300 – Three Tickets

On the first weekend of every year, the Glory Pro Alliance assembled all of the pro players and host a gathering. The gathering would have many performances, especially the All-Star Competition. 24 pros would be chosen through a fan vote. It could be said that these 24 pros were the 24 most popular players, with the largest fan bases. Because of this Glory event, the gathering was also called the All-Star Weekend.

After the great success of the first All-Star Weekend in the Glory Pro Alliance’s third season, the event came back every year with a different Club responsible for hosting it. This year, Glory’s eighth season and sixth All-Star Weekend was hosted by Club Samsara. Club Samsara was located in City S. Once Ye Xiu heard Chen Guo say that they were going to City S for the weekend, he thought of this special day and understood what was going on.

“Are we going to participate in the All-Star Weekend?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yup! I managed to get three tickets. How amazing am I?” Chen Guo exclaimed.

Even though the competitiveness during the All-Star Weekend might not be as great as a normal match, for the many fans, having the chance to watch such an exciting event was already worth the ticket price. As a result, the All-Star Weekend’s tickets were in very high demand. If you wanted to buy one, money wasn’t the only thing you needed. Luck played a huge part as well.

“Not bad, not bad.” Ye Xiu forced a smile.

All-Star Weekend…… With his status, he had been chosen as one of the 24 players every single year. Even this year, starting from when the votes started at the beginning of the season, the amount of votes he got was very high. It was only because he had retired mid-way that his name got wiped from the list.

For Ye Xiu, who didn’t want to be exposed in front of the public, the All-Star Weekend was an event that required a lot of interaction, so truthfully, it wasn’t an event he liked to participate in. The All-Star Weekend was a performance, so the competition there wasn’t very serious. The battles between two sides wouldn’t be in an enclosed area like conventional matches. The stage was set where the audience could directly see them. As a result, Ye Xiu always hid behind the stage. His computer would then be connected to the stage by a cord.

Ye Xiu was the only one who wouldn’t come up on stage. In the past, his invisibility was a part of the All-Star event and it had even turned into a type of joke. But All-Star’s Competition this time around would no longer have this part.

Ye Xiu had managed to escape from this year’s All-Star Competition with great difficulty. How could he have known that Chen Guo would buy a ticket and call him to go along. In the past, he had been a participant and this time, he would be a spectator. Thinking about this, he decided that it’d be fine and, as a result, he wouldn’t decline Chen Guo’s good intentions.

In Chen Guo’s mind, she didn’t think that anyone who played Glory would refuse this type of trip. That was why she had notified Ye Xiu. She didn’t have any intention of negotiating and didn’t notice Ye Xiu’s reluctance. She had already put in order the issue about the three not working at the Internet Cafe for the weekend.

Three tickets naturally meant three people. Ye Xiu, Chen Guo, and the other person was, of course, Tang Rou. Tang Rou already knew, though she displayed her usual boredness. She clearly wasn’t as crazy of a fan as Chen Guo was.

After Ye Xiu went online, he played for a bit and then saw that Su Mucheng’s Cleansing Mist had come online.

“I’ll be going to City S tomorrow!” Su Mucheng messaged. Considering Su Mucheng’s skill level, there was quite a dispute as to whether or not she belonged among the top 24 players. However, the invitations to the All-Star Competition weren’t chosen based on ability, but rather popularity. In this area, Su Mucheng was the favorite among Glory fans. From the very start of the event, she had been chosen as one of the 24 stars every time.

“Yeah, I’ll be going too.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ah? You’re going too? They found you?” Su Mucheng asked.

“What? Who found me?” Ye Xiu was puzzled.

“For this year’s All-Star Weekend of course. Samsara hoped that you would be able to come on stage with a special invitation, so they contacted Excellent Era. The manager even came to ask me whether I could contact you. I, however, ignored him.” Su Mucheng replied.

“Oh, not that…… I have a ticket.”

“You bought a ticket….. How thoughtful!”

“Nah, it’s my boss. She got three tickets and asked me to tag along.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, oh, as a spectator!”

“Yeah!”

“It’ll probably feel very different, right?”

“Probably?”

“I want to be a spectator too.”

“Get sick again?” Ye Xiu suggested.

“It probably won’t work this time.” Su Mucheng sent a sad face. When she skipped the team’s Christmas activity, it was obvious that being sick was just an excuse. They just didn’t bother with her. As for this All-Star event, even though it wasn’t an official competition, it was definitely an official event. Sick? You’d need proof.

“Come on.” Ye Xiu obviously understood. This type of official event was quite difficult to escape from. Ye Xiu wasn’t the only one who didn’t want to participate in the All-Star event, but everyone still went anyways.

After chatting for a bit, the two continued to play. It was just the All-Star Weekend. They had gone many times already. There was nothing extraordinarily amazing about it. It was just that Chen Guo had only watched the streams before and she didn’t have any partners before, so she was too lazy to go. Now that she had Ye Xiu and Tang Rou to accompany her, Chen Guo got three tickets and prepared to join in on the excitement.

A day passed and Friday came. In the afternoon, the three flew over to City S. They arrived at the hotel Chen Guo had booked. She and Tang Rou would be in one room. Ye Xiu was lucky and got his own room to himself.

After packing up, Chen Guo shouted at them to get ready to leave. The All-Star Weekend didn’t only last one day. It would start from eight on Friday and would last for two and a half days. Chen Guo was already unable to wait any longer. She dragged the two out the door and studied the map the entire way there. After looking at it for a long time, she still didn’t understand the directions to the event. Ye Xiu was just about to say something, when Chen Guo suddenly made a decision: call a taxi.

But this taxi driver clearly wasn’t a Glory fan. In his mind, “Club Samsara” wasn’t a landmark. After hearing her, he stopped the taxi and repeatedly asked Chen Guo to confirm that those were the correct words. He then asked, at a loss: “Do you know how to get there?”

Chen Guo coughed blood. She had called a taxi because she didn’t know where it was.

“It’s not too far from here.” Chen Guo vaguely said. It was true that it wasn’t that far. She had booked the hotel near Club Samsara.

Ye Xiu wiggled into the conversation: “Go along Changde Road and take a left at Zhaojia Bridge. Once you get past the intersection, we’ll have arrived.”

“Oh, there!” The taxi driver heard and immediately understood. He stepped on the pedals and they went on their way.

Chen Guo replied stupidly: “Where’s that?”

“Club Samsara!” Ye Xiu said.

“You’ve come here before?” Chen Guo asked, when she suddenly thought again: “Oh, I forgot. Even though you were just a small character, you still had to be a part of a team, right? Have you been to all the Clubs?”

“Yeah, yeah……” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Then why didn’t you say anything earlier!” Chen Guo said.

“I was about to…..”

Once the taxi started moving, Chen Guo stopped arguing. The taxi went with Ye Xiu’s directions and, sure enough, it really wasn’t that far away. Just as they were about to arrive , the taxi suddenly stopped. The taxi driver stuck his head out the window and looked at the traffic. He opened his mouth, stunned: “Why’s the traffic so bad?” The taxi driver couldn’t understand the reason for the traffic jam.

“See the sidewalk up ahead? You can let us off there!” Ye Xiu said.

As a result, the three got off at the sidewalk. They looked at the traffic jam. Chen Guo wasn’t unhappy, but rather, she was excited: “Wow, wow! Is this all because of the All-Star Competition? How exciting! Look!”

“Yup!” Ye Xiu obviously knew the reason. Experienced fans wouldn’t drive to the event. They’d be stuck in traffic and it was highly likely that they wouldn’t be able to find a spot to park.

“Lead the way!” Chen Guo waved her hands. After knowing that Ye Xiu knew the way, she threw her map into the trash can.

Ye Xiu looked around left and right. He led the two and they soon arrived. The entrance had already been arranged. Amidst the crowd of people, the three quickly entered Samsara’s stadium.

The eSports stadium wasn’t any smaller than a conventional stadium. The biggest difference was that the stage in the middle of the stadium had many, many, many electronic screens.

Those watching the TV and Internet broadcast could only watch as the stream chose the scenes for them. But at the actual location, everyone had their own display screen especially for them. The spectators could choose to watch from all sorts of points of view. There were also slow-motion shots for them to look at. In this type of eSports arena, besides the atmosphere, they could watch from all around, which was something that those, who watching the broadcast, didn’t have access to.

Especially in the team competition, the ten characters were all fighting at different spots on the map. How the broadcast chose the viewpoint really made the internet watchers curious. Only those at the scene could fully appreciate the competition’s brilliance.

Chapter 301 – The Show Begins

The venue for the All-Star event bustled with noise. As the main host, after finishing the Alliance’s requirements, Club Samsara obviously put in all of their efforts to show off their power. On the brochure, each of the 24 players chosen for the All-Star event had their own page. The page had a photograph, the player’s information, an introduction, and a hand-drawn picture of the player’s powerful Glory character. The production was quite good.

Who were the 24 chosen players? A fan like Chen Guo knew the answer way before the event started. Right now, she was holding the brochure. The more she flipped through it, the more excited she became, especially when she got to Su Mucheng’s page. She was so enamored that she had even forgotten to move.

Chen Guo had seen these types of All-Star brochures before. Those times, Ye Qiu would certainly be beside Su Mucheng. Except his photo would always be a shadow, making him look like an enigma. This time Excellent Era’s new core member, Sun Xiang, was next to Su Mucheng’s page.

One Autumn Leaf looked as mighty as ever, but his owner had changed.

These were the only two players that were chosen from Team Excellent Era. If the players were chosen based on the team’s performance, then it would be very hard to argue for the dismally-placed Excellent Era. Even though they were recently moving along a positive trend, it was still pretty much hopeless for them to enter the top eight. Su Mucheng’s popularity had no relationship with the team. With her popularity, even if she was never put into a match, it was very possible that her fans would push her onto the All-Stars list anyways.

As for Sun Xiang, he had only just transferred into Excellent Era mid-season. He had an extraordinary run with his previous team, Conquering Clouds. He had led the very ordinary team into the top eight. After transferring to Excellent Era, Team Over the Cloud’s performance immediately fell, while Team Excellent Era’s performance rose. This could be considered proof of his extraordinary ability. He had been titled the Most Outstanding Rookie last year. His popularity this year had clearly gone up a level.

Amidst the liveliness, the three found their seats. The event had not yet officially started. Chen Guo looked all around and seemed indescribably excited as if she had discovered something new.

They sat like this for half an hour. The spectators gradually trickled in as the official start of the event grew nearer and nearer.

At eight o’clock sharp, the music that had been playing the entire time stopped. The venue suddenly turned pitch black, as if a movie were going to be shown. Not waiting for people to cheer, a pillar of light dropped down onto the stage. In the middle of the light, a projection of a Glory character appeared. One after the other, in a circle, characters descended down onto the stage as if the they had come from the heavens. The audience immediately erupted into cheers and shouts. Chen Guo was also extremely excited. She pulled at Ye Xiu and Tang Rou, pointing at those glowing characters.

Tang Rou obviously couldn’t identify them. Ye Xiu was more familiar with them than Chen Guo, but he didn’t say anything. He only smiled as he heard Chen Guo excitedly point out every character she recognized.

“One Autumn Leaf! That’s One Autumn Leaf!! Look, look, look!!”

Amidst Chen Guo’s cries of joy, One Autumn Leaf with his Silver weapon, Evil Annihilation, descended down. This character didn’t have a life, but at this moment, it looked alive. While Chen Guo was shouting, she suddenly recalled the player behind the character that had recently retired. Her voice suddenly stopped and her expression dimmed.

However, it was only for a short moment. The character that closely followed One Autumn Leaf’s character quickly ignited Chen Guo’s spirit again. The shout she made that instant was completely unrecognizable to Ye Xiu and Tang Rou.

Dancing Rain!

The character that followed closely behind One Autumn Leaf was Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain. She heaved a cannon on her shoulder and her long hair fluttered in the wind. She clearly looked like a warm and kind-hearted girl, but she had chosen a character that used heavy artillery. Ye Xiu thought of this and couldn’t help but smile.

“What are you smiling at?” Chen Guo looked strangely at this guy’s weird smile. Then she thought of her recent excessive fangirling. The people around her had been startled by her and were now all staring at her, making her feel a bit embarrassed. Seeing Ye Xiu’s smile again, she immediately felt that he was mocking her.

“It’s nothing. Su Mucheng! Cool!!” Ye Xiu shouted, while applauding wildly, relieving Chen Guo of some of the attention. Many of the people were now staring at Ye Xiu instead of Chen Guo.

“Yeah, yeah! If you’re coming to watch it live, you have to join in with the crowd!” Chen Guo was very pleased with Ye Xiu’s attitude. She didn’t care if her fangirling was a bit excessive. She turned to look at Tang Rou: “What do you think, Little Tang?”

“I don’t know. I don’t know them……” Tang Rou shrunk back. She pretended that she didn’t know who the two people beside her were…….

“Come, come, come. I’ll introduce them to you.” Chen Guo was very enthusiastic and she began introducing the characters in the pillar of light to Tang Rou. Chen Guo knew who the 24 chosen players were long before the event started. As long as she saw the character’s class, she could pretty much guess who it was seven times out of eight. She pointed at each one and didn’t make a mistake.

Finally, 23 characters had been shown. For the final character, the character’s descent was slightly slower. By stopping and moving repeatedly, the action beautifully created a feeling of anticipation. It made it seem as if the 23 characters prior had been little soldiers opening the way for the great general to arrive.

Club Samsara had taken advantage of their powers as the host to have this 24th character be the last one to come out. This character was obviously their Samsara’s trump card, Zhou Zekai’s character, known as the Great Gunner: Cloud Piercer.

Even though Chen Guo was a fan of Excellent Era, she didn’t have any ill will towards Zhou Zekai’s character and applauded. However, since this was Samsara’s home grounds, Samsara clearly had more fans here. Cloud Piercer appeared majestically on stage. The applause and cheers from the audience were simply deafening. The people who had turned their heads to glare at Chen Guo and Ye Xiu had lost their own poise and were clearly Samsara fans.

Apart from the audience’s reactions, there was no other noise. As Cloud Piercer descended, the pillar of light flickered into 24 pillars. The pillars flashed in an alternating manner, shining on all 24 All-Star characters.

The audience’s cheers grew even livelier. Then, the 24 characters, which had been quietly standing there, suddenly sprang into action.

Dashing, attacking, dodging, jumping…….

The 24 characters displayed all sorts of movements. The audience erupted into another wave of cheers. The projections looked as if real people were moving around in a cosplay act.

After they all performed a set of movements, the pillar of light suddenly dimmed, leaving the audience in darkness again. The audience’s cheers also calmed as the stadium darkened. Everyone was waiting for the next part of the show.

A pillar of light…… a pillar of light once again dropped down, shining on a single character. This was the first character that had descended down. The leader of last year’s Champions. Team Tiny Herb Captain Wang Jiexi’s Magician: Vaccaria.

The audience wondered if the character was going to do something again. Then, they watched as Vaccaria hopped onto his broom and flew into the air. Vaccaria turned his head in mid-air and lifted up his arms. The pillar of light followed as he flew and the audience focused their attention onto the red potion bottle in his hands. Players who were familiar with the Witch class would recognize this Witch skill: Lava Flask.

“Shatter…..”

In the absolutely silent stadium, the breaking of the Lava Flask could clearly be heard. It was exactly the same as in the game. Following the shatter was an explosion. Lava burst forth from the flask onto the stage. The flames burned and surged.

As the audience watched, stunned, Vaccaria lifted his hands again. A white fog-like item was thrown into the air. Puffs of clouds formed and blue rain poured down. The audience immediately recognized this as another Witch skill: Acid Rain.

Then, Vaccaria revealed a few more skills. The visual effects were exactly the same as in the game. The stunned audience only now realized that these visual effects were only projections. In that instant of realization, shouts and cheers erupted across the stadium. Vaccaria’s pillar of light faded away and the darkness returned. The second character followed with another display of skills.

After each of the 24 characters performed, the audience awaited the next scene.

The previous performance had been done individually. If all of the projections began shooting out their skills and engaging in battle, what would the scene be like then?

The host didn’t disappoint. After the individual performances, they immediately began the battles.

1v1, 2v2…… even a 12v12 fight!

The skills from the various characters mixed into a flurry of colors. The Silver weapons in each of the God-level characters’ hands glittered like gems.

The scene in front of the audience’s eyes was no longer as if they were in the game, but rather a movie. It looked as if each and every character was standing in front of them. It was much more vivid than looking at the game. As for the chaotic battle, no one noticed the skills that were being used. They had been entranced by the splendid visual effects. They hoped that it would never end……

However, since these 24 characters represented the 24 All-Star players, they couldn’t show a winner or a loser. After enjoying the on-stage effects, Samsara’s trump card, Cloud Piercer, suddenly jumped into the air and flew towards the top of the stadium. The other characters ascended like stars as if they were chasing after him. The 24 characters flew up to the top and then exploded with a bang, like fireworks. The audience stuck out their hands to touch the lights, only to confirm that the projections truly weren’t real.

Soon after, the lights on the stadium lit up. The large screens hanging in the air broadcasted the images of real fireworks that had been shot into the air above the stadium. The host’s voice boomed: “This year’s All-Star Weekend has officially begun!”

Chapter 302 – Rookie Challenge Competition

The audience had their spirits excited by the opening. The fireworks that were going on outside, the commentator’s commentary, and the highlight reel from the past year felt somewhat lacking comparatively. The audience still hoped that it would continue. Even if the opening repeated itself, they still felt that it would at least be more exciting than the current program.

Amazing! Beautiful!

This was the impression that the audience received from the opening. But for professionals like Ye Xiu, the stunning opening was no more than just that. What he wanted to know was whether those characters’ movements had been planned beforehand or whether they were being controlled at the scene.

If it was the latter, then this opening would be the mark of a new era. Utilizing projection technology to display Glory’s matches —- if that concept had truly became a reality, then the audience would be able to see projections of the map, as well as the characters. The scene from the matches could then be shown to the audience. At that moment, not only the audience, but also the players themselves would feel as if it were real.

The scene! This was what it meant to be at the scene!

While the audience was entranced by the opening, Ye Xiu had quickly thought about all of this. Such a change would affect the business more. With the development of the business, more attention would naturally come. This would then, in turn, attract more people to Glory’s eSports scene and increase the competitiveness of it. It would indirectly push the game forward.

The use of this technology would become an important milestone in Glory. Even though Ye Xiu couldn’t be certain, using it in the opening of the All-Star Competition was already an indicator. Or perhaps the Alliance was doing it to test the technology. The All-Star Competition wasn’t an official match, but it would attract a lot of attention. There wasn’t a more suitable place to publicly test it out.

Would they still continue to test the new technology? Ye Xiu couldn’t be more familiar with the All-Star Competition’s layout. On the first day, after the opening, the first event would be the Rookie Challenge Competition.

The participants for the Rookie Challenge Competition didn’t need to be chosen. As long as you hadn’t been a pro for at two full years, you had the qualifications to sign up. Afterwards, you would then be allowed to freely choose from non-rookie players and 1v1 them. The two parties usually wouldn’t use their own accounts, but rather they would use two equally strong characters provided by the host to fight. This was clearly done to take care of the rookies. If they had used their own accounts, then the majority of the rookies wouldn’t compare to the veterans’ characters. As a result, by equalizing the characters the two parties used, they would both fight on equal grounds.

Since the rookies signed up on their own, their information wouldn’t be announced to the public. As a result, every year during the All-Stars Weekend, guessing which rookies would participate was a huge part of the fun for the audience. The rookies’ popularity definitely wouldn’t be able to compare to the Gods’, but for Glory fans, as long as they were on the host’s team, any of the team members would attract a huge amount of attention to them. Even more so, there were a few rookies whose names were quite renowned.

This time’s Rookie Challenge Competition had quite a few rookies the fans were looking forward to, so everyone was filled with anticipation towards this Challenge Competition.

At this moment, the host, who was only heard but not seen, finally announced the first participant in the Rookie Challenge Competition: Team Thunderclap, Dai Yanqi.

When the name was announced, the applause from the audience wasn’t too crazy, but it wasn’t too quiet either. Dai Yanqi wasn’t considered outstanding by any means among the rookies. If something had to be said about Dai Yanqi, then it’d have to be that she was a female player. For female players, fans always harbored a different type of anticipation and attention. That was why, when compared to the others at the same skill level, they received a bit more attention.

The age of the rookies usually weren’t very high. Dai Yanqi was only 17 years old. However, she was quite outgoing and wasn’t afraid of going up on stage. As she walked on stage and became the focal point, she waved her hands to everyone and then announced in a loud voice who she would challenge: Chu Yunxiu.

“Sister Chu has always been an idol for us girls. I respect her a lot. I’m using this opportunity to challenge Sister Chu and I hope i’ll be able to receive her instruction.” Dai Yanqi’s issue of challenge had been filled with reverence. She clearly wanted this battle to be a chance for her to greet her respected senior. Whether she lost or not wasn’t important. The audience clearly wasn’t too excited about this match and only gave her an applause as a sign of courtesy. And at this moment, Chu Yunxiu entered the stage from the players’ seats.

Players who had been called could not refuse the challenge, even if they had fought consecutively. And in the history of the event, the most tragic participant was Ye Xiu. At his very first All-Stars Competition, he was the rookies’ most respected player, as well as their opponent whom they most wanted to try and beat. That year, all seven rookies who had participated in the Rookie Competition had chosen Ye Qiu. The final participant that went up no longer had a good reason to fight him and just simply said “Same”. Ye Xiu had also created a record for “The Player to be Called Out the Most in the Rookie Challenge Competition”. Whether it was in a single competition or the total times overall, he was the champion…….

Chu Yunxiu was also someone who had seen the stage before. After going up on stage, she naturally said a few warm words to her junior. The two then chose their classes, took the character accounts provided by the host and headed to the competition stage.

The two walked in opposite directions. As they walked farther and farther from each other, the audience finally noticed that in this year’s All-Star Competition, the competition stage wasn’t set in the middle, but rather on opposite corners of the stadium.

The audience felt a bit uncertain because of this, but Ye Xiu had noticed something.

As the two walked to the competition stage, the display screen above the stage began to show the match interface. The entire stadium’s lights dimmed. As the match was being set up, the empty space in the middle of the stadium began to glow. Not long after, along with the audience’s shouts of astonishment, the map chosen by Dai Yanqi appeared in front of everyone’s eyes.

When the match began, the two characters emerged onto the two ends of the map. The audience had finally realized what was going to happen.

In order to fit the entire map onto the stage, the projection couldn’t be shown at a 1:1 scale; it had to be shown on a different scale. The two characters would naturally be affected and their characters were smaller than the ones in the opening scene.

Because of this, some of the details couldn’t be seen clearly. The surrounding display screens played like they had in the past. However, at this moment, everyone’s attention fell on the unclear projection.

“This this…….. Is too amazing!!” Chen Guo said, stunned. Her reaction was the same as the audience’s.

The conjecture Ye Xiu had made earlier had been verified and he understood that this was a new age for Glory. However, it looked like the scaling seemed to be a big issue. The scaling was too small and couldn’t be seen clearly. It didn’t seem likely like it could replace the display screens, though this issue would most definitely be solved sooner or later.

While the audience was still astonished by this, Chu Yunxiu and Dai Yanqi had already met. They hadn’t chosen to do any sort of special movement and simply met with each other in the middle of the stage in the fastest way. Afterwards, the two politely asked whether the other side was ready in the chat box and they began to fight.

By looking at both the display screens and the projection, they discovered that the projection synchronized perfectly. No one cared at this moment who would win or lose. They had been completely captivated by the new competition display. As they watched the two characters go back and forth, everyone had already forgotten their names.

In the end, the match ended without too much suspense. Chu Yunxiu easily beat Dai Yanqi. The two then, once again, politely gave their respects and the match ended.

The applause afterwards and the quality of the match was quite an illusion. Even Chu Yunxiu and Dai Yanqi themselves knew quite well that the majority of the applause wasn’t towards them, but rather it was towards the new technology that allowed them to feel a new experience.

The projection disappeared and the stadium lit up once again. The fans continued to discuss the new display, while the host announced the second rookie to come up on stage: Team Tiny Herb’s Gao Yingjie.

The applause was deafening!

This applause this time was the real deal. Gao Yingjie’s recognition as a genius, whether or not it had been pushed forward by Tiny Herb, had always been well known in the Glory scene. He had already been designated as the player who would inherit Vaccaria and, up until now, he hadn’t appeared in an official match. Just how good was this genius? Glory’s fans had been curious about this since long ago and now they finally had the chance to see it.

Gao Yingjie also walked around the stadium in a circle and said a few words. But compared to the girl Dai Yanqi, he was much more modest. With his head lowered, and both his hands and feet stiff, he walked onto the stage. He quickly raised his head, waved them around, and said a simple, “Hi everyone. My name is Gao Yinjie.” His voice went from loud to soft. His last three words were said so quietly that he himself might not have been able to hear them.

At the seats for the pro players, Tiny Herb’s members were quietly shaking their heads. If Gao Yingjie had decided this on his own, then he definitely wouldn’t have signed up for the match. The reason that he had signed up was because Wang Jiexi had acted in place of him and signed him up. This child truly needed some discipline.

“The player who I want to challenge is our Tiny Herb team captain, Wang Jiexi.” Gao Yingjie’s voice was as soft as ever. However, at least Wang Jiexi’s name had been said. The reason for his challenge was even softer than the noise made by a mosquito. The host once again reminded him to speak a bit louder through his earpiece, but it proved to be no use.

Helpless, and not waiting for the child to finish, Wang Jiexi came up on stage to rescue him. The God was naturally able to control the stage and, after quickly saying a few simple words, the two players sat at their respective seats amidst the audience’s applause.

The lights dimmed and the projection once again appeared after the map was chosen. Both players chose the Witch class and their characters appeared at opposite ends of the map.

Chapter 303 – Intentional

Even though they were players who played the same class, the skills they were used to using and their equipment styles might not have been the same. This was why the hosts provided players with Level 70 Blank accounts. Their skill points hadn’t been added yet and their equipment could be chosen freely. Of course, they didn’t have Silver equipment though. They were using all common equipment from the game. Since the All-Star Event was in cooperation with Glory’s gaming company, the required accounts and equipment needed for the All-Star Event weren’t lacking.

Wang Jiexi and Gao Yingjie’s Witches entered the stage. Their skill points and equipment had be chosen. Gao Yingjie was the player who was going to inherit Wang Jiexi’s Vaccaria, so in terms of skills they chose and their equipment choices, the two weren’t too different from each other. At this moment, the two Witches were headed towards the middle of the stage. It was practically impossible to see who had moved first.

Similar to the last match, the two directly dashed towards the middle. As players from the same team, they knew about this battle beforehand, which was why they hadn’t said any greetings or anything at all before the match began, like Dai Yanqi and Chu Yunxiu had done. The two Witches on their brooms gradually flew closer and closer to each other. The first to act was actually Gao Yingjie as he raised his hands and sent a Magic Missile towards Wang Jiexi’s character.

This match would truly be a beautiful fight.

In comparison, the audience had placed most of their attention onto the projection’s visual effects in the prior match. This time around, the audience had been pulled back to the main theme through Gao Yinjie and Wang Jiexi’s brilliant fighting. The projection’s true effects had returned to its original purpose. It complemented the performance instead of surpassing the match’s beauty.

The two Witches danced around the map like butterflies. Lava, acid, and traces of their skills laid everywhere. All sorts of magic items had been thrown onto the ground. Let alone the projection, but even with only the broadcasted scenes, the match was already astonishing enough. It could be seen from just how many times the commentator wowed. Because this was a one on one match, the two sides’ tempo was truly too fast. By the time the commentators finished explaining an exchange of blows, the two sides had already moved on and exchanged who knew how many more blows by then. How could the audience care to pay attention to the commentators’ sputter. In the end, the commentators decided that it’d be best to just keep quiet.

“Is this match for real……”

At the pro players’ seats, quite a few had already started discussing the match. Apart from Tiny Herb, all of the other teams were greatly surprised. Not only players from the same team, but even players from different teams rarely fought so seriously at an All-Stars event.

Simply speaking, this was only a show planned by the Alliance. It was said to be a Rookie Challenge, but in reality, very few rookies would refuse to allow the old generals to leave the stage with their heads held high. There also weren’t any old generals who would go all out against a rookie. For example, Dai Yanqi and Chu Yunxiu’s battle was a perfect example. Everyone politely did their act and that was it. Currying a senior person’s favor may not be something rookies understood, but there were always people who would remind them.

But in Gao Yingjie and Wang Jiexi’s match, since both of the players were from the same team, the two unexpectedly fought so seriously and intensely. For the senior, if the senior won too hard, it would feel as if the big were bullying the small. But if the senior lost, then that’d be even more embarrassing. And as for the rookie? The rookie didn’t have a lot of experience in the Alliance. If the rookie refused to let the senior leave the stage with his pride intact, then later on, if he were met with a revenge attack, then his development would certainly take a hit. Right now, Gao Yingjie’s opponent was his team captain. If the team captain were truly offended, then Gao Yingjie’s position within the team would be perilous.

All of the pro players were discussing this and glancing over at Team Tiny Herb’s members, but all they saw was that Tiny Herb’s members looked on as if this was very normal. Those who were familiar with Tiny Herb’s team members moved closer to ask what exactly was going on but nothing came out of it. Tiny Herb’s atmosphere seemed to be frozen.

As the audience cheered and yelled, the battle grew even more intense. Originally, the two had been fighting at the center of the map but now they had shifted to a corner. The two sides’ health bars were about the same, but by looking at their characters’ advances and retreats, the one at a disadvantage was unexpectedly Wang Jiexi. It looked as if Gao Yingjie’s Witch was chasing and attacking, while Wang Jiexi was defending and retreating.

Gao Yingjie was called a genius, but since he had never gone on stage, no one knew how good he actually was. Previously, when the genius shyly climbed up onto the stage, quite a few had laughed in their hearts. But who would have thought that when the match started, after taking his character, he would immediately turn out to be so fierce. They watched the high-level battle and saw that Wang Jiexi was actually the player who was being suppressed. Everyone’s impression of him had immediately changed.

Team Blue Rain had once stolen the food from the tiger, taking away Team Tiny Herb’s Championship title once and ruining Tiny Herb’s chances at being consecutive Champions. The relationship between the two were like fire and water.

Team Tiny Herb having such a talent wasn’t good news for Blue Rain. The team members were turning their heads to talk in each other’s ears about this Gao Yingjie.

“What do you think?” Team captain Yu Wenzhou continued to watch the match. His head didn’t turn as he asked Huang Shaotian.

“The little kid’s playing is extremely quick. He might even be above Wang Jiexi and is using it to pressure him. But because it’s so quick, openings sometimes appear. But these openings are only for an instant and are very difficult to catch. I think he knows about these short, temporary openings but he just doesn’t care and lets them be in order to increase his speed even further. As a rookie, how could he know to do this? Wang Jiexi definitely taught him. Why does it seem more and more like the kid was specially taught to deal with me?” Huang Shaotian chattered a whole bunch.

“And Wang Jiexi?” Yu Wenzhou naturally filtered out all the rubbish in what Huang Shaotian said and only paid attention to the important parts.

“His fame’s about to get destroyed. I can’t wait to call and congratulate him. Where’s my phone…..” Huang Shaotian began to search around.

Just as he said this, the audience gasped in astonishment. The two characters each fired a violently strong attack towards each other. Neither side benefited and the two were blown away, flying. Soon after, they immediately grabbed their brooms and flew into the sky to fight in a flurry once again.

The two characters had been fighting for a while and their health bars had been dropping the entire time. In the beginning, it was hard to see who had more or less health. But at this moment, without much health left, it was clear who had the advantage.

The player who was unexpectedly losing was Wang Jiexi! In this match, the rookie Gao Yingjie was unexpectedly winning and was about to send out the final blow to his team captain.

Gao Yingjie was still a rookie after all and hadn’t gotten any spotlight in an official match. Even though he was known as a genius, his popularity couldn’t compare with Wang Jiexi’s. In this match, in terms of emotions, Wang Jiexi had way more supporters. Those who wanted to see Gao Yingjie win were only those that wanted to see an upset or perhaps they just didn’t like Wang Jiexi. After seeing Wang Jiexi losing, the entire crowd’s atmosphere had become restrained.

“This kid…… is pretty amazing…….” Chen Guo said to Ye Xiu and Tang Rou. She didn’t care about Wang Jiexi or Gao Yingjie and didn’t want to see an upset. She had come to purely enjoy the show.

Tang Rou couldn’t help but glance at Ye Xiu and saw Ye Xiu let out a sigh.

“Wang Jiexi shouldn’t lose to him.” Yu Wenzhou suddenly said on Team Blue Rain’s side.

“Yeah, this kid’s too outrageous. No rookie in our team would dare to act like that. He’d be put on clean-up duty for a month, no two months! Uh……. maybe three months. Yeah, three months sounds about right.” Huang Shaotian said.

Automatically filtering out Huang Shaotian’s nonsense, Yu Wenzhou continued to pay attention to the scene: “Wang Jiexi didn’t add all of his points.”

“What?” Huang Shaotian heard this and was startled.

Yu Wenzhou’s mechanics greatly limited his ability, but in terms of game knowledge, Yu Wenzhou was undoubtedly among the top. The issue of Wang Jiexi’s Witch not adding all of his points was something that Huang Shaotian hadn’t noticed. He had been paying more attention to the openings when the two fought. He hadn’t really noticed something so minute.

“As a result, the damage from his skills were slightly lower. In such a blow for blow exchange, the minute differences add up.” Yu Wenzhou said.

“So you’re saying.. that he intentionally lost to the kid?” Huang Shaotian said.

“Seems like it and it looks like he doesn’t want anyone to find out……”

“Does he have to support him so carefully?” Huang Shaotian whispered.

“It’s different for everybody…… some people rise up after being beaten badly. Some people needs this type of victory for confidence. We don’t need this child well. Wang Jiexi must have his reasons for doing this.” Yu Wenzhou plainly said.

“Then, how can we let him succeed? Let’s hurry up and expose him.” Huang Shaotian said.

“Let’s be nicer! In order to help him, Wang Jiexi has already sacrificed a lot. Plus, it’s risky. If we expose them, the opposite result might happen. The difference in skill levels definitely won’t be large. It looks like only two skills are a level lower, that’s all. To make the match so close is also intentional!” Yu Wenzhou sighed.

Huang Shaotian didn’t say a whole bunch after hearing this. He finally said after a short pause: “How confident. Did he not think we’d see through him?”

Yu Wenzhou only chuckled. He then turned his head to ask: “Did Ye Qiu come?”

“How would I know!” Huang Shaotian said. He also turned his head, except he did it towards Excellent Era’s side, towards the beautiful girl there. He pinched the two fingers on his right hand together and put it in his mouth, letting out two shameless whistles.

Excellent Era’s players looked over. However, the girl only tugged on her neck collar and then turned her head in the opposite direction.

“D*mnit , that f*king girl!!” Huang Shaotian was extremely depressed.

Yu Wenzhou looked at him and laughed helplessly. He saw that Excellent Era’s players were all looking towards them. He waved his hand and greeted them. Excellent Era’s players waved their hands back, confused.

Chapter 304 – Shouldering the Future of Tiny Herb

“Wang Jiexi’s has already done what he can for him. Whether or not it works will depend on the child.” After waving his hands towards Excellent Era’s players, Yu Wenzhou turned his head to continue speaking.

Huang Shaotian understood what he meant. Wang Jiexi would let him win, but not by too much. He had to rely on fighting with two less skill points and then show his weakness after an intense fight. If Gao Yingjie made a mistake, then Wang Jiexi couldn’t let the opening go and would ensure his victory. Even though Wang Jiexi was letting him win, if he wanted to win, he still had to perform well.

Would Gao Yingjie make a mistake?

The two who knew the truth about these two competitors were already thinking about this. Amongst the audience, these two weren’t the only ones to harbor these thoughts.

Ye Xiu!

Yu Wenzhou hadn’t asked about him for no reason. He asked because he was certain that Ye Xiu was well aware of this.

The amateurs watched the excitement, while the experts looked for the truth.

Very few experts were able to see the truth in this match.

“Shatter!” Another Lava Flask broke and a large piece of land was eroded away by the magic item, turning the area into a field of burning lava.

“Oh…….” And at the same time, two people at two different seats of the stadium let out a sigh. One of the sighs came from the audience, while the other came from the pro players’ seats. And in the pro players’ seats, many had come to a conclusion from their discussions: Wang Jiexi was going to lose.

At this moment, Wang Jiexi’s Witch had already retreated to the corner of the map and had no place left to run. The Lava Flask had been thrown down by Gao Yingjie’s Witch and the field of lava burned Wang Jiexi’s character. With no place left to run and under attack from a Witch’s AoE damage skill, there wasn’t much he could do to come back.

Wang Jiexi’s Witch suddenly flew up and tried to escape out of the corner, but his student Gao Yingjie had seen through his intent. He flew over to block him and threw down an Acid Rain. He swept his broom and engaged in combat once again with Wang Jiexi’s character.

The consecutive damage and battles had already made it so that Wang Jiexi’s Witch no longer had any room to use any skills. The deadlock had been broken and Wang Jiexi was completely at a disadvantage. His character only had a few health points left and he clearly had no way of escaping this predicament.

Wang Jiexi never stopped trying however, but it was to no avail. His Witch was swept down by Gao Yingjie’s character and never stood up again.

The entire stadium gasped in astonishment and then was dead silent. After a short moment, people began clapping here and there. The few claps spurred more claps and the noise grew louder and louder. Even though the end result was very different from what the majority of the audience wanted, they couldn’t deny that it had been a splendid match.

Amidst the applause, two figures had even stood up.

Yu Wenzhou in the pro players’ area.

Ye Xiu in the audience.

In their eyes, the brilliance didn’t come from the match, but rather, from Wang Jiexi’s sacrifices.

By not fully adding in his points, he wrote the plot for the match and the momentum of the battle. Everything had been completely engineered by him. The worry that Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian had over whether Gao Yingjie would make an error had been taken into account by Wang Jiexi long beforehand.

When was it most likely that Gao Yingjie would make a mistake? Of course, it would be at the end of the battle. Once he became aware of the fact that he was about to strike down a God-like player in the Alliance, who was also his respected team captain, the timid and shy child would definitely become shaken. For him, it truly was a difficult obstacle to overcome.

However, Wang Jiexi had anticipated this. At the ending parts of the battle, he had his character retreat into a corner. Attacking an opponent in a corner was the most fundamental method of attack for a Witch. Let alone Gao Yingjie, no pro player that played a Witch would make any mistakes in that type of situation. Even though Gao Yingjie’s heart had been shaken, being placed in such an easy and practiced scenario was enough to help him overcome the obstacle. As a result, he obtained the victory.

Yu Wenzhou hadn’t seen everything, though.

Wang Jiexi had done even more than he had analyzed. He had even chosen the routes he would take to reduce the probability of Gao Yingjie making a mistake. This was something that he had been doing all the way till the end. Yu Wenzhou and Ye Xiu, who had figured out Wang Jiexi’s intent long ago, had only recently become aware of this when Gao Yingjie threw down his Lava Flask.

This Tiny Herb team captain truly did his utmost to ensure Gao Yingjie’s victory. He had succeeded and his brilliant sacrifice had won the two Gods’ sincere applause.

“What a brilliant match!” Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo.

Chen Guo was also applauding, but she couldn’t quite understand why Ye Xiu would suddenly stand up like that. She had originally believed that it was because her ability to appreciate the match wasn’t good enough and that she wasn’t able to see just how brilliant the match was. But when she looked around, she saw that among the audience, besides Ye Xiu, no one else had jumped up so enthusiastically. Many of the people surrounding them were already giving him gazes of doubt as if they were looking at a noob.

“Brilliant, brilliant! It sure was brilliant. Hurry up and sit down!” Chen Guo said while pulling on Ye Xiu.

But Ye Xiu unexpectedly stayed standing and refused to sit down. Chen Guo pulled down twice, but he just wouldn’t budge. Helpless, all she could do was to sit sideways, learning from Tang Rou, and using the “I don’t know him” technique.

On stage, Wang Jiexi and Gao Yingjie had already left their playing platforms.

Gao Yingjie had returned to his shy look, walking out with his head lowered. The surrounding applause made him feel as if he were in a dream. What just happened? He couldn’t believe it. It seemed like he beat his captain? And in front of so many people, too?

He had been told to sign up for the All-Stars Challenge by his captain and challenging his captain was also his captain’s idea. Being in a match, where victory or defeat wasn’t important, and wanting to feeling the stadium’s atmosphere, was something Gao Yingjie felt he should experience. That was why he had agreed to the captain’s orders.

And then, the team captain required that he had to pretend that he was playing in the finals and had to go all out. Gao Yingjie did as he instructed, but to have actually beat his team captain was something he would have never imagined.

The victory had made Gao Yingjie somewhat surprised, somewhat scared, but also somewhat happy.

When he walked to the middle of the stadium and faced his team captain, Wang Jiexi, the feeling of fear took over Gao Yingjie. He had heard of the unwritten rules of the Rookie Competition from his seniors before. But his captain had told him to go all out, so he went all out, because, in his heart, he felt that going all out wasn’t going to result in anything anyways. He felt like he didn’t even have a one in a millionth chance of beating his team captain.

But he had done it and now that he was standing in front of his team captain though, thoughts of what his seniors had told him of what not to do flooded into his mind. He immediately felt like he had let his captain down. In a stadium where millions of people were watching, to have beat his captain, this, this, this……..

Gao Yingjie’s head drooped lower and lower. He was the winner, but his heart was filled with guilt and he didn’t want to meet with anyone.

Suddenly, his left hand was grabbed. He immediately looked and saw that he was holding his captain’s right hand. And then, he watched as his left hand was raised high up into the air, along with applause from all around the stadium. The instant his hand went up, the applause seemed to have become louder.

“You played very well.” Wang Jiexi said.

Gao Yingjie was somewhat astonished because there seemed to be a trace of a smile on the captain’s face.

“You’re going to be the one to shoulder Tiny Herb’s future! Yingjie.” Gao Yingjie heard the captain say this to him. In that instant, his surroundings seemed to have turned silent. He saw the captain let go of his hand and slowly walk off the stage. When he regained his composure, he was already the only one on stage with his arm up in the air, receiving the applause from all around the stadium…….

“Do you think Wang Jiexi is mad? To be beaten so embarrassingly by some little kid in his own team?” Chen Guo whispered when she saw Wang Jiexi leave Gao Yingjie alone on stage. When Ye Xiu heard this, he just smiled. The less people knew about Wang Jiexi’s motive, the better.

The second match of the Rookie Challenge ended and Gao Yingjie left the stage soon after. However, the news of Tiny Herb’s genius beating his team captain, Wang Jiexi, had already become the headline story. In their eyes, there was nothing more worth seeing in the Rookie Challenge Competition. Right now, the reporters were trying their hardest to get an interview.

But the Rookie Challenge Competition wouldn’t stop because of this unusual occurrence. After Gain Yingjie left the stage, the host announced the next challenger.

Tiny Herb team member, Qiao Yifan.

The audience was in an uproar. The challenger was a completely unknown player. Not just them, but even in the pro-circle, they were all whispering in each other’s ears to find out who this person was. “Who is this? Who is this?” Chen Guo was also unsure. Tang Rou quietly looked at Ye Xiu and all she saw was a completely calm face.

A youth stood up from Tiny Herb’s seats. Amidst his team’s indifferent gazes, he walked onto the stage.

The whispering didn’t stop, but the host continued to follow the program.

“Qiao Yifan wishes to challenge the owner of the number one Phantom Demon, Sobbing Ghost, Team Void Captain, Li Xuan!”

This time, the audience and the pro players weren’t too surprised. The targets in the Rookie Challenge were usually these types of ace players. However, Qiao Yifan’s own Team Tiny Herb, on the other hand, was in an uproar.

Chapter 305 – Exceeding Everyone’s Expectations

The Rookie Challenge Competition was completely up to the rookie. Signing up didn’t have to be done through the Club or the Team. However, rookies usually gave their Team a heads up beforehand. Clubs would sometimes publicize their rookies and would also sometimes ask their rookies to sign up.

Qiao Yifan obviously didn’t belong to the latter. With a genius like Gao Yingjie, if the Club was going to publicize a rookie, it most certainly wouldn’t be him. Participating in the Rookie Challenge Competition was Qiao Yifan’s own idea. He had given the Club a heads up, but everyone was just surprised, that’s all.

For someone like him to participate in the Rookie Challenge Competition, he was somewhat overestimating his abilities. This was what everyone was thinking about and it was something Qiao Yifan had thought about too, but it hadn’t changed his decision. It was just when the news got to the captain, he still felt somewhat uneasy. If the captain didn’t support his decision and he was still going to be stubborn about it, then even though the rules said that no one could stop him, his future in the Club might be gone.

However, aside from the Rookie Challenge Competition, there was no other chance for Qiao Yifan to appear on stage. This was his only chance and he hoped that he’d be able to seize it.

He had succeeded!

Team Captain Wang Jiexi didn’t have any objections to his decision and he wasn’t treated coldly, like how the other team members treated him. Wang Jiexi simply gave him the attitude a team captain should have by giving him a few words of encouragement and hoping that he would perform well and learn.

“I will!” Qiao Yifan was very excited. Afterwards, he prepared for this day the entire time. No other person cared so much about the Rookie Challenge as much as he did because he knew that it was just for “show”. Qiao Yifan also understood this, but he hoped that he’d be able to “show” something different in this “show” in order to win a turning point in his career.

Qiao Yifan versus the number one Phantom Demon, Li Xuan.

The host announced the contestants. The players and the audience responded normally. A few of them were excited, and they were mostly Li Xuan’s fans.

They didn’t know what was so astonishing about this match, but Tiny Herb’s players knew.

They knew because Qiao Yifan played as an Assassin, but he chose to challenge a Phantom Demon, Li Xuan. It was somewhat unheard of.

The rookie had complete control over his decision and he also had his reasons. Usually, rookies would choose to challenge seniors they liked in the Alliance, which was why it was very common that players who played the same class fought in the Rookie Challenge. Outsiders would only think this type of reasoning when Qiao Yifan chose to fight Li Xuan, but to the more familiar players of Tiny Herb, they had no idea what the reason was for Qiao Yifan decision.

After Qiao Yifan went up on stage, he said some common words on how he wanted to learn from his senior, which made Tiny Herb’s players even more puzzled.

“The kid likes Li Xuan?”

“No idea!”

They were completely at a loss. And only now did they discover that they knew very little about their younger teammate. They all looked towards Gao Yingjie. Qiao Yifan and Gao Yingjie had a very good relationship with each other. This was perhaps the only thing they knew about Qiao Yifan’s situation and the reason for this was because of Gao Yingjie’s existence.

Gao Yingjie was also at a loss, perhaps even more puzzled than his seniors. This was because he understood Qiao Yifan well, but he couldn’t understand why he would challenge Li Xuan…… He recalled how Qiao Yifan was always very busy, how he was often alone, and how they hadn’t been talking much lately. Gao Yingjie felt like something had happened.

Li Xuan had already walked on stage. As an ace and a God with the status of a team captain, his bearing was much greater than Qiao Yifan’s. After going up on stage, he said a few kind words to his younger generation and then the two walked to their competition platforms.

From the audience’s perspective, this match would be the same as the first one. Only Tiny Herb’s players felt that it was unordinary. On the other hand, Ye Xiu completely guessed Qiao Yifan’s intent, but…….

“Sigh……” Ye Xiu let out another gentle sigh, which had coincidentally been seen by Tang Rou again.

Another sigh? Tang Rou muttered in her heart. In the last match, she had seen Ye Xiu sigh, but she hadn’t seen anything worth sighing for in that match. And in this match, he sighed once again. Qiao Yifan……. Tang Rou obviously recognized him as the one who played with them as One Inch Ash because when they partied together, he didn’t hide his name. Then did Ye Xiu’s sigh mean that Qiao Yifan couldn’t win?

Tang Rou was a new Glory player through and through. Chen Guo knew that the All-Star Weekend was more for show than it was for competition, especially the Challenge Competition. However, she hadn’t thought of explaining this to Tang Rou, who thought it was a serious competition. At this moment, since she knew the player, she was hoping for the youth to win. But Ye Xiu’s sigh made her aware that her hopes would probably fall through.

The map had already appeared on stage. The two players chose their characters, added their points, and then chose their equipment. Soon afterwards, they entered the match.

Li Xuan choosing a Ghostblade wasn’t a surprise to anyone.

Qiao Yifan choosing the same Ghostblade wasn’t a surprise to anyone except for Tiny Herb’s players.

“What’s the kid doing?” Everyone was puzzled again.

“He’s going too far.” Tiny Herb’s teammate Xiao Yun said.

“Luckily no one knows that he doesn’t actually play Ghostblade, right?” The female team member Liu Fei said.

The Rookie Challenge was more of a show, but the rookie had to show his respects, too. Challenging a God with a class that he didn’t even play was simply too disrespectful. After seeing Qiao Yifan choose a Ghostblade, even captain Wang Jiexi wrinkled his brow.

However, what Liu Fei said wasn’t wrong. Besides their Tiny Herb players, no one knew that Qiao Yifan played as an Assassin. The audience probably didn’t even know who Qiao Yifan was.

On stage, the match quickly began. Just like the first and second matches, the two sides headed straight for the middle of the map.

The match’s map was a ruins map. There were a lot of walls and the terrain was quite good for Ghostblades to perform on. This type of terrain allowed for the player to hide themselves behind something, throw down a Ghost Boundary and then lure the enemy into the boundary. This was a very common tactic among Phantom Demons.

In a duel between Ghostblades, the duel was very rarely a battle between hand speeds or mechanics.

They often competed in decision-making, game knowledge, and…… dirtiness.

As the number one Phantom Demon, God Li Xuan’s abilities were naturally first class. The two sides closed in towards the middle of the map, but way before the two met, Li Xuan’s character halted.

This halt just happened to be outside of the Ghost Boundary set by Qiao Yifan’s Ghostblade. He then stepped over to the side twice and hid behind a wall. The audience could see the entire map and they could see this very clearly. But if they looked at Qiao Yifan’s point of view, Li Xuan’s character had already disappeared.

In the Rookie Challenge, the first to take action was unexpectedly the God-level character.

The audience might not be too surprised, but the pro players understood very clearly that, in normal circumstances, the “fatherly” senior always gave the rookie the first move before showing off. But Li Xuan? He snatched the first move.

Li Xuan wasn’t someone with no style, but after seeing the match between Tiny Herb’s members, he couldn’t help but be a bit careful.

The previous match had clearly been a real fight and Tiny Herb’s rookie had been merciless even to his own team captain. In this match, how could he dare consider this a “show” like the first match.

Even though the rookie in front of him wasn’t a genius like Gao Yingjie, who knew if he was Tiny Herb’s secret weapon? Perhaps they wanted to use this Rookie Challenge to have this rookie step on him to make a name for himself.

It couldn’t be said that he was being overly suspicious since it was very reasonable. If any other senior had come up, they probably would have thought the same way, too. However, even so, they might still maintain their style. But Li Xuan had no choice because Phantom Demons were extremely adept at controlling the field. If he fell into a disadvantage at the start and was controlled by the opponent, then turning the situation around was much harder to do than any other class. This was why Li Xuan had to be the first to act. Losing a bit of style in the opening was still better than Wang Jiexi’s losing to a rookie.

After Li Xuan’s character hid behind the wall, Qiao Yifan immediately stopped as well. The field paused for a moment like this.

In a competition between knowledge and decision-making, the match would sometimes be dry and dull like this. The parties would constantly stop in order to make an assumption about the other side’s intent. Right now, the two hadn’t even fought and yet the situation was already like this.

Behind the wall, Li Xuan’s character didn’t move. Qiao Yifan’s character took a few steps, crouched, and then continued to slowly move. Crouching made the character’s movements slow, but there wouldn’t be any noise from his footsteps. Of course, that depended on the terrain, but it was definitely the case for this map.

Li Xuan’s character stuck to the wall as if he was focused on trying to hear the other side’s footsteps. The short pause between the two had cut off. Now, the two were inching closer. Even though the audience could see it all, it was still nerve-wracking.

Watching as Qiao Yifan’s character moved closer, everyone was guessing what the two sides would do next, when Li Xuan’s character suddenly jumped up from behind the wall in such a grand manner that it looked to be unblockable.

Qiao Yifan had thought of this possibility long beforehand, but with the distance between the two, it was a bit too late to cast a Ghost Boundary. Qiao Yifan didn’t hesitate. The instant Li Xuan’s character jumped out, a Ghost Slash was already heading towards him.

As for Li Xuan? His character slashed downwards. A dark purple glow arced down; it was a Ghost Slash as well.

The same skills had been executed and they had been done at the same time. After the skills hit, the two sides both took damage. There shouldn’t have been any advantage. But that was not the case here. After the two skills flashed and then faded away, Qiao Yifan’s character flew backwards. But Li Xuan’s character stepped forward like an arrow. He turned his hands over with a Moonlight Slash and launched his opponent into the air.

“Ah!” Everyone cried out in astonishment. With just one move, the opponent was launched into the air. Things didn’t look good.

The experienced pro players had already figured something out: Li Xuan’s Ghostblade wasn’t his specialty Phantom Demon. In this match, he had unexpectedly chosen to use a Sword Demon instead.

Chapter 306 – Hopelessly Worried

Phantom Demons and Sword Demons were two different types of styles. Their skills were chosen based on whether the Ghostblade wanted to mainly use Sword Skills or Ghost Boundaries. In terms of PvE, Phantom Demons were actually better than Sword Demons. But in terms of PvP, Sword Demons were clearly the winner. This was especially true in a 1v1 PK, where Phantom Demons were publicly accepted as a weaker class. Even for Li Xuan, the user of the number one Phantom Demon Sobbing Ghost, he rarely came out during the Individual or Group Competition.

This wasn’t an issue of mechanics. It was simply because the class wasn’t set up for duels. Anyone who was able to join the pro scene wouldn’t be bullied easily by anyone, which was why, even for a Phantom Demon master like Li Xuan, even he wouldn’t play a 1v1 match against one.

But the Rookie Challenge Competition was, after all, only a show. Winning or losing didn’t matter too much. Normally, Li Xuan would use his Phantom Demon to do battle. But today, with Gao Yingjie and Wang Jiexi’s previous battle looming over him, Li Xuan was too afraid to think of this match as just a show match. Moreover, he wasn’t sure whether or not the other side had wanted to lure him into playing his Phantom Demon and then use his Sword Demon to suppress him. As a result, Li Xuan cautiously put in his points into making a Sword Demon.

In the end, Qiao Yifan actually chose to use a Phantom Demon. Li Xuan had figured this out when he made his first move.

Apart from the difference in skills for Sword Demons and Phantom Demons, they also chose different equipment.

Sword Demons mainly used Sword Skills, which were all instant casts, so they sought after attack speed. On the other hand, Phantom Demons mainly used Ghost Boundaries, which were all cast abilities, so they sought after cast speed like mages did. After the two Ghostblades chose their equipment, one of them would have a faster attack speed, while the other would have a faster cast speed.

When the two contested with Ghost Slashes and attacked at the same time, the Sword Demon had the advantage, which was why Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon had been hit.

In a duel between Phantom Demons, the players contested against decision making and wretchedness. It could be said that Qiao Yifan couldn’t compare to Li Xuan. That guy had wretchedly chosen to create a Sword Demon instead of a Phantom Demon.

His hit had connected. But in Li Xuan’s mind, even though he knew that the other side was a Phantom Demon, he couldn’t relax just yet. Not just him, but these fundamental combos were already reflexes to him. When the Ghost Slash hit, the follow-up Moonlight Slash was practically done without any thought.

As for Qiao Yifan? He had studied the Ghostblade recently and knew about this. The instant his attack hit, he realized that Li Xuan was unexpectedly using a Sword Demon. Qiao Yifan was still a rookie, after all. A lot of his thinking wasn’t as deep as those veterans. He had originally thought that the other side would definitely pick a Phantom Demon against him. This sudden change instantly messed up his plans and he had made a mistake because of it. It was also his very first time being on such a large stage and he had initially been very nervous. The sudden difference between reality and what he had imagined caused his mind to turn blank.

Moonlight Slash, Full Moon Slash. Ghost Claw into a Sword Boundary into an Upward Slash, a Gore Cross, and then another Moonlight Slash.

Li Xuan was incomparably skilled with this combo. Sword Demons mainly focused on Sword Skills and only learned a few skills from other Swordsman classes, such as the Blade Master’s Upward Slash, the Berserker’s Gore Cross, etc. These low-leveled skills weren’t learned for damage, but rather as links for combos to allow cooldowns to come off.

Li Xuan didn’t let up while comboing. This player wasn’t a monster so it wouldn’t just passively take a beating while it was in the air. This was especially true for pro players, who practiced thoroughly in escaping from mid-air predicaments. But for Phantom Demons, no one was more clear than Li Xuan on what methods could be used in mid-air. He watched very closely and set up plans for dealing with whatever movements the opponent would make. However, in the end, he had done all that thinking for nothing. After being launched into the air, his opponent was just like an NPC. He didn’t respond in any way and just flopped around, taking a beating. Li Xuan had even been able to complete the full combo.

The audience went into an uproar. The long combo had caught everyone’s attention, but the pro players were all looking at each other. A pro player being hit by a full combo was something that was completely unheard of. Was Tiny Herb’s rookie that bad? It looked like he didn’t even attempt to escape. Could he even be called a pro player? Even a normal Glory player would randomly hit their keyboards and struggle, no?

Uncertain, bewildered, and disdaining…… all sorts of gazes were sent towards Tiny Herb’s players. Tiny Herb’s players were all uneasy, too. Liang Fang, who had a more explosive personality, had already jumped up: “What is Qiao Yifan doing? His play is too embarrassing, no?”

It was true that the Rookie Challenge was just for show and it was true that no rookie truly wanted to beat their senior, but going up there to act like a sponge really was too embarrassing.

“Sit.”

Liang Fang had only just vented his anxiousness, when he heard his captain Wang Jiexi coldly order him. Liang Fang immediately quieted down and sat down. He had a lot of words he wanted to say, but he didn’t dare to speak now.

Others who wanted to speak also quieted down. They also thought that Wang Jiexi must be in a very bad mood right now. No one cared as much about Tiny Herb as their captain. If Qiao Yifan really did lose like this, then it would definitely leave a black mark on Tiny Herb.

The outsiders all cheered, while the insiders were puzzled. Li Xuan was one of the insiders. After completing his combo, the other side’s health bar had dropped to half, but he was confused now.

He had originally thought that his opponent would be like Gao Yingjie with a fierce and godly skill, which was why he had made a Sword Demon to defend against him. But how could he have known that he was facing such a noob? The rookie didn’t even know about such a fundamental skill like escaping from a mid-air situation. Against such a noob, no matter how brilliantly he won, his victory wouldn’t look good. Yet he had actually been so wretched at the start. Right now, Li Xuan was starting to regret what he had done and was doubting that this Tiny Herb rookie had specially come out to defame him. But he also couldn’t figure out why his opponent was acting like this and being so incomprehensible.

Li Xuan was feeling a bit embarrassed, so he didn’t follow up.

After Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon was hit by the combo, he finally woke up. He Quick Recovered and then heard the applause from all around. His life had dropped to half, while his opponent was far away, as if he didn’t intend on following up.

What am I doing!!!

Wide awake now, Qiao Yifan was somewhat angry. This was a battle that he had put careful thought into. His goal was very simple: to use the stage to show his ability. It wasn’t just for Tiny Herb to see. He hoped that there would be someone, in any of the teams watching, who was like God Ye Qiu watching him, would see his ability and then let him continue playing in the pro scene.

But the result? With just a small, unexpected change, he was immediately at a loss. Why was he such a lost cause?

Sword Demon? So what? Was he so amazing that he’d be able to beat Li Xuan if he had picked a Phantom Demon? All he had to do was perform. Why did it matter whether the opponent went Phantom Demon or not?

After clearing his head, Qiao Yifan discovered that he had been hopelessly worried. He had been anxious about things that weren’t worth paying attention to. What he had to do was show his ability. That was it.

He looked at his health bar and saw only half of it was remaining. However, he had finally cooled down.

‘There’s still hope!’ Qiao Yifan quietly reminded himself. His Phantom Demon began to move.

Li Xuan’s Sword Demon didn’t move, though. Against a rookie who didn’t even know how to get out of an aerial combo, he felt too embarrassed to act first. He was still puzzled. How was such a rookie scouted by a Champion team like Tiny Herb? What was so special about him?

Li Xuan’s attitude had completely changed.

He had previously been worried over whether or not his opponent would eat him, but now he was only curious to see what the rookie had in him. Seeing that his opponent was moving again, he stood still and began looking forward to see what was to come. This type of attitude was normal for a Rookie Challenge.

Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon rushed forward and when he reached a certain distance, he let out a purple slash.

Li Xuan smiled and raised his sword to do the same.

Even though he had acted slower, he already grasped the two sides’ attack speeds. He was slow, but his attack still reached his opponent first.

He hadn’t expected his opponent to suddenly cancel his Ghost Slash. His opponent rolled forward, dodging Li Xuan’s Ghost Slash, and was going to take advantage of Li Xuan’s not-yet-finished Ghost Slash animation to close in two positions.

Following right after, the tip of his sword glowed, but it wasn’t a sword attack. White-blue ice crystals formed on his blade. He was preparing to cast an Ice Boundary.

“Oh!” Li Xuan understood Qiao Yifan’s intent, but he didn’t panic. After finishing his Ghost Slash, he immediately jumped. The Ice Boundary had already begun to condense. The Sword Demon raised his sword with both hands and swung down with the Blade Master skill “Falling Light Blade.”

This attack wouldn’t arrive in time to interrupt Qiao Yifan’s Ice Boundary. However, if Qiao Yifan finished the cast, he wouldn’t have enough time to dodge the attack, either.

What was he going to do?

They didn’t have to wait long to see Qiao Yifan’s decision.

He didn’t dodge. He continued to finish his Ice Boundary. The Boundary congealed, but his Phantom Demon had already been knocked down by Li Xuan’s Falling Light Blade.

Qiao Yifan immediately Quick Recovered.

Then, Qiao Yifan heard a “bo” sound and he suddenly felt delighted.

“He’s been frozen!” Qiao Yifan thought as he turned his camera. Sure enough, Li Xuan’s Sword Demon had turned into an ice cube. Qiao Yifan didn’t delay and immediately sent a slash.

“Bo!”

Another sound came the same time the slash was released. The ice cube shattered and it looked as if Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon had broken it.

Li Xuan’s Sword Demon seemed to have anticipated this. The ice shattered and his character shot out, leaping backwards, while unleashing a Berserker’s Gore Cross towards the Phantom Demon.

A blood red cross. Qiao Yifan had to dodge to the side. Even if he took the hit, he still wouldn’t have been able to close in on his opponent, because the Gore Cross had a slight knockback effect.

Chapter 307 – Dazzling Stage

Qiao Yifan’s character rolled diagonally and it looked like he had made his way through the empty space beneath the blood cross. His dodge had been extremely dangerous. He had done it because he didn’t want to miss the opportunity to attack, while his opponent was still in the Ice Boundary.

Avoiding the Gore Cross, Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon raised the tip of his sword. He wanted to open another Ghost Boundary in order to seal off his opponent’s escape route. Using a successive Ghost Boundary to trap the opponent into a Boundary was a commonly used tactic among Phantom Demons. Qiao Yifan’s Ice Boundary surrounded Li Xuan’s Sword Demon. He believed that he had had opportunity and began casting another Boundary. But as soon as he began chanting, Li Xuan’s Sword Demon suddenly turned around and swung.

The two were quite a distance away from each other and a normal slash definitely wouldn’t hit. But after swinging his sword, the ground inside the Ice Boundary suddenly surged like a wave towards Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon.

Spellblade Skill: Earthquake Sword.

Li Xuan had only put in one point into this low-leveled Spellblade skill. This could be seen from the length of ground that had been swept forward. But it didn’t matter, so long as it reached where Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon was standing.

This time though, Qiao Yifan didn’t have a choice. If he was swept away by the Earthquake Sword, then his casting would definitely be interrupted. Helpless, he cancelled his casting and dodged the attack.

From Falling Light Blade to Gore Cross to Earthquake Sword. These low-leveled Blade Master, Berserker, and Spellblade skills had only been ranked up once. They weren’t learned for damage, but rather for their effects. By using these three low-leveled skills, Li Xuan’s Sword Demon safely escaped from the Ice Boundary, while Qiao Yifan was unable to set up another Boundary to trap his opponent.

Qiao Yifan felt that it was unfortunate. It hadn’t been easy to confine his opponent in the Ice Boundary. The Freeze effect had even worked. It had been a great opportunity, but he hadn’t been able to seize it.

But PK were always ever-changing. If an opportunity could be fully grasped so easily, then PK would be way too simple. Furthermore, his opponent was a God among Ghostblades. Even though Qiao Yifan felt that it was a pity, he wasn’t discouraged. He carefully observed the position of Li Xuan’s Sword Demon and rushed forward again.

Li Xuan wasn’t alarmed in the slightest, however. With just that single exchange, he fully grasped Qiao Yifan’s ability. His performance had been orderly and methodical, but it couldn’t be said that he was extremely skilled. Seeing Qiao Yifan rush forward, he didn’t hurry. Instead, he casually set up a Sword Boundary.

Qiao Yifan looked and immediately came to a stop. He wouldn’t let himself enter his opponent’s Boundary. Standing outside the boundary, he began to chant. Purple flames jumped up from his Phantom Demon’s blade, congealing into a flaming figure. He had cast a Flame Boundary.

With the ghost out, numerous dark-purple fire ghosts leapt into the area within the boundary. The ghosts scattered around as if they were looking for a target to burn. The Flame Boundary had been cast inside Li Xuan’s Sword Boundary. The two Boundaries overlapped. However, Li Xuan’s Sword Demon had already jumped backwards and didn’t set foot into the Flame Boundary.

Qiao Yifan didn’t think that the Flame Boundary would trap his opponent. The Boundary had been cast for his own protection, so he’d be able to enter the opponent’s Sword Boundary.

Everything sounded complicated, but in reality, it had all happened within the span of a few seconds. Inside the boundaries, the two moved around extremely quickly. Inside his Flame Boundary, Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon quickly dashed into Li Xuan’s Sword Boundary. But to his surprise, Li Xuan’s Sword Demon also suddenly rushed into his area as if he wasn’t afraid of the Flame Boundary’s damage.

Li Xuan’s charge forward had been outside of Qiao Yifan’s expectations. Li Xuan’s Sword Demon raised his sword with a Moonlight Slash and then slashed down. He would then naturally follow up with a Full Moonlight Slash closely after. Players had even given the combo a name: Double Moon Slash.

Qiao Yifan didn’t have the time to defend and the two strikes connected. The damage from a Sword Demon’s strike buffed by a max-leveled Sword Boundary was quite terrifying. The health bar on Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon went down a chunk, but he immediately stood back up with a Quick Recover. The opponent had rushed into his Flame Boundary. It was another opportunity for him.

But the audience could see the situation more clearly than he could.

The instant Li Xuan’s Sword Demon rushed into the Flame Boundary, those dark-purple flame ghosts immediately pounced at him. In that short interval, Li Xuan’s Sword Demon had used the Double Moon Slash and then leapt back. Even though those flame ghosts were quick, they hadn’t been able to hit him. Li Xuan’s Sword Demon had escaped from the Flame Boundary.

The audience cheered wildly.

Going into the Flame Boundary without being entangled by the purple flame ghosts was undoubtedly a testament to his extremely precise mechanics and decision-making. Li Xuan deserved to be called the number one Phantom Demon since no one else had a deeper understanding of these things than he did.

When Qiao Yifan got up, he saw that Li Xuan had escaped from the Flame Boundary. This time, he was surprised. At the same time, he faintly felt that he had failed to consider a few things when he had made his decision.

Li Xuan retreated and stopped moving again. He was waiting for Qiao Yifan to move up. He had entered his persona now and had completely taken this match as a teaching opportunity for the new rookie. He hoped to be a bit more stylish and more technical in order to erase the audience’s previous impression of him as wretched and without style.

Qiao Yifan no longer had a way out and could only move forward.

He used the terrain, pathing, and his character.

Dual Chain Boundaries, Triple Boundaries…..

Qiao Yifan used everything he knew and without any mistakes either. Everything he did had been done 100%. However, it was no use. Every strategy he used was crushed by Li Xuan. From the audience’s cheers again and again, Qiao Yifan could tell that they weren’t towards him. His health continued to drop. After all these exchanges, he hadn’t even been able to take off a fifth of Li Xuan’s health.

Qiao Yifan was at a loss again.

The first time was because he had panicked after encountering something unexpected. After adjusting his attitude, he resolved that panic feeling. But this time, he felt completely powerless.

Qiao Yifan was already at wit’s end. All of the tricks and tactics he employed were all useless. None of them had made a difference. Every single one of his plans was destroyed by a single move from his opponent. The only thing that had happened with every exchange was his health bar depleting.

And his opponent? Throughout these numerous exchanges, his opponent never made the first move. He didn’t even dodge. He would always wait for him to rush forward. Then he would proceed to tear down his plans, calmly dissolving his attacks and easily countering back. Even when there was an opening, he wouldn’t combo him to death like he had done in the beginning. He would always let him go and have Qiao Yifan continue.

Beat his opponent?

Qiao Yifan no longer carried any hope of this fantasy. Even his ultimate goal of displaying his ability hadn’t been achieved. His thoughts and intents had been completely seen through and no matter how hard he tried, they never worked.

His health was already red. In the next exchange, he was afraid that he would go down.

Fight!

At this moment, what else could Qiao Yifan do? He once again focused and rushed forward. His fingers fluttered and his movements were quicker than before. His character quickly met with Li Xuan’s Sword Demon and he instantly set four Ghost Boundaries.

His opponent?

His opponent was once again standing outside of the boundary. He had been moving like this ever since Qiao Yifan’s first Ghost Boundary. His character constantly moved and slipped out from the small cracks in the four consecutively casted Ghost Boundaries.

Qiao Yifan felt hopeless. Movements he wasn’t even able to do in practice had been easily accomplished by his opponent. Li Xuan’s Sword Demon pounced on him and from his poker face, Qiao Yifan felt like he saw a cynical smile. No, not one, but two, no, three, no, even more…… some he recognized, some he didn’t.

The sword light swept down. Amidst the cheers, Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon fell.

Qiao Yifan stood up from his platform, dizzy. He knew that he had been completely crushed.

Two pillars of light dropped down onto the two contestants. In the Rookie Challenge, both sides were given the same treatment.

Qiao Yifan walked down from his platform to the center of the stage. He saw Li Xuan standing in front of him, full of smiles. Li Xuan said a few words to him, but Qiao Yifan couldn’t hear any of it. He shook hands mechanically and then silently walked away from the stage.

Behind him, Li Xuan was waving his hands and calling out to the audience. Many of his words were in praise of Qiao Yifan’s performance. But Qiao Yifan knew that these words were just common courtesy. The other side was only showing off his style. The praise didn’t have anything to do with him. Even if he had just sat there stunned like he was in the beginning, Li Xuan would still praise: “Not bad. You played very well.”

Qiao Yifan walked over to his seat and saw his teammates. They were supposed to be the people he knew best, but they felt like strangers now.

Qiao Yifan ground his teeth. He didn’t walk towards them and continued along the path past them.

“Yifan!”

He heard someone call him from behind. He could tell that it was Gao Yingjie’s voice. He didn’t stop and walked even faster.

The stadium’s lights were focused on the stage and were scattered sparsely around the audience’s seats. In order to enhance the effects for today’s projection technology, these unnecessary places were even darker. Gao Yingjie chased after him, but it was already too late to find which direction Qiao Yifan went.

After reaching the exit, Qiao Yifan couldn’t help but look back.

The stage was as dazzling as ever. It had been his first time going up onto such a beautiful stage, but he was afraid that it might be his last.

Chapter 308 – Opportunity Goes to Those Who Are Prepared

The passageway leading outside of the stadium wasn’t completely dark. There was still some light. Qiao Yifan silently walked towards outside, but after going around in a few circles, he discovered that he had gotten lost.

Qiao Yifan didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. He really was unfamiliar with these official stadiums! By himself, he couldn’t even find the exit.

He had met with a crushing defeat on stage. Aware that it was very likely that his career was about to end, Qiao Yifan had walked away. Lost, he couldn’t bear the aching in his heart anymore as tears began flowing out out his eyes. Qiao Yifan raised his arms, wiping off his tears.

His heartache only drove his stubbornness, though. He refused to believe that he didn’t even have the ability to find the exit. Wiping away his tears, Qiao Yifan didn’t try to find where he was and blindly pressed forward.

“You were too reckless.”

Suddenly, a sound echoed out from the gloom. Qiao Yifan stopped, startled. He then shook his head. This was just a passageway. What was so strange about hearing someone’s voice?

Thinking this, Qiao Yifan took a step, when he heard the voice again say: “I’m talking to you! Don’t run!”

Qiao Yifan startled. Was he talking to himself? He halted, turned his head, and saw a long shadow stretched out in the passageway. A person stood there, but in the darkness, it was hard to see the person’s features clearly.

“Are you…… talking to me?” Qiao Yifan didn’t recognize him.

“Yes!” The person walked towards him, while continuing: “I know what you’re thinking. You wanted to use the stage to show to everyone your ability as a Phantom Demon, but you went too far with your opponent, no? You actually chose Li Xuan? What were you thinking?”

The person’s voice echoed in the passageway. With this, Qiao Yifan suddenly felt that, whether it was the person’s voice or tone, they both felt familiar. He waited until the other side walked over. He saw his face clearly, but he didn’t recognize him. Qiao Yifan was still puzzled as the other side finished talking. Qiao Yifan replied with a complete loss: “I want to play as a Phantom Demon, so…..”

“If you were there to learn and you wanted to greet your senior, then choosing Li Xuan would obviously be the correct choice. But if you were there to showcase your ability as a Phantom Demon, then Li Xuan is the one person you don’t want to choose.”

Qiao Yifan stared blankly. On stage, he had felt that there were places where he hadn’t fully considered. Now that he heard this, he suddenly came to a realization.

“In the entirety of Glory, no one is more familiar with Phantom Demons than Li Xuan. If you wanted to show your ability as a Phantom Demon in front of him, then of course you’d be restrained. You’re displaying your slight skill in front of a master. How could you even be able to show a tenth of your strength?”

Qiao Yifan understood. He completely understood.

He had taken the line of thought that other rookies used in the Rookie Challenge and chose the expert who played the same class as him, Li Xuan. But he forgot that his reasoning for participating in the Rookie Challenge was different than that of the others. He wanted to show off his Phantom Demon, but he ended up choosing the opponent who was most familiar with Phantom Demons. He had directly given himself the hardest obstacle there was.

“And besides……” The other side continued, “Phantom Demons are most valuable in a team. It’s difficult to showcase your team awareness and mechanics in a 1v1 match like the Rookie Challenge. In addition, you still have very little experience. You haven’t even practiced for a month and you want to challenge Li Xuan already. I’m completely speechless…..”

“God Ye Qiu!!” Hearing this, Qiao Yifan finally figured out who the person in front of him was. Not many knew of his identity, nor that he was practicing a Phantom Demon. At first, everything had been muddy. He only felt that the voice sounded familiar, but he just couldn’t think of anything. Now that he saw that this person knew so much about him, he connected the two together and finally figured out the person’s identity.

“Yeah, it’s me.” Ye Xiu nodded his head. He practically never showed himself in public, so the only pro players that did know him were those at a certain level. For players like Qiao Yifan, who hadn’t even participated in an official match, even though he was in the pro scene, he had never seen Ye Xiu’s true face before.

“

“You don’t need to doubt your ability.” Ye Xiu said, “But don’t think that you’ll be able to catch anyone’s attention right now. There are quite a lot of people with potential, but if you want to be seen by a pro team, then you first need to have, at the very least, some substance. You’re still very far from being an expert at playing a Phantom Demon. But you’re still young. You still have time to continue practicing. Keep waiting for the opportunity to come. It’s only been a month and you want to challenge the number one Phantom Demon? Glory isn’t as simple as you think.”

With this, Qiao Yifan’s face reddened.

In the past, he had always thought that he was no good. But after hearing the God’s encouragement, he suddenly had renewed confidence in himself. He had thought that if God Ye Xiu was able to see his potential, then others would be able to see it, too. All he needed was a chance, a stage.

This was why he had participated in the Rookie Challenge.

He hadn’t thought hard enough when choosing Li Xuan as an opponent. He understood the reasoning now, but he wouldn’t get wrapped up in it anymore.

It was because his choice wouldn’t have made a difference. Even if he had picked a different opponent, with only a month of practicing his Phantom Demon, did he really think that he’d be able to move a pro team’s emotions with his ability right now?

Ye Xiu wanted him to understand this. He wanted him to understand that his thinking had been too reckless.

Qiao Yifan’s thoughts turned and he quickly acknowledge this. He had never thought that he was as talented as a genius like Gao Yingjie. Even Ye Qiu had never given him such an evaluation.

He recalled their first meeting. God Ye Qiu had only told him that an Assassin wouldn’t be able to show his potential and that a Phantom Demon suited him more. That was all.

He still needed to practice. He needed to practice until the day he would truly glimmer.

Qiao Yifan wiped away the last tear from the corner of his eyes. The despair in his heart had suddenly been swept away. Because this time, he finally truly understood himself. He finally knew where he was at.

Opportunity? Stage?

It was still much too early to think of these things. Opportunities were left to those who were prepared. As for him? He wasn’t even close to being prepared, yet he anxiously wanted to grab at an opportunity he thought looked good, which had only resulted in his falling.

But from now on, Qiao Yifan decided that he wouldn’t think of all this. He just had to focus on practicing. After the season ended, would he still be admitted into the team? His greatest worry had finally been seen through.

Would there be a team that would accept him? What was even the point in worrying over it? He first had to train hard before an opportunity would come. Even if he was kicked off his team after this season, it didn’t matter. He was still young and could still practice. In the worst-case scenario, he would start over from the beginning as a new rookie.

The passageway was still as dark as before, but after understanding all of this, Qiao Yifan’s heart was a field of light.

“Thank you, Senior.” Qiao Yifan expressed his gratitude to Ye Xiu.

“You can do it!” Ye Xiu nodded his head and turned around, ready to leave.

“What about you, Senior?” Qiao Yifan suddenly asked, “Why did you choose to retire so early?”

Tiny Herb’s players could be considered as having the most interactions with Ye Xiu after his retirement. They would spar every week and they would always lose miserably. It was true that unspecialized characters had a class advantage, but everyone was still at a pro level. Losing every match like that was a bit too much. Besides having a class advantage, it was clear that the user’s skill level had to be respected.

Choosing to retire with such skill had been discussed in Tiny Herb long before now. Qiao Yifan had broken from his spell and asked Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu turned his head and smiled: “I’m looking for an opportunity, too!”

Qiao Yifan stared blankly: “You’re going to come back?”

“Of course! Even though I’m a bit old, I’m not done yet!” Ye Xiu said as he turned around. He waved his hands at Qiao Yifan and slipped away into the darkness.

Qiao Yifan stood there silently for a while and then began walking. After coming to a sudden understanding, the direction he should go cleared up. The passageway was still the same passageway, but after a few more steps, he quickly came out. But the direction that he came out from wasn’t the exit, but rather the stadium. He had returned to look at that dazzling stage.

In the stadium, the next match had already begun. Because the characters in the Rookie Challenge were all temporary, the audience usually couldn’t tell who the player was from the ID. But in this round, the IDs on top of the two characters weren’t unfamiliar.

Delilo, Three Hits.

These two were undoubtedly active characters in the Alliance. In order to not let the veterans have an advantage in characters, they set up the rule so that they wouldn’t use their accounts. But if the rookie wanted the veteran to, then the veteran could use his account.

The rookie had clearly put out the requirement in this match.

Tang Hao had been an unknown rookie in his first year. But after the summer passed, it was as if he had suddenly gained enlightenment. He took off in the competitive season and became a core member of Team Hundred Blossoms after their captain Zhang Jiale suddenly retired.

The only pity was that his Brawler character, Delilo, couldn’t match his beautiful God-level performance.

As a second-year rookie, Tang Hao still had the qualifications to be in the Rookie Challenge. With his not quite God status and also a rookie status, it was beneath him to join the Rookie Challenge. But Tang Hao had chosen to sign up and he had chosen to fight against a player playing the same class, Lin Jingyan, and proposed the request for him to use his active account.

The challenged veteran could not refuse. Lin Jingyan had no choice but to use what was considered the number one Brawler character, Three Hits.

Tang Hao’s purpose wasn’t to show his respect and it definitely wasn’t to ask for advice. In the pro scene, although Tang Hao’s name resounded far and wide, many regarded Lin Jingyan as the same. He was old, but still vigorous. This challenge was a true challenge. Tang Hao seemed like he wanted to use this opportunity as proof of his superiority.

This was because when he went up on stage to speak, Tang Hao only said five words: “The junior succeeds the senior.”

Chapter 309 – The Junior Succeeds the Senior

Qiao Yifan watched the match as he felt his way back to Tiny Herb’s seats.

“Yifan!” Apart from Gao Yingjie’s shout of surprise, the others only glanced at him.

If this was the past, Qiao Yifan would definitely feel ashamed, but now, his attitude had already completely changed after going out and coming back. The team’s cold treatment towards him was no longer important. As long as he had enough strength, he wouldn’t need to worry anymore.

“I went to the restroom.” Qiao Yifan smiled to Gao Yingjie, while quietly moving to Gao Yingjie’s side, where his original seat was at.

“Tang Hao’s challenging Lin Jingyan! He’s being very disrespectful. As soon as he went up on the stage, he said that the junior would succeed the senior. Both of them are using their own accounts and both are truly sparked.” While Qiao Yifan sat down, Gao Yingjie hastily told him the match’s situation.

“Oh, oh.” Qiao Yifan nodded his head and immediately focused on the match. He felt very grateful in his heart. He knew that his best friend wasn’t just saying all of this to have him catch up on the parts he had missed. He had said all that to help distract Qiao Yifan from his worries. No one would feel happy with the results of that previous match. Gao Yingjie was a very shy person. He wasn’t the type to directly say any consoling words, so all he could do was use this type of method to help Qiao Yifan bring up his spirit.

There was quite a bit of discussion among the pro players and some of it made its way to Qiao Yifan’s ears. Everyone was discussing the current match. Quite a few of them were comparing it to the previous match between Gao Yingjie and Wang Jiexi.

It was clear that this year’s Rookie Challenge was abnormal. Gao Yingjie and Wang Jiexi had fought seriously and the new rookie had mercilessly struck down his captain.

Also, during this match, which had Tang Hao versus Lin Jingyan, everyone could tell that it would be another great match just from Tang Hao’s attitude. Sure enough, as soon as the match started, the two sides rapidly met and began to battle without any signs of holding back. Tang Hao’s words had been announced wide and clear. If Lin Jingyan backed out, no one would see it as style. If he was going to back out, he would have to at least convince Tang Hao through fighting. Then, if he said something nice, that would be true style.

However, this was just a theoretical situation. Tang Hao wasn’t a normal rookie. If this was during any other time, this wouldn’t only be considered a challenge by a rookie. In everyone’s eyes, he was already at the same status as a senior.

The Alliance did desire this type of challenge by a highly skilled rookie, though. Putting the rookie experience limit to two years had been a result of this consideration.

Tang Hao’s conduct wasn’t consistent with the Rookie Challenge’s intentions, but it was certainly eye-catching. This could be seen from the audience’s loud cheers and shouts. The atmosphere right now was even more intense than it had been for any previous match.

The reporters who had originally thought that nothing today would ever top the match between Gao Yingjie and Wang Jiexi had their spirits rekindled once again.

It was true that Gao Yingjie beating Wang Jiexi had been surprising news, but the genius rookie himself didn’t have a very suitable persona. How could he be more eye-catching than Tang Hao’s “the junior succeeds the senior” words?

The reporters were all appreciating the match. Quite a few of them had already started writing down things. The battle on the field was extremely intense, but any experienced Glory player could tell that Lin Jingyan’s situation was looking very bad.

In his former years, he had been the King of Brawlers, but it was already a fact that his condition had greatly fallen. Although his Three Hits was much stronger than Tang Hao’s Delillo, in a direct match, he was still much worse overall.

Tang Hao’s play was quicker and he was practically always on the offensive. Lin Jinyan’s reaction speed and mechanics were no longer as acute as they were before and he was only barely keeping up through his experience. He knew that, for this match, there was no point in talking about any style for winning. Leaving the match as a whole was already looking like an extravagant hope.

His only hope was that Tang Hao would make a mistake.

It wouldn’t be surprising if someone, who had only been playing as a pro for two years, made a mistake. The efficient and shrewd Lin Jingyan tried his hardest to keep up. As time went on, he hoped that he’d be able to catch Tang Hao in a mistake and counterattack. He truly wasn’t capable of clashing directly with him anymore.

Lin Jingyan had already carried out every method he knew, but things never turned out the way he expected.

Tang Hao had obviously made a few mistakes, but his reactions had been faster and he made up for it quickly, too. Half of these openings were seen by Lin Jinyan, but he wasn’t able to seize any opportunities and could only watch as Tang Hao closed the openings. Aside from these, there were those he was able to seize, but the damage he returned couldn’t even compare to Tang Hao’s repeated fierce attacks.

Lin Jingyan knew that he was too slow. He saw many openings, but he wasn’t able to capitalize on them. Tang Hao’s quicker hands were always able to dissolve his counterattacks.

Was there no chance?

Many thought this way. However, the veteran’s perseverance wouldn’t let him give up. Lin Jingyan persevered and continued to wait for an opportunity. Until the very last second, no one would know of the result. Perhaps a huge mistake he could capitalize upon would come. It was still too early to give up.

So the match continued.

The junior succeeds the senior. The main theme was being displayed beautifully right now.

Tang Hao and Lin Jingyan weren’t home players, so there was a clear divide between the fans. After all, Tang Hao wasn’t someone like Gao Yingjie and Qiao Yifan who hadn’t participated in an official match. His godly performance in the season had quickly helped him gather quite a few fans.

The match’s situation could be seen from the two sides’ supporters.

On Lin Jingyan’s side, the fans were encouraging him.

And Tang Hao’s side? His fans were already yelling like crazy. They were no longer shouting anything of substance and had already entered a party animal state.

Tang Hao’s fierce attacks looked even madder. Brawlers weren’t a class that directly fought. Brick, Sand Toss, Apply Poison. Just from these skill names, people could figure out this class’s wretchedness. However, Tang Hao’s Delillo looked as if he were a Striker.

Attack, attack, attack. Continuous attacks.

Waiting waiting waiting. Patiently waiting.

The fans’ emotions wouldn’t affect a veteran like Lin Jingyan. He was still patiently waiting for an opening to arrive.

Here!

Just as he entered a Red Blood state, Lin Jingyan’s eyes brightened. The fierce Tang Hao finally failed to follow up on one of his attacks, creating a huge opening. With the match nearly over, such an opening might not be enough to reverse the situation, but it could be the start of one.

Lin Jingyan didn’t overthink it and seized the opportunity to fiercely attack Tang Hao.

His right hand shot out. Three Hits executed a Strangle towards Tang Hao’s Delillo.

However, Delillo suddenly somersaulted as if he knew the attack was coming.

Lin Jingyan started. He hastily tried to adjust himself, but then his screen turned black. Delillo’s legs kicked forward and smashed into Three Hit’s forehead.

Brawler skill: Powerful Knee Strike.

Lin Jingyan knew that things weren’t looking good. So his opponent was ready for it… Had the previous opening been a bait?

The Powerful Knee Strike wasn’t enough to make the opponent fall, but the instant Delillo struck Three Hits, he grabbed him with his arms and used the skill Tiger Flipping Mountain to knock Three Hits to the ground.

Delillo also flipped over, but he Quick Recovered faster than Lin Jingyan. Three Hits wasn’t able to get up in time and was pressed to the ground by Delillo, which was followed by a flurry of fists.

High-leveled Brawler skill: Tyrannical Chain Punch.

Lin Jingyan well understood the skill’s damage. He looked at his health and saw that there was no longer any hope.

Under Tang Hao’s quick hands, the Tyrannical Chain Punch came out even faster. And after this move was completed, Three Hits’ health disappeared and he was not able to stand up anymore. Along with the word “Glory”, the announcer announced the final winner.

The junior had succeeded the senior.

The media only wanted more things to talk about. They wouldn’t favor any one side because of their feelings.

The two players came down from their platforms and shook hands in the middle of the stage.

“You played well……..” Lin Jingyan forced a smile. After playing in the pro scene for so many years, he was already used to hiding his true emotions.

“The junior succeeds the senior.” Tang Hao shook Lin Jingyan’s hands. Only these five words were said.

Even the master of ceremonies felt that the situation really was somewhat awkward. Just as he was about to interrupt, the two players finished shaking hands. Tang Hao stood up, waved his hands towards the audience, and then left the stage.

The master of ceremonies looked pitifully at Lin Jingyan. He didn’t know what he should do.

But Lin Jingyan only continued to smile at the host and then after waving his hands to the audience, he silently left the stage. By normal standards, he wasn’t considered old at all. But on the eSports stage, his leaving figure made the audience feel as if he was doddering a bit.

The pro players looked at each other. Tang Hao’s actions had challenged the tradition. Even though Gao Yingjie had beaten his team captain, from start to finish, he hadn’t been disrespectful in the slightest.

Amidst everyone’s discussion, the commentators announced the next match.

Rookie challenger: Team Excellent Era, Sun Xiang.

Veteran challenged: Team Tyrannical Ambition, Han Wenqing.

Soon after, the commentators excitedly announced that for this match, the rookie requested that the veteran use his own account.

The shouts and cheers from the audience were earth-shattering.

With this request, the hype for this match far exceeded the last one.

Tang Hao’s Delillo was a very mediocre character in the pro scene. And even though Lin Jingyan’s Three Hits was considered the number one Brawler character, it wasn’t considered a God-level account. But the accounts owned by Sun Xiang and Han Wenqing were very different.

Battle God, One Autumn Leaf.

King of Fighting, Desert Dust.

Ever since the Glory Alliance was founded, these two God-level characters had never stopped fighting.

Chapter 310 – A Conclusion

It could be heard from the audience’s cheers just how sensational the appearance of these accounts were.

It was already difficult enough to see a God-level account come out in the Rookie Challenge. For there to be two God-level accounts coming out as opponents, this was definitely a first in the history of the Rookie Challenge. Every reporter today was destined to be busy tonight. They hadn’t yet finished switching the lead story to “The Junior Beats the Senior”, when suddenly, an even more explosive story had come out.

Of course, the more explosive the story, the more excited these diligent reporters became. The previous drafts they had didn’t need to be trashed. All they had to do was switch their positions on the page. Right now, they were hoping that Sun Xiang would be like Tang Hao and say a challenge similar to “the junior beats the senior”. If that happened, the reporters would certainly go crazy.

On stage, Sun Xiang loftily walked up.

Without a doubt, no rookie had a greater reputation than he did. He was in his second year as a pro like Tang Hao, but he was far more eye-catching than Tang Hao. In his first year, his god-like performance won him the Most Outstanding Rookie title. His performance in this season also continued to be outstanding. Halfway through the season, he transferred to Excellent Era and after receiving the God-level account, One Autumn Leaf, it could already be said that Sun Xiang stood together, alongside the top Gods. Critics even praised that his control over One Autumn Leaf was more than enough to allow Excellent Era’s fans to forget about Ye Qiu. The majority of players probably even forgot that he was still a rookie.

If Sun Xiang went up and respectfully greeted his senior, he probably won’t win many people’s approval. After all, his status was already different. If he put himself as a regular rookie, then that would be too excessive. Undue modesty was conceit.

Furthermore, Sun Xiang had never been a modest person. The keen reporters predicted that Sun Xiang definitely wouldn’t let this match be a dull one.

Sun Xiang’s appearances weren’t bad either. After walking up on stage, he had already begun waving his hands to the audience as if he were already the winner.

The host walked forward and asked for Sun Xiang’s reason for challenging Han Wenqing as if he were interviewing him.

“The reason is very simple.” Sun Xiang smiled with a manner of a God, “For Excellent Era and Tyrannical Ambition, I will settle the old grudge between One Autumn Leaf and Desert Dust.”

After the audience heard this, they were at first, stumped for words. But then they began to shout and cheer loudly again. Sun Xiang’s words weren’t as ruthless as Tang Hao’s “the junior beats the senior”, but what it represented was extremely rich. Tang Hao’s words were only limited to the contest for the number one Brawler, while what Sun Xiang planned on doing was a true God vs God battle. In addition, his words represented the rivalry between two of the oldest Clubs in the Alliance.

Sun Xiang was Excellent Era’s team captain and used One Autumn Leaf. He was worthy of taking the responsibility. Although the majority of the people here were Samsara fans, no one would ever dare to object to watching an exciting match. As long as they were a Glory fan, no one wanted to miss the rivalry between these two teams.

Amidst the mass of cheers, there was also a small portion of cursing, which were naturally from Tyranny’s fans. Sun Xiang’s challenge was too much to bear, so they impolitely began cursing.

If there were Tyranny fans, then naturally there would be Excellent Era fans. Except Excellent Era’s fans were the only ones cheering, so they looked about the same as the majority of the audience and didn’t stand out.

However, the Excellent Era fan next to Ye Xiu was quite eye-catching. She jumped up and down, waved her arms, and shouted: “Beat Han Wenqing!!!”

“Slow down…….” Ye Xiu hastily called. He was afraid that Chen Guo would stumble from being too excited and fall into the front seats.

Under the host’s introduction, Tyranny’s team captain Han Wenqing finally walked onto the stage.

Even though Sun Xiang wasn’t modest, under the audience’s eyes, he didn’t want to appear impolite, so he extended his hands: “Please advise me, senior.” He would still say the polite words any player should say.

“It’s an honor.” Han Wenqing shook Sun Xiang’s hands and emotionlessly replied.

Sun Xiang chuckled and turned around to walk towards his competition platform. The host wanted to ask Han Wenqing few questions, but when he got up close and saw Han Wenqing’s cold gaze, his heart trembled and he was unable to utter a single word. Han Wenqing waved his hands towards the cheering audience and then headed over to his platform.

The two were both using their own accounts, so they could skip choosing the equipment and adding skill points part. The lights quickly dimmed and the projection appeared onto the stage. One Autumn Leaf and Desert Dust had already appeared at the two ends of the map.

The commentator was even more enthusiastic for this match. He already knew that the two would quickly begin fighting, so without wasting a breath, he quickly introduced the two players and their characters.

“Battle Mages and Strikers are classes that excel at direct confrontations. If we take a look at this market street map that Sun Xiang chose, the map doesn’t favor either of the two classes. It doesn’t seem to have been chosen for any tactical purpose.” After introducing the two sides, the commentator began talking about the map. These types of commentary were quite rare in the Rookie Challenge, but the commentator had already recognized that this match would be a true fight, which was why the commentator began analyzing the match from the very start.

“Okay, the two sides didn’t do any unnecessary actions and headed straight for the middle of the map.” The commentator said.

The two characters met at the corner of one of the streets.

The Silver weapon, Evil Annihilation, held in One Autumn Leaf’s hands glinted a dark, cold light. The Silver weapon, Flame Fists, worn by Desert Dust were two fiery flames that enveloped his fists.

Right now, the two sides were about ten positions away. Both stopped there for a short while as if they were sending their respects and then rushed forward, practically at the same time.

In terms of attack range, the Battle Mage’s long weapon was undoubtedly much greater than the Striker with the shortest fist weapon, so the first to attack was of course, Sun Xiang. A black light flashed and One Autumn Leaf’s Evil Annihilation initiated with a Dragon Tooth.

Han Wenqing didn’t dodge. His Desert Dust continued forward as his two hands twisted towards Evil Annihilation answering with an Empty-Handed Blade Block.

Sun Xiang obviously wouldn’t give him an opportunity and immediately turned the stab into a slash, turning the Dragon Tooth into a Sky Strike.

The Empty-Handed Blade Block hit nothing and the skill couldn’t be used immediately again. Desert Dust sidestepped Evil Annihilation, although it looked like he really didn’t want to. As soon as his body passed by the attack, he immediately punched forward.

The blazing fists shot out like a fierce mountain tiger. Sun Xiang hastily jumped back to dodge. Han Wenqing, who didn’t know about the word retreat, once again went forward to attack. The advantage of the Battle Mage in attack range wasn’t able to be shown. From just that quick exchange, Han Wenqing had already broken through the advantage and sent Desert Dust up next to One Autumn Leaf.

Sun Xiang looked to be having some difficulty warding off the flurry of fists. However, not just anyone could show this. Against someone with slightly less skill, who knew how much damage Han Wenqing’s fists would be able to do.

The tempest of attacks stopped. Sun Xiang heaved a sigh of relief and just as he was planning on attacking, he saw Desert Dust crouch into a horse stance. His left hand swayed in front of him, while his right hand pressed on his waist.

“Not good!” Sun Xiang startled. This was the starting animation for the Striker skill “Emperor’s Fist”. This skill had an extremely long cooldown and was usually used in the middle of a combo to inflict heavy damage while the opponent had no place to run. Right now, Sun Xiang’s One Autumn Leaf wasn’t in this type of situation. Using this huge type of skill in this situation would prove to be extremely easy to dodge for a pro-player. It really was a huge waste.

Sun Xiang hadn’t thought that Han Wenqing would use the skill at such a moment, but Han Wenqing had done it. Sun Xiang didn’t dare to try and attack. Just from the name, it could be seen that “Emperor’s Fist” wasn’t an ordinary skill.

Punch!

A sharp whistle split the air. Emperor’s Fist was only a single punch, but the power and speed of it was at its extreme.

Sun Xiang dodged in a flurry and avoided it. But the wind from the punch caused One Autumn Leaf to stumble. Sun Xiang’s mechanics indeed weren’t ordinary. Despite his character staggering and his camera being unsteady, One Autumn Leaf’s Evil Annihilation did not stop dancing in front of his body. The blue waves emanating from it weren’t jumbled. It was evident that his control was exceptional.

His Evil Annihilation shook and pierced through the waves of blue, which gathered onto the spear’s tip.

Even though he hadn’t been hit by “Emperor’s Fist”, the wind from it put Sun Xiang into an unfavorable situation. In this scenario, most players could only watch as their opponent followed up with a wave of attacks. But Sun Xiang was able to complete a powerful skill in this situation.

Dragon Rises from the Sea!

Evil Annihilation flew through like an ocean spray. The blue colored waves rolled along, sounding like an unceasing torrent.

Desert Dust was still in his end animation. The attack came quickly and could not be dodged. The strike connected. Sun Xiang seized this opportunity and followed up with a string of attacks, giving Han Wenqing a beat back.

The two went back and forth. Large skills and small. Amidst the flood of light from the visual effects, it was almost difficult to see the characters. The two were evenly matched. Apart from the starting exchange, neither side was ever able to combo more than three attacks again.

Lance and fist.

The surroundings had already been destroyed. The battle was clearly extremely intense. However, the amount of health that dropped was extremely small. In this type of intense battle, the majority of the attacks from the two were either dodged or blocked. The match was in a deadlock and in the blink of an eye, ten minutes had passed.

Chapter 311 – The Foreshadowed Climax

Ten minutes. This duration of time wasn’t short in the slightest for a duel.

In the early days of the Glory Alliance, matches had a time constraint. In those days, a 1v1 match had a five-minute time limit. If there was no winner after five minutes, the winner would be decided on who had more health left.

The time constraint was originally intended to help out the broadcast, but because of this type of rule, a lot of passive strategies were used. For example, after obtaining a certain lead in health, they wouldn’t try to fight the opponent and ran around the map instead to play hide and seek.

In this way, there were a lot more tactical options, but these types of hide and seek tactics were extremely boring to watch. The opponent was depressed and the members of the audience weren’t happy. Even the commentators fell speechless when these types of matches came about. As a result, the Alliance quickly called a meeting and they decided to remove the time limit. From then on, no match would have a time constraint. The match would be decided by who lived and who died.

With this, even if the players played dirty, they also needed to take the initiative. Running away and hiding would no longer be the main strategy and the matches became much more enjoyable. Though without the time constraint, the broadcast did find it more troublesome to plan out a schedule, but it wasn’t so bad that they couldn’t resolve it. Enjoyable matches were also beneficial to their revenue. The broadcast didn’t want any boring hide-and-seek matches just to make things more convenient.

The time constraint had been scrapped, but the reason they had chosen five minutes as the time limit had been logical. Five minutes was more than enough time to complete a duel. Apart from dragging the match over the five-minute mark, the strategies used were more of the dirty and cautious types, where the two sides slowly wore each other down.

But the current match clearly wasn’t of this kind. One Autumn Leaf’s and Desert Dust’s intense fighting had quickly demolished a fifth of the surroundings. Where was there any sign of dirty fighting?

Yet in this way, the two sides were unexpectedly locked in a stalemate for ten minutes. This truly was rarely seen. They weren’t done yet either. Right now, the two players still had a quarter of their health!

The audience watched in awe. The commentator quickly searched up some data and brought it up.

“10 minutes! Sun Xiang and Han Wenqing have already fought for ten minutes. Right now, the two sides still have a quarter of their health left. If we go according to their pace, the match should take around 13 minutes. Those who are familiar with Glory’s records might not think that this time is that incredible, but everyone should know that those extremely long matches are mostly due to dirty fighting. But to be able to achieve a duration of more than ten minutes with such intense direct fighting, this is my first time witnessing such a match in my career.” The commentator talked nonstop. Due to the unexpected nature of the event, he hadn’t done any prior research. The commentators could only rely on their relatively rich experience to show that this match wasn’t ordinary.

How extraordinary was ten minutes? In reality, experienced Glory players could tell that with such intense fighting, it truly wasn’t normal. No one really paid attention to the commentator’s talking. Everyone was focused on the match.

“Who’s going to win?” Chen Guo grabbed Ye Xiu’s arm and asked. This match really was even. It was impossible to tell who had the advantage. Chen Guo doubted that she was good enough to tell, so she asked the more skilled Ye Xiu on his thoughts.

“It’s hard to tell right now.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?”

“They still have a lot of health left.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you mean?” Chen Guo didn’t understand.

“Right now, neither of them are able to fully take the initiative. They still have a quarter of their health left, so they still can’t rely on a single opportunity to win the match. Just a bit more. They have to at least reach red blood!” Ye Xiu said.

“And after they reach red blood?” Chen Guo asked.

“After they reach red blood, a single high-damage ultimate can decide the match.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh…….” Chen Guo nodded her head in understanding. As for Tang Rou, she was extremely focused on the match. After all, the Battle Mage was the class she was currently using. This match could open up a lot of doors for her. It was just that her Soft Mist wasn’t even Level 40 yet, so she still lacked a lot of the skills. The number of things she could learn were limited. However, just from the low-leveled skills that Soft Mist could use, Tang Rou could already see a huge difference between them.

Whether it was the player or the character……

The audience wasn’t cheering anymore. Because in this type of deadlock, while the two sides were continuously attacking each other, they were also continuously blocking each other’s attacks. The audience had thought that there would be a climax soon, but the only thing that came up was a blank. Shouting and cheering when there was nothing to shout about made everyone feel a bit awkward. If they kept on doing so, wouldn’t it show how unskilled they were?

Thus, the audience quietly watched and quietly awaited the match’s conclusion.

Everyone suddenly awoke with a start: Ah! The two characters’ health dropped again.

No one knew the details on how exactly their health dropped. Many in the audience were already at a loss about whether this match could be considered as intense. The two were always fighting, but it also never seemed like anything was happening. The only thing they could see was their health slowly dropping. But then after ten minutes, the two characters’ health suddenly began to flash red.

“Red blood!” Chen Guo called.

“Yeah, it’s time for the match to be decided. Watch carefully.” Ye Xiu said.

The time for the match to be decided had come.

Ye Xiu wasn’t the only one to understand this reasoning. The people in the pro player seats were all holding their breaths.

The previous ten minutes were just a buildup. This final moment would be the climax. The climax for the entire match would also be the match’s deciding point.

On stage, after the exchange, One Autumn Leaf suddenly retreated. In this crucial moment, he changed strategies and gave up on blindly attacking. Relying on his Battle Mage’s buffs from the Chasers, as well as the high mobility from Battle Spirit, he began to wander, waiting for the opportunity to move, ready to give the final blow to his opponent.

And Han Wenqing? In this final moment, he would use his advance forward strategy to the end.

“Wah!!!” The silent audience suddenly erupted into cries and applause…… After this change, in these audience members’ eyes, which hadn’t been able to clearly see the situation, Han Wenqing had taken the upswing. Even though the reason for the audience’s eruption was wrong, the match’s climax had begun.

“F*ck, this stupid Sun Xiang!!!” Chen Guo shouted angrily. In this match, she wasn’t some neutral fan. She was one hundred percent hoping for Sun Xiang to win. But most of this was due to her being a supporter of the team. After all, Sun Xiang hadn’t been in Excellent Era for long. Chen Guo hadn’t become his brainless fan yet! Now that she suddenly saw him running around with his tail behind, she immediately felt extremely disdainful of him.

“Don’t be alarmed. Just watch carefully.” Ye Xiu urged.

“Look at that hopeless guy!” Chen Guo shouted.

“I feel like he’s playing quite cool-headed.” Tang Rou, who hadn’t been participating in their discussion, interrupted.

“I agree.” Ye Xiu also nodded his head.

“Really? Then that’s good……” Chen Guo didn’t argue. She had been nervous, but after hearing that Sun Xiang might not lose, she felt quite gratified.

Attack! In this crucial moment, Han Wenqing seemed to not know what the word cautious meant. As if he didn’t know what calm meant either, he continued to attack ferociously.

Collapsing Fist! Desert Dust punched straight forward at the One Autumn Leaf whom had just rolled backwards in a flurry.

Whirlwind Kick! Desert Dust chased after, blowing up a whirlwind of air. The two skills had been linked together very quickly, but Sun Xiang moved faster. His One Autumn Leaf didn’t get up after rolling backwards and instead rolled to the side. This was only a basic movement, but seamlessly connecting these two rolls like this definitely wasn’t easy. If the second roll had been slightly delayed, then he would have certainly been swept away by the Whirlwind Kick.

Soaring Tiger!!!

Han Wenqing once again used a high-leveled skill at an inopportune moment. Desert Dust flew forward, his two legs aimed towards One Autumn Leaf.

“Pu!”

This time, even a seamlessly connected roll wouldn’t be able to dodge this. Desert Dust’s two legs shot straight towards One Autumn Leaf’s head, knocking him down. Desert Dust followed the momentum and leaped behind One Autumn Leaf. He kicked again in mid-air for an Eagle Stamp in preparation to end One Autumn Leaf. Soaring Tiger’s damage wasn’t enough to kill him instantly, but with these other skills, it would be enough.

The audience thought that the match would end in this instant. Chen Guo was practically about to start cursing, when she saw the knocked down One Autumn Leaf roll backwards with a Quick Recover. His character hadn’t yet completely gotten up when his spear Evil Annihilation pricked forward and diagonally, a Sky Strike.

Sky Strike was the Battle Mage’s lowest leveled skill, but this Sky Strike made when the opponent was behind him. Using this abnormal pattern, One Autumn Leaf snuck the attack in and collided it with Desert Dust’s Eagle Stamp.

A stamp down and a slash up.

The two skills collided with neither side winning. One Autumn Leaf was forced sliding backwards and Desert Dust was pushed back in the air as well.

Following that, One Autumn Leaf pulled back his spear and then lifted the black Evil Annihilation like a dragon raising its head, accumulating surging magic power onto its tip. A Battle Mage was still a mage. His battle strength wasn’t completely physical. An even greater part of it was magic.

Evil Annihilation thrust forward. The accumulated magic had congealed into a black dragon. Its roaring lifted the dust and rocks, pouncing towards Desert Dust.

Battle Mage Level 70 Ultimate: Rising Dragon Soars Through the Sky!

The audience once again thought that the match was decided. This time, Chen Guo was ready to cheer out loud.

“GLORY!!!”

The electronic screen also displayed this word.

But after seeing the magic dragon dissipate from Evil Annihilation’s Rising Dragon Soars the Heavens, the players discovered in astonishment that Desert Dust was standing next to One Autumn Leaf.

A target hit by the Rising Dragon Soars the Heavens could not appear next to the user, which meant that the attack had not connected.

The one who had obtained the glory was Han Wenqing and his Desert Dust. One Autumn Leaf had fallen.

Chapter 312 – You’re Still Too Green

The originally orderly round of applause gradually turned into chaos, until the noise completely faded into nothing.

The audience members that had been applauding for Sun Xiang had already stopped in embarrassment. And those who were feeling sorry for Han Wenqing suddenly flew from hell to heaven and didn’t know how to react for a moment.

Even the host was secretly celebrating after a moment of shock. He had almost announced the incorrect result. He had thought that Han Wenqing had certainly died and was just about to congratulate Sun Xiang on his victory.

The dead silence continued for a few seconds, until the audience finally regained their composure and erupted in applause. The broadcast used this moment of shock to quickly show the camera shot of that final instant. Every screen switched to the frame of that cut and repeatedly transmitted it.

Only then was the audience able to understand.

The moment the black dragon roared forward from One Autumn Leaf’s Rising Dragon Soars Through the Sky, the still in mid-air Desert Dust repeatedly stamped down.

Those who were familiar with Glory recognized that he was using Eagle Stamp.

Eagle Stamp didn’t consist of only a single stamp. As the skill level increased, the number of stamps could reach five. Desert Dust had clearly leveled the skill to this point. When his stamp collided with Sky Strike, even though his character was hit away, Eagle Stamp’s skill hadn’t been interrupted. The next four stamps allowed Desert Dust to drop down diagonally.

By relying on this diagonal drop, Desert Dust was able to dodge the black dragon’s roar. After landing on the ground, he immediately used a Dashing Jab. At this moment, One Autumn Leaf’s Rising Dragon Soars Through the Sky hadn’t completely finished yet, so how he could dodge this attack? With only a sliver of health remaining, he fell under this Level 10 skill.

This short instant played repeatedly. The broadcast hurried with their work and cut out all of the exchanges after the red blood and then showed them on the screen from different points of view. The replay at normal speed looked like it was playing at high-speed and the slow-motion replay looked like the proper speed.

The applause continued to resound.

Han Wenqing stood up from his platform. In the same manner that he had appeared on stage, he walked down to the center.

As for Sun Xiang? He couldn’t believe what had happened. He couldn’t believe that he’d lost on that final strike.

As a pro player, losing was a very common occurrence. It was just that he had been so confident in this match. He had already said that he would end the grudge between Excellent Era and Tyranny. But he was the one who had actually lost. It truly made him feel ashamed.

Sun Xiang really wished that he could hide behind the platform and wait until the All-Star Weekend’s first day ended before slipping out. But he knew that this wasn’t possible. Hiding wasn’t an option. The longer he hid, the more embarrassed he’d be.

Sun Xiang sucked in a deep breath and finally stood up. He had to face what was to come.

He walked down from his platform and saw that Han Wenqing was already standing at the center of the stage. Han Wenqing didn’t say anything and didn’t leave. He just stood there.

Sun Xiang’s eyes twitched.

Han Wenqing was waiting for him and certainly wanted to say something. Unfortunately, he definitely wasn’t a friendly senior.

He finally walked to the center of the stage and saw that Han Wenqing’s cold glare was fixated on him.

Sun Xiang walked in front of him and was still able to force a smile.

Tyranny and Excellent Era were originally rivals in the Alliance. And before the match, Sun Xiang had even said such arrogant words. It was obvious just how unfriendly this match was. Despite the host’s abundant experience, at this moment, even he didn’t know what to say. He looked to the left and then looked to the right. Suddenly, he noticed that Han Wenqing’s cold stare was aimed at him. The host shivered. He didn’t say anything and handed the mic over to Han Wenqing.

“Ha ha.” Han Wenqing laughed, “The children want a change in dynasties, but they’re still too green.”

The entire stadium went into an uproar, especially the media. Everyone was excited.

No one had thought that this year’s Rookie Challenge would turn out like this.

Han Wenqing! He deserved to be called the Tyrant. His taunt wasn’t aimed solely at Sun Xiang, but also at the earlier Tang Hao, who had said “the junior succeeds the senior”. And perhaps he was also including Gao Yingjie, who had beaten Wang Jiexi earlier, as well.

This year’s Rookie Challenge kept having actual challenges to seniors. The previous two had been successful, but when it got to Han Wenqing, he finally helped the veterans restore their reputation. His “still too green” represented a powerful reply to all of those rookies who were impatiently hoping to beat the veterans.

Sun Xiang’s face was filled with bitterness, but what could he do? Han Wenqing’s counterattack had been made after winning the match. He had proof to show, magnifying the strength by a hundred times.

Sun Xiang had originally been someone who was put shoulder to shoulder with Gods like Han Wenqing. But his evaluation of “still too green” mercilessly killed off Sun Xiang’s status as a God. At this moment, he had been degraded into a true rookie, impatient to seize the top. But in truth, he had already reached there……. There is a story where someone tries to steal a chicken, but ends up losing a handful of rice. It was just like this.

And Han Wenqing wasn’t done yet.

His previous words had been directed at all of the rookies, but his next few words were especially for Sun Xiang.

“Not bad. You played quite well.” Han Wenqing also said these courteous words, but his ice-cold tone made it feel awkward.

“Being able to accurately hit out a Sky Strike from behind is something that few people can do. Amazing.” Han Wenqing said.

Sun Xiang was astonished. That truly was a god-like display of his mechanics and decision-making. It was exceptionally brilliant. He didn’t think that Han Wenqing would especially highlight it.

The broadcasts also followed along. When they heard Han Wenqing’s words, they immediately showed the clip of Sun Xiang’s brilliant Sky Strike. For a short while, the atmosphere turned friendlier. The host’s eyes brightened and he wanted to say something too, but Han Wenqing spoke first: “But if that was Ye Qiu, then at the very least, he wouldn’t have missed that Rising Dragon.”

After saying this, he turned around and walked out.

The situation suddenly turned stiff. Han Wenqing had went in a circle with Sun Xiang, but with this, everyone was able to understand what he was saying.

“You’re quite good, but compared to us veterans, you’re still too green.”

And even worse, he had brought Ye Qiu into it.

The Excellent Era fans who were ready to jump up and shout for Sun Xiang all silently sat back down after hearing this.

Although Ye Qiu had retired, his glorious silhouette still wouldn’t leave their hearts. If Han Wenqing had said that Sun Xiang wasn’t as good as he himself was, everyone would definitely jump up and argue. But by using Ye Qiu as a comparison, Excellent Era’s fans could only accept this. Chen Guo was one of these fans.

After Han Wenqing won and began to ridicule Sun Xiang, she flew into a rage. But after he mentioned Ye Qiu, she suddenly quieted down and silently sat back down like a lady.

The stadium once again turned silent and watched as Han Wenqing walked off stage. The screens were still playing Sun Xiang’s brilliant Sky Strike, but the scene was quickly changed. It was clear that the broadcasters felt like showing it didn’t fit the situation.

Sun Xiang was left alone on stage. The host stood to one side and truly didn’t know what to say.

In the end, Sun Xiang took the initiative and grabbed the microphone.

“I lost today and there’s nothing I can say about it. But tomorrow, that might not be the case!” After saying this, he handed the mic back to the host and walked off the stage without looking back.

The audience silently watched. This time’s Rookie Challenge brought about a lot of different feelings. At this moment, no one knew if this was a good or bad thing.

The atmosphere in the stadium was stiff, which was something the host or broadcast company definitely did not hope to see. They immediately cleared the stage and moved to the next match.

The next match would be today’s final challenge. It had originally been a show the hosts had meticulously planned out. However, they didn’t expect that the Rookie Challenge would be so eye-catching. It was likely that the show they had planned wouldn’t bring out the desired results.

The hosts were from Team Samsara and their final match would be a rookie from their own team against their ace player, Zhou Zekai.

Samsara obviously couldn’t sacrifice Zhou Zekai to a new rookie. They had planned on using the Rookie Challenge to put a spotlight on Zhou Zekai. With a player from the same team, Zhou Zekai could make the show much more dazzling than anyone else’s with greater ease. But Samsara hadn’t expected that the rookies this time would all be so strong and create such a strong wave.

For the Rookie Challenge, the hosts only got to know the participants beforehand. They had expected it to be the usual, where the rookie and the senior would have a friendly match. But this time, none of the rookies thought of the match as a show and played for real. The veterans refused to fall behind and, in the end, the Rookie Challenge turned into a huge competition where the new and old fought to win. This was something that completely surpassed Samsara’s planned performance. At this moment, it seemed like they should just have things turn out like the first match. That way, everyone could appreciate the new projection technology. The dazzling colors would attract a few eyes and perhaps leave more of an impression.

And right now? When the challenger’s name came out, the audience’s reactions were clearly mediocre. After seeing the huge climax between Sun Xiang and Han Wenqing, the audience members were no longer expecting anything.

Samsara members were depressed, but there was nothing they could do and could only continue as planned. The rookie and Zhou Zekai went up on stage, said a few words to each other, and then fought. The two fought beautifully and splendidly. Since it was Samsara’s home grounds, the audience’s reactions were still relatively warm, but they were only warm and far from excited.

Samsara was helpless. Their meticulously planned performance really did become simply a performance in the eyes of the audience.

Chapter 313 – News Conference

After the final match ended, the audience’s applause sounded somewhat mechanical. They clearly weren’t feeling any genuine excitement and were only giving them a courtesy clap.

Samsara’s ace player, Zhou Zekai, didn’t seem to mind. Once he finished the match, he waved his hands to the audience and gave a “thank you” before swiftly exiting the stage.

From the start of the opening show, he was supposed to be tonight’s brightest star. But in the end, it looked as if he was a part of some trash program played after midnight. All of Samsara sighed. Although this year’s Rookie Challenge was undoubtedly the most spectacular and successful show in Glory’s history, the competition hadn’t given any spotlight to their pro players. It had only made them even more depressed when they thought about it.

Once the Rookie Challenge ended, the All-Star Weekend’s first day was basically over. All of the matches were 1v1s, but even though each match wasn’t long, the intermission, talking and opening had made the event take almost two hours.

After this was another projection show and some raffle events. If this was in the past, by this time, most of the audience would have already left the stadium. But with the new projection technology, a large part of the audience weren’t satisfied just yet and stayed to continue admiring it.

The ending show continued for almost half an hour before the hosts officially announced that the first day of the All-Star Weekend was over. During this half hour, the security personnel, in charge of maintaining order as people left, had gotten to their positions. The stadium lights gradually brightened until the whole stadium was lit. The audience got up and began to exit the stadium. Several of the crazier fans were still looking left and right. While they were at the scene, they hoped to find a chance to see or meet one of their idols.

However, the host had obviously prepared for this. The pro players had their own passageway and wouldn’t mix together with the normal audience. When the lights turned on and the audience turned to look at the pro players’ seats, they discovered that they had already dispersed.

The crowd of people slowly moved outside. After they were outside, they immediately felt more freedom. Many of the audience members were local people, so they already had plenty of experience with the stadium. After exiting, they didn’t stop to rest and immediately scrambled over to the roadside. Even though several, more business-minded taxis had come knowing that there would be business here, there weren’t enough, making the roadsides unbelievably noisy.

These three weren’t unfamiliar with this type of scene. Ye Xiu, of course, obviously didn’t need to be mentioned. As for Chen Guo and Tang Rou, the Internet Cafe was right next to Excellent Era’s stadium. Whenever Excellent Era had a match in their stadium, the scene looked the same. How could they not have experienced this before? In the end, the three loitered around for another half an hour before finally getting a taxi.

When they returned to the hotel, the three were both tired and hungry. They had eaten their dinner on the plane. Once they arrived at City S, they ran straight to the hotel and then hurried over to the stadium without any time to rest. While they were focused on watching the matches, waiting in line and waiting for the taxi, they didn’t feel tired or hungry. But once they arrived at their final destination, they immediately felt as if their hearts were stuck to their backs and rushed straight for the dining hall.

After picking a few items, the three of their gazes fell onto the large TV screen in the dining hall.

Nowadays, the eSports business was vigorously developing and the Glory Alliance was among those that stood out. Adding in the extremely large Glory player base, the foundation for it was extremely solid. The hosting of Glory’s All-Star Weekend was naturally a grand occasion for City S. At this moment, the TV screen was showing a few highlights from the first day of the All-Star Weekend’s Rookie Challenge.

This went from the opening show to each match in the Challenge.

The three had just seen these, so when they saw the highlights, they didn’t find anything new. Chen Guo kept her excited state and called the two of them to quickly look whenever anything spectacular happened. The only gloomy part was the moment when Han Wenqing beat Sun Xiang. This was originally the night’s highest point, but for Chen Guo, she clearly wasn’t happy about it.

After the highlights were shown, the TV screen switched to the news conference after the event.

As the host, even though Samsara felt somewhat depressed at the way things turned out, they still praised the success of the projection technology, as well as the brilliance of the Rookie Challenge.

They then invited a few all-stars to talk with them. Most of them went by the official view and praised this year’s event. But how could reporters be so easily dispatched? The dispute over the new and the old in the Rookie Challenge was naturally tossed over to them in a series of questions.

But the Alliance was already prepared for this. The members who were sent out to talk with the reporters were all experts at interviews. Against these sharp questions, not one of them didn’t laugh, stressed sportsmanship and felt that the fight between the new and old players were a reflection of Glory’s development.

Clearly, the reporters weren’t going to get much out of these players. The reporters waited patiently though, because they knew that, according to the rules, part of the participants in the Rookie Challenge had to accept interviews.

In the end, four of the participants from the Rookie Challenge appeared at the news conference. From the rookies came Dai Yanqi from the first match and Samsara’s rookie from the sixth match. As for the veterans, Wang Jiexi and Zhou Zekai showed up.

When the reporters saw this, they took note of the host’s slyness! None of the people they wanted to interview appeared. What was there to ask Dai Yanqi and that Samsara rookie? The only person the reporters were interested in was Wang Jiexi.

The reporters quickly flocked over and flooded Wang Jiexi with questions. Naturally, their questions were focused on his loss to Gao Yingjie.

Wang Jiexi was an old veteran. Even more so, that match had been completely engineered by him, so the current situation had been anticipated long before. Him participating in the news conference was something he personally requested. How could he be unprepared for this?

Wang Jiexi didn’t hurry or delay over the reporters’ questions and replied clearly to them.

Even though the reporters didn’t get anything amazing like they were expecting out of him, Wang Jiexi’s truthful responses were acceptable to the reporters. It wasn’t easy for them, either. Facing the star, who knew how many times they received supercilious looks from their sharp questions. There was no shortage of questions towards Wang Jiexi. There were even questions on whether he intentionally lost, which Wang Jiexi patiently replied to.

Compared to him, Zhou Zekai and the others weren’t given much attention. Only those who weren’t able to squeeze into Wang Jiexi’s crowd came to ask them a few questions.

This type of scene was quite common. In reality, getting interviewed wasn’t something exciting for the majority of the pro players. Some of them were even happy when they were ignored by the reporters.

For example, Zhou Zekai, who was currently Glory’s most popular player, felt quite pleased when receiving such little attention.

Though, compared to the two rookies, Zhou Zekai still received more attention. The God’s opinions on things were much more attractive than some rookie’s opinion. The majority of the players who couldn’t get to Wang Jiexi ran over to Zhou Zekai.

“As a representative of the mid-generation players, towards this year’s Rookie Challenge and towards the rookie’s drive, do you feel like this sort of behavior is a form of disrespect towards the veterans?” a reporter asked.

Silence…… Several seconds of silence. After thinking for a while, Zhou Zekai lifted his head and then said earnestly: “It’s fine?”

And then…. and then there was nothing after that. After saying these two words, Zhou Zekai already looked at the reporters, indicating that he was ready for the next question.

The reporters were stump. They did know beforehand that interviewing him was a very difficult task. Considered as the number one most handsome guy in Glory, he definitely had the appearance to match it. But when it came to talking with others, he was quite uncommunicative, especially towards the media. For extremely long questions, he would sometimes only reply with a “Yeah”, “Ah!”, “Oh” or a “No” like how he had replied earlier with his “It’s fine?”. It couldn’t be said that he didn’t reply to the reporter’s question, but……. What was the point in reporting this type of response?

“Ha ha ha ha……” Chen Guo, who was watching the interview, laughed, pointing at the screen: “I like watching his interviews.”

For Tang Rou, who was watching an interview of Zhou Zekai for the first time, she immediately discovered that he was different than the norm. She asked in astonishment: “Were those two words his reply?”

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

But how could the reporters be so quick to give up? It was rare for them to not need to scramble in order to ask Zhou Zekai questions. Everyone was determined to overcome this difficult obstacle.

“Tang Hao defeated Lin Jingyan today. Do you think he can be called Glory’s number one Brawler now?” A very direct question.

Zhou Zekai thought for several seconds again before speaking: “They played very well.”

“They? Who exactly do you mean by they?”

“Um……” thinking, “Everyone!”

“Everyone? Then do you think your skill level is at the same level as Yu Nian’s?” Yu Nian was the rookie who played against Zhou Zekai.

“Uh…… he tried very hard!” Zhou Zekai said.

“But trying hard doesn’t mean he’s skilled, no?” Another reporter asked.

“As long as you try your best, then it’s good.” Zhou Zekai said after a short pause.

The reporters had their cheeks streaked with tears. Chen Guo was already hitting the table in laughter. Tang Rou couldn’t resist laughing either and asked Ye Xiu: “Is he actually like that or is he just playing with the reporters?”

“Trust me. He really is like that.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Chapter 314 – I Wouldn’t Get Tired Even After Another Ten Years

“Ha ha ha ha, yeah, yeah. He’s always like that. He’s pretty funny, isn’t he?” Hearing Ye Xiu’s affirmation, Chen Guo also nodded her head and said a few more words about Zhou Zekai.

On TV, the reporters admitted their complete defeat and the scene returned back to Wang Jiexi. His interview session was almost over. Wang Jiexi really knew how to push what he wanted through. During the interview, he spared no efforts in pushing Gao Yingjie into the spotlight. The phrase he used most in his answers was “Tiny Herb’s future”.

Wang Jiexi’s passion might not have been easily felt by the audience, but pro players were easily moved by it.

Especially Ye Xiu, who had seen through his intent. In his eyes, Wang Jiexi and Gao Yingjie had been the biggest highlight of the Rookie Challenge.

He had silently devoted everything he had to the team. Wang Jiexi’s actions were on a completely different level than everyone else.

He should have been the one to have received the most applause and respect in the Rookie Challenge, but there was no way he was going to get it. In the future, he would be remembered as the God that was beaten by his own team’s rookie.

“Eat! Are you not going to eat?” Chen Guo tapped Ye Xiu, who had been thinking of something else.

“Oh!” Ye Xiu turned his body and continued to eat. Chen Guo once again made a few more comments on Wang Jiexi’s match, which Ye Xiu only smiled at as he listened. He wouldn’t justify what Wang Jiexi did because that wasn’t what Wang Jiexi wanted. Wang Jiexi was a player who was completely devoted to his team. He was the Alliance’s best team captain.

The three finished eating. The news conference was done as well, so the three returned to their rooms. The day had been quite long. After eating, they quickly fell asleep.

Chen Guo had a good sleep schedule. On the second day, she woke up naturally. Although, before she was entirely awake, she heard what seemed to be keyboard and mouse noises.

As the owner of an Internet Cafe, Chen Guo wasn’t a stranger to these sounds. Now that she lived in a room with good soundproofing inside the Internet Cafe, she wasn’t disturbed by these sounds. In the early years, when the Internet Cafe was only a single small room, she shared the room with the customers and the computers. During that time, who knew how many times she had slept on the temporary bed.

At that time, as soon as she woke up, she would hear clicking and tapping noises from keyboards and mice. There was also her father at the bedside, waving his hands as if to fan away the smoke from Chen Guo. No one knew how effective it was, but he always did it like so.

When she woke up today and heard these sounds, Chen Guo felt a sense of nostalgia, as if she were still dreaming.

However, she quickly came to a realization. She was definitely at the hotel and on her bed. She turned her head, along with her blanket, and saw that Tang Rou had already woken up. She was sitting in front of the hotel’s computer. The clicking and tapping was obviously coming from there and, of course, she had woken up early to play Glory.

“You’re really working hard.” Chen Guo said.

“Ah, you woke up?” Tang Rou turned her head.

“Yeah. When did you get up?” Chen Guo got up from her bed and asked.

“Not too long ago.” Tang Rou said.

Chen Guo walked up to her and looked. She thought that there was something really exciting that Tang Rou couldn’t be calm about. But when she got closer, she saw that Tang Rou was only leveling and killing monsters.

“You’re really working hard…….” Chen Guo muttered her previous words.

Tang Rou chuckled. She wanted to hurry and level, so she could play together with Chen Guo in the Heavenly Domain. This had been her previous plan. And now, she had a few other thoughts after seeing yesterday’s Rookie Challenge.

Even though the rookies were some of the least skilled pro players within the pro scene, compared to normal players, they were still extremely skilled. Tang Rou had already experienced this when she fought against Tiny Herb’s members in 1v1s. She had still yet to obtain a single victory. She knew that even though she had some talent, compared to those in the pro scene, she was still far from them.

And this year’s Rookie Challenge had a lot fewer traditional rookies. Participants such as Gao Yingjie, Tang Hao, and Sun Xiang were exceptionally skilled pro players. Their skill levels were on a completely different level than normal rookies. Their spectacular fights against their seniors were truly exciting.

And the atmosphere was only complemented by the new projection technology.

Tang Rou had been moved by it and felt a sort of longing for this type of intense competition. She discovered how lacking everything she did in game was to this. Last night, when she got into bed, she had even thought of the invitation that Tiny Herb’s captain had given to her.

She had already figured out who that person’s identity was.

Tiny Herb captain, Wang Jiexi. After watching yesterday’s interview, Tang Rou remembered the name and remember the person.

Pro Alliance? Tang Rou felt a wave of emotions after thinking of Wang Jiexi’s invitation. When she thought of these two words, she felt an almost magical force attracting her.

However, she clearly understood her position. Wang Jiexi had beaten her in less than 30 seconds. If she really did enter the pro scene……. Tang Rou couldn’t help but think of her initial fight versus Ye Xiu and how she had lost over and over again, completely helpless.

She was still far from being strong! Tang Rou understood this well. In the pro scene, the truly strong could be found everywhere.

That boy who beat Wang Jiexi, that guy afterwards who was the same class as Steamed Bun , that One Autumn Leaf that Chen Guo really liked and the person who beat him……. Against these people, which one of these couldn’t beat her in 30 seconds?

She had to improve! She had to rise!

Tang Rou suddenly felt a rush of motivation. She had motivation and direction.

After getting strong, she would beat Ye Xiu. That was her initial motivation for playing Glory. But now, she was even more motivated because she found so many more opponents to beat.

When she entered the scene, these opponents would fall one after the other to her battle spear. Tang Rou had carried that sort of frenzy with her to sleep.

And when she woke up, it overtook her again. The powerful motivation had gotten Tang Rou to immediately get up and play Glory.

She said to Chen Guo that she had woken “not too long ago”. This was only what she felt. She had already been playing Glory for nearly three hours.

Chen Guo, who had finished her morning routine, saw that Tang Rou was completely focused on the game, so she immediately called: “Hey, hey, stop playing. First, wash your face and brush your teeth, okay? Hurry up and then we’ll go eat breakfast.”

“Yeah, yeah. One sec.” Tang Rou replied, but she didn’t move.

As an experienced gamer, Chen Guo could immediately tell that Tang Rou really did need a bit of time to finish what she was doing, so after throwing down a “hurry”, she left the room to knock on the next door.

“Who is it!” Ye Xiu called.

“You’re still sleeping? Get up!” Chen Guo shouted.

To her surprise, the door quickly opened with Ye Xiu inside, dressed all neatly.

“You woke up pretty early!” Chen Guo said. Ye Xiu chuckled and then ran back into his room. Chen Guo walked in and looked. D*mn, this guy was also playing Glory. These two people had gone out on vacation and they were still like this. The rooms cost 1500 RMB for a day! Did these two guys think that this was an Internet Cafe? That was too luxurious!

“Both of you, stop playing. Let’s eat breakfast!” Chen Guo said.

“Both?”

“You’ve completely ruined Little Tang!” Chen Guo could only scold Ye Xiu.

“She’ll do well in the future.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Oh?” Chen Guo suddenly had interest, “How good do you think she’ll be able to get?”

“As long as she doesn’t lose interest, she shouldn’t have any problems entering the pro scene. As for just how high she’ll go, that’ll depend on how hard she works.” Ye Xiu said.

“How hard she works? You’re questioning how hardworking Little Tang is?” Chen Guo laughed.

“She truly is very hardworking when she’s interested. But what happens when she loses interest one day?” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo thought for a bit and then jumped up: “That’s what I mean! You guys need to control your gaming! If you guys keep playing for so long everyday, then won’t you quickly lose interest? Do you understand what it means to maintain the game’s freshness?”

“I don’t need to.” Ye Xiu chuckled, “Even if I played for another ten years, I wouldn’t lose interest.”

Chen Guo stared blankly. Another ten years? Chen Guo thought of herself as someone who loved Glory. But after playing for five years, she couldn’t help but acknowledge that she wasn’t as passionate at it compared to her first years. The current her could control the amount of time she spend on the game very well. Apart from having better self-control, it had to be said that her loss of interest was a factor as well.

Not losing interest even after ten years?

Chen Guo might say it if she was bragging, but Ye Xiu’s tone seemed very casual, but also carried resoluteness and confidence.

Ye Xiu turned his head in a very carefree manner and continued to play.

“Breakfast……” Chen Guo suddenly switched to the subject.

“Oh, oh, one sec!” Ye Xiu played earnestly.

“Okay.” Chen Guo said and left the room, returning to hers. Tang Rou had finished her playing and was currently doing her morning routine in the bathroom.

“Little Tang!” Chen Guo stood by the door and called.

“Hm?” Tang Rou bit down on her toothbrush and turned around to look at her.

“If you kept playing Glory like this, how many years do you think you’ll be able to play for?” Chen Guo asked.

“Years?” Tang Rou was stumped by the question.

“I have no idea.” After a pause, Tang Rou turned her head to reply. To her, this was her most honest answer.

Chapter 315 – Event Day 2

“Do you find Glory fun?” Chen Guo asked solemnly.

“It’s not bad.” Tang Rou said.

“Do you think you’ll find it more and more fun as you play?” Chen Guo asked.

“Yeah, I have that type of feeling.”

Chen Guo smiled. Having this sort of upward trend was a good sign. Interest could be built up, too!

After tidying everything up, the three went to eat breakfast together. At the front desk, Chen Guo grabbed a free City S tour guide and looked through it: “See if there’s anything fun to do.”

Ye Xiu and Tang Rou quickly glanced at each other, but Chen Guo caught them. She didn’t even lift her head as she said: “Don’t think of staying in your room and playing games. We’re here on a business trip. There are official matters to attend to.”

Official matters….. Ye Xiu and Tang Rou began to sweat as they listened to Chen Guo studying: “Nanquan Road’s pedestrian street is City S’s largest dining and shopping street. This seems pretty good! Look.” Chen Guo put the tour guide in front of their faces.

Ye Xiu took it and nodded his head. He then suggested: “Boss, what do you say we find a few relatively large Internet Cafes to get a feel for their business and service?”

“I like this idea!” Tang Rou nodded her head.

“No need. I grew up in an Internet Cafe. Who could be more experienced at this than me?” Chen Guo denied Ye Xiu’s suggestion.

After saying this, the three all burst out laughing. Going out on a business trip was obviously complete nonsense. Checking out other Internet Cafes would just be beating a dead horse. Those sorts of thoughts were obvious at a glance.

“Alright, I won’t stop you guys.” Chen Guo was honest, “You guys can do what you want! I’m going to go on a stroll, though. I haven’t come all the way here to do nothing.”

“Uh……” Ye Xiu and Tang Rou thought. Their boss Chen Guo had paid for their tickets, road fares, and hotel fees. She brought them along for a vacation and if the two of them only played Glory, then it’d be somewhat disrespectful. The two slapped the table and decided that they would go out today and not play Glory. They would take a good look around City S.

“Really? Then hurry up and come here. Let’s look for where we should go!” Chen Guo quickly handed over the tour guide to them so they could look at it.

Ye Xiu definitely wasn’t a person who was interested in shopping, so he simply stood to the side and was responsible for nodding his head and saying “Okay.”. After Chen Guo and Tang Rou discussed for a bit, he had no idea where they were going. But in any case, he would follow along!

Their day went by richly. The two bright, beautiful girls attracted the attention of others wherever they went. There was also the person behind the two girls who attracted a different sort of attention. He always looked so lifeless. He seemed like the sort of guy who’d shuffle his feet when he walked.

Ye Xiu’s lifeless look was something Chen Guo and Tang Rou were used to seeing, so they didn’t really care. They followed along their planned route. Initially, they chose five destinations to go to. But in the end, they only got through two of them before they ran out of time. At a modern fashion store, the two sisters spent a full two hours wandering around.

During those two hours, Ye Xiu sat at a seat specially provided by the store for resting. There sat a full row of men. Everyone looked at each other and, if they had something to say, they’d chat with the person next to them. Finally, they chatted until they got to the event that the city was hosting, Glory’s All-Star Weekend, which immediately turned into the main subject. There were evidently quite a few Glory fans here. Everyone discussed excitedly. Some of the men didn’t even want to leave when their female companions finished looking around.

“Go look around some more. Have you went over there, yet?” The men, who were called to leave, often refused in this way.

After finishing up, the two girls had bought quite a lot of things. The most extravagant spender was Chen Guo, who had even bought a pair of high quality binoculars, which were clearly going to be used for tonight’s All-Star Event.

The two girls wanted to continue, but the All-Star Event was something that couldn’t be missed and, in the end, they reluctantly called a taxi and returned to the hotel. After dropping their bags to the floor, they immediately headed towards Samsara’s stadium.

All-Star Weekend Day 2. The pamphlet handed out showed today’s list of events.

The nature of the second day was always as a show. There were almost no competitive elements in the matches. Today’s event was often filled with mini-games, such as Glory’s running race, climbing race, target match, obstacle course, etc.

These very ordinary sounding names naturally had a different feeling to them when they were placed in the game. The key condition was that, in these mini-games, many of them had no restrictions on players attacking each other. Killing opponents was perfectly fine. It was just that everyone had to take note that they weren’t the only contestants there. If two people were too caught up in fighting each other, then the others would win.

These events had been there since the start and were well-received by the audience, so they hadn’t gotten rid of them. Many players even tried to emulate these mini-games for fun.

The second day was also a day where they interacted with the audience more. For these small mini-games, audience members would be randomly chosen to play with the pros.

After showing the mini-game using the projection technology, the event officially entered the first segment: Hurdles.

The projection lit up and an athletic track appeared on stage. Eight runways and eight participants. It looked very realistic.

The host in charge was currently drawing straws. The audience all had their own seat numbers. The chosen all-star would randomly choose audience members to go onstage and play with the pro in the match.

The chosen all-star for the first match was Samsara’s ace player, Zhou Zekai.

“Zekai, how do you plan on choosing four members from the audience?” The host asked Zhou Zekai.

“Uh, it doesn’t matter!” Zhou Zekai said after thinking for a bit.

“We can do it randomly using a computer or you can call out random seat numbers yourself. You could also pick up something and throw it at the audience. Whoever catches it comes. Or if you have any other ideas, you’re welcome to go ahead and do it. How about it? Do you want to think of your own method?” the host said.

“Okay, then that one!” Zhou Zekai said.

“That one?”

“By random.” Zhou Zekai said.

“By random? Are you talking about using the computer?”

“Yeah!”

“Then, then we’ll use that method to choose an audience member. Look at the screen and when you say stop, then it’ll stop.” the host said. The screen began to display numbers. Zhou Zekai immediately called for it to stop.

The person controlling the screen was somewhat delayed. After Zhou Zekai said stop, two more numbers passed. The host began to sweat furiously: “So you’re yelling stop as soon as possible. Okay, that’s fine. Let’s see who our guest is…… Oh, you’re already here.”

The host didn’t need to call whoever got chosen to come up. The chosen guest had already rushed forward excitedly.

“Okay, next up, for the second guest, are you going to switch methods, Zhou Zekai?” The host asked.

Zhou Zekai’s hands quickly rose. But before anyone could see what he was doing, his hands dropped and he said: “Uh, keep going!”

“Keep going? Are you saying to keep the numbers on the screen rolling? Or are you going to be using a different method?”

Zhou Zekai nodded his head.

“Okay! Then the screen will continue rolling. But this time you can……”

“Stop….”

“You can let it roll for a bit longer…..” The host hadn’t finished his words, when Zhou Zekai had already told him to stop. Another seat member was chosen.

Again, without the host needing to call the guest forward, the guest began to head towards the stage.

“Okay, there’s still two more. Zhou Zekai, do you want to switch methods?” The host simply stopped bothering and directly went forward.

“No need.”

“Okay! Then this time, can you wait a bit longer before telling it to stop?” The host asked.

“Okay.” Zhou Zekai nodded his head.

“Good! The rolling continues.” After the host announced it, the numbers began to roll. The host hadn’t been able to stop correctly because of Zhou Zekai’s suddenness, but this time, he was determined to get it.

The numbers continued to roll. The host was ready to stop at any moment. Waiting, waiting. The screen was already growing blurry. He looked at Zhou Zekai strangely. Zhou Zekai was focused on the screen and he seemed to be trying very hard to wait a bit longer before yelling out a stop.

“Zekai…..”

“Stop!”

“F*ck!” The host muttered in his heart. He had messed up again. Luckily, the audience was giving him more face and were more empathetic. The guest didn’t come up without him telling him to. Only until the host announced the chosen guest’s seat number did the guest come up.

“For the final guest….. Zhou Zekai, perhaps you could change a method. You can say a random number. It can be whatever you like.” It wasn’t easy for the host either. He hoped that there would at least be some variation.

“Okay.”

“Then, what number are you thinking of?”

“17.” Zhou Zekai said.

“17? Oh! 17. How did you come up with the number 17?” The host asked.

“Uh…..” Zhou Zekai “uh”ed but didn’t follow up. His gaze was focused on the host. The host stared blankly for a while and then suddenly thought of something and lowered his head.

The cameraman also figured out what had happened. He quickly switched to the host’s body. His T-shirt had a 17 on it.

The audience laughed. The host wasn’t too embarrassed. He was happy to sacrifice himself for the audience’s pleasure.

Though with just a “17”, it was hard to tell who the audience member was exactly. Samsara’s seats were arranged by area, row, and then number. The host lead him some more until Zhou Zekai finally said a complete seat number.

After sending Zhou Zekai down, the host wiped off a bead of sweat. How tiring! He deserved to be called the most difficult person to interview in the Alliance.